-Well, hello thorn.
-HI, I hops wo'ro not too late.
-No, no. Perfect tlmlng.
-0kay.
-stan, thl: I: my husband, Walt.
-Hl.
-Good to meat you.
-N|co to meat you.
-Sandla Laboratorlu, huh?
-Yoah.
l hoar Iomo falclnatlng stuff
you on out thorn.
Yoah, wall, you know.
Worklng on anythlng
you can talk about?
I'm plcturlng glant space laurl.
Am I rlght?
Honoatly, what I do
would bore you aonaoloaa.
Glant apaco laaora? That sounds cool.
I'll brlng It up at our next ataﬂ' mootlng.
-Woll, Juat romambor I got a out.
-All rlght. It's a dual.
So thla la It, honey. What do you say?
Wanna take a tour?
-Sure.
-0kay.
Look, how about
I glve ya'll aome prlvacy?
I'll go out to the car, make a few calla.
Take as much tlme as you need.
-All rlght.
-0kay, thanka.
-He'a a nlce guy. He doesn't puah.
-Yeah.
So as you can see,
there's thla klnd of flow golng on here.
-lt'a a nlce blg llvlng room.
-Yeah.
And thla lathe dlnlng area.
-0h, the dlnlng area. nght.
-Yea. Oh, and...
...lt'a got a pool.
Pool la nlce.
Backyard could be a llttle blgger.
And-- 0h, there's a breakfast bar
klnd ol' dealle here, whlch la nlce.
And, I don't know,
the kltchen'a really apacloua...
...and, you know,
got good appllancea and....
How many bedrooma?
Three. Told you.
They're all pretty good alze and--
0h, thla la the ﬁrst one here.
And then there's two more
at the back.
Only three bedrooms?
We're gonna need at least l'lve,
don't you thlnk?
-Flve?
-Yeah.
What, do I look llke
I'm about to drop a lltter?
No, no, no.
We'll have three klda total, eventually.
Yeah, but we'll need
a spare room for a study...
...ao that I can work at home
and you can wrlte.
Yeah, no.
I don't thlnk thla la gonna be enough.
Okay, what about a wlne cellar?
I mean, we certalnly cannot be
expected to llve wlthout a wlne cellar.
Very funny. IJuat thlnk we need
to let our alghta hlgh la all.
-At least, hlgher than here.
-Walt, thla la a good nelghbourhood.
It's got a good elementary
and a very good hlgh achool...
...and belleve me, because I have
del'lnltely looked everywhere.
For our prlce range,
thla la as good as It gets.
Well, then let's atretch our prlce range.
Truly. I mean, why...?
Why buy a starter house when we'll
have to move out In a year or two?
Dld you wln the lottery
and not tell me?
I'm aerloua.
Come on. Why be cautloua?
We've got nowhere to go but up.
-Yeah.
-Walter, you see us?
Yeah. I see you.
I'd llke you to exlt your vehlcle
and start walklng toward us.
And then what?
I'm gonna need some....
Some klnd of assurance.
lassure you,
I could klll you from way over here...
...lflt makes you feel any better.
Walter, you've been busy.
You wanna put your arms out
to your sldes for me, It you would?
You know I haven't slept
slnce Thursday?
l was out all nlght
cleanlng up after you.
I need my sleep.
You sald no hall' measures.
Yeah. Funny how words can be so open
to lnterpretatlon.
-You get your car l'lxed?
-Not yet.
You're gonna wanna
get your car l'lxed.
Let's see how thls goes l'lrst.
Has your condltlon worsened?
-Excuse me?
-Your medlcal condltlon.
-Has It grown worse?
-Not that I know of, no.
Is there a rlnglng In your ears?
Are you seelng brlght llghts
or hearlng volces?
-l'm qulte well, thank you.
-No. Clearly, you are not.
No ratlonal person would do
as you have done.
Explaln yoursell'.
My partner was about
to get hlmsell' shot.
l lntervened.
Some worthless Junkle.
For hlm, you Intervene
and put us all at rlsk.
Some contemptlble Junkle who couldn't
keep the peace for elght hours.
That's rlght. He couldn't.
He was angry
because those dealers of yours...
...had Just murdered
an 11-year-old boy.
I heard about It.
He should have
let me take care of them.
Maybe.
Then agaln, maybe he thought
It was you who gave the order.
Are you asklng me
It I ordered the murder of a chlld?
I would never ask you that.
Where Is Plnkman now?
I wouldn't know.
Couple of tlme zones away, at least.
Beyond that, I'd only be guesslng.
He has enough money to last forever,
he knows he needs to keep movlng.
You'll never l'lnd hlm.
I don't know, Walt...
...lt's what I do, after all.
He's out of the plcture.
I saved hls lll'e, I owed hlm that,
but now he and l are done.
Whlch ls exactly what you wanted,
Isn't It?
You've always struck me
as a very pragmatlc man.
So It I may,
I would llke to revlew optlons wlth you.
Ol' whlch, It seems to me,
you have two.
Optlon A:
You klll me rlght here and now.
Apparently,
I have made that very easy for you.
You can klll me, no wltnesses...
...and then spend the next few weeks
or months...
...tracklng down Jesse Plnkman
and you klll hlm too.
A polntless exerclse, It seems to me,
but that Is optlon A.
What Is optlon B?
l contlnue cooklng.
You and I both forget about Plnkman.
We l'orget thls ever happened.
We conslder thls a lone hlccup...
...In an otherwlse long
and l'rultl'ul buslness arrangement.
I prefer optlon B.
You'd need a new asslstant.
-I could get rlght on that.
-No.
Thls tlme, I choose.
Your car...
...get It l'lxed.
Yeah.
Really?
It's good to see you.
Thanks.
It's good to be back.
Well, shall we?
By all means, Gale, let's cook.
What about that rhlnoceros?
You thlnk he'd make a good pet?
-No.
-No?
Don't you thlnk It you called,
he'd come runnlng?
I bet he would.
I bet he'd come runnlng:
You're sllly, Pop-Pop.
Well, a llttle. But he'd probably
knock everythlng over.
-Plus, there's that blg nose of hls.
-That's not a nose, that's a horn.
-Is that so?
-Hls real nose ls llttle.
I learn all klnds ol' thlngs
belng wlth you.
Okay, June bug, these are for you.
-What about the rest?
-The rest are for me.
No, they're not.
You're too old for balloons.
You're never too old for balloons.
lee me a hug.
I see your mama.
Don't keep her waltlng.
-Bye, Pop-Pop.
-Bye, baby.
HI, sweetle.
Dld you have fun wlth Pop-Pop?
Please. Please, no.
Chow, you have anythlng
you wanna tell me?
Thank God you're here.
They keep me prlsoner.
-They keep you prlsoner.
-I don't do nothlng for them ever.
They try and make me. I say, no.
They steal my chemlcals.
I can't stop them. I am buslnessman.
You're a buslness--
The lady out front--
Hey, lady, are you stlll there?
Ask her If she's stlll there.
She says, yes.
How's her drlvlng? Drlvlng.
Is she good behlnd the wheel?
Good. She's good drlver.
Llcensed? Dependable?
She has a Camry.
The trucks wlll be here
I'lrst thlng In the mornlng.
I strongly recommend
that you return our calls next tlme.
So have her drlve you to the hospltal.
She's gonna need her shoe.
-Where'd they cross?
-Laredo, looks llke.
They dldn't exactly send
thelr A players.
But llke you sald, lt's cartel, all rlght.
Problng for weakness.
Well, they dldn't I'lnd any.
What about Plnkman?
I'm maklng enqulrles.
Yeah, that's two.
All rlght, let's close It up.
All rlght, brlng It down.
You ready?
Okay, we're good.
You can take your mask off now.
Does that guy ever leave?
When exactly dld that start?
It's new.
We had a....
We had a llttle drama
wlth the person you replaced.
-Sorry to hear that.
-No, It'll be l'lne.
Thlngs wlll contlnue
to smooth out and....
Yeah, It'll be l'lne.
By the way, If you're at all worrled
about worklng wlth me--
No, I'm not.
Whatever my shortcomlngs
last tlme...
...l lntend I'or thlngs to go perl'ectly
from here on out.
-So If there ls--?
-Gale, you're great.
-Serlously.
-I Just....
However you llke thlngs to be done
ls exactly how we're gonna do them.
Perlod.
From here on out, so....
Please, teach me.
Okay.
Gale. It's good to see you.
Mr. Frlng.
Wow, thls ls--
I should have called.
I'm not lnterruptlng anythlng, am I?
No. No, no, not at all.
Please, come In.
Can I offer you somethlng?
A creme de menthe?
No. No, thank you.
I'm sorry for the lnconvenlence.
Oh, no, no. It's no lnconvenlence.
I need to talk to you
about somethlng.
Somethlng rather presslng.
II' push came to shove,
l was wonderlng...
...how soon you mlght be able
to take over the lab yoursell'.
You and an asslstant.
Why would...?
-Why would push come to shove?
-Has Walter ever talked to you...
...about why he got Into
thls partlcular llne of work?
I guess I assumed
It was because It pays so well.
It Is, but specll'lcally...
...has he ever spoken to you
about hls health problems?
I'm not surprlsed.
He's a very prlvate person.
What exactly
are hls health problems?
He's dylng of cancer.
It Is why he does thls, to provlde I'or
hls I'amlly, whlch he's accompllshed.
They wlll never want for anythlng,
he's seen to that.
How long does he have?
That Is very much the questlon.
He does not wanna talk about It.
And every tlme l brlng It up wlth hlm....
I don't know that he's l'ully accepted
the reallty of It.
And not to sound cold-blooded,
but I am runnlng a buslness here.
-No, I understand.
-I have a very large Investment In thls.
There's so much overhead
that I can't afford to shut down.
Not even for a week.
So you understand my concern.
And my deslre for contlnulty.
I do. Absolutely.
Now, I lntend to keep Walter on
as long as he wants...
...assumlng that
he's physlcally up to It.
But as he cannot or wlll not tell me
how long that mlght be...
...I must prepare
for the worst-case scenarlo.
Well, worst-case scenarlo....
I suppose If we had...
...at least a few more cooks together.
You don't thlnk you're ready now?
Well, I mean...
A master.
There's always more for me to learn.
But I'm thlnklng that If we had...
...say...
...OIII or two more cool“.
One more...
...I guess would do It. I suppose.
l belleve ln you, Gale.
I know that when the tlme comes,
you wlll be ready.
What's up?
Walt, Is there...?
Any partlcular trlck
to purglng the catalyst bed?
No, It's pretty stralghtforward.
I'll show you when we get there.
Yeah?
Tell hlm I'm In conference.
-l'm ln conference.
-l'm looklng to flnd a cllent of yours.
l was hoplng you could help me out
wlth an address.
-Wh|ch cllent?
-Jesse Plnkman.
Jesse-Plnkman-ln-the-phone-book
Jesse Plnkman.
How would one track hlm down,
I wonder.
-You're stlll here.
-I need your full attentlon, Saul.
Jesse Plnkman.
Current whereabouts.
The sooner you tell me, the sooner
you get back to whatever thls ls.
What am I, an 8th-grade hall monltor?
Current whereabouts.
-Let me tell you somethlng, Mlke, you--
-Whoa, you are good rlght there.
Now, let's both get comfortable.
Now, when I say,
I'm looklng for Plnkman...
...we both know why, don't we?
You pretendlng otherwlse only wastes
my tlme and serves to annoy me.
Look, Mlke...
...there are rules to thls lawyer thlng.
-Is that rlght?
-Yeah.
Attorney-cllent prlvllege.
That's a blg one.
That's somethlng l provlde for you.
So If I glve up Plnkman...
...then you're gonna be asklng,
'Saul glves them up pretty easy.
What's to keep hlm
from glvlng me up?' You see?
So then, where's the trust?
I trust the hole In the desert
I'd leave you In.
Yeah, that's an argument.
...don't make me beat you
tlll your legs don't work.
Now tell me where to flnd hlm.
You know It's the rlght thlng.
I can't tell you, Mlke, all rlght? l....
Look, If I was to tell you, well, l]ust--
I couldn't llve wlth myself.
I'm sorry.
But who's to say I dldn't wrlte
the address down In my day planner?
Or on a scratch plece of paper
somewhere?
Who's to say
I dldn't wrlte down a locatlon...
...strlctly for
my own professlonal use?
Do not touch anythlng on my desk.
I'm gonna leave the room,
make myself a Nescafe.
I'm Just looklng out for you, that's all.
lee a mother hen.
Money-launderlng aln't what It used
to be. God, do I mlss the '80s.
You're wastlng your tlme.
I'm buylng the car wash, end of story.
Well, one look at thls place,
you're gonna fall In love, so....
Was I rlght? Where else you gonna flnd
a cash-only buslness that's thls fun?
Unless we're talklng massage parlours,
and, I don't see It. Shall we?
You ever actually play laser tag?
You know, It's good cardlo.
Plus, you get to shoot at klds.
You got your bumper cars over there
down that way.
Got your arcade here,
all the latest vldeo games.
Snack bar's there. Nothlng stopplng
you from selllng beer to the parents.
-That's a whole new revenue stream--
-All rlght, already. We're good.
Holy Chrlst.
We're good? Thls constltutes good
where you're from?
-My car ls bugged?
-l sald, maybe. Maybe bugged.
I'm belng followed?
What the hell have you gotten me Into?
My own Pl ls threatenlng to break
my legs. That's llke Thomas Magnum...
...threatenlng that llttle prlssy guy
wlth the moustache.
Over and above.
Servlce-wlse, thls ls over and above.
You and l survlve thls...
...l'm serlously rethlnklng
my prlclng, yeah.
And that goes double for you,
Hlp-Hop.
Okay, my guy's no dummy, rlght?
l glve us maybe 24 hours before he
flgures out that address goes nowhere.
You guys do your thlng,
make It snappy.
I'll go see If they have 'Tetrls'
or somethlng.
So how you holdlng up?
You?
I got my old Job back.
At least untll they klll me
and Gale takes over.
-So he's thelr boy, huh?
-He's thelr boy.
How long you thlnk you've got?
Well, he asks a lot of questlons
about the cooklng process.
I try to be as vague as posslble,
but I got that guy Vlctor watchlng me...
...llstenlng to every word I say.
You know, maybe that the only thlng
savlng me Is Gale's fastldlousness.
And once he feels confldent
that he knows my entlre method....
So, what do we do?
You know what we do.
There's got to be some other way.
Maybe It's better for you
to Just go to the cops.
All rlght? I mean,
I can't belleve I'm saylng that and all...
...but for your famlly.
The DEA would love you,
all the shlt you could tell them.
Federal wltness protectlon,
that's a good deal.
As for me, I'll hlt the road, yo.
I mean, I'll make It.
We had a good run.
But It's over.
Never the DEA.
The cook can't stop.
That's the one thlng I'm certaln of,
productlon cannot stop.
Gus can't afford to.
So If I'm the only chemlst
that he's got...
...then I've got leverage,
and leverage keeps me allve.
It keeps you allve too.
lthlnk I can see to that.
If I'm the only chemlst that he's got.
I can't do It, Mr. Whlte.
lee you sald, l'm....
I'm not a....
I can't do It.
I'll do It.
I'm gonna need your help.
I mean,
they're watchlng me day and nlght.
They never leave me alone wlth Gale,
not for a moment.
Hell, I don't even know
where the man llves.
He's not In the phone book,
I can't flnd hlm on the Internet...
...and I can't do It In the lab,
Vlctor's always there.
But If I could Just...
...shake Vlctor,
for even an hour one nlght...
...l thlnk then that....
I may be able...
...to make It look llke an accldent.
There's got to be some other way.
I'm all ears.
But when It comes down to you and me
versus hlm, I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry...
...but It's gonna be hlm.
Now, you are the only edge
that I've got...
...as long as they don't know
that you're ln town.
But I need you to track hlm,
get me hls address.
And I'll do the rest.
Look, I saved your llfe, Jesse.
Are you gonna save mlne?
Yeah?
Please, tell me you found hlm.
6353 Juan Tabo Boulevard.
Apartment 6.
-You there?
-Yeah.
6353 Juan Tabo. Number 6. Got It.
-He's home?
-Yep.
Anyone watchlng the place?
No. Looks pretty much wIde-open.
When are you gonna do It?
Tonlght.
Once It gets dark.
Don't do thls, Mr. Whlte.
Please. Go to the cops.
We got a problem.
Some klnd of chemlcal leaklng
In your lab.
Better come wlth me.
I'll follow you.
They tell me to brlng you, I brlng you.
Come on, get In the car.
I don't know If It's a barrel leak...
...but you got somethlng
mlghty stlnky down there.
After you.
Walter, the sooner you flgure out what
thls Is, the sooner we all go home.
Please, don't do thls.
...you don't have to do thls.
Yeah, unfortunately, I do, Walter.
Downstalrs.
I'll cook. I'll cook for free. There won't
be any more trouble, I promlse you.
-No.
-II I could talk to Gus--
-...I can make hlm understand.
If I could talk to Gus,
I can convlnce hlm.
Just let me, please-- Please.
-Please, let me talk to hlm.
-Shut up! Shut up.
I can't do It. I'm sorry.
I'll glve you Jesse Plnkman.
lee you sald, he's the problem.
He's always been the problem.
And wlthout hlm, we would--
And he's ln town, all rlght?
He's not In Vlrglnla
or wherever you're looklng.
He's rlght here In Albuquerque
and I could take you to hlm.
I'll take you rlght to hlm.
-What do you say?
-Where Is he?
-nght now, you glve me an address.
-I don't-- He moves. He moves around.
But If you let me call hlm--
No, no, please.
No, l]ust-- My phone. I'll Just--
It's Just my phone. I'll call hlm
and I'll have hlm meet me.
All rlght? Okay?
Okay?
Dld you do It?
Mr. Whlte?
No, l dldn't do It.
I can't now.
-It's gonna have to be you.
-What? No way, man.
You're closer than we are.
You'll have a 20-mlnute lead.
They've got me,
they're goIng to kIII me.
-Jesse, do It now! Do It!
-Son of a bltchl
Do It, Jessel Do Itl
Just what the hell was that exactly?
You mlght wanna hold off.
Yeah?
-Why?
-Because your boss ls gonna need me.
6353 Juan Tabo, Apartment 6.
Yeah.
HI. How can I help you?
Take whatever you want.
l have money. I have--
I got a lot of money.
l have....
Please, don't do thls.
You don't-- You....
You-- You don't have to do thls.