Marlano, It's me.
I nud you to get Skyler on the llne.
No, no, I nud you to get har
on the phono rlght now.
Toll har It's urgent.
No-- What do you mean
:ho won't get off the phono?
I am glvlng you pormlulon, Marlano.
You maka har get off the phono.
Marlano, who I: Skyler
on the phono wlth?
Yoah.
Okay.
-Where I: the? Whero': Skylar?
-She Just klnd of left.
She dldn't say when :ho was golng.
Skylar, my-- My hand I: Iplnnlng.
And yours, I....
I can't even Imaglne.
So much maku unu to me now.
You Jumplng In the pool,
you undlng us your klds, I get It.
ljult wlshod I'd sun It sooner.
Ho's a monster.
Look, I don't know what he dld to you
to force you to keep hls secrets.
If he threatened you,
or whatever mlnd games he played....
I don't know If there was abuse.
But I want you to know that
you can be open wlth rne.
Don't hold anythlng back, okay?
I mean, I don't even understand It you
know the full extent of thls...
...what he's done.
Not Just the meth cooklng,
but the llves he's destroyed.
But, look, that's all behlnd you,
startlng now.
You're done belng hls vlctlm.
Because here's what we're gonna do.
Sky, here's what we're gonna do.
You and the klds wlll move back
to our house...
...where you'll be safe,
where he can't get to you.
Hank, does Marle...?
No. We'll get to that soon enough.
It's Just you and me rlght now, okay?
Okay.
Before we....
I'm gonna ask you to tell me
everythlng you can.
Take as long as you llke.
Just start from the beglnnlng when you
l'lrst became aware of Walt's actlvltles...
...and Just try to be
as detalled as you can.
What, rlght-- nght here?
-nght now?
-Sure. Why not?
Whlle lt's stlll l'resh, you know?
And Just remember to state your name
and the date before you start.
Hank, do...?
Do we have to do thls rlght now?
No, we don't have to do thls
rlght now, no.
Here's the thlng, I need somethlng solld
that I can brlng to my people.
A statement, on the record.
So you testlfylng to Walt's
crlmlnal actlvlty...
...whatever you know,
goes a long, long way here.
Okay? I mean, you see,
bulldlng a case thls blg...
...gatherlng evldence,
enough to get a convlctlon...
...we're talklng a long-haul proposltlon.
I don't want that bastard runnlng out
the clock. But wlth your testlmony--
What do you mean,
runnlng out the clock?
Hls cancer. Hls cancer ls back.
So he says.
He dldn't tell you?
Who's to say It's even true?
Lylng plece ol' shlt.
Look, regardless,
I mean, we'll Just assume.
Flne. Okay?
That son of a bltch looks me In the eye
and he says If what I know Is true-- 'll'.'
--he'll be dead before I can prove lt.
The balls on that son of a....
I got all these llttle pleces.
They're all part of the story.
They don't mean much on thelr own,
but when you tell me what you know...
...we start l'llllng In the gaps, I'll have
hlm ln lockup before the sun goes down.
lthlnk maybe....
Maybe I need a lawyer.
What?
No, no, no, you don't.
Yeah, lthlnk maybe I do.
Skyler, understand,
I am here to help you.
But to do that, I need your help.
We start brlnglng ln lawyers
and they start puttlng up roadblocks...
...where they don't need to be...
...and my ablllty to control
thls sltuatlon dlmlnlshes.
Just for my own protectlon, and Just....
You know, It seems to make sense
that I should have someone to talk to.
Skyler, I'm your blggest advocate here,
and I'm telllng you, for your own good...
...you need to get out
ahead of thls thlng.
I mean, you start, you know,
gettlng del'enslve--
I'm not saylng lt's rlght,
but I'll tell you It's a fact...
...the DA wlll look at you dlfl'erently.
-But you don't know that.
-Skyler, yes, I do.
I've been around long enough to know.
It's In your best Interest...
...to get out there and show the world
you have nothlng to hlde.
Look...
...no one In the world
Is more Important to me...
...than your slster.
So belleve me when I tell you...
...that your best Interests
and mlne are the same.
But, Hank, you telllng me
not to talk to a lawyer...
...doesn't sound llke that at all.
It sounds llke what you want....
What you want Is to get Walt...
...at all costs.
Okay.
Okay, let's Just...
You can....
You can talk to a lawyer later.
But rlght now, what we need to do...
...we need to go get the klds.
We need to brlng them to my house
so that they're sal'e...
...and then we need to help each other
put that anlmal away, okay?
-Come on.
-Hank.
Let's go to the house
and we'll deal wlth It there.
Am I under arrest?
-What?
-Am I under arrest?
Skyler, l--
You're not thlnklng stralght about thls.
You have to llsten to me. In
Skyler. Skyler. Skyler.
-Am I under arrest?
-No.
-No. Sky--
-Hank, are you arrestlng me?
.sky..
Am I under arrest?!
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
I gotta do It, man.
What are you dolng? Huell.
Hey, qult screwlng around.
We are here to do a Job,
not channel Scrooge McDuck.
-You hearlng me?
-I hear you.
Screw It.
All's I'm saylng.
Guy hlt1o guys In Jall
wlthln a two-mlnute wlndow.
All's I'm saylng.
Yeah, It's me agaln.
Llsten, you've got to hlde those bags.
The monkey Is In
the banana patch, caplche?
-That's her.
-Don't.
-l have to talk to her.
-You don't.
Answer that phone and Schrader's
on the llne wlth a wlretap...
...recordlng everythlng.
You're not dolng anybody any I'avours.
Why do you stlll have a battery
In that thlng? Take It out.
They mlght be trylng
to trlangulate your movements.
I'm not belng paranold. Do It.
-I can't belleve she went to hlm.
-She Just panlcked.
She went rlght to hlm
wlthout even talklng to me.
I'm not saylng It's not bad.
It's bad, but It could be worse.
Really? How much worse could It be,
exactly, In your estlmatlon?
What does she actually know?
What has she seen?
Nothlng. It's hearsay.
It's all he sald, she sald.
The only real evldence
that she can lead them to Is your money.
Once we take care of that, well, yeah,
then they got nothlng.
Nothlng? Hank knows.
That's not nothlng.
Yeah. I can't exactly see hlm
turnlng the other cheek.
Of course there's always....
Always what?
Have you glven any thought
to sendlng hlm on a trlp to Bellze?
-Bellze?
-Yeah, Bellze.
You know, where....
Where Mlke went to,
off on a trlp to Bellze.
Saul, you better not be saylng
what I thlnk you're saylng.
-lt's Just conjecture on my part.
-Hank ls I'amlly.
-Okay, It's an optlon that--
-You understand that?
It's an optlon that has worked well
for you In the past.
-Jesus. What Is wrong wlth you?
-My mlstake. Famlly oft llmlts, of course.
I'm Just throwlng thoughts out there.
Thls Is a sale room, rlght?
Jesus. Send hlm to Bellze.
I'll send you to Bellze.
Flnally.
It's about tlme.
Have you two been followed?
Are you sure?
If they had,
we'd all be In handcuffs rlght now.
I took the tops off.
Flgured you'd wanna check
to make sure It's all there.
You flgured rlght.
Close enough.
-If you need any help on the other end....
-These thlngs are a bltch to move.
-l'll manage.
-And we don't mlnd overtlme.
Aln't no thlng.
Pay Huell and Kuby and take your cut.
The rest ls mlne.
Insurance In case I need you.
In case you need me?
I'm thlnklng the probablllty ls hlgh.
Just flnd Jesse.
Keys.
Saul Goodman, please. Skyler Whlte.
No, no, please don't tell me
he Isn't there.
I know he's been avoldlng my calls.
All rlght, well,
has my husband been there?
What do you mean you don't know?
Elther he has or he hasn't. I don't--
Sweetle.
Sky?
Sky, I know you're home.
Let me In. Let me talk to you.
I'm Just gonna walt here
untll you open the door.
So let me In now
or three hours from now...
...but I'm not leavlng untll I see you.
Skyler, please.
Just you.
Not Hank.
Tell me Hank ls crazy.
Tell me he doesn't know
what he's talklng about.
You gotta glve me somethlng, Skyler.
Anythlng to help me understand.
It can't be true.
Oh, my God.
How long have you known?
Hank sald that when you walked
Into the pool, that's when you knew.
When you had your....
But not then. Before that.
Slnce Gus Frlng?
The money.
All that money that Walt made...
...when you bought your car wash.
And your whole gambllng story.
-That was a lle.
-l....
Dld you know then?
You had to.
Skyler...
...dld you know
slnce before Hank was shot?
Skyler?
Marle.
I am so sorry.
You're sorry.
You're....
I'm slck of--
You won't talk. You won't talk to Hank...
...because you thlnk that Walt
ls golng to get away wlth thls.
Oh, God.
Come on, baby. Come on.
-Let's go.
-Marle. Marle. Hey.
What are you dolng?
Hey, what are you dolng?
-She's comlng wlth us.
-No, she Is not. She her back to me.
Marle.
You are not leavlng thls house
wlth my daughter.
lee her back to me.
-Marle, glve her back to me.
-Stop It.
You're scarlng her.
-lee her back.
-l'm trylng to protect her.
-l'm her mother.
-She's not gonna llve In thls madhousel
You don't know what you're
talklng about. She her back.
-Marle.
-L|sten, l wlll call the pollce.
-You call them. You call them, Skyler.
-l wlll. lee me my baby.
-Marle, put her down.
-You can't take her away.
-Marle.
-lee me my baby.
-We are not leavlng wlthout her.
-lee me my baby nowl
Marlel
Do It now.
lee her back.
That's rlght. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. I got you.
Okay, Mama has you now.
Mama has you now. Mama has you.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
You have to get hlm.
Thlrty-four, 59, 20, 106, 36, 52.
Walt.
Where have you been?
Oh, my God.
What happened?
You moved the money, dldn't you?
You burled It somewhere.
Dld you get my messages?
I told Hank nothlng.
Walt, I swear I dldn't.
Say somethlng.
Please.
Oh, my God.
Walt. Walt.
Hey.
How--? How long was I out?
Four or flve hours.
How are you feellng?
It's true.
The cancer ls back.
ls thls It?
Does that make you happy?
I can't remember
the last tlme l was happy.
Just tell me.
I know you talked wlth Hank.
I know you made a deal.
Skyler, I'll make thls easy.
I'll glve myself up
If you promlse me one thlng.
You keep the money.
Never speak of It.
Never glve It up.
You pass It on to our chlldren.
lee them everythlng.
Would you do that?
Please.
Please don't let me
have done all thls for nothlng.
How dld Hank flnd out?
Dld somebody talk?
No, no one talked.
It was me.
I screwed up.
The way Hank talks...
...he's got hls susplclons.
Not much else.
You can't glve yourself up
wlthout glvlng up the money.
It's the way thls works, Walt.
So maybe our best move here...
...Is to stay qulet.
Okay, you can take It off now.
All rlght, what's so Important
you had to come way out here?
The amount of money I'm brlnglng In,
I deserve to see why It's golng wrong.
You an expert on meth labs now?
You gonna tell us
how to flx our operatlon?
And what If I can help?
What wlll It hurt to show me?
I don't llke my tlme belng wasted.
Well, I'm here, and 10 mlnutes
Is a small sacrlflce...
...when we're talklng about
a $50 mllllon shortfall.
So?
Safe to come down?
Yeah. You're good.
Ladles flrst.
-Okay, now you've seen It.
-Yeah, now I've seen It.
What?
Well, how about we start wlth It's fllthy.
What are you, my mother?
What fllthy? It's Just dlmly llt.
Do you serlously thlnk thls ls up to
the standards of your predecessor?
Because It's not. Not even close.
Well, the product we're maklng,
It's selllng Just flne.
Helsenberg's standards
don't matter anymore.
To whom?
A bunch of scabby Arlzona tweakers?
They matter to my buyer In the Czech
Republlc, therefore, they matter to me.
Look, I cannot move what thls person
ls maklng If It's substandard.
And It Is. It Just Is. No offence.
-If you can do better, do better.
-I don't know what to tell you.
You trled to get the man back, rlght?
He sald no, so....
I mean, what do you want me to do?
Todd. Use Todd agaln.
Look, he learned from hlm, all rlght?
At least Todd's flrst two cooks
were at 74 percent.
On hls thlrd cook, he started a flre.
Look, I trled Helsenberg's way.
It dldn't work out.
I wanna cook In my terrltory.
I wanna use guys that I trust...
...not Todd, who I don't.
And that's the end of the conversatlon
as far as I'm concerned.
I really wlsh you'd have
glven hlm a chance.
Hey. We have a problem.
You stay here.
Get down!
Hello? Ma'am, you okay?
Hello?
Safe to come up whenever you want.
I don't want to see.
Okay.
Cool, so I guess maybe....
Maybe Just close your eyes.
Okay.
Thls way.
To the rlght.
Are you klddlng me wlth thls?
Uncle Jack.
Flre In the hole.
It's okay. Sorry about that.
It's cool, lady.
Okay, boys, let's take It all.
Let's get everythlng.
Hey.
You...
...golng Into work today?
You're klddlng, rlght?
What about you?
Are you golng to the offlce?
You have to tell them, Hank.
Today.
Marle, l]ust-- I Just don't have It yet.
The plece I need to prove It all,
It's Just not here.
Then let them help you.
Tell Steve, tell Ramey.
You've got enough to get them
to belleve your story at least.
Put the whole DEA on It.
That's how thls ls supposed to work,
rlght?
No?
What no? What are you,
Lone Wolf McOuade?
-Look, baby--
-You've gotta go In wlth thls, Hank.
Look, the day I go In wlth thls...
...that's the last day of my career,
all rlght?
I'm golng to have to walk In there,
look those people In the eye...
...and admlt that the person
I've been chaslng the past year...
...Is my own brother-ln-law.
It's over for me.
Ten seconds after I tell thls story,
I'm a clvlllan.
And then how can we help Skyler
If she comes to her senses?
When I go In there...
...l'm brlnglng proof, not susplclons.
I can be the man who caught hlm,
at least.
What If you walt...
...and they catch Walt wlthout you?
If they flnd out that you knew
and you sald nothlng?
Hank, wouldn't you go to Jall too?
Hey, Hank. Welcome back.
Mornlng.
-Hey.
-Hey, boss.
-How you dolng, Hank?
-Hey.
Hey. Look who's back.
I had to see It wlth my own eyes.
-How you dolng?
-Good. Yeah, yeah. You mlss me?
Mlss you? lee my balls
mlss Jock Itch, maybe.
Yeah? I dldn't know you had balls.
All rlght, don't make me sorry
I stopped by here.
Anyway, you got a budget meetlng
In an hour...
...then a meet-and-greet wlth
the new prescrlptlon task force guys.
All rlght. Hey, you know, llsten.
Let's see If we can get
that budget meetlng pushed...
...and Instead see If you could set up
a conference call wlth Ramey.
What for?
Just a 'gettlng back up to speed' thlng,
you know, for me.
All rlght. You got It.
Oh, hey. Dld you hear
about that money thlng?
No, what money thlng?
Oh, you're gonna love thls.
It Involves your old pal Jesse Plnkman.
Plnkman?
I'll glve you thls.
Jesse, you're never borlng.
Not borlng at all.
So come on, buddy, share wlth us.
Why were you tosslng mllllons of dollars
all over Albuquerque?
l promlse you we can hold out
Just as long as you can.
That's a fact. I got a bladder
the slze of a hot water bottle.
Man, all that cash. I wouldn't
be able to stop talklng about It.
I know. But I don't thlnk
I'd be tosslng It out my car wlndow.
Yeah. My take-home doesn't allow
for that whole Robln Hood thlng.
-But apparently Jesse ls raklng It In.
-Yes, Indeed.
I'm sure he's got a perfectly reasonable
explanatlon for where he got It.
Sure. He found It.
-Or won It In a card game, maybe.
-That's It. Won It In a card game.
Lucky nlght at the caslno.
Jesse, dld you have a lucky nlght?
Okay. Jesse, we're gonna let you
gather your thoughts...
...so we can contlnue
thls stlmulatlng conversatlon.
Can we get you anythlng?
Coffee? A soda?
-nght.
-Yeah. Thought not.
l have a hlstory wlth Jesse Plnkman...
...and l thlnk he can be helpful to me
on another actlve Investlgatlon.
Look, I'm only asklng
for a couple mlnutes here.
You sald he wasn't talklng?
Let me tell you, that kld hates my guts.
Desplses me, okay?
Maybe I can get hlm cranked up
enough that he starts yapplng.
Then you guys go In, get what you need
from the llttle shlt-staln, flnlsh hlm off.
lees me anythlng useful whlle
he's wlth me, I'll share It, 100 percent.
I could use a smoke break.
Yeah. How about you?
Yeah. Maybe you could keep an eye on
our suspect for us, for a few mlnutes.
Absolutely. I can do that.
Okay.
All rlght, guys.