-Good mornlng, offlcer.
-Can you turn the muslc down?
Oh, okay.
Down moan: off.
You know why I pulled you ovar
thl: mornlng?
Well, I'm pretty sure
lwun't Ipudlng.
l'vo bun ullng the crulu control,
so I don't--
No, Ilr, your wlndlhlold.
Llcenu and roglltratlon, ploau.
nght.
Thla-- Thla was from Wayfarer 515.
-My house was In the debrla l'leld.
-0kay.
And that's what shattered
my wlndahleld...
...aome plece ol' wreckage
from the plane.
I understand.
You know of l'llght 515, the plane crash?
You're wearlng the rlbbon.
Yes, slr.
I'm qulte aware of Wayfarer 515.
l was one of the ﬁrst responders
on the scene.
-Then what are you dolng?
-CItlng you, slr.
What? What, you don't belleve me?
Regardless of how that wlndshleld
was damaged...
...th|s car ls unsafe to drlve ln
thls condltlon. stay In the car, please.
Walt. Walt Just a mlnute.
Just one mlnute.
-I asked you to stay In the vehlcle.
-I can get out of my own car.
-SIr, llsten--
-No, you llsten to me.
It's tlme for you to llsten to me.
-Take a deep breath, calm down.
-Thls ls Amerlca, okay?
-Get back In that car.
-I have rlghts. You understand that?
At least have the common decency
to hear me out.
-step back now.
-Dld you even hear what I sald?
-SIr, calm down.
-You're glvlng me a tlcket?
I told you that my house
was In the debrls l'leld.
Do you have the remotest lnkllng
of what that means?
-SIr, calm down.
-Helll'lre ralned down on my house...
...where my chlldren sleepl
-I need you to step back now.
-There were body parts In my yard!
-Are you klddlng me?l
-SIr, last warnlng.
-You got two seconds to stand down.
-0r?
-l'm gonna pepper-spray you.
-Pepper-spray me. That Is Just perl'ect.
Pepper-spray the man who's expresslng
hls oplnlon under the Flrst Amendmentl
Lastly a llttle somethlng from
down El Paso way.
Border Patrol came across multlple
homlcldes Just thls slde ol' the border.
Truck turns out to be a chlcken run
out of Juarez Into Laredo.
Border Patrol's been playlng
hlde-and-seek...
...wlth these polleros for two years.
But thls tlme, soon as they made It
across, someone hlt them.
Hlt them hard.
We're talklng a drlver and nlne Illegals.
No slgn ol' the shooters.
So thls truck was carrylng more
than Just people.
What are we looklng at,
weed, coke or meth?
No, doesn't look llke
they were transportlng narcotlcs.
Why'd the Border Patrol
klck thls to us?
They dldn't. I pulled lt.
You ask me, thls ls hlgh-end
cartel work. Los Zetas, maybe.
Questlon ls, why do we have
Juarez-style actlon...
...on our slde ol' the DMZ?
They sendlng a message?
Clearlng a path?
Or was thls about stopplng
one partlcular border-hopper?
Maybe one of those extra-crlsples
knew somethlng he shouldn't.
All rlght, that's lt. Slow news day.
Add one more to the countdown.
Oh, yeah? What's that, Gomey?
We're waltlng on that famous
blue meth of yours.
Twenty-nlne days slnce
we saw It last.
It's stlll out there, Gomey.
Don't worry.
Local P.D. I gotta take thls.
Gomey, go beat your plllata.
Rest of you Jokers,
too damn qulet ln here.
Catch some bad guys.
Schrader.
Hey, what's up, Walt?
What?
Jesse?
Hey, Dad.
-lelng up the house, huh?
-Dolng a llttle work, yeah.
Well, I'll bounce. It's cool.
You dolng okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
IJust happened to be drlvlng by
and saw the slgn.
So you're selllng the place.
In thls market. Can you belleve It?
I see you moved the garage.
That's bold.
Your mother's Idea.
It's qulte an operatlon.
We dld all new stucco,
all new master sulte...
...sandblasted,
l'umlgated the basement.
nght on.
You know, l'lxlng up the place
totally Increases resale value.
I read that In, I wanna say,
llke TIME magazlne.
So, what'd you do
wlth the upstalrs bathroom?
All redone. New tlles
In the bathrooms and kltchens...
...granlte countertops, new appllances.
All top-ol'-the llne.
Damn. That's great, Dad.
Thlnk I can get a tour?
These guys are trylng to l'lnlsh up.
Maybe we'd better stay out of thelr way.
There are plctures on the webslte,
It you want to take a look.
Cool.
You're looklng healthy.
I'll tell your mother. She'll be happy.
You know, I could come by sometlme
l'or dlnner or somethlng.
Yeah. Sometlme.
Okay.
Later, Dad.
You know, look,
he's a hlgh-school teacher.
He's never been In trouble
a day In hls lll'e.
He l'lnds out he's got lung cancer...
...and now hls wll'e klcks
the poor bastard out of hls own house.
I mean, look, guys, If anybody rates
a llttle slack, here's the guy.
Hey, Walt.
Remember OI'I'Icer Cavanaugh?
OI'I'Icer, I'm very sorry that
I lost my temper.
There's no excuse for my behavlour.
It was dlsrespectl'ul.
Yeah. Thanks, man.
She's dlvorclng me.
I don't know what to tell you, buddy.
It Is what It Is.
She doesn't want me to see the klds.
She sald that?
Yeah.
You don't wrlte, you don't call.
It's a dlsaster.
-It Is not a dlsaster.
-0h, okay.
It's not a dlsaster, all rlght?
She's not golng to the cops,
she's not gonna tell a llvlng soul.
You wanna know why?
One word: blowback.
If she blabs, It'll be a dlsaster,
for her.
He'll be lucky If they let hlm
bust glue-snlfl'ers at the hobby shop.
The klds? Paglng Dr. Phll.
My daddy's a drug dealer
and my mommy turned hlm In.
And the house? Gone. Feds would Rlco
her and the klds out on the street.
Good luck argulng wlth them on that.
No. It's not gonna happen.
Her golng to the pollce
Is not the polnt, Saul.
She's out of my lll'e.
Do you understand?
I've lost my l'amlly.
Everythlng that I care about.
Hey, buddy.
-lt's bad. It's a calamlty.
-0h, my God.
But we llve to l'lght another day.
And after a decent Interval ol' tlme...
...well, there are other l'lsh
In the sea.
You've been out of clrculatlon
tor a whlle.
You'll be Just amazed at
what's out there.
Thalland, the Czech Republlc.
I mean, those women are so grateful
to even be here.
In the meantlme,
Idle hands are the devll's playthlng.
So why don't you get back on the horse
and do what you do best?
Flrst step:
Talk to our l'rlend and get cooklng.
I can't be the bad guy.
What?
Okay.
You know, we'll revlslt.
Just promlse me
you won't hang yourself In the closet.
Pop-popl
Pop-pop, the Ice cream manl
-Don't tell your mom.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-lt's me. We may have a wlfe problem.
Look, lneed eyes on It.
You got an address?
Hey. Dlnner's gonna be late.
Uncle Hank and Aunt Marle
are brlnglng takeout...
...but If you're hungry,
I could rustle somethlng up.
Hey, buddy,
pass the ketchup, wlll you?
What? I've had enough trans-l'at
for one lll'etlme.
Two-day drlve
from the nearest ocean...
...and you're eatlng raw l'lsh.
That's all I'm saylng.
Been awhlle slnce that mlnnow's
been swlmmlng. nght, buddy?
Yeah.
You know, Flynn here Is looklng
tor a part-tlme Job...
...so, I don't know, It you know of
anythlng you mlght want to--
My name's Walter Jr.
lee, what,
you can't even say hls name?
If you've changed your mlnd
about belng called Flynn...
...all you need to do Is Just tell me
that you don't want to be called Flynn.
Dad dldn't even show up
tlll l'ourth perlod.
And hls eyes were all red,
llke he's been crylng or somethlng.
But you, you don't even care!
And now he won't even
drlve me home.
He won't say why, but I know
It's because you told hlm not to.
-Honey, In
-What?
I don't know what your problem Is.
You may not love hlm anymore,
but I do.
I mean, why you gotta be--?
Why you gotta be such a bltch?l
-Hey, hey, hey. No, no, no.
-Oh, God.
-You can't talk to your mom llke that.
-Hank, no. Hank. Hank, It's--
It's all rlght.
Hey, hey.
Skyler, I know that you must have
your reasons for all of thls.
Sky, the--
I know It's none of my buslness...
...but keeplng Walt from the klds?
I mean....
You're rlght, Hank.
It's none of your buslness.
Oh, my God. After all of that?
Please, tell me
that you are stlll not curlous.
-There's nothlng to be curlous about.
-Oh, please.
The day I heard the words
'second cell phone,' I knew.
-Belleve me. Seen It a hundred tlmes.
-Okay. All rlght.
So, what? Stop danclng around It.
What Is It exactly that you have seen
a hundred tlmes?
Please, please, enllghten me.
Look, a guy llke Walt?
Nlce guy, decent, smart.
But, let's face It, underachlever,
dead-end lll'e, okay?
He gets cancer. Tlme's runnlng out.
Mld-lll'e crlsls.
He acts up. He steps out.
And the wll'e, she catches hlm.
I mean, It's a story as old as tlme.
Look, do the math, Marle.
It only comes out one way.
Knowlng Walt, he felt so gullty,
he probably told her hlmsell'.
l-- I don't know.
lthlnk II' he cheated on her,
that she would have told me by now.
It Just l'eels llke somethlng more.
Yes, yes, yes, 2417 coverage.
Need you ask?
How much Is thls gonna run me?
Jesus, I'm In the wrong buslness.
Yeah, I'll call you.
Return of the prodlgal,
back to the land of the llvlng.
-How you l'eellng?
-l'm good.
Of course you are.
The world's your oyster. Am I rlght?
Unencumbered young man
wlth stacks of cash.
Hey, I'm Jealous.
Hand to God, I'm Jealous.
Speaklng of cash, you know
what's glvlng me heartburn lately?
Your former partner. Thls guy,
he works llke a bastard, rlght?
Flnally the blg money shows up
and what does he do? He walks out.
Talent llke that and he l'lushes
It down the crapper.
It's llke Mlchelangelo won't palnt.
Look, I know you're out of It
and all...
...but you wouldn't talk to hlm,
would you?
Help hlm pull hls head
out of hls ass?
All rlght, all rlght, scratch that.
Yeah, he won't llsten to me,
he's not gonna llsten to you.
All due respect.
You want a Job?
A Job?
-Who's got a Job for me?
-I do.
There you go.
-Hey.
Thought I'd...
-...well, vlslt, It you don't mlnd.
-Ol' course not.
-You don't need the room, do you?
-No, no, no.
I Just needed some more space
to spread out.
Wanted to say hello to llttle Holly.
Hey, glrl. HI, baby. Oh, It's okay.
It's okay, It's okay. Oh, yeah.
She's a beauty. Look at her.
Hey, thanks for belng so l'lexlble
on me comlng In.
I Just wlsh we had you back l'ull-tlme.
You do brlghten up the place.
Llsten, belleve me, thls Is--
I don't want to brlng thls up,
but I can't slgn off on these quarterlles.
I'm sorry, lJust can't.
Is that rlght?
If you're gonna do thls,
It can't be so glarlng.
Glarlng.
Okay.
That does sound bad.
Show me what's botherlng you.
Keller.
Agaln. Oh, God, I'm sorry.
I know how you feel about thls.
Revenue wlth no backup.
Here, here and here.
I don't even know what to say.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, okay.
Thls Is l'lxable, rlght?
How about II' I Just push 28,800...
...out of thls Into next quarter?
Would you slgn It then?
I'm Just saylng I can't slgn It
as It currently exlsts.
Falr enough.
I'll take care of It.
Thank you for the heads-up.
You won't have to deal wlth thls agaln,
I swear.
What If your klds found out?
-ll' my klds found out?
-Th|s. What you're dolng.
Someday they're gonna be old enough.
How would you explaln It to them?
Well, put me on the spot,
why don't you?
I guess maybe l'd....
I'd say that l mlght have feet of clay...
...but that whatever I dld,
ldld thlnklng of them.
You know, trylng to provlde.
And I'd ask them to try
to take the tlme to understand....
You know what? Truth ls,
I haven't thought that far ahead, Skyler.
I'm Just trylng to keep my head
above water, so....
I'd better get back to It.
Oh, God.
HI, Walt.
Llsten, I can't tal--
I'm at work rlght now--
What?
Louls dropped hlm off.
He was here when I got home.
No, no, no, of course.
No, he's not staylng.
He understands that.
-l'll brlng hlm anywhere you want.
-Dad.
Well, yeah. It Is rush hour.
I mean, I could l'lght trafﬁc
and brlng hlm down to Beneke now.
But wouldn't It be easler II' we--?
nght, okay, good.
So we'll meet you at the house.
Okay, bye.
Why are you dolng thls?
She's Just trylng to keep me from
seelng you and you're helplng her.
Well, son, I mean, your mother,
she has her reasons.
What reasons?
They're....
Well, they're....
Well, they're Just a llttle dll'l'lcult
to dellneate.
But, I mean, yes, there are two sldes
to every story, always.
But she....
Yeah.
Thls Is Just how It has to be
for now, okay?
Now, look, your home Is your home
and that Is where you belong, all rlght?
But It's where you belong.
Dad, It's your house.
Uncle Hank, Aunt Marle...
...everybody knows
that you haven't done anythlng wrong.
Everybody Is on your slde.
Well, It's not about taklng sldes,
though.
-How can you let her treat you llke thls?
-Come on.
-How can you Just take It?
-Now Just llsten to me, okay?
No matter what, all of thls has nothlng
to do wlth how we feel about you, okay?
We both love you very,
very much, okay?
You and your slster wlll
come l'lrst always.
Come on.
Let's try to see thls
In a posltlve llght, okay? Both of us.
Let's Just buck up.
And I'll take you home.
Let me l'lrst Just
hlt the old bathroom here.
Hello. Good afternoon.
-N|ce to meet you. Saul Goodman.
-N|ce to meet you.
You're not that lawyer
on late-nlght televlslon, are you?
Better call Saull
I get It all the tlme.
We're here to dlscuss the sale of
the property at 9809 Margo.
I get It. Flat-fee cllents, am I rlght?
Well, folks, today's your lucky day.
I represent a cllent
who shall remaln nameless.
However, for our purposes...
...you mlght Just as well vlsuallse
a large bag of money.
Thls Indlvldual wants
to buy your house today for cash.
-Cash?
-Cash. I know, In thls economy.
The money Is already burnlng a hole
In my cllent's account.
You can ask Mr. Gardlner. I've shown
hlm all the pertlnent flnanclals.
It's the only reason
we're slttlng here.
Falr enough. We get a few papers
slgned and notarlsed...
...we can take care of thls rlght now.
In fact, I could wlre you your money
thls very afternoon.
There's Just one llttle halr
In the soup.
The prlce.
We feel 875 Is very falr.
But I suppose there's always
a llttle wlggle room.
Well, why don't you wlggle us on down
to 400 and you got yourselves a deal?
Four hundred thousand?
What Is that, a Joke?
No, that's my offer.
That's less than half-prlce.
We put that much
Into the renovatlons alone.
Why don't we Just cut
the clown act...
...and you tell us what you're wllllng
to come up to?
Four hundred thousand.
That's my flnal offer.
-Waste of tlme.
-Rldlculous.
How could you posslbly lmaglne
we'd entertaln thls?
-Come on, hon.
-I don't know.
I thought some allowance was In order
once I heard about the meth lab.
That used to be In the basement.
I looked over your slgned dlsclosure
statements...
...and I don't see any mentlon
of a meth lab. Nope.
Oh, you got your termlte Inspectlon.
That's good.
But no meth lab.
Now, some would call that fraud
In servlce of conceallng a felony.
I, myself, am more open-mlnded.
But It Is trlcky.
Now, don't get me wrong.
I applaud your coJones.
I mean, good try...
...at sneaklng a meth-contamlnated
property past a buyer.
I mean, could've been a good deal
for you. Too bad.
Now, I could flle a sult and encumber
thls property lndeflnltely.
Or I could start some crlmlnal
proceedlngs.
But I don't thlnk any of us want that,
now, do we?
How about It, counsellor?
Do you concur?
There you go, son.
Come on. It's not Devll's Island.
Okay.
-Oh, hey.
-Hello.
-Brought plzza.
-Yeah. Well, I'm maklng dlnner.
Okay, I'll Just put It In the frldge.
It's even better the next day.
HI, honey.
Sorry.
Skyler.
I mean, what klnd of example do
we want to set here, rlght?
I mean, can't we at least Just slt down
and eat a plece of plzza together?
Just hash thlngs out llke adults?
We have dlscussed everythlng
we need to dlscuss.
I thought I made myself very clear.
I got dlpplng stlcks.
You've reached Wall's
temporary number.
Please, leave a message.
When I went out thls mornlng
to get the newspaper...
...I saw a plzza on our roof.
Would you know anythlng about that?
Llsten to me, Walt.
You need to control yourself.
Calm down, accept the sltuatlon
and keep your dlstance.
If you can't manage that,
I wlll get a restralnlng order.
Skyler. Skyler.
Got your restralnlng order rlght herel
Restraln thlsl
Breaklng even Is not so bad.
In thls economy, a lot of people
would klll to break even.
Poor Jake. He had hls heart set
on golng to Space Camp.
Oh, no.
Oh, God. Thls Is all we need.
Hey, Mom, Dad. How's It golng?
Jesse, It's really not a good tlme.
Come on.
Jesse, the house has been sold.
The new owners are expected
at any moment.
-Where do you thlnk you're golng?
-lnslde.
I bought the place.
Be back by seven, okay?
Love you.
Bye.
Oh, God.
It's me. There's somethlng
he should know about.