Just get me homo.
I'll do the rut.
You, hello, thl: I: Davld Llnn
from The New York Times.
May I speak wlth Susan, plan?
Thank you.
HI, Susan, It's Davld agaln.
l was Just calllng to sea If m can sot--
Well, yes. Wall, lflgurod
we'd havo to do the lntorvlow by phono...
...slnco they'vo alroady left Now York.
But what we'd roally lovo to get
Is a photo of Mr. and Mrs. Schwartz...
...to go along wlth the artlcle.
When are they scheduled
to get home?
Oh, so they'll be home tonlght. Gotcha.
Now, the address I have on them
Is Upper Canyon Road. Is that stlll...?
No, It Isn't. They've-- Let me get a pen.
Where do they...?
Tesuque. I see.
And the address?
Is that up near the opera house?
I hear that's nlce.
Well, I'll be In contact
wlth my photographer...
...to check on hls schedule.
No, no, It's thelr call.
I know how busy
Mr. and Mrs. Schwartz are.
Thank you.
Thls should make one hell of a story.
Goodbye.
I 'm just saylng,
lt's apples and oranges.
Llsten, l malntaln, It I want plzza...
-...I go to a plzza place.
-Yeah.
It I want Thal, I go to a Thal place.
-What Is the polnt ln comparlng...
-Dld I marry you?
-...plzza to Thal?
-What has happened?
-Thls ls dll'l'erent.
-They're completely--
Oh, come on,
are you the man I marrled?
I am the guy who wants to end
thls rldlculous conversatlon...
...klck off my shoes,
and have a very large glass of wlne.
Well, I'm gonna tell you
to be my guest.
All rlght, walt.
The answer Is 21.
-No.
-Yes.
Yes, because It has hlstory.
Come on.
Prohlbltlon.
-The Sweet Smell of Success.
-And Per Se has Thomas Keller.
-Game, set, and match.
-The whole vlbe ls so Yountvllle.
You transplant It to Manhattan--
Transplant It to Islamabad,
I would eat there.
0h, there's a good thought.
-What, Islamabad?
-No, Napa. We have to go to Napa.
Oh, my God, all thls talk of food.
Do you thlnk Juana left us anythlng?
She doesn't thlnk we're comlng back
untll Wednesday.
-Unless you told her.
-No, I haven't talked to her.
Oh, look, here.
-Just a pear, that'll be perfect.
-Yeah.
You wanna get us
a nlce bottle of wlne?
Do you thlnk we have any of those--?
What are those crackers wlth,
llke, the sun-drled tomato...
...and they were sllghtly peppery,
but not too peppery.
-We don't have them?
-No.
-Ask Juana.
-We haven't had them In I'orever.
-I don't know why she doesn't get those.
-Why don't you talk to her?
She's got that thlng wlth her daughter.
-Anyway, Napa?
-Yeah.
-How long slnce we've been?
-Two years.
Jesus, that's two years.
-Yeah, too long, rlght?
-ls thls okay?
Oh, that looks perfecto.
You wanna get the I'lreplace?
Is It good?
Is It rlpe?
Yeah.
We could Invlte George and Delores.
They could come up from Marln.
And Blll and erlam Cohen.
We could have a llttle spa actlon, rlght?
And then we could do
some sort of wlne, and then--
Hello, Gretchen.
Elllott.
I really llke your new house.
Walt.
Thls....
Are we looklng east?
My God, you must have one great vlew
ol' the Sangre de Crlstos.
Walt, what are you dolng here?
I saw you on Charlle Rose.
You looked great.
-You both dld.
-ll' you are here to--
-To hurt us--
-Walt, whatever It Is you're plannlng--
Actually, I'm here
to glve you somethlng.
It's out In my car.
How about the three of us take a walk
to It? It's Just parked down the road.
I couldn't get It past your gate.
Elllott, If we're gonna go that way...
...you'll need a blgger knll'e.
Keep stacklng. It'll all I'lt.
That's all rlght.
Yeah, Just throw It on top.
Gretchen, would you mlnd? We don't
want to lose any under the I'urnlture.
All rlght.
That Is $9,720,000.
Where dld It come from?
And why Is It here?
I earned It, and you're golng
to glve It to my chlldren.
-What? Why?
-Walt, I don't thlnk we--
On my son's 18th blrthday...
...whlch Is 10 months
and two days from today...
...you wlll glve hlm thls money...
...In the form of an lrrevocable trust.
You wlll tell hlm that It Is hls
to do wlth as he sees I'lt...
...but wlth the hope
that he uses It for hls college educatlon.
-And for the betterment of hls I'amlly.
-Walt, I'm not sure that we follow.
Why....?
I mean, why, In partlcular, would we--?
It you wanna glve your klds drug money,
go do It yoursell'.
I can't.
My wll'e and son hate me.
They won't take my money.
Even If they dld...
...the federal government
wouldn't let them.
But two rlch benel'actors who are known
for thelr charltable endeavours...
...who would thlnk nothlng of,
for Instance...
...wrltlng a $28 mllllon cheque...
...to help vlctlms
ol' methamphetamlne abuse?
l have to thlnk that your money
would be very welcome.
It wouldn't make any sense
comlng from us.
It certalnly would.
My chlldren are blameless vlctlms
ol' thelr monstrous I'ather.
A man who you once knew qulte well.
Call It a beau geste,
call It llberal gullt...
...call It whatever you want, but do It.
And you are not to spend
a slngle dlme of your own money.
If there are taxes or lawyers' I'ees owed,
you wlll take It rlght from here.
They use my money, never yours.
Okay, Walt, sure.
That sounds reasonable.
So, what happens next?
I guess we shake on It, and I leave.
I can trust you to do thls.
Yes.
Absolutely you can.
Don't move. Don't--
Don't dare move a muscle.
You don't want them to thlnk that
you're trylng to get away. Just breathe.
Just thls afternoon,
I had an extra $200,000...
...that I would have loved dearly
to leave on top of thls table.
Instead, I gave It to the two best
hlt men west of the Mlsslsslppl.
...whatever happens to me tomorrow...
...they'll stlll be out there.
Keeplng tabs.
And II', for any reason...
...that my chlldren
do not get thls money...
...a klnd ol' countdown wlll begln.
Maybe a day or so later,
maybe a week, a year...
...when you're golng tor a walk
In Santa Fe...
...or Manhattan or Prague, wherever...
...and you're talklng
about your stock prlces...
...wlthout a worry In the world.
And then suddenly...
...you'll hear the scrape
of a I'ootstep behlnd you...
...but before you can even turn around:
Darkness.
Cheer up, beautll'ul people.
Thls ls where you get to make It rlght.
Oh, yeah, rlght.
You know, I don't exactly know
how to feel about all thls.
For real, yo.
Whole thlng I'elt klnd ol' shady,
you know, llke, morallty-wlse?
Totally.
How do you feel now?
-Better.
-Yeah, del'lnltely lmprovlng.
What's thls I hear about
blue meth stlll belng out there?
-What do you mean?
-Have you heard anythlng?
Is It stlll belng sold?
Yeah.
By whom?
It's you, rlght?
I mean, aren't you stlll cooklng?
We were sure It was you,
because that shlt ls cholce, yo.
Better than ever.
I mean, you know.
-Jesse.
-Serlously?
-You sald he moved to Alaska.
-That's what I heard.
nght on, Jesse.
Passlng the torch.
Damn, man, couldn't he at least
throw a brother a bone?
Whoa, what happened there?
It's my blrthday.
Yeah? Well, happy blrthday.
It's easy money. Tlll we catch you. Say
the word, I'll take you on a rlde-along.
You can watch us
knock down a meth lab.
Get a llttle excltement In your lll'e.
Yeah, someday.
-Welcome. Would you llke a menu?
-No, thank you.
-Chamomlle tea wlth soy mllk, please.
-All rlght, you got It.
Hey, how you dolng?
How's thlngs?
Hey, I llke your....
Shlrt.
-My blouse?
-Nlce. Yeah, I llke the colour.
That's a nlce colour on you.
It's klnd of a--
I don't know exactly what you'd call It.
It's klnd of a cornl'lower blue.
Before you say or do anythlng,
Just hear me out.
-Todd.
-Nobody knows that I'm here.
Just llsten for two mlnutes,
and then I'll leave.
Please. No. Please.
Just two mlnutes of your tlme.
That's all I ask.
Please.
You're runnlng out of methylamlne,
aren't you?
I can do the math.
You've been at It long enough.
You must be runnlng low.
l have a new method...
...that requlres no methylamlne.
It's easy,
and It wlll keep you In buslness.
And, Todd, I could teach It to you.
How dld you know to flnd us here?
Ten a.m.
Every Tuesday mornlng,
you and I met here.
You're rather schedule-orlented,
I guess.
Sorry.
I need the money.
I've spent almost all of mlne already...
...Just trylng to stay one step ahead
of the pollce.
Mr. Whlte, I don't thlnk there's--
How much would It cost us?
Nothlng short of a mllllon.
And belleve me, for thls,
that Is glvlng It away.
-l thlnk Jack should hear thls.
-Yeah, I don't know.
Now, llsten, I can come up there tonlght
and talk to hlm.
He'd get It.
Thls Is a wln-wln sltuatlon.
-Hl, what can I get for you two?
-He's Just leavlng.
Good seelng you agaln. Take care.
For you?
And I need more stevla.
Okay, no dlsrespect to the man,
but dolng buslness wlth hlm?
nght now, that's not--
Of course we're not dolng buslness
wlth hlm.
Todd, please.
Don't make me walk you through thls.
Jesus. Dld you look at hlm?
You'd be dolng hlm a favour.
Hello, please record after the tone.
Truce, all rlght?
Skyler, I have news about Walt,
and you need to hear It...
...so If you're there, plck up.
Skyler--
Hey.
What's up?
Wall's In town.
Yeah?
That car they thought he stole
In New Hampshlre...
...they found It In a Denny's parklng lot
rlght on Central.
And your next-door nelghbour,
on the rlght-- What's her name, Becky?
-Becky's on the left. Carol's on the rlght.
-Becky, Carol, whatever.
She saw hlm at your old house.
Just thls mornlng, plaln as day.
He's there, walklng out of your house,
and he calls her by name.
-He dldn't hurt her, dld he? He dldn't--?
-No, he's Just llke, 'Hey, Beckyl'
0r Carol, whatever.
She sald he looked exactly
llke the Unabomber.
But she's posltlve It was hlm.
They're gettlng calls from all over town.
He's here, he's there,
he's golng to blow up clty hall.
He has some sort of manlfesto.
He wants to be on the news.
-Who's maklng these calls? Hlm?
-There are two or three volces.
They're not sure If they're crank calls
or people he's put up to It...
...or If they're actual anonymous tlps.
It's stretchlng them thln,
whlch ls maybe the polnt.
As far as I'm concerned...
...there are three places that he
would go: To you, to me, or Flynn.
mam.
They're watchlng the hlgh school.
They're probably watchlng
your place too.
...I know that's what Hank would do.
There Is no way Walt's gettlng to you.
They are absolutely golng to catch hlm.
No doubt about It.
That arrogant asshole thlnks he's some
crlmlnal mastermlnd, but he's not.
But on the off chance....
Yeah.
0n the mllllon-to-one chance...
...you be on the lookout, okay?
Thanks.
You got It.
Flve mlnutes.
You dldn't klll anybody
sneaklng In here, dld you?
-You dldn't hurt anybody?
-No.
Dldn't have to.
You look terrlble.
Yeah.
But I feel good.
So talk.
Why are you here?
It's over.
And I needed a proper goodbye.
Not our last phone call.
So you're golng to the pollce?
They'll be comlng to me.
If you're In custody...
...what stops those people
from comlng back?
When--
When I stlll had the house...
...three men came
In the mlddle of the nlght...
...wearlng masks,
threatenlng Holly and Flynn and me.
They told me not to talk about
that woman at the car wash...
...and If you're In custody--
They're not comlng back.
Not after tonlght.
What's tonlght?
We don't want your money, Walt.
I thought Flynn made that clear.
And I don't have any to glve you.
I spent the last of It gettlng here.
All I have to glve you...
...ls thls.
Call the DEA once I leave.
Tell them I was here.
That I forced my way In.
Tell them....
Tell them I wanted
bacon and eggs on my blrthday...
...and that I gave you that tlcket.
Those numbers are GPS coordlnates.
For what?
A burlal slte.
That's where they'll
flnd Hank and Steve Gomez.
It's where l burled our money.
And the men who stole It from us...
...the men who stlll have It...
...they murdered Hank and Steve...
...and put them In that hole.
Now, you trade that...
...for a deal wlth the prosecutor.
You get yourself out of thls.
Skyler.
All the thlngs that l dld...
-...you need to understand--
-II I have to hear...
...one more tlme...
...that you dld thls for the famlly--
l dld It for me.
I Ilked It.
l was good at It.
And...
...really....
l was allve.
Flynn wlll be home soon.
Before I go...
...may I see her?
Damn, man, thls thlng's a classlc.
What block you got In It?
The 500 or the 425?
Couldn't tell you.
Well....
Flve hundred.
That's the one you want.
No replacement for dlsplacement.
Where to?
To the clubhouse.
Go ahead, Just park It rlght In front
over here.
No, no, no, Just stralght In, man.
Just-- What are--?
All rlght, flne, here, whatever.
Hey, how you dolng?
Turn around,
put your arms out llke thls.
Whlle you're at It,
why don't you llft your shlrt up...
...glve us a spln?
Chrlst, I'm not wearlng a wlre.
Okay?
-My wallet and keys?
-Yeah, you'll get them back. Just relax.
Stay here.
Keep your eyes open.
Jesus, look at you wlth that head of halr.
Is that real?
Yes.
-That's not a wlg? Serlously?
-No.
What were you dolng before,
shavlng It?
Yes.
Chrlst, that Is one flne head of halr.
I mean, otherwlse,
you look llke shlt, but--
Hello to you too, Jack.
Now, can we talk buslness?
I don't thlnk so, no.
-Dld Todd tell you what I'm offerlng?
-Yeah, he told me.
The thlng ls
we're not really In the market.
You're low on methylamlne.
What happens then?
No, we'll get more.
That Quayle woman's got her own setup.
The heat's off her.
She can break loose a barrel.
It aln't broke, so why flx It?
Todd, please, would you explaln thlngs
to your uncle?
Explaln to hlm the beneflt
of what I'm offerlng.
You really shouldn't
have come back, Mr. Whlte.
I'm sorry.
-Wa|t. Jack.
-Where do you want It?
I don't know,
anywhere but my llvlng room?
-Take hlm out back.
-Jack, look, you owe me.
-You owe me.
-Hey, hey, hey.
-Let's go.
-I owe you, what for?
Jesse Plnkman. You promlsed
you would klll hlm, and you dldn't.
-lnstead, you partnered wlth hlm.
-All rlght.
-You're hls partner now--
-Whoa, stop.
Partners? What are you talklng about?
He's allve, Isn't he?
He's cooklng for you.
What, are you gonna lle?
Hlm belng allve
Is not hlm and me belng partners.
Not by a damn slght.
What, you thlnk I'd partner wlth a rat?
-Where Is that llttle plece of shlt?
-He's flnlshlng up a batch.
Go get hlm. Brlng hlm here.
-Uncle Jack--
-No. No, no, no.
Thls one here, calllng me a llar?
He Just lnsulted you,
he lnsulted me, all of us.
Jesus. Hustle It up. Come on.
Let's get thls over wlth.
I'm gonna show you
Just how wrong you are.
Then I'm puttlng that bullet
In your head myself.
Yeah, you see what I'm talklng about,
you son of a bltch?
Now, does thls look
llke a partner to you?
Come here. Take a look.
Come here!
Take a look at hlm.
Have a gander.
Thls Is my partner.
nght, partner? nght, buddy?
Hardworklng, good partner.
FIfty-flfty partner.
Can you hurry thls shlt up?
Make It qulck?
-Toddy, get hlm off, would you?
-Yeah, Toddy, get them both off.
Uncle Jack.
Jesus.
Mr. Whlte.
Walt. Walt.
You want your money, rlght?
You wanna know where It Is?
You pull that trlgger, you'll never--
Do It.
You want thls.
Say the words.
Say you want thlsl
Nothlng happens untll I hear you say It.
I want thls.
Then do It yourself.
Plck up the phone.
Hello?
Is It done?
Is he gone?
Yeah, It's done.
He's gone.
They're all gone.
Todd? Who Is thls?
It's Walt.
How are you feellng?
Klnd of under the weather?
lee you've got the flu?
That would be the rlcln I gave you.
I sIIpped It Into that stevIa crap
that you're always puttlng In your tea.
Oh, my God.
Well...
...goodbye, Lydla.