[SECURITY WAND BEEPING]
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Hay, Darla. How you dolng today?
DARLA: Hay, Dan.
I'm looklng for somethlng
In a Markowskl.
That'd be, uh, Dannl: Markovukl?
That's the one.
[SECURITY WAND BEEPING]
Oh, and Wu got my paralegal
wlth me today.
Paralegal? Comlng up In the world.
You know It.
[BUZZER SOUNDS IN DISTANCE]
[MEN YELLING IN DISTANCE]
[KEYS JANGLING]
[noon OPENS]
Hay, Dannla.
Hava a sat.
[MEN CHATTERING
THEN BUZZER SOUNDS]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
INDISTINCTLY OVER EARPHONES]
You haar about Chow?
Yaah, paopla aay ha aklppad town.
Ha'a daad.
It wasn't ma.
It wasn't a maaaaga.
It wasn't payback.
It was a mlataka mada by a ther party
who has alnca baan daalt wlth.
You got It?
Yaah.
Sacond thlng.
Tha daal you had wlth Frlng,
lt'a atlll In placa.
Okay.
Don't 'okay' ma.
You got aomathlng to say?
Mlka, I'm kaaplng
my mouth shut.
Tha laundry
waa rlght abova tha lab.
Thara'a no way I could lay
lwaan't In on It.
I'm looklng
at alght yaara mlnlmum.
But I'm dolng my tlma
Ilka I'm auppoaad to.
I'm no rat, and you know It.
l maan, what alaa la thara to say?
All dua raapact,
what ara wa talklng about hara?
Tha daal la tha daal.
How'a tha daal tha daal?
Tha l'ada took away my hazard pay.
My wll'a aaka ma whara
tha mortgaga la comlng from.
I got nothlng to tall har.
l knaw tha rlaka. Wa all dld.
But that wasn't tha daal.
And I know for a fact
thay got Holt and Paraz yaatarday.
Now, It's not gonna ba ma,
but abaant tha hazard pay,
aoonar or latar, aomaona'a gonna l'llp.
No ona'a l'llpplng.
Evaryona gata thalr hazard pay,
lncludlng you.
l appraclata what you'ra aaylng
and all, but tha man la daad.
Okay? Tha lab'a
a hola ln tha ground.
IJuat don't aaa lt.
l'va got aomathlng naw.
It's Just atartlng up.
It's gonna maka you whola.
Somathlng naw?
Wlth tha l'ada looklng at you?
How?
'How' la my bualnaaa.
Hanglng tlght'a your bualnaaa.
Your l'amlly'a gonna ba l'lna.
You wlll ba mada whola.
Now, you got my word.
You naad mora?
MIKE: Who'a naxt?
That's your cholca.
A.P.D.'a got Martlnaz across town.
McGann'a up In Sandoval.
Tha Sandla trlbal copa
ara holdlng hlm for tha I'ada.
[noon BUZZES]
And Holt and Paraz
ara In lockup In Loa Lunaa.
You don't maan
to gat to tham all today?
Yaah, I do.
Hay, lat'a goI Opan upI
[MIKE BANGING ON DOOR
THEN DOOR BUZZES]
[J'J'J']
[HUMMING]
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
Back hara.
[CHUCKLES]
0h, hl. How was your day?
Uh... Ara you movlng back In?
Yaah. I'll kaap
tha condo for now.
Salllng It In thla markat,
I'd gat klllad.
But, yaah, I'm homa.
lt'a tlma.
Do you, uh, raallythlnk
that's a good ldaa?
Yaa.
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[LABOURED BREATHING]
SAUL:
So you brlng hlm hara? Coma on.
Tha thraa of us,
wa'ra tha thraa amlgoa.
All for ona, ona for all.
Wa don't naad a fourth amlgo.
Saul, Mlka knowa tha bualnaaa.
Ha knowa dlatrlbutora.
Mlka'a okay.
Ha'a okay?
Ha aald ha was gonna
braak my laga.
And don't tall ma
ha dldn't maan It, okay?
Bacauaa ha gava ma
tha daad mackaral ayaa.
Ha maant It.
WALT:
Saul, Mlka thraatanad ma.
Ha thraatanad Jaaaa.
Ha probably thraatanad aomaona
bal'ora braakl'aat thla mornlng.
It's what ha doaa.
Coma on. Grow a palr.
Lat It ba notad
that I do thla undar duraaa.
Duly notad.
All rlght. Lat hlm In, Huall.
Mlka, I'm axtandlng you--
Uh-huh.
Now that wa'ra all togathar,
hara ara tha ground rulaa.
Dlvlalon of labour.
l handla tha bualnaaa.
Maklng tha stuff,
that's your and.
I don't tall you how to mlx
your chamlcala and whatnot,
and you do not tall ma
how to taka cara oI' bualnaaa.
la that abaolutaly claar?
Sura.
All rlght. Lat'a taka tha tour.
Hay, you'ra okay wlth that?
Yaa.
Ha handlaa tha bualnaaa,
and l handla hlm.
SAUL:
Wa'ra talklng about
rantlng, not buylng.
You naad an ongolng bualnaaa,
aomaplaca you can allda In,
do your thlng and ramaln anonymoua.
I'm not gonna mlnca worda.
Thla Ia your baat bat.
Got machlnaa runnlng, I'orkllfta,
paopla comlng and golng.
You'ra gonna stay
way undar tha radar.
And tha ownar'a aolld. Ha can't
walt to throw up a curtaln wall,
atack aoma boxaa In front of It,
glva you tha apaca you naad.
Altar that, ha'a got hla bualnaaa,
you'va got youra,
and navar tha twaln ahall maat.
lt'a outatandlng. Am I rlght?
Machlnaa Ilka thla,
gotta ba planty oI' powar.
What about tha amall?
Ah. Mora good nawa.
l'va baan hara whan It's up
and runnlng. Thla placa atlnka
alraady. You'll bland rlght In.
How many amployaaa?
Ha. I knaw you'd aak.
Slxtaan lllagala,
all hlghly motlvatad to
stay daal', bllnd and dumb.
You'll want to vat tham,
I'm aura.
Yaa, Indaad.
So, what do you lay,
maaatro? Huh?
la It unanlmoua?
You know, I workad In a box I'actory
ona aummar In hlgh achool,
and l havan't aaan
ona oI' thaaa In yaara.
Trlp down mamory lana.
That'a parI'act.
You know what thla Ia?
It's a corrugator.
It uaaa ataam and salt to crlmp
kratt papar I'or cardboard.
And It makaa a hall of a rackat
dolng It, whlch Ia graat. nght?
Staam and salt.
Whan thla thlng Ia runnlng,
It'a Ilka a Jungla In hara.
Shlt. It'll ruln tha product.
You can't Juat pop down to Costco
and gat a coupla dahumldll'lara?
What--? Flna. Flna. Movlng on.
[MACHINES WHIRRING LOUDLY]
Spacloua, laolatad locatlon,
no humldlty,
and you gat all
tha I'raa tortlllaa you want.
That'a tha apaclal I'aatura
oI' thla placa.
I don't know.
It'll maka tha tortlllaa
amall Ilka cat plaa.
Somabody'a bound
to notlca that.
All rlght. Wall, thara'a gotta ba
aoma klnd oI' workaround, rlght?
It's a tachnlcal problam.
You guys ara tachnlcal guya.
You know, ba craatlva.
Put your haada togathar.
Anythlng I'ood-ralatad Ia
gonna hava unannouncad
govarnmant Inapactlona.
[LATIN MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Owl OwI OwI
SAUL:
All I'm aaklng
Ia that you kaap an opan mlnd.
Danny'a alraady aat aoma apaca aalda
bahlnd tha Skaa-Ball gamaa.
SAUL:
I know It's a long shot.
All I can say to racommand thla
Ia wa'ra talklng about an ownar hara
who la, how should I put It,
hlghly amanabla.
Look, I gat It. Just say no
and wa'll go gat dlnnar.
All rlght. So I'll start.
No way wa'ra cooklng In hara.
No apaca,
nowhara for tha small to go.
Look at that door. That thlng roll: up
and wa'ra opan to tha world.
MIKE:
I don't know If anybody notlcad,
but thara'a a cop shop
a quartar of a mlla away.
Tha hammar comaa down,
It's gonna ba Cuatar'a Last Stand.
lt'a parI'act.
What?
How ara wa gonna I'It a lab
In hara?
Who aald hara?
[KIDS CHATTERING]
WALT:
A houaa Ia Inl'aatad.
Tarmltaa, cockroachaa, whatavar.
Homaownara hlra
a past control company.
Truck roll: up, homaownara laava.
Tha craw tanta tha houaa.
Thay bomb tha placa wlth polaon.
Tha houaa ataya Ilka that for days.
No ona looka twlca
at a tantad houaa.
Now, mayba thara'a a atranga amall
comlng out of It.
Doaa aomaona thlnk
to Invaatlgata? No.
Doaa anyona go Inalda? Hall, no.
And that's whara wa'll cook.
Thay tant, what,
thraa, I'our houaaa a waak?
So wa plck tha ona
that'a baat for us.
Enough I'loor apaca, aaay accaaa.
Onca tha tant Ia up,
wa go In, wa cook a batch,
wa bomb tha placa and laava.
So wa gotta mova In
and out for avary cook?
Sat up a lab, cook,
and than taka avarythlng down?
lt'a challanglng, but doabla.
Tall ma about thaaa guya.
Uh, Mr. Ponytall on tha aldawalk,
that'a Ira. Ha'a tha ownar.
On tha rooI' Ia Sandor.
Tha laddar'a Farnando,
and down balow, that'a Todd.
Tha paat control oparatlon Ia laglt.
l maan, thay'ra llcanaad,
thay'ra bondad.
Thay do as good a Job
aa anyona In town.
But thay'ra alao top-drawar
aacond-atoray man.
'Sacond-atoray'?
B and E artlata.
Thay'ra burglara.
Yaah. l maan, hay,
thay play It amart.
Thay don't booat anythlng
whlla thay'ra on tha Job.
Thay copy tha kaya,
locata tha valuablaa and alarms,
and thay call that Inl'ormatlon to othar
crawa. Or, altar a dacant Intarval,
thay'll lltt tha gooda thamaalvaa.
And you know tham how?
Oh, l'va baan pulllng thalr
chaatnuta out of tha I'lra,
lagally apaaklng, I'or I'lva yaara.
Ira and hla guya ara good.
I maan, thay know how
to kaap thalr mouth: shut.
And It you buy tham,
thay'ra gonna stay bought.
You can chack Into tham youraall'.
l wlll, II' It comaa to that.
So do wa taka a vota?
Why?
[HONKS HORN]
[PLAYING CLASSICAL MUSIC]
[PLAYING DISCORDANT NOTES]
Wa aound graat.
Rock on, man. Solld.
That Yamaha'a got
a raal nlca touch.
You Ilka tha aound?
lt'a huga, huh?
Yaah, It'a raal nlca,
but wa'ra looklng I'or
aomathlng alaa today.
You got any roadla caaaa?
For aura. What alza?
Blggaat you got.
That'll I'It through, Ilka,
a ragular-alza doorway.
You got It. Follow ma.
[PLAYS NOTES]
Top of tha llna.
Racaaaad hardwara, I'oam llnlng,
quartar-lnch lamlnatad walla,
3-lnch caatara.
Halght Ia good, wldth Ia good.
How much walght wlll thla hold?
lt'a ratad for 900 pounds.
[FEEDBACK SOUEALS]
Unlaaa your band plays laad brlcka,
you should ba okay.
[PLAYING DRUMS]
Wa'ra gonna naad, um...
Hay, man, I'm trylng to do bualnaaa
ovar hara, bltch.
Sorry. Ha'a, Ilka,
ovarly anthualaatlc.
Anyway, um,
I'm gonna naad tour of tham.
Four? That gonna ba layaway?
Bacauaa l naad to aaa
a bunch of ID: for that.
Okay. Hay, uh, you know what?
I'll throw In atancllllng.
What's your band callad?
PETE:
Damn, brothar.
Not aaklng no quaatlona, but It aura
looka Ilka you'ra back In bualnaaa.
No Joka.
You way back In bualnaaa, man.
Look at thla.
Yaah.
Oh. You'ra atacklng tha banjlaa
tlll tha rubbar band popa.
Yaah, yaah.
All'a wa'ra aaylng Ia
wa know you'ra major laagua now,
but It thara'a avar anythlng alaa
you naad from us...
Mm.
Any way wa can gat In on thla at all.
thtla atul'l', blg atul'l'...
Wa would ba all ovar It.
You know, uh,
mayba aomaday.
That's cool.
I guaaa wa battar hlt It than.
Yaah. Kaap on kaaplng on, brothar.
Latar.
[METAL DOOR WHIRRING]
MIKE:
Okay, It Is the same job as always.
You go out, you lnapact,
you daal wlth tha cuatomara,
ragular drlll.
Evarythlng'a tha aama,
axcapt I'or ona Important datall.
No ataallng.
MIKE: No ataallng.
Not a toothplck, not tha apara changa
batwaan tha couch cuahlona,
not tha pantlaa out of tha hampar.
Nothlng. And I maan nothlng.
II' you'ra out wlth your buddlaa
and thay ask If you got
a hot tlp on a B and E,
you tall tham you got nada.
You'ra out of tha gama.
Tha bottom llna Ia that thaaa houaaa
ara out of bounds, now and I'oravar.
Got It?
All rlght.
From tlma to tlma,
you'ra gonna aaa thaaa two.
Now, as tar as you'ra concarnad,
thay ara ghoata.
You don't aaa tham.
You don't haar tham.
You don't say 'good mornlng.'
You don't apaak
unlaaa you'ra apokan to.
On tha othar hand,
It thay tall you to Jump,
you don't ask what for,
you Jump.
Now, you naad a nama I'or tham?
You call tham 'Yaa, alr'
and 'No, alr.‘
You got any problama,
you coma to ma.
JESSE:
Hara'a tha daal.
Tha I'Inlahlng tank'a a tlght I'lt.
And wlth thla motor you'va got on top...
WALT: Tha agltatlon motor.
Tha agltatlon motor hara on top,
tha tank'a not gonna I'It In tha box.
It's Just, uh... It's Just too tall.
You know, I thought wa'd put
a collar on tha tank
and carry tha motor In aaparataly,
alongalda tha condanaar.
And on tha day,
wa Juat klnd oI' twlat It Into placa,
you know,
whlla wa'ra aattlng up.
Yaah.
That's good.
That wlll work.
And Joa and hla guy:
can bulld It, rlght?
Yaah. You know, thay'ra, uh...
Thay'ra up for It.
Joa alraady bought a TIG waldar
for tha alumlnlum work.
And, you know, I I'Igura
II' thay can pull off tha magnat,
thay can handla thla.
Um... Now, llatan,
about tha amall...
About kaaplng It out of paopla'a
drapaa and I'urnltura and whatnot...
Whan l was down In Maxlco,
thay, uh...
Thara waa thla blg, blg,
plaatlc hoapltal tant
thay sat up lnalda of tha--
[DOOR UNLOCKING]
Oh, ahlt. Sorry.
Oh, hl. Sorry.
No, no, no.
Wa wara Juat wrapplng up.
Um, thla Ia my, uh...
Frland. HI. Walt.
Nlca to maat you.
You too.
JESSE:
Thla la, uh, Brock.
HI, Brock. I'm Walt.
l'va haard a lot about you.
l undaratand
you wara In tha hoapltal.
And Jaaaa told ma
that you wara vary brava.
Yaah. A man of law worda.
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm sorry. Ha moatly Just want:
to play hla gama.
Oh, I know that.
l hava two of my own.
A boy and a glrl.
[VIDEO GAME BEEPING]
Wall, I should, uh...
I should go.
lwaa thlnklng I could
maka us all aoma dlnnar.
Ara you aura you don't wanna...?
Yaah. Why don't you stay
for a baar at last?
Sura. Why not?
A baar sound: good.
Thank you.
Mm-hm.
[VIDEO GAME BEEPING]
[CLATTERING IN KITCHEN]
[KIDS CHATTERING]
How ara you today, alr?
Wa'ra good. Good. How ara you?
Famlly all packad up, raady to go?
Yaah.
Hara you'ra acknowladglng
that you'va ramovad all pata
and plant: from tha houaa
and that food has baan
ramovad or doubla-aaalad
In tha baga wa provldad.
Uh-huh.
Thla acknowladgaa you'va
ramovad or baggad any
madlclna, tobacco, pat I'ood.
Battar maka aura you got
any madlclna you mlght naad.
lt'a alraady In tha car.
Okay.
Holy crap.
How much polaon ara you ualng?
Eh, It's not how much,
It's gattlng It whara It'a naadad.
Thoaa ara your I'oggara.
Thay dlaparaa tha I'umlgata
Into tha atructura
whara It'll allmlnata
any nympha or larvaa
as wall as
tha I'ull-grown blattodaa.
So, uh, do wa hava
all your kaya?
Any axtraa on hara
you mlght wlnd up naadlng?
No, I'm good.
Okay.
Thla laat ona hara acknowladgaa
that you hava baan Inl'ormad
that you may not
raantar tha pramlaaa
untll It has claarad
tha poat-I'umlgatlon Inapactlon.
So you'ra gonna gat tham all, rlght?
Wa'll klll tham daad.
That's a guarantaa.
TODD:
Slr? Uh, alr?
Yaa?
Thara'a a nanny cam
In tha llvlng-room clock.
l dlaablad It.
IJuat thought you should know.
What's your nama?
Todd, alr.
[THE PEDDLERSI 'ON A CLEAR DAY
YOU CAN SEE FOREVER' PLAYS]
J' On a clear day I
J' Rlsa and look around you I
I And you wlll see who I
J' You ara J'
J' On a clear day I
I How It wlll astound you I
I That the glow of your balng J'
J' Outshlnas avary star I
J' You'll feel part of every mountaln J'
J' Sea and share I
I And you can hear I
I From far and near I
J' A word you'va navar heard before I
I But on that clear day I
J' On that clear day I
J' You can see forever I
I And ever I
I Ever more I
J' You'll feel part of every mountaln J'
J' Saa or share I
I And you can hear
From far and near I
J' A word you'va navar
Haard bafora J'J'
Chaars.
You know, l'va gotta say,
saalng you wlth Andraa
and that llttla boy... Hah.
It was nlca.
Yaah. It's good, rlght?
Yaah.
And tha way sha looks at you... Oh.
You thlnk?
Oh, dal'lnltaly.
[CHUCKLES]
[CARTOON MUSIC PLAYS OVER TV]
So Is It, um...? Is It movlng
In any partlcular dlractlon?
Uh, I don't know. Mayba. Yaah.
You know, somatlmas l thlnk,
you know,
II' It I'aals rlght, than...
II' It I'aals rlght, It I'aals rlght.
Somatlmas you Just
gotta llstan to your gut.
l maan, Instant I'amlly.
What mora can you ask, rlght?
Absolutaly.
MOE [OVER TV]:
Cut the cards.
Hava you thought about
what your plan Is?
You know, vIs-a-vls honasty?
You maan how much
sha knows about thls?
Um... Sha doasn't
know anythlng.
l maan, you know, sha's not stupld.
Sha knows I'm Into somathlng, but...
Sha could maka
a pratty good guass.
But I navar told har anythlng.
I'm not gonna.
Okay.
l maan It.
I know you do.
Jassa, I can't pratand that thls
doasn't aftact ma. It doas.
But wlth avarythlng that
wa'va baan through, tha two of us,
thls has to ba your daclslon.
l maan, you'va aarnad that.
Sarlously?
Yaah.
Sacrats craata barrlars
batwaan paopla.
I'm spaaklng I'rom axparlanca,
ballava ma.
All that you'va dona,
It's a part of you, and...
l maan, It you choosa to spand
tha rast of your lll'a wlth thls parson,
than you'll hava to daclda
how much you'll shara wlth har.
Maanlng what? lea avarythlng?
lea Gala?
I'm Just trylng to say that I trust you,
and I know you'll maka tha rlght call.
II' sha lovas you,
sha'll undarstand.
Thay'ra laavlng straaks.
Thls mora athnlc-looklng ona,
ha's dolng a graat Job,
but tha othar ona
Is golng back and forth
Ilka ha's scrubblng a wall.
Thay hava to go In clrclas
or you'ra golng to laava straaks.
That's pratty baslc, rlght?
I don't maan to tall you
your buslnass.
It's Just--
It's slmpla quallty control.
So l'va got soma good naws.
Guass what.
What?
No, raally. I want you to guass.
Marla, l raally--
Okay. Hank's back at work.
That's wondarI'ul.
Yaah.
Sura, thay lova hlm now, but whara
wara thay whan ha naadad tham?
Markart and all tha rast,
thay laughad hlm out of tha oI'I'Ica
whan ha told tham
about that chlckan man.
As far as I'm concarnad,
too llttla too lata.
II' It wara ma,
I'd tall tham all to go to hall.
Do I sound blttar?
But It's what ha wants, rlght?
Yaah, It's dolng hlm good.
l maan, hls PT Is golng gangbustars.
Ha's hardly uslng hls cana at all.
And thank you for that, raally.
l maan, God knows whara
ha'd ba II' wa had to go
through hls haalth plan.
I'm Just glad ha's I'aallng battar.
So, spaaklng oI' whlch,
wa hava anothar blg avant comlng up.
Hava you thought about
what you'ra gonna do?
Walt's blrthday.
Whatavar you naad, I'm hara.
Mm. Yaah. I, um...
I don't thlnk wa'ra gonna
do anythlng thls yaar.
What ara you talklng about?
OI' coursa wa'ra gonna do
somathlng.
Skylar, ha was dlagnosad
around hls blrthday, rlght?
So It's baan a whola yaar.
Llstan, l'va had my problams
wlth Walt.
Why ha wouldn't coma to tha housa
whan wa wara all practlcally--
Whatavar. Watar undar tha brldga.
But at thls polnt,
avary yaar Is praclous. Wa ara--
What ara you dolng?
Uh...
You don't smoka.
You havan't smokad slnca collaga.
You can't ba sarlousI
Wlth tha baby and Walt?
You'ra not smoklng around tha baby,
ara you? And you can't smoka hara.
Thara's gotta ba soma rula
or ragulatlon, I'm sura.
You can't I'orca your amployaas
to braatha sacondhand smoka.
I know for a fact that that Is lllagal.
Marla, shut up.
What? I'm sorry,
plaasa don't spaak to ma Ilka that.
I am slmply saylng--
Wlll you shut up?
Shut tha hall up.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Plaasa stop--
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
[SOBBING]
JESSE:
That's 5.23.
WALT:
Flva-polnt-two-thraa.
JESSE:
Last ona.
FIva-polnt-two-slx.
That comas to 49.27.
Good ylald, rlght?
That Is an axcallant ylald.
All rlght.
[FUMIGANT HISSING]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hay, Marla.
How you dolng?
Whara Is Skylar?
In tha badroom. Sha's rastlng.
ls avarythlng okay?
Braakdown?
What doas that maan?
It maans I don't know what alsa
to call It. But l'va navar saan har
Ilka that, avar.
Wall, what dld sha say
whan sha was yalllng?
Nothlng.
Sha Just yallad, 'Shut up, shut up,'
ovar and ovar agaln.
Dld you know sha's smoklng?
Occaslonally, mayba.
It's not a ragular thlng.
Ah... IJust wlsh I had gottan
your massaga.
Massagas, Walt. Plural.
I probably callad you I'lva tlmas.
I'm not laavlng hara untll I know
what's got har so upsat.
Ara you gambllng agaln?
Is that what thls Is?
Plaasa, God,
tall ma tha cancar Isn't back.
It's not tha cancar.
Wall, somathlng happanad.
I don't maan to polnt tha I'lngar,
but thls dldn't Just coma
out of nowhara.
It's tlma to tall ma tha truth, Walt.
All of It.
l maan It.
You'ra rlght.
You haard about Tad Banaka?
Tha accldant?
What accldant?
Oh.
Um...
A coupla waaks back,
Tad took a fall, a bad ona.
Ha gava hlmsall' a concusslon
and, uh, I'racturad
a coupla vartabraa.
Ha's stlll In tha hospltal.
Ha may navar walk agaln.
Oh, my God. I dldn't know.
I'm so sorry to haar that.
Yaah.
But that couldn't axplaln
Skylar's...
Uh, yas. Yas, It could.
You do know, rlght? You...
You must know.
Oh, God.
Sha was havlng an aftalr.
Wlth Tad Banaka.
Llstan. It wasn't...
It wasn't ongolng or anythlng, and...
Skylar and l hava baan trylng
to put thlngs back togathar.
And than tha accldant happanad,
and sha got...
Marla, I'm bagglng you.
Plaasa kaap thls to yoursall'.
I don't want Hank
to thlnk lass oI' har. Or ma.
Whan dld you, um...?
Was sha--? I'm gonna go.
Okay. All rlght.
Thank you.
I'm sorr--
No.
[DOOR cLOSES]
MAN [OVER TV]:
Ouchl That lookad nasty.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING OVER TV]
Hay, you okay?
Raally?
Yaah.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING OVER TV]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE OVER TV]
[YELLING OVER TV]
[LOUD BLASTS OVER TV]
Coma on. You wanna fuck wlth ma?
Okay.
You llttla cockroaches.
WALT JR.:
Dad, walt.
TONY [OVER TV]:
You wanna play games?
Okay. lplay wlth you. Come on.
WALT: Thls Is It.
WALT JR.: Walt. Walt for It.
[CHUCKLES]
Ready?
TONY: You wanna play rough? Okayl
Say hello to my llttla frlendl
BOTH: 'Say hello to my llttla I'rlend.'
Nlca. Just--
Hay, Mom. Um, I'eellng better?
Hey. Hey, why don't you ]oln us,
It you feel up to It?
We have popcorn.
l thlnk there's some plzza left.
If you're up to It.
Yaah, Mom. Joln us.
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE OVER TV]
Oh, my God. Look. Look.
You whoresl
WALT:
Oh. Everyone dles In thls movle,
don't they?
[BEEPS]
MIKE:
Okay.
For you and you and ma.
Three hundred and slxty-seven
thousand dollars each.
Ooh. Walt a mlnute.
After the dealers got thalr cut,
we should be
looklng at 1,379,560.
Mlke, you're short.
You're almost 300,000 short.
You're I'orgettlng about the mules.
They get a flat 20 percent.
The what?
The drlvers.
They're the ones that take the product
from us to the dealers.
And so transportatlon
Is worth 20 percent?
They're taklng a rlsk.
Two hundred and seventy-I'lve
thousand dollars worth of rlsk?
What dld Gus pay hls mules?
Gustavo Frlng dldn't use mules.
He dldn't need them.
He spent 20 years
bulldlng hls own dlstrlbutlon.
He had 16 rel'rlgerator trucks
runnlng hls product.
And do you know
where they are now?
Government Impound.
You don't Ilka paylng 20 percent?
Maybe you shouldn't have klllad
the guy.
Hey, hey. There's stlll over
a mllllon bucks here, all rlght?
That's for one cook.
Slnce you're puttlng on
the green ayeshade,
my suppller and I
came to an agreement.
The mathylamlne
Is free thls tlma.
But brace yourself, because
the next barrel Is gonna cost blg.
Can we contlnue, or you got
any more burnlng questlons?
Okay, kld.
You I'ronted us 120 to get us golng.
So that's 401'rom hlm and ma.
One hundred and twenty.
Yes. Thank you, Jessa.
MIKE:
Okay.
Now, Ira gets 110
for our place of the buslness
and 25 par cook.
That Is 45
from each of us.
lra's guys get 10 each per cook.
Goodman's cut, 10,0001'rom each.
Legacy cost, $351,000.
That's 117,000 each.
'Legacy cost'?
I got nlne guys.
You don't know them, but they were
part of the prevlous oparatlon
and they know a lot. And rlght now,
some of them are In ]all
and more wlll be soon.
The lads RICO-ad thalr hazard pay.
So we are gonna make them whola.
We are gonna make them whola?
What Is thls 'we'?
These were Gus' employees,
not ours.
They mlght have been Gus'
employees, but they're my guys.
So, what are they dolng
to further our Interests?
The cops are looklng at them
very closely.
We don't want them
I'urtherlng our Interests.
So we are paylng them, why?
Because It's what you do.
Oh. It's what you do.
Huh.
My guys are kaaplng thalr mouths shut.
We make them whola.
One hand washes the other.
It's as slmple as that.
Huh. It sounds Ilka
a slmple shakedown,
slmple as that.
We're paylng I'or thalr sllence.
That's blackmall.
Buslness Is my and.
Thls Is buslness. End of story.
Thls Is your problem.
It should come out of your and.
Hey. Hey. Just take It out of mlne.
All rlght? Go for It.
I don't care. Just take It.
Well, Jessa, thank you,
but no.
I'll pay my share.
Let me tell you somathlng.
Thls...
Is how It's gonna be
from here on out.
My guys are
an ongolng axpandlture,
so you best get yourself
comfortable wlth It.
WALT:
A hundred and thlrty-seven thousand.
[CHUCKLES]
That's less than wlth Frlng.
Llsten, Walter.
Just because you shot Jesse James,
don't make you Jesse James.
MIKE:
Tomorrow.
How are you I'eellng?
Okay, I guess.
Broke It oft wlth Andrea.
I had to.
She's gonna tell Brock.
I'm stlll gonna take care
of the rent and stuff.
It's the rlght thlng to do,
but, you know--
I meant thls.
How are you I'eellng
about the money?
You're looklng at It wrong.
When we worked for Gus,
we were cooklng
200 pounds a week.
Thls last batch was great,
but we dldn't even crack 50 pounds.
We maybe claarad less money,
but we got a blgger place of the pla.
It's Ilka you sald, we're owners,
not employees.
I've been thlnklng about Vlctor.
Yeah?
Yaah.
All thls tlma,
l was sure that
Gus dld what he dld
to send me a message.
Maybe there's another reason.
lee what?
Vlctor trylng to cook
that batch on hls own?
Taklng llbertles
that weren't hls to take?
Maybe he flew
too close to the sun,
got hls throat cut.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[METAL DOOR WHIRRING]
[J'J'J']