How blg': the batch?
Should be about so pounds,
glve or take.
Uncle Jack, that mask...
...l thlnk you should....
Mr. Whlte nld the fumes
aren't good to broathe.
Let me worry about
what I breathe, kld.
Juat hurry thla up
so I can grab a smoke.
Seventy-alx percent.
-Nlce golng, nephew.
-Thanka, Uncle Jack.
Where's the blue?
-Where'a the what?
-The blue colour.
Does It come later,
when thla hardena?
Where I: It?
I am correct In aaaumlng
thla should be blue?
See, I'm thlnklng the headllne here
should be '76 percent.‘
Yeah. Whole lot more than It was.
That dude who looked llke Wolverlne?
He couldn't crack 70.
Flne. Yes, percentage-wlse,
lt's marglnally Improved.
And congratulatlons, Todd.
But blue Is our brand, all over Europe.
It's what our buyers pay top dollar for.
If we're down a blt ln purlty
from the Helsenberg days...
...maybe they'll let us sllde on that,
but not It It's not blue.
I don't know. To my eye...
-...|t's klnd of blue.
-Yeah, a llttle.
It's blulsh.
Todd, you're the chef.
What do you thlnk?
Yeah, klnd ol'.
It It catches the llght Just rlght...
...I could see how you'd thlnk
there's a touch of blue...
...blue-green In there.
-Aquamarlne.
-Hell, we'll put food colourlng In It.
Make It any damn shade you want.
Yeah, llke they do
l'arm-ralsed salmon. Yeah.
I mean, Jesus, you ever see how plnk
they make that crap?
lee, l'lamlngo plnk.
It sure as hell don't come out
the ocean looklng llke that.
All rlght. Let's make some money.
-Here you go, Ms. Quayle.
-Lyd|a.
Thank you.
Is the tea okay?
I made It Just llke you asked.
You sure? It It's too weak or somethlng,
I can go put another bag In It.
I'm sure.
Look, about the product...
...l'm really sorry about the colour.
For a mlnute or two,
It Just got a few degrees too hot...
...In the mlxlng kettle, lthlnk.
l mlght've Just
cooked the colour rlght out of It.
You burned lt, llke a cake.
Yeah, sort of, I guess.
But the polnt ls l thlnk I can l'lx lt...
...and l thlnk I can brlng
the purlty up too.
I mean, I'm dolng everythlng
Just llke Mr. Whlte taught me, so....
You know,
It's bound to get better, rlght?
l appreclate you maklng
every posslble effort...
...because, as you know,
my buyers expect a certaln threshold...
...a contlnulty.
Yeah. Yeah, totally.
About your buyers...
...I could ask my uncle
to smooth thlngs over wlth them...
...ll' you want.
I'll pass. Thanks.
I've put a lot of l'alth
In your abllltles, Todd.
l belleve In you.
Please do make the cook better.
It's very Important to me.
I've got a l'llght to catch.
-Hello.
-Hey. It's Walt.
Hey, Mr. Whlte. How you dolng?
I'm okay.
l....
Todd, I thlnk I mlght have
another job for your uncle.
Oh, okay.
You want me to set up a meetlng?
l-- Yes. Please. Let's do that.
Any heads-up I should glve hlm, llke...
...whlch Jall, how many targets,
stufl' llke that?
-Mr. Whlte?
-Just one target.
Not currently In [all.
Jesse PInkman.
You got It.
I'm surprlsed you dldn't strangle hlm.
So now what? Book hlm?
I'm sure the AUSA wlll have plenty to
say about how to play hlm agalnst Walt.
Knowlng what we know about
how Walt deals wlth rats behlnd bars?
Punk has to be safer
wlth the marshals...
...than out here
where It's open season.
What does that mean?
What are you thlnklng?
The kld's got an Idea.
What kld? That kld?
Tlmmy Dlpshlt there?
The one that screwed up our stlng?
I'm all ears.
Just hear hlm out, would you?
Okay, genlus, what's the Idea?
You guys need evldence
to put hlm away.
Only he's too smart
to leave any out there, rlght?
So you say.
Well, I know some evldence...
...that greedy asshole
would never destroy.
Hls money.
-You know where he keeps hls money?
-No.
But I know someone who mlght.
0h, hey. How'd It go?
Tralled hlm to the Dog House,
plcked hlm up there.
Seemed to be looklng for someone.
-Had a lot of questlons.
-No calls though, rlght?
-You got hls phone?
-Yeah.
-He's on Ice?
-Sal'e house oft Rlo Bravo.
We've got Van Oster babyslttlng hlm.
Yeah. What about Van Oster?
Dld he have any questlons?
Probably, but he knows better
than to ask.
Good Job.
I gotta tell you thls up front, Hank.
ll' thls guy decldes
he wants to lawyer up...
...I don't care It you are my boss,
I'm gonna put a stop to thls.
He won't lawyer up.
What the hell, man?
You're up.
Hey there. You mlnd
taklng It outslde tor a mlnute?
-No, slr. You got It.
-All rlght, thanks.
Know who I am?
I'll take that as a yes.
Thanks for your patlence.
As Agent Gomez sald,
you're not under arrest.
Why am I here?
Well, you're here
for your own protectlon, slr.
How you l'lgure that?
Well, we both know how dangerous
my brother-In-law can be.
Nlce poker l'ace.
Look, relax.
There's not much new you can tell me
about Walter Whlte.
Multlple murders...
...tles to a whlte-power prlson gang...
...ran the largest meth racket
In the entlre Southwest.
I'm not asklng,
you're not answerlng...
...whoop-de-do.
Let's cut to the chase.
We have a wlre on Walt's phone.
We Intercepted a call between hlm
and a certaln Saul Goodman, Esq.
You know, your employer?
Anyway, In the call, Walt sald
that he was golng to, quote:
'Take care of one Jesse Plnkman,'
unquote...
...and that you were next on the hlt llst.
That's why you're here.
Bullshlt. That don't make no sense.
I got the recordlng.
I can-- I can let you hear It.
Your assoclate, Goodman's l'lxer--
What's hls name?
Some carrottop named Patrlck Kuby.
Boston P.D. ran hlm out of Beantown
a few years back.
Came out here for the sunshlne.
Walt sald he was gonna do thls Kuby
guy the same way he does you.
In fact, Kuby's already mlsslng.
Sorry to say, thlngs are looklng grlm
for your-- Your redheaded buddy.
Belleve us, don't belleve us.
Sult yoursell'.
Whatever you do,
I would not call Goodman.
He sold you down the rlver blgtlme.
-The hell you talklng about?
-Don't take It personally.
Goodman's next on the chopplng block
II' he doesn't do what Whlte says.
To be l'alr, your clrcus clown of a boss
dld try to spare you for all of, what...
...about 15 seconds...
...bel'ore he declded
to help Walt track you down.
You see, Goodman's got
a trace on your phone...
...and as soon as you call hlm...
...Walt wlll l'lnd out
where you're hldlng.
Then It's Just a matter of tlme
before you end up llke thls.
Oh, man. Oh, man. I swear to God,
I dldn't know he was gonna klll hlm, man.
-l dldn't know he was gonna klll hlm.
-Relax.
II' we thought you dld,
you'd be In lockup...
...l'or consplracy to commlt murder
Instead of under our protectlon.
Tell us everythlng you know
so we can get hlm before he gets you.
Why would he wanna klll me?
-l aln't do nothlng.
-Who knows wlth thls guy?
From what he sald,
It may have to do...
...wlth hlm tylng up loose ends...
...regardlng polsonlng
some kld named Brock.
Or maybe It's because
you know where hls money ls.
I don't know where hls money ls.
That aln't what we heard.
You aln't llstenlng
to the people In the know.
Me and Kuby rented a van
for the dude...
...loaded hls cash up
In a self-storage unlt...
...handed over the keys to hlm
at Goodman's.
Who knows where he took It
from there?
A van, huh?
How much money we talklng?
Seven barrels' worth.
Seven barrels?
When you say 'barrels,'
you mean 'barrels' barrels?
Barrels, man. You know,
plastlc, black, 55-gallon type.
I got them at Home Depot.
Fllled up every last damn
one of them too.
And where dld you rent the van?
Larlat. The one
on Candelarla and Monroe.
-Larlat on Candelarla?
-Yeah.
Kuby rented the van.
Mr. Whlte dropped It oft.
He had us wash It good
before Kuby took It back.
Wash the rental? Why?
It was l'llthy, man,
llke he went oft-road wlth It.
After we had hosed It down,
he grabbed a shovel out the back...
...handed over the key,
and that was It.
That's all I know.
All rlght, Mr. Bablneaux.
Agent Gomez and l are golng
to do everythlng we can...
...to l'lnd thls son of a bltch.
lee l sald, you're free to go.
But II' I were you,
I wouldn't take one step out that door.
And remember, no phone calls.
0h, actually, I almost forgot.
I took the llberty
ol' removlng the battery...
...so Walt can't track you by GPS.
So don't put that back In.
Agent Van Oster
wlll stay here wlth you.
You're In good hands.
He's our best man wlth a gun.
Don't dlscuss the case wlth hlm
because the less you dlstract hlm...
...the better he can protect you.
How long you gonna be?
As long as It takes to keep you safe.
So Just one guy thls tlme.
Not even In lockup.
Some former partner, Todd says?
Yeah.
So, what are we talklng, rat patrol?
Rat p--?
Rat patrol? No. No, he's not a rat.
He's Just....
He Just won't llsten to reason.
-0kay.
-He's Just angry.
He's not a rat.
All rlght.
Angry non-rat. Got It.
How angry we talklng, by the way?
lee, Hulk angry?
lee, Rambo-James Bond
badass Indlvldual?
Not somethlng you'd do yourself, huh?
Jesse Is llke l'amlly to me.
Look, I want what you do
to be qulck and palnless.
No sufl'erlng, no fear.
Bullet to the back of the head.
Somethlng he doesn't see comlng.
I respect that.
-There's too many savages out there.
-Let's Just talk about the money.
No, we don't want your money.
We want you to cook for us.
You know I'm out of the buslness.
Just a couple tlmes
to tutor my nephew here, that's all.
Get hlm on track
to brlnglng the purlty up.
Get the colour rlght too.
Apparently that blue touch
you put on It...
...lt's all the craze
wlth those Slavlc types.
-So I'm told.
-No. Absolutely not.
Look, what was the prlce per head
last tlme? I'll trlple It.
A drop In the bucket compared to
what we alm to earn from the blue stufl'.
Don't sklmp on l'amlly,
that's what I always say.
You want us to do thls Job?
Do It rlght? That's the prlce.
One cook...
...after the Job Is done.
Tlme Is ol' the essence.
Do you understand?
Do hlm tonlght It you want.
Just tell me where he ls.
I don't know where he ls...
...but I know how to flush hlm out.
You want strlng cheese
or yogurt squeezers wlth your PBJ?
Both.
-l dldn't hear you.
-Both, please.
Hold on, honey.
HI, Andrea.
I don't know It you remember me.
I'm Walter Whlte, Jesse's l'rlend.
-Oh, yeah. Yeah, of course. HI.
-Yeah. Yeah.
0h, hl. HI.
I'm sorry to Just barge In
on you llke thls...
...but I was hoplng that I could
have a moment to talk wlth you.
It's about Jesse.
Sure. I'm sort of rushlng around
rlght now.
Wanna talk lnslde
whlle I get my boy ready?
Oh, well, yeah. II' It's--
II' It's okay, yeah, sure.
Thank you.
-You met Brock bel'ore, rlght?
-Yes. Yes, I have. At Jesse's.
How you dolng, Brock?
Brock, he asked you a questlon.
Froot Loops.
That's good stuff.
So Jesse....
Yeah, I....
I don't wanna alarm you...
...but I've been trylng
to reach hlm for days.
I've stopped at hls house...
...l've left all klnds of messages
on hls volcemall...
...and he won't return my calls.
I can't flnd hlm anywhere.
Have you heard from hlm?
No, not slnce the last tlme
he called to check on Brock.
That was, I don't know,
two weeks ago, maybe.
Andrea...
...Jesse's uslng agaln, and l....
l have a bad feellng about thls.
Have you trled calllng the pollce?
Or a better Idea.
Jesse's lawyer's name Is Saul Goodman.
l have hls card somewhere.
I mean, he may have ways of flndlng
Jesse wlthout gettlng hlm In trouble.
'Better call Saul.' Yeah. l-- l dld that.
He was able to verlfy
that Jesse's not locked up...
...but, otherwlse, very llttle help.
You see, the thlng ls...
...Is that Jesse and I
had thls argument recently.
And I won't bore you
wlth the detalls, but he's....
He's-- He's pretty upset wlth me and....
And I'm hoplng that's the reason
he hasn't called me back...
...lnstead of hlm belng....
Well....
Well, I'll try hlm rlght now.
I mean, If that's It, he's mad at you...
-...maybe I'll have better luck.
-That would be such a help. Yes.
What--? What--?
What number are you calllng hlm on?
-H|s cell.
-You know, he recently got a new one.
And there. That--
That's hls new number there,
the hlghllghted one.
Jesse, hey, It's Andrea.
Your frlend Walter Just dropped by.
He's here at the house rlght now.
We-- We're thlnklng of you.
Call me back as soon
as you get thls message.
I really need to hear from you.
It's Important.
Thank you, Andrea.
l appreclate that.
Well, I better-- I better be golng.
You're welcome to stay a few mlnutes
to see If he calls back.
No, no, no. You're trylng to get
your son off to school.
If he does happen to call back,
would you call me?
Better yet, I've got your number.
I'll call you back, okay?
And thank you.
See you, Brock.
We on?
Yes. It should be any tlme now.
Copy that.
Remember, fast and palnless.
And take hlm away from here.
I don't want the mother
or the boy to know.
You got It.
Jesse, hey, It's Andrea.
Your frlend Walter just dropped by.
He's here at the house rlght now.
Wen We're thlnklng of you.
Call me back as soon
as you get thls message.
I really need to hear from you.
It's Important.
Nlce try, asshole.
How'd It go at the rental place?
Van have GPS?
No GPS. Nope.
They used to have GPS
untll about slx months ago...
...when the ACLU or somebody
sued them...
...and they had to get rld of It.
Well, that's It. Game over.
Yo, man, you can't Just glve up on thls.
-Who sald we're glvlng up?
-What do you got?
Just thlnklng about
what Bablneaux sald...
...about the van belng dlrty...
...and the shovel
that Walt had wlth hlm.
I'll bet you 1o-to-1
he burled that money.
No klddlng. So what?
There's a whole lot of desert out there.
How we gonna flnd the spot?
You sald It yourself,
there's no GPS on the van.
Yeah. But Walt doesn't know that.
All rlght.
Here's your change.
-Oh, count It out, please.
-Here.
Three. That makes 15.
Plus 5, that Is 20.
-G|ve thls to your car wash professlonal.
-Thank you.
Say It.
-Have an A-1 day.
-Oh, you too.
-Good.
-Why--? Why do l--?
Who do I gotta say that?
Because It relnforces our brand.
So gettlng the hang of It?
lt's-- It's pretty baslc.
Mom, It's Saturday.
Can--? Can I go?
-Go where?
-Home.
Plck up a few thlngs,
maybe chlll for a llttle blt.
I'm sure the smell Is gone by now.
Why don't you Just stlck around here
for a whlle longer?
-I need you.
-Hl.
Who do I glve thls to?
You know what? I'll take care of It.
Excuse me, son.
That'll be 14.97, please.
Hey. How you dolng?
You're on our blllboard. You're--
-You're the lawyer guy, yeah.
-'Better call Saull'
Okay.
So 3 makes 15, and 20, 25, 30...
...35, 4n, and 10 makes 50. Thank you.
l llke your commerclal.
What--? What happened to your face?
Oh, thls Is a-- I guess you'd call It
an occupatlonal hazard.
Thank you, and please glve that
to your car wash professlonal.
Very good. Thank you very much.
Good to meet you.
-Yeah.
-Don't drlnk and drlve.
-Okay.
-But If you do, call me.
Have an A-1 day.
Mom, you forgot to say It.
Yeah. Yeah, I dld. Okay.
Make sure you get In there
between the cushlons, all rlght?
That's It. Way In there. Attaboy.
What the hell you dolng here?
I swear to God, the kld left
so much booger powder In there...
...my Caddy Is a K-9 unlt's wet dream.
Is your phone broken? All 200 of them?
Huell's gone where?
No Idea. AWOL. Nobody's seen hlm.
He's not answerlng hls phone.
So, what about Jesse?
He hasn't shown up yet.
He wlll, Saul.
He's probably hlgh as a klte...
...and hasn't gotten our message yet.
Or he got It loud and clear,
flgured out It's a setup.
The kld Is not as dumb as you thlnk.
Are you wearlng a bullet-proof vest?
Dld you mlss the part about
my bodyguard has gone mlsslng?
Look, I had hlm
watchlng the Dog House...
...flgurlng the kld mlght show up.
Next thlng I know, radlo sllence.
You're the math whlz.
Add up two and two.
Jesse Is not on some kllllng spree.
It's me he wants.
It's Just me.
Well, then where the hell's Huell?
-Any news?
-Not yet, but soon. I promlse.
Have an A-1 day.
Next, Inventory llsts.
These are the Inventory llsts.
Every day, after close of buslness...
...you tally the total
of every Item sold...
...and you mark It
under the approprlate column.
So say we sold, I don't know,
10 plne-scented alr fresheners.
You mark '10' under thls column...
...and then you subtract 10
from the stock column.
Okay? Why don't you try that?
Jesse?
Got my photo, bItch?
That barrel look famIIIar?
Because I just found st more
exactly IIke It.
That bIg bastard
who works for Goodman...
...I pIstol-whlpped that melon
he calls a head...
...tIll he gave up what he knew,
whlch led me to your rental van...
...whlch, It turns out, had GPS.
How do you llke that, genlus?
Guess you dldn't thlnk of everythlng.
Look, Jesse, I don't know
what you plan on dolng here, but--
Well, I'll glve you a hInt, Walt.
It Involves a couple of fIve-gallon cans
of gasollne and a lIghter.
No, no, no! Jesse, please, llsten to me.
No, you llsten to me, bltch.
You get your ass out here
as fast as you can.
Yes, I'm comlng. Okayl Okayl
And don't even thlnk about
calllng anyone for help, all rlght?
You hang up on me, put me on hold...
...lose my call for any reason...
...as soon as you do,
I'm burnlng all of It.
All rlght? One bIg bonﬂre.
You get the pIcture?
-I get It, I get It. Okay.
-All rlght. You better hurry...
...because I'm burnlng
10 grand a mlnute...
...tIll you get here, startlng rlght now.
l sald, I'm comlngl
Don't you touch my money!
FIre In the hole, bltch.
There goes to G's.
-Oh, nIce orange ﬂames.
-No, no, no!
Jesse-- Jesse, please.
I'm dylng. My cancer Is back.
You're not hurtlng anyone
but my famlly. Okay?
I can't spend thls money.
It's not for me. I won't be around
long enough to use It.
It belongs to my chlldren.
Oh, you're gonna talk about kIds.
You're serIously gonna go there?
I am sorry about Brock.
No, you're not.
-I am.
-You're not, but you're gonna be.
Yes, I am sorry about Brockl
But he's allve, Isn't he?
He's flne, Just as I planned Itl
Don't you thlnk I knew
exactly how much to glve hlm?
That I had It all measured out?
Come on!
-Don't you know me by now?
-I know you're a lyIng, evIl scumbag...
...that's what I know.
Manlpulatlng people...
-...messIng wlth theIr heads.
-Open your eyes!
Can't you see that I needed you
on my slde to klll Gus?
I ran over those gangbangersl
l kllled Emlllo and Krazy-al Why?
l dld all of those thlngs
to try to save your llfe...
Only you're too stupld to know It!
Jesse.
Jessel
Jesse, talk to me.
Jesse, l dldn't hang up! Jessel
Jesse?
Jesse, I'm here. Where are you?
Son of a bltch.
Son of a bltchl
Come on, come on.
Yes.
Yeah?
It's me. I've got Jesse In slght...
...and he's comlng for me rlght now.
He knows I'm alone.
-Let's go, boy.
-I'm guesslng he's got backup.
-How many guys?
-I do-- I-- I don't know.
-Where are you?
-To'hajIIlee.
An IndIan reservatlon west of town.
-Get a pen.
-Go.
Okay.
'Thlrty-four, 59, 20...
106, 36, 52. "
Those are coordlnates.
If you want me around
to cook for you...
-...you get here now.
-You got It.
As fast as you can. Okay. Walt.
They're comlng.
Looks llke there could be
three men total.
Walt a mlnute.
What? What Is It?
-Stay In the car.
-Oh, my God.
Walter, what Is It?
Walter, you stIll there?
Walter?
Walter, you got eyes on hlm?
What do you see?
Walter, talk to me.
Forget It.
Don't come.
What do you mean, 'don't come'?
It's off.
Do not come.
Walt!
Come on out!
I know you're out here!
It's over!
Walt!
Come on out, Waltl
Got hlm.
Drop It!
Walk towards me slowlyl
Stop.
Turn around.
Lace your flngers
behlnd your head.
Walk backwards to me.
Stop.
Get on your knees.
How'd you llke my barrel photo, huh?
Took It In the backyard
by the barbecue grlll.
You know, where we used
to cook out wlth the famlly.
Gomey thought the dlrt
mlght not match. But me?
I bet your greedy ass
would be so worked up...
...about the prospect
of loslng your cash...
...that you wouldn't catch It.
Looks llke l was rlght.
Yo, I remember thls place.
It's the very flrst place
we cooked, llke, ever.
It Is, Isn't It?
Hey, what say you save us
the busywork, Walt...
...and polnt out the spot
where you burled your money?
No?
No matter.
I'll get a search team out here.
We'll flnd It.
Agent Gomez, should we fllp a coln
for the honours?
No way, man. It's all yours.
Walter Whlte...
...you have the rlght to remaln sllent.
Anythlng you say can
and wlll be used agalnst you...
...In a court of law.
You have the rlght
to speak to an attorney...
...and have an attorney present
durlng questlonlng.
If you cannot afford an attorney...
...one wlll be provlded for you
at the government's expense.
Do you understand these rlghts
as l have Just reclted them to you?
Coward.
-Get-- Get over here!
-Brlng Itl
-Get In the truck, wlll you?
-Brlng It, bltchl
-Put hlm In the car!
-Come on!
Get In the car! Hurry up!
Get In the car, kld. Come on.
Gonna take hlm down
for booklng, okay?
You should stay here
tlll I come back wlth a search team.
-You got It.
-l'd take the kld wlth me...
...but they'd probably
klll each other on the way.
-Congratulatlons, buddy.
-Hey.
I'll call the trlbal pollce,
let them know we're here.
Hank, why Is there what looks llke
bralns In our garbage can?
Hey, baby. I got hlm.
Dead to rlghts.
-You got Walt?
-Yeah.
I got hlm In handcuffs as we speak.
Want me to wave to hlm for you?
Well, he's not--
He's not feellng too frlendly.
Oh, my God.
You dld It.
Thank God.
Thlngs are gonna be a llttle rough
for the next couple weeks...
...but they'll get better.
Baby, you okay?
I'm much better now.
I gotta go.
It may be a whlle before I get home.
I love you.
Who the hell Is thls?
Trlbal pollce?
Pollcel Drop your weapons!
Jack, don't do It!
Jackl
Drop your weapons!
You heard the man! Put them down!
How do we know you're cops?
Damn stralghtl Let's see some badgesl
Jackl
Jack, don't do It! Jackl
No, Jack, It's offl Jackl
We'll glve ourselves up,
you show us some badgesl
Slmple as that!
How about It?
Jackl
Jack, It's offl Forget Itl