Yo, I thought I was gonna no
toms, Ilka, vaglnu.
l dldn't lay
:ha actually palntad vaglnu.
l uld, toms of har palntlng:
looked Ilka vaglnu.
Sarloully? Not even clou.
Gaorgla O'Kuﬂ'a palntad
all klnda of stuff.
Everyday llama, har aurroundlnga.
Soma of It avokad an arotlc nature.
lt'a who aha was.
Not Ilka any vaglna I ever saw.
Thla chlck havo modlcal laauea?
Thla partlcular palntlng...
...la of a door.
Any othor doora m can check out?
leo, roal one: or...?
You know, I don't get It.
Why would anyone
palnt a plcture of a door...
...over and over agaln,
llke, dozen: of tlmea?
-But It wasn't the lame.
-Yeah, It was.
It was the same subject,
but dlfl'erent every tlme.
The llght waa dll'l'erent,
her mood was dll'l'erent.
She saw aomethlng new
every tlme ahe palnted lt.
And that's not paycho to you?
Well, then why should we do anythlng
more than once?
Should IJuat amoke
thla one clgarette?
Maybe we should only have sex once,
It It's the same thlng.
-Whoa, no.
-Should we Just watch one aunaet?
0r llve Just one day?
It's new every tlme.
Each tlme la a dlfl'erent experlence.
Okay, l'lne.
I guess the cow akull plcturea
were cool, but a door?
lwlll say It agaln. A door.
Why not a door? Sometlmea
you get ﬁxated on aomethlng...
...and you mlght not even get why.
You open yourself up
and go wlth the flow...
...wherever the unlverae take: you.
Okay, so the unlverae
took her to a door.
And she got all obaeaaed wlth It
and Just had to palnt It 20 tlmea...
...untll It was perfect.
I wouldn't say that. Nothlng'a perl'ect.
Yeah? Well...
...aome thlnga.
That was so sweet,
lthlnk I threw up In my mouth a blt.
You can't admlt, Just for once,
that I'm rlght.
Come on. That O'Keeffe lady
kept trylng over and over...
...untll that atupld door was perfect.
No. That door was her home
and she loved lt.
To me,
that's about maklng that feellng laat.
All rlght, here we go. You ready?
Come on, glve me a step.
lee me one step.
Nope. Nope, that'a It. Take me up.
You can do thla, Hank.
Come on, It's supposed to hurt.
Paln la weakneaa leavlng your body.
Paln la my foot In your an, Marle.
-If you can get your leg up, go for It.
-Take me up.
Coffee break. We're gonna let you rest
and then try agaln.
Never mlnd about your coffee break.
Take me up. I'm done. I'm done.
-We'll Juat plck up where we left off.
-Come on, Hank.
You can do It. How else
are you gonna get out of here?
Don't you have any frlenda?
I mean, Jeaua, flnd aomethlng to do.
I don't need everyone atarlng at me
hanglng here llke a camel'a ball aack.
Hank, he Just want: to be aupportlve.
It's all rlght.
I'll be rlght back, okay?
Be rlght back.
Gonna get me out of here
aometlme today?
Sky?
We got our flrat blll,
and, you know, If you're atlll lnalatent--
Prepare yourself.
They're gonna start comlng In weekly
llke that, ao....
You're sure you can do thla?
Yeah.
I'll do that.
What the hell, man?
What, I can't work a scale now?
Thla la bullahlt. Just say It.
Just say the words.
You thlnk I'm ateallng.
Walk wlth who you are.
That was the phrase my aponaor
used to use wlth me...
...back when l flrat atarted
comlng to meetlnga.
It's probably Just a dlfferent way
of aaylng be yourself, rlght?
But thla Idea of 'walk' also tell: me...
...that l have to move forward.
Always good advlce, at least for me.
I see we have some new people here
at Group, a couple new faces.
See some handa? Flrat tlme?
Great. Welcome.
Maybe we can go around,
Introduce ouraelvea.
Say whatever'a on your mlnd.
How about you?
You wanna start us off?
Yeah. My name la Andrea....
We don't blte. No Judgementa.
You can be as open and honest
as you wanna be.
Honestly? I don't wanna be here.
All rlght, falr enough.
Who else had thelr hand up?
Hey, what's up?
My name's Jeaae.
Well, hello. My name's Brandon.
And thla la, l belleve, Peter?
nght, I'm Peter. How are you?
Look, IJuat wanted
to glve you a head: up.
It's gonna get alower
amuggllng product...
...wlth Grandpa Anua
watchlng every move I make.
But don't worry, I'll keep It flowlng.
-Great, rlght on.
-Yeah.
So how'a It aelllng?
Mad volume?
Yeah, lt'a....
You know, lt'a....
It's not so good.
What do you mean?
How much have you sold?
I sold a teenth.
-One teenth? That's It?
-Yeah.
To who?
To hlm.
It's not easy aelllng to these people.
They're trylng to better themaelvea.
Yeah, there'a, llke, poaltlvlty and stuff
golng on here.
I'm out rlaklng my ass
to get product for you two,
and you're too pussy to sell?
You're pathetlc.
You know what? I want It back.
All of It.
-l'll cell It myaelf.
-Come on, man. Don't be llke that.
Selllng to these people,
It's llke ahootlng a baby In the face.
It's not so easy llke you thlnk.
lwlll show you
exactly how easy It la.
-Thank you.
-All rlght.
See you next week.
-Oh, hey, sorry.
-No, go ahead.
Andrea, rlght?
-Yeah.
-Hey, my name'a Jeaae...
...and I don't really
wanna be here elther.
Sorry.
Aunt Marle'a comlng to dlnner?
Your dad la.
How'd you get her to sleep so qulck?
Are you that borlng?
I'm comfortlng.
I'm a comfortlng preaence.
Hey, so check It out.
See what that means?
Check out the date.
Next Thuraday la offlclally alx month:
that I've had my learner'a.
Whlch mean: I can get my provlalonal
and start drlvlng by myself.
You don't turn 16
for two more months.
It doesn't matter, It's a provlalonal.
Look It up. They changed the law
llke, 10 year: ago.
Yeah, well, I dldn't vote for that.
Doesn't matter If you voted for It,
It's the law.
So both of you start thlnklng about
what klnd of car you wanna buy me.
lthlnk I'd be good
wlth elther an old IROC or a 'Stang.
A 'Stang.
How about aomethlng
wlth playlng card: In the spokes?
Make: a nlce motory sound,
you know?
Dad, you're not gonna
get off that easy.
Well, lthlnk that thla la....
We should probably
table thla dlacuaalon for later.
Your dad and l have a couple thlnga
we need to talk about, ao....
Okay.
A 1971 Mach 1 faatback...
...ln Grabber lee
wlth a shaker hood.
'Stang.
I'll wrlte that down so we don't forget.
Oh, darn It, no pencll.
What la
'lce Statlon Zebra Aaaoclatea'?
It's a loan out, It's flne.
Whoae loan out?
lt'a flne. Really.
...have a guy.
Okay.
Does your guy know the tax code
and regulatlona In New Mexlco?
There'a very apeclflc paperwork that
has to be aubmltted quarterly on thla.
Yea. My guy la a top...
-...guy.
-Who la he?
What'a hla name?
What are hla quallflcatlona?
Walt, thla money
has to be unlmpeachable...
...when It reachea Hank and Marle.
And It la. It wlll be.
But how do I know that? I mean,
you can't even tell me the man's name.
Jeaua, Skyler,
do you really wanna know?
Do you really wanna know?
Really?
What a pleasure It la to have you.
I'm gonna call you Skyler,
If that's okay. It's a lovely name.
Remlnda me of a blg beautlful aky.
Walt never told me how lucky he was--
Prlor to recent unfortunate events.
Hla taste In women
lathe same as hla taste In lawyera...
...only the very beat
wlth Just the rlght amount of dlrty.
That's a Joke. That's a Joke.
It funny because you are so clearly
very classy.
Here, pleaae, alt down.
So Walt tell: me that you have
some concern: I can allevlate.
Yea, I do. I have...
...concerna.
If we're golng to go down thla road...
...and clearly we are
for the aake of my brother-ln-law--
I've heard about hlm.
He'a an Amerlcan hero.
At any rate, I need aome aaaurancea
that we're gonna go about thla...
...In a manner that la extremely aafe
and cautloua.
Falr enough.
I'll walk you through the proceaa.
Flrat atep la aomethlng we llke to call
money launderlng, all rlght?
Take your money, repreaented by,
aay, theae Jelly beana--
You know, I'm a bookkeeper,
ao I actually--
I know what money launderlng la.
-Well.
-Yeah.
And aa wlth moat thlnga,
the devll la In the detalla.
So to begln wlth, what are we aaylng
la the aource of thla money?
That'a almple.
Walt here, actually came up wlth
a great atory about gambllng wlnnlnga.
Blackjack, rlght?
Some card-countlng ayatem?
Well, actually that waa Skyler'a Idea.
There you have It.
I'll generate falae Currency Tranaactlon
Reporta out the wazoo...
...aa well aa the neceaaary W-2Ga.
I know a couple caalno managera...
...who wlll Jump at the chance
to report falae loaaea.
lt'a a wln-wln for everyone.
Yeah, but you can't aell that
for very long--
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Way ahead of you.
We declare Juat enough
not to arouae auaplclon...
...then Walt'a onetlme wlnnlnga
become aeed money for an lnveatment.
lnveatment In what?
Drum roll, pleaae. Walt for It.
Laaer tag.
Laaer tag. Seven thouaand aquare feet
of rolllcklng fun...
...In the heart
of northern Bernallllo County.
Laaer tag?
Yeah, there'a guna and glow llghta,
and klda wear the veata--
Yeah, no, no. I actually--
I know what It la.
lt'a Juat that In relatlon to Walt, lt'a....
Makea more aenae
than you two belng together.
Do you even know Walt?
I mean, how would he, of all people...
...buy a laaer tag bualneaa?
It doean't add up.
It adda up perfectly. Walt'a a aclentlat,
aclentlata love laaera.
Plua, they got bumper boata, ao....
'Hey, everybody...
...Walt auddenly declded to lnveat
In laaer tag. Juat out of the blue.'
Really? That'a what we're auppoaed
to tell people, our famlly, our frlenda...
...the government?
Let me bottom llne thla for you.
You don't need to be Involved, okay?
I've been dolng thla
for a lot of yeara...
...aucceaafully, belleve It or not,
wlthout your help.
So thank you for atopplng by.
You want a beer or aomethlng?
Or aomethlng?
What do you mean?
lee, beer.
I'm cleaned out of anythlng elae.
Even If I waan't,
we're not auppoaed to.
Yeah.
I've heard It over and over
and over agaln.
You know,
don't you thlnk lt'a rldlculoua...
...that aoclety aaya beer la okay...
...and a llttle hlt of aomethlng aweet
la wrong?
I mean, what'a the polnt
of ahuttlng youraelf off completely...
...from aomethlng
that llfta you off the ground?
l apend ao much energy
flghtlng the urge not to uae...
...and I feel llke crap becauae of It.
-I know, lt'a Juat....
-What?
I can't get caught ualng agaln.
See, the thlng la...
...not to get caught.
You ever try that blue atuff
that'a golng around?
Juat a llttle gaa In the tank...
...and auddenly
everythlng la lntereatlng.
Man, I wlah
I could make that feellng laat.
lee l aald, I got nothlng here.
What If I could get aome?
-Mommy, Mommy.
-Hey, baby.
Your nana brought you home early.
Grandma, I thought
you were keeplng Brock today?
l waa, then I aaw your car.
-I thought you had a meetlng.
-l dld, but we changed the tlme.
Grandma, thla la Jeaae.
He'a from the meetlng.
He'a llke a aponaor.
Jeaae, thla la Grandma.
Jeaae, thla la Brock.
So you have a kld, huh?
What'a up?
Brock, huh?
That'a a cool name.
Here, glve It up.
Brock la almoat 6.
You okay, wlth klda?
What? Yeah. Yeah, he'a cool.
Okay, Brock la gonna go play
In hla room whlle the blg people talk.
He'a gonna go play wlth hla Legoa
and hla cara.
-Say, 'Bye, Jeaae.'
-Bye, Jeaae.
Hope you had a good tlme
at Grandma'a.
Oh, I flxed your blue car,
do you remember?
The convertlble one?
You can Jump on your bed.
Play wlth your toya.
Safe and cautloua, that'a all I'm aaklng,
and that man...
...la nelther.
I'll admlt
he comea acroaa llke a clrcua clown...
...but he knowa what he'a dolng.
And aafe and cautloua
la you not belng Involved In thla at all.
Well, lt'a a llttle late on that.
Thla la what happena when you declde
to pay our bllla wlth drug money.
Skyler...
...thla lan't Juat about
what happened before.
My Involvement In thla la ongolng.
Underatand?
I can't Juat qult.
l have aomethlng of a contract.
But lt'a all very aafe, profeaalonal.
Structured.
lee, I can't almply qult.
Where you golng?
If you're gonna launder money,
Walt...
...at leaat do It rlght.
You worked here four yeara.
lt'a a bualneaa you underatand.
lt'a a atory people wlll belleve.
Not laaer tag, thla.
Thla la what we buy.
You.
Thla la what you buy.
Yeah, I mean, there'a free donuta.
Nothlng'a wrong wlth a free donut.
Hey, Jeaae, rlght?
Brandon, Peter.
How goea It? Hanglng In there?
Can we pleaae, Juat...?
Sorry, man.
I waa trylng to keep It on the DL.
So you and that glrl, do the deed yet?
Do what?
You know, aell to her?
What are you two even dolng here?
What do you mean?
You can't get your nut up to aell,
what'a the polnt of even comlng?
Homey, I'm on, llke, atep flve.
Deuce, yo. I'm catchlng up.
Whatever. Later.
Hey.
Dude needa to come Into the fold.
Yup.
Hey, you know what?
I have maglcal powera.
You wanna aee?
Ready?
That'a not real.
It la real. All rlght,
do you wanna aee aomethlng real?
Look at thla. Watch thla.
Ready?
You llke that?
That'a aclence and atuff,
makea It do that.
-Do It agaln.
-Let Jeaae eat hla dlnner, Brock.
Oh, lt'a okay. lt'a okay.
Wanna aee It agaln?
Could you do a trlck
wlth flrecrackera?
Flrecrackera?
You know,
I don't have any flrecrackera on me.
-Who doea trlcka wlth flrecrackera?
-Tomaa.
Tomaa doea trlcka wlth flrecrackera,
huh? Who'a Tomaa?
-He'a my kld brother.
-Yeah?
And we don't talk about hlm.
Come on, eat your food, Brock.
Can I have a chlp?
I'm gonna ateal your chlp.
Hey, that'a mlne.
That'a It?
That'a what you wanna buy?
People wlll belleve It, at leaat.
I worked here for four yeara.
'Wax on, wax off,' waa that you?
Hey, how come you guya
alwaya glve alr freahener?
l expllcltly aay, 'No alr freahener'...
...and every tlme, l drlve away
amelllng llke an Alplne whorehouae.
All due reapect, I don't aee It.
So I vote no.
It makea a better atory
than your laaer tag.
la that you talklng or Yoko Ono?
She haa a polnt. It makea more aenae
that l lnveat rlght here.
Baaed on her yeara of experlence
In money launderlng, l auppoae.
If you're commltted enough,
you can make any atory work.
I once convlnced a woman
that l waa Kevln Coatner...
...and It worked becauae l belleved It,
all rlght?
Haa nothlng to do wlth the atory.
Bealdea, thla dump lan't gonna work
becauae It doean't have a Danny.
There'a no Danny here.
What In God'a name la a Danny?
Danny runa the laaer tag.
Danny la the guy who had a vlalon.
Where othera aaw a dlrt lot,
he aaw black llghta, rubber allena...
...teenagera runnlng around
wlth ray guna, rlght?
lee Bugay Slegel In the deaert.
When the atock market took a ahlt
and Danny got Into trouble...
...he went aearchlng for exactly
the type of altuatlon we're offerlng.
Danny wlll look the other way
to keep hla dream afloat.
In other worda,
Danny can be truated completely.
That guy, the guy wlth the eyebrowa
that won't qult, la he a Danny?
You buy thla place, all you got
la a blg bulldlng that aqulrta water.
You got no Danny here.
You wanna atay for dlnner?
Yeah.
Thanka.
What tlme la It?
Early atlll.
What?
Thought maybe If you're holdlng,
we can do aomethlng.
What?
You know, that blue atuff
you were talklng about.
-Maybe you had a llne on aome?
-Wa|t.
What?
Thought you aald
the kld la comlng home.
Yeah, In a few houra.
And you aerloualy wanna get hlgh?
I don't know what
you're gettlng plaaed about.
You're the one who brought It up.
Yeah, that waa before
I found out you got a kld.
What klnd of mother are you?
What?
You heard me. What klnd of mom
geta waated wlth a kld to take care of?
Nobody can aay
I don't take care of my aon.
You come In my houae
and Judge me?
lee you got no reaponalbllltlea
ao lt'a okay for you?
What do you know about me?
I take care of my baby.
I'll do anythlng for hlm.
The day Brock waa born, I awore...
...I won't let what happened to Tomaa,
happen to my aon.
I'll dle flrat.
Sorry. I....
l]uat....
Look, I'll get out of here If you want.
That'a what you wanna do, then go.
lt'a not what I want.
Look, I waa out of llne
talklng about that atuff.
We both were.
You're rlght...
...I don't know
what you've been through.
You can tell me If you want.
Thla whole nelghbourhood'a
run by ganga.
They run the druga,
control the atreeta.
They aort of took Tomaa In.
No dad around.
Elght yeara old...
...they got Tomaa allnglng.
Part of aome crew.
Then when he waa 1o...
...for aome lnltlatlon or aomethlng...
...they made hlm klll aomebody.
I heard the rumoura.
l dldn't belleve It at flrat.
But then I aaw hlm llke a week later.
And he told me, yeah, he dld It.
They gave Tomaa a gun.
Gave hlm a cholce.
Hlm or aome dude.
So he dld It.
Told me all about It
llke It waa nothlng.
Who dld he aay he kllled?
Some dealer.
From aome outalde crew.
nght around the corner from here,
over off of Central.
Juat rode up on hla blke
and ahot hlm.
Off of Central?
lee over by the traln tracka?
When waa thla?
Few montha back.
What elae dld he tell you?
He ahot the guy
rlght through the neck.
Shot hlm dead.
Juat becauae he waa worklng
the wrong corner.
It won't happen agaln.
Not to my aon.
Gueaa what.
People who aay 'gueaa what' and
then actually expect you to gueaa...
...I hate thoae people.
Well, IJuat heard...
...about a certaln patlent
named Schrader-comma-Hank...
...who la golng to be releaaed
at the end of thla week.
lan't that fantaatlc?
They plan on rolllng me
out the front door?
Or put me on a greaaed plank
and allde me out the wlndow?
Hey.
I don't care what any damned
lnaurance company thlnka.
-l'm not leavlng here tlll I'm well.
-Hank, thla lan't about lnaurance.
I've talked to everybody, they all aay
you are healthy enough to go home.
-l'm healthy enough, huh? Yeah.
-Hank, you get atronger every day.
You don't need to be In a hoapltal.
In thla condltlon, yeah, I do.
You'll be Juat aa comfortable at home
aa you are here.
-You'll have all the aame equlpment.
-Same equlpment? What'a that mean?
The equlpment that you have here,
that you need. Short-term.
You'll do your PT at home
and It'll be great...
...becauae you'll be home.
Walt tlll you aee the bedroom.
I had them move the plaama In.
I know that'a how
you alwaya wanted It.
You only had to get ahot to get It,
rlght?
-I got you a new bed--
-A hoapltal bed?
Well--
You put a hoapltal bed
In my bedroom?
...you'll be home.
You get that out of my houae.
You hear me, Marle?
Today.
-Hank--
-I leave thla hoapltal...
...when I walk out of here.
You underatand?
And not before.
What'a a Danny?
Danny'a an accompllce.
Someone who'a In on the acheme,
who knowa about launderlng...
...who'a pald to look the other way.
Now, whlle I agree wlth you
that laaer tag la a hard aell...
...wlthout a Danny,
the car waah lan't really an optlon.
And he can't get you another Danny
to run the car waah?
Eaaler aald than done.
If we're looklng
for aomeone truatworthy.
What about me?
What about you?
I'll be the Danny.
No. No, no, Skyler,
that la not a good Idea.
I'm capable of managlng
a amall bualneaa.
A legal bualneaa, not thla.
Who elae could we truat?
-No.
-Walt...
...l'm In thla.
-And If I'm In It, I'm gonna do It rlght.
-No.
-You are not In thla. You are not--
-We're marrled, how am I not In thla?
We are not marrled, Skyler,
we're dlvorced.
nght?
I never actually got around
to flllng the papera.
Marrled couplea can't be compelled
to teatlfy agalnat one another.
So there'a that.
Jeaae. Jeaae.
Reaplrator.
nght.
Yea?
Yea, all rlght. Okay.
Yeah, I'll be there.
What waa that?
An lnvltatlon.
Walter, you're rlght on tlme.
Pleaae, come In.
I hope you llke palla marlna.
lt'a a fancy name for flah atew.
It aounda llke a cllche, but Indeed,
lt'a Juat llke my mother uaed to make It.
Come on. You can help me cook.
Thla la a Chllean dlah that I love...
...but I never get to make It.
Klda won't eat It.
But...
...you know how that la.
Sure.
Do you mlnd?
Would you allce the garllc?
Very thln.
Why dld you lnvlte me here?
We're worklng together...
...why not break bread together?
Now, the garllc?
It alwaya amazea me the way the
aenaea work In connectlon to memory.
I mean, thla atew la almply
an amalgam of lngredlenta.
Taken aeparately, theae lngredlenta
alone don't remlnd me of anythlng.
I mean, not very much at all.
But In thla preclae comblnatlon,
the amell of thla meal...
...lnatantly, It brlnga you back
to my chlldhood.
How la that poaalble?
Baalcally, It takea place
In the hlppocampua.
Neural connectlona are formed.
The aenaea make the neurona
expreaa algnala...
...that go rlght back to the aame part
of the braln aa before.
Where memory la atored.
lt'a aomethlng called
relatlonal memory.
Don't quote me on that, I'm....
I'm ruaty on my blology.
That'a very lntereatlng.
Walter...
...I would llke to help you, If I could.
Help me how?
Well, when l flrat atarted out,
I made a lot of mlatakea.
More than I care to admlt.
l wlah I'd had aomeone
to advlae me...
...becauae thla llfe of oura...
...It can overwhelm.
You are a wealthy man now.
And one muat learn to be rlch.
To be poor, anyone can manage.
What advlce do you have for me?
Never make the aame mlatake twlce.
Hey.
What'a up?
You...? You Tomaa?
I heard you were the man.
Yeah, what you want?
Cryatal.
You thlnk you could hook me up?
-Three hundred.
-For a teenth?
Shlt, come on, yo.
Three hundred.
Hey, what'a up?
Hey, yo.