[J'J'J']
JESSE:
There.
That's tham.
Your play, Waltor.
You're on your own.
DECLAN:
Look: Ilka you're about 1000 gallon:
llght hora, Mlka.
Whero': the Julco?
The mothylamlno Isn't comlng.
Why I: that?
And who the hell are you?
I'm the man who's kuplng It.
What the hell': thll?
We had an agreement, rlght?
We got our deal.
So where's the tank, Mlke?
Mlke doesn't know where It la.
Only I do.
And you're deallng wlth me now,
not hlm.
Why don't you Just cut
to what It la you want
or what you thlnk
la gonna happen here, all rlght?
Because we're gonna get
what we came for.
That 1000 gallon: of methylamlne
la worth more In my hand:
than It la In your: or anyone elae'a,
for that matter.
But I need dlatrlbutlon.
Dlatrlbutlon.
That'a rlght.
So It you agree
to glve up your cook
and sell my product lnatead,
I'll glve you 35 percent of the take.
Thlrty-l'lve percent? Wow.
Wow, are you klddlng me?
Thlrty-l'lve--
Mlke, please tell me thla la a Joke.
Know how far we had to atlck our
neck: out to get our hand:
on thla caah?
Why the hell would we want you? You
know we have our own operatlon, rlght?
I know all about your operatlon.
See, my partner: here tell me
that you produce a meth
that's 70 percent pure,
If you're lucky.
What I produce la 99.1 percent pure.
So?
So lt'a grade school T-ball
versus the New York Yankees.
Youra la Just some tepld,
oft-brand, generlc cola.
What I'm maklng la Claaalc Coke.
All rlght. Okay.
So, uh, ahem, If we Juat waate you
rlght here rlght now
and leave you In the desert
then there la no more Coke
on the market, rlght?
See how that works? There's only us.
Do you really wanna llve
In a world wlthout Coca-Cola?
[CHUCKLES]
My partner tell: me that your crew
awltched to a P2P cook
because of our success.
You dye your meth wlth l'ood colourlng
to make It look llke mlne.
You already ape my product
at every turn.
But now,
you have the opportunlty
to cell It youraell'.
DECLAN:
I need you to llaten to me.
We're not gonna glve up thla deal
to be your errand boys,
do you understand?
For what?
To watch a bunch ol'Junklea
get a better hlgh?
A better hlgh
meana customers pay more.
A hlgher purlty mean: a greater yleld.
That'a 130 mllllon dollar: of prol'lt
that lan't belng plaaed away
by some aubatandard cook.
Now you llaten to me.
You've got the greatest meth cook
In A-- No, the two
greateat meth cooka ln Amerlca
rlght here, and wlth our akllla,
you'll earn more
from that 35 percent
than you ever would on your own.
DECLAN:
Yeah. So you lay.
Juat wonderlng why we're so lucky.
Why cut us In?
Mlke la retlrlng from our crew
ao hla share of the partnerahlp
la avallable,
It you can handle hla end,
dlatrlbutlon,
and It you glve hlm 5 mllllon dollar:
of the 15 mllllon
that you brought today.
Juat thlnk of It as a l'lnder'a fee
for brlnglng us together.
We have 40 pound: of product
ready to ahlp, ready to go.
Are you ready?
[CHUCKLES]
Who the hell are you?
You know.
You all know exactly who I am.
Say my name.
Do what? I don't have a damn clue
who the hell you are.
Yeah, you do. I'm the cook.
I'm the man who kllled Gua Frlng.
Bullahlt. Cartel got Frlng.
Are you sure?
That'a rlght.
Now, lay my name.
You're Helaenberg.
You're goddamn rlght.
[J'J'J']
I gotta hand It to you, Walter.
Hey.
l appreclate the klnd worda
but I'm out too, remember?
I know. We'll talk.
Maybe we should talk about how
and when I'm gonna get
my 5 mllllon dollara.
And we wlll do that.
Abaolutely.
It's Just, you know--
Look, Jeaae, Juat glve me
some tlme here, okay?
I'll need help gettlng thlnga
up and runnlng durlng thla tranaltlon.
You can at least do that for me, rlght?
Huh?
Come on. Don't worry.
We'll l'lgure It out.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Well, I guess that's lt.
Partlng thoughts,
of whlch l have two:
Flrat, as l aald,
I'll handle the legacy coata
out of my end
so you won't have to worry about
my guy: anymore. Second, the bug.
The DEA wlll do a sweep.
Can't say when, could be anytlme.
But you need to get It out of there,
sooner rather than later.
All rlght.
That's It?
No 'thanka tor the 5 mllllon dollara,‘ no
'aorry I'or chalnlng you to a radlator'?
Just get the bug, Walter.
JESSE:
So, hey.
I guess I'll see you around.
No. Don't thlnk ao.
When I'm out, I'm out.
Well, I'm out too, Mlke.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Kld, Just look out for yourself.
[KNOOKING ON DOOR]
[KNOOKING ON DOOR CONTINUES]
Are we good?
You tell me.
Okay, Jeaae. Back It up.
You're good. Keep It comlng.
Stralght back.
Slow It down.
All rlght. That's good.
Hey, Mra. Whlte.
[TRUCK DOOR OPENS]
'Vamonoa.‘
All rlght. Let's get thla thlng
hooked up.
Ahem. Walt.
What la thla?
Do you really wanna know?
Why are you hldlng It here?
Don't worry about It.
Who are you hldlng It I'rom?
l aald don't worry about It.
SKYLER:
From the pollce?
Or someone else?
Someone who would klll for It?
Why don't you go back In the ofﬁce?
Why don't you go back In the ofﬁce
and let us do thla?
We'll get It out of your halr.
[CLACKING]
[RATTLING]
Ho-ho. What'd you brlng me thla tlme?
They're bacon banana cooklea.
la there bacon In these? Oh, my God!
Juat blta. Juat llttle blta of bacon.
Juat enough to make
those auckera really pop.
Dan, thla la too much.
I'm not aharlng thoae.
Bad ofI'Ice ethuette?
I don't glve a crap.
They're mlne.
They're your: to do wlth as you please.
Good, because my husband's
not gettlng any elther.
How la Mlckey?
Don't get me started.
He wants to buy a boat.
I can't even get hlm
to start the lawnmower
and he want: to buy a boat.
I don't know. A boat mlght be nlce.
A llttle one, maybe.
Oh, please.
Where would you even take a boat?
All the way down to Elephant Butte?
Or Caballo. lt'a beautll'ul down there.
You can even leave It at the lake
It you don't want to haul It.
We're not buylng a boat,
I'll tell you that rlght now.
And the last one la 545.
569.
Dang It. I almost got them all that tlme.
Very good.
But actually, I've got an extra one
for you thla week. 603.
603. Where la that?
nght down there.
Ah.
All rlght. I'll let you get to It.
Thanka, Dot.
[DUKE ELLINGTON'S 'OVERTURE'
PLAYING]
Young Kaylee'a gonna need
a second aal'ety depoalt box
It you declde to leave
one more dollar to her.
How's the rest of It?
Oh, It's empty, as usual.
The I'amlllea are pretty rellable
wlth the plckupa.
Nobody complalnlng
about wantlng It all at once?
No, they get It.
Slow and steady wlna the race.
So I guess thla la It for a whlle?
Don't worry about the I'amlllea.
They'll keep gettlng thelr dellverlea.
HANK:
I know tlme: are tlght,
but It's for the klds
and your sponsorshlp
would sure be appreclated.
Yeah, we have a sllver level,
but the gold and platlnum levels
really get your name out there
on the banners and T-shlrts.
Sure. No, that's not a problem. You call
me dlrectly If thlng: change, you hear?
Ugh. Gomey, take a brlck
to my head lfl ever have
to make another Fun Run call.
I'm done.
What's up? Why you smlllng?
GOMEZ:
The Ehrmantraut warrant
just came In.
HANK:
Now we're talklng. How qulck
can you get your group together?
GOMEZ:
Two, three hours.
HANK:
Make It two. We're gonna nall
that con ofa bl--
[J'J'J']
[WATER SPLASHING]
[WHISTLES]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
MAN:
Pollcel Search warrantl
MIKE:
Comlng. Hold your horses.
[DOOR UNLOOKING]
Search warrant.
Pollcel Search warrantl
AGENT 1: Pollce. Search warrant.
AGENT 2: Pollce. Search warrant.
How's that reatralnlng order
worklng out for you?
It you want me to read that,
I'm gonna need my glasses.
[CLINKING]
MAN 1 [OVER TV]:
Too bad you had to make the trlp out
from headquarters, sergeant.
MAN 2:
From out of bed, you mean. When a cop
kllls hlmself, they want a full report.
MAN 1:
Just to say hello to who's In
charge of the Record Bureau.
MAN 3:
A slngle contact wound.
Powder burn on hls temple
and rlght hand.
Sulclde, I'll bet you.
MAN 2: Tell the boys they can have hlm.
MAN 3: Yes.
WOMAN [CRYING]:
When I found hlm, he was...
He was dead.
[noon OPENS]
Heyl Perfect tlmlng.
Just about to get started.
Uh-- You know, It you can get golng
on that settllng tank,
that would be a huge help.
We left that stuff In there too long
after the last cook.
Mr. Whlte--
I mean way too long.
Now we have a tremendous amount
of resldue.
You know what we need to Invest In
Is a power washer.
Mr. Whlte, can we Just take a second
and talk about all thls?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Um--
Look, you know what I thlnk
we need to talk about?
Doubllng down?
Mm-hm.
Cooklng 100 pounds a week,
not 50.
As In startlng a new lab,
a lab that you'll run.
A cook all of your own.
Why not? You deserve It.
You're every blt as good as me.
Well, what do you thlnk?
Mr. Whlte, lthlnk that
nothlng has changed for me.
IJust wanna get my money
and get out.
Jesse, thls...
What we do...
Is a very rare thlng.
You don't Just toss
somethlng llke that away.
And what, you wanna squander
that potentlal?
Your potentlal? Why?
To do what?
I don't know.
Well, thlnk.
To do what, Jesse?
l'll-- I'll llgure It out, all rlght?
Look at you.
What have you got In your Ille, huh?
Nothlng. Nobody.
Oh, walt. Yes.
Vldeo games and go-carts.
Mr. W--
Oh. And when you get tlred of that,
what then? Huh?
And how soon wlll you
start uslng agaln?
Look...
Look, I know how upset you are
about what happened to thls boy.
I am Just as upset as you are.
Are you? Really?
How can you say that to me? Jesusl
I mean, I'm the one
who's the father here.
What, do I have to curl up In a ball
In tears In front of you?
Do I have to lock mysell away In a room
and get hlgh to prove It to you?
What happened to that boy
Is a tragedy
and It tears me up lnsldel
But because It happened, what,
am I supposed to Just lle down
and dle wlth hlm? It's done!
It makes me slck that It happened,
Just llke everyone else
who has dled In our wake.
What Todd dld,
you and l have done thlngs
that are Just as bad.
Yeah.
All the people that we've kllled,
Gale and the rest.
It you belleve that there's a hell,
I don't know If you're Into that,
but we're already pretty much
golng there, rlght?
But I'm not gonna lle down
untll I get there.
What, Just because I don't wanna
cook meth anymore, I'm lylng down?
How many more people
are gonna dle because of us?
Now that we're In control,
no one else gets hurt.
You keep saylng that,
and It's bullshlt every tlmel
No.
Alwaysl You know what?
I'm done, okay?
You Just glve me my money,
and you and I, we're done.
Okay. Mm-hm.
Why?
Why do you want thls money?
Because It's mlne. It's my cut.
But Isn't It lllthy blood money?
I mean, you're so pure.
You have such emotlonal depth.
No, no, no. You shouldn't touch
that dlrty money.
I'll save you from that, Jesse.
Come on.
You want It.
You want It Just as much as I want It.
And It's not wrong to want It. Okay?
So stay and work wlth me
and you can make ten tl--
Twenty tlmes as much.
Whatever, man.
You don't wanna pay me,
I don't care.
Yes, you do.
It's on you, all rlght?
I'm done.
No, you're not.
You're not done. You're not leavlng.
Because It you leave, you get nothlngl
Do you understand me? Nothlngl
[noon CLOSES]
Jessel
Budget for the current ﬁscal year
for electronlc survelllance
Is 1.5 mIIIIon, on par wlth
ATF and the Marshal Servlce
but stIII just a fractlon of FBI totals.
We're Iobbylng Congress
for an addltlonal 1.41
but we're waltlng on actlon reports
to demonstrate
we're actually gettlng worthwhlle
results.
[FADING OUT]
Our undercover operatlons
reap the most successful
actlonable Intelllgence
If you refer to the chart
In Appendlx 4.
If ASAC Schrader can tell us about
the survelllance man-hours...
Hank?
Hankl
I thlnk we're golng to wrap thls up.
If ASAC Schrader can stay behlnd
whlle everyone else clears out.
Thank you, everybody.
You know no one wants
to see you succeed at thls
more than me, rlght?
Yes, slr.
I know how good you are.
I wouldn't have stuck my neck out
to get you here I“ dldn't.
But you're not knocklng down
doors anymore, bubba.
You're In charge ofa dlstrlct offlce,
and that comes wlth responslbllltles.
Imean, Hank, basIc reports
aren't belng ﬂled In a tlmely manner.
I'll work on It. It'll get better.
Yeah, It wlll, because way too much
tlme and money
Is belng spent on the Frlng case,
a case whlch Is essentlally over.
All thls overtlme to survell
Mlchael Ehrmantraut?
That's just money that could
be better spent elsewhere.
I understand, but I'm not maklng
these cholces llghtly.
We've got Increased reports
of blue meth on the street,
Frlng's gang ls stlll operatlonal,
and Ehrmantraut Is Involved.
It's that slmple.
Ibelleve you. But so what?
It's one case out of dozens,
and you don't play favourltes
wlth It because It used to be yours.
I really thlnk--
Don't play favourltes.
You got a blgger job than that.
I mean, forget the ﬂnanclal cost.
I hear you're personally servlng
search warrants out In the fleld?
That was an error In Judgement.
Won't happen agaln.
You're damn rlght It won't.
I'm just gonna bottom-Ilne thls for you.
The survelllance budget for
Ehrmantraut Is now zero. We clear?
Sure. Thank you.
Clear.
Good.
We'll be In touch.
[KNOCKING]
Yeah?
Hey.
[SOFTLY] Hey.
So Ramey wanted
to catch up wlth you?
Talk sports and stuff, I guess?
Yeah, somethlng llke that.
No more followlng Ehrmantraut.
Not worth the llnanclal Investment.
Well, It's not llke
the guy's golng anywhere.
He's not even botherlng
to throw our talls anymore.
He's Just llvlng a borlng old-man llle
llke he has nothlng left to hlde.
And none of Frlng's crew ls talklng?
Not glvlng an Inch.
You sweeten the pot enough?
Zero Jall tlme and an all-expense-pald
trlp to Maul?
Heh. Not that, but close.
Nobody wants to blte.
Chrlstl
They're elther the most loyal crew In
hlstory or someone's paylng them off.
You stlll checklng bank records?
No one llvlng beyond thelr means.
Nlne perps, all belng represented
by one lawyer.
Not unusual In a case llke thls.
Yeah, thls guy, what's hls name?
Danlel Wachsberger?
He represents every one of these
douche bags except for Ehrmantraut.
Can we llnd out more
about the lawyer?
You want me to start
talllng a lawyer?
lee the shlt aln't deep enough
for you already.
Ramey sald we couldn't
follow Ehrmantraut.
He dldn't say anythlng
about anybody else.
Do It.
You're the boss.
[noon OPENS]
All rlght. Shall we get started?
Now, I know that most of thls,
or all of thls, ls gonna be new to you.
But dld you take chemlstry
In hlgh school?
Just baslc?
Okay. That's all rlght.
As we go, I'll be as detalled as posslble
wlthout belng overwhelmlng.
Yes, slr.
Look, Todd, I don't need you
to be Antolne Lavolsler.
Um... What I do need Is your full effort
and attentlon.
Llsten and apply yourself.
If you do that, then we Just mlght have
a llghtlng chance here, okay?
Okay.
Well, here we go.
J' Floatln' down the rlver
Wlth a saturated llver J'
J' I wlsh I could forglve her
But I do belleve she meant It I
I When she told me to forget It
And I bet she wlll regret It I
I When they ﬁnd me In the mornlng
Wet and drowned J'
I And the word gets 'round
Goln' down I
Slowly. Steady.
J' Comlng' up for aIr
It's pretty stuffy under there I
J' I'd IIke to say I dldn't care
But I forgot to leave a note I
I And It's so hard to stay aﬂoat J'
[TALKING INDISTINOTLY]
J' It's front page news
Goln' down, goln' down I
The alumlnlum helps
speed up the dellvery
of hydrogen chlorlde.
J' Ishould have taken tlme to thlnk
Besldes I got the plcture stralght J'
J' She must have had another date I
Gently pour It In. Don't splll It.
I Don't want no more
Goln' down I
I I'm goln' down I
[SWITCH CLICKS
THEN MACHINE HUMS]
J' I should have learned to swlm Instead
And now It's really got me stumped J'
J' I can't belleve why I jumped
I'd IIke to get my tummy pumped J'
J' I can't belleve they drlnk thls stuff
In town I
[TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
J' Goln' down I
J' Goln' down
I'm goln' down I
J' I wlsh I looked before I leaped
I dldn't know It was so deep I
J' Been down so farI don't get wet
Haven't touched the bottom yet I
J' Thls rlver scene Is gettln' old
I'm hungry, sleepy, wet and cold I
J' She told me to forget It nIce
I should have taken her advlce J'
J' I only want to go on home I
MAN [OVER TV]:
You're gonna IIke the llttle Schtlcky,
but you're gonna love the blg Schtlcky.
For blgger messes IIke dust bunnles...
I My pappy taught me how to ﬂoat
But I can't swlm a slngle note I
J' He threw me In to teach me how
I stayed there ﬂoatln' IIke a mama cow J'
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
I If know thls has to be a dream
I“ could ﬁnd my way to shore J'
J' I'd never
Never do thls anymore I
[AIR HISSING]
I I'm goln' down just one more tlme.
Goln' down I
J' Goln' down
I'm goln' down I
J' Goln' down J'J'
the CO2 freezes the llquld
crystalllslng It
whlch glves us our llnlshed
methamphetamlne.
Whew.
Now all that's left
Is to break It up, welgh It,
and we're done.
Wow, thls ls, um...
Thls ls compllcated. It's gonna take me
a few more tlmes to get a grasp on It.
Oh, yeah. It'll take a few more tlmes.
I do all rlght?
You dld flne, Todd.
You applled yourself.
That's as much as I can ask.
Now all that's left,
I guess, Is to talk money.
We can talk money
once I get thls rlght.
[GLOVE SNAPS]
[ZIPPER OPENS]
Mornlng. Guess what I have.
Cake pops.
They're balls of cake on a stlck.
Very nlce. Thank you, Dan.
See? I put llttle faces on them.
[KEYS JINGLING]
Hey.
[MICROWAVE WHIRRING]
[MICROWAVE BEEPING]
All rlght.
I'm worklng wlth a new guy now.
And I thlnk that It...
lthlnk It could posslbly work out
I'm trylng, Hank. I really am.
I'm trylng, but there's... There's...
I mean,
It's llke I don't even exlst to her.
Well, yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I know she's struggllng.
I know, but I Just don't know what to do.
I mean, what can I do?
I mean, we-- Both of us,
we Just have screwed up so much.
I'm Just...
I'm sorry. I don't-- Um--
Do you have any coffee?
Maybe I can--
Coffee? You bet. Yeah, you bet.
What, you take cream, rlght? Yeah.
Yeah.
[IMITATES GUNSHOT]
[noon OPENS]
All rlght. Here you go, buddy.
Oh, thank you, Hank.
Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry to waste your tlme
wlth all thls.
No.
It's, you know-- But It's-- You know.
Yeah.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Hey, could you excuse me?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure, sure.
Tell me somethlng good.
You tell me.
Sweated the guy for 14 hours.
That should be some klnd of record.
Qult your bragglng.
What'd you get?
He's gonna do It. He's gonna fllp.
He's wllllng to glve us
Ehrmantraut?
[CHUCKLES]
HANK:
What are you wastlng your tlme for?
Throw a net around that son of a bltch.
GOMEZ:
All rlght.
[SWING CREAKING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
DAN: Mlke, hey, It's me.
Can you talk?
I can.
Great. Look, there's a small
sltuatlon wlth the money.
I don't wanna do thls on the phone.
Are you avallable?
I can come by In a few hours.
That's not good for me.
Where are you now?
I'm at the park
wlth my granddaughter.
Where exactly?
Palomlta.
Oh, you know what? I'm not far.
I'll come to you. You just hang tlght.
[snows]
Yeah?
WALT: Mlke, they're comlng for you.
nght now. They're comlng.
Slow down, Walter. Who?
The DEA. The DEA--
Somebody ﬂlpped.
They have some klnd of
bank survelllance.
And somethlng about some lawyer.
Someone Is talklng, Mlke,
and they're comlng for you rlght now--
[J'J'J']
SAUL:
How could Mlke use
that clown of a lawyer?
Dan Wachsberger. Heh.
He would've had better luck wlth
the law flrm of Moe, Larry and Shemp.
Always consult wlth me
before uslng outslde counsel.
All rlght, Saul, enough, please.
Instead of]ust slttlng around here,
what can we do?
Besldes pray that he gets away,
I'm open to Ideas.
Because If the DEA
catches up wlth hlm,
and he fllps, It's good nlght,
John-boy.
No. No way Mlke would ever fllp, okay?
No way.
Yeah, yeah.
Never say never.
Thls Is the second tlme the DEA
has conflscated hls bankroll.
Ha-ha. You know?
Jesus, fool me once, rlght?
Look, he won't fllp.
But hls nlne guys wlll.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Hey. Whoa, whoa. It's hlm.
Mlke, I got you on speaker phone
wlth the braln trust.
MIKE: The what?
The... Walt and Jesse are here.
I don't want Walt and Jesse, Saul.
I want you. I need your help.
What do you need?
MIKE: I got a go-bag at the alrport.
Passports, money,
but there are eyes everywhere.
I can't get close.
I need you to plck up that bag
and get It to me as soon as posslble.
Do you know how thlck
the crap storm ls out there?
Told you not to use that lawyer.
He's a hack!
Shut up, Saul, and get the bag.
Hey, Mlke, I can get It to you, all rlght?
Just tell me what to do.
No, kld. Not you.
I'm paylng Saul.
He can do the ]ob ]ust flne.
Yeah, you're paylng me,
and the DEA knows I represent you
so they're probably slttlng
on my car rlght now,
hoplng I do somethlng stupld.
Mlke, I can do It, okay?
It's not a problem.
No, Jesse.
Jesus, I'll do It.
Besldes, you're out, remember?
Mlke, tell me where to get thls bag.
[WATER SPLASHES]
[CAR APPROACHING]
MIKE:
Hello, Walter.
Before I hand thls over,
I need somethlng from you.
And what's that?
The names of your nlne men.
[SCOFFS]
Why? You're never gonna pay them off.
What's the polnt?
The polnt ls, Mlke, It affects me.
It affects Jesse too.
And we deserve to know.
The only thlng left to do now
Is leave town. You understand?
'Leave town.' Wow.
Yeah, l]ust can't up and leave
llke you, Mlke.
I've got a famlly,
I've got people who depend on me.
Yeah.
Goodbye, Walter.
You're welcome!
[SCOFFS]
I'm sorry, what?
I want those names, Mlke.
You owe me that much.
I don't owe you a damn thlng.
All of thls, falllng apart llke thls,
Is on you.
Wow.
Heh. Wow.
Oh, that's some klnd of loglc
rlght there, Mlke.
You screw up, get yourself
followed by the DEA,
and now suddenly,
thls Is all my fault?
Why don't you walk me through thls?
We had a good thlng,
you stupld son of a bltchl
We had Frlng. We had a lab.
We had everythlng we needed,
and It all ran llke clockwork.
Oh, my God.
You could've shut your mouth,
cooked, and made as much money
as you ever needed.
It was perfect.
But, no, you Just had to blow It up.
You and your prlde and your ego!
You Just had to be the man.
If you'd done your Job,
known your place,
we'd all be flne rlght now.
[snows]
[noon OPENS]
[noon CLOSES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[J'J'J']
l]ust...
l]ust reallsed that Lydla
has the names. I can get
them from her.
[PANTING]
I'm sorry, Mlke.
Thls... Thls whole thlng
could've been avolded.
Shut the fuck up...
and let me dle In peace.
[sorr THUD]
[SWING CREAKING
AND CHILDREN CHATTERING]
[J'J'J']