You can come on out.
It's an actual store.
l guns: I flgurad vacuum cleaner repalr
was a farm of art.
If you would step rlght here
on thla blue spot.
Leave your luggage
where It I: for the moment.
That good?
-Sure.
-What about thla?
I'll Photoahop that out.
0h, Nebraska. What's In Nebraska?
You. From now on.
It's gonna take me some tlme
to get your new altuatlon l'lxed.
Untll then,
you're gonna be ataylng here.
I got a place downatalra, out of alght.
It's not the thz-Carlton, but lt'a
comfortable enough for short-term.
How short-term?
Conalderlng you got your face up
on buses and blllboarda all over town...
...l'm thlnklng two days.
Maybe three.
Only thlng la...
...and I don't llke to do thla...
...but you'll have a bunk mate.
Oh, yeah? He'a atlll here?
For the moment.
He's a apeclal caae.
Gonna take some dolng.
How'a he holdlng up?
You be the Judge.
We wlll l'lnd Hank.
steve too.
They're out there,
and we're gonna l'lnd them.
You have my word.
Slr.
Call It In, get her out of here. Move.
I get to Ms door...
...and I could hear muslc lnslde.
lee squeaky volces.
Andl thought, you know, maybe...
I knocked on Ms door.
The musIc stopped,
and then he was rIght there.
When he saw the gun, he thought...
Hey, Kenny.
Does thls pussy cry
through the entlre thlng?
Just watch.
He kept sayIng that, you know,
"You don't have to do thls. "
HIs eyes were so bIg.
-They hIgh-fIved because It worked.
-Such a bltch. He won't qult.
Then, you know, we turn around...
...and there Is thls kId on a dIrt bIke...
...IookIng at us.
Drew Sharp.
That kId that went mIssIng
up In WhIte Horse.
It's hIm.
And then out of nowhere...
Todd, that OpIe,
dead-eyed pIece of mu...
...pulls out a gun and shoots the kId.
ThIs Is Todd AIquIst
we're taIkIng about?
He kIIIed Drew Sharp?
LIke It was nothIng.
Hey, Uncle Jack. Hold up.
We should keep hlm tor a whlle,
get a couple of cooks under our belt.
You serlously glvlng me
thls turn-the-other-cheek crap?
He ratted you out, personally.
We stlll got 600 gallons of methylamlne.
Meth? Who glves a shlt about meth?
We won the lottery here.
We've got all the money In the world.
You're taIkIng to me
about selllng crank?
I mean, thls ls mllllons, Uncle Jack.
No matter how much you got,
how do you turn your back on more?
You llttle...
...son of a bltch.
It's that Lydla woman.
You're sweet on her, you llttle bastard.
-Hey, Kenny, you belleve thls?
-Hey, It's all about thls rlght here, huh?
Come on.
You can do better.
That one's so uptlght, probably
got a wood chlpper tor a coochle.
stlck It In down there,
you're pulllng back a stump.
Oh, what the hell?
Heart wants what
the heart wants, rlght?
Let's go back and watch some more
of that crybaby rat, huh?
How thlck Is It?
Thls ls mlld steel?
No, thls would be cash.
What?
Nothlng.
Hey, you know what?
Make yourself usel'ul.
lee me a llst ol' hltters, mercenarles.
Yes, yes, I remember.
You've got 'concerns.'
Don't worry. We'll take the tlme
to vet them.
Make sure there are no
undercover cops on the team.
Flve should do It, provldlng they're
the rlght men for the Job.
I'm gonna hate myself for asklng,
but who are we hlttlng?
Jack Welker and hls men.
They murdered Hank.
They stole my lll'e's work.
I don't know any hlt men.
You know a guy who knows a guy.
Just get me the contacts.
Anybody In that world.
I'm paylng top dollar. We'll I'lnd them.
You mlnd II' I glve you
a nlckel's worth of advlce?
Just for old tlme's sake?
You're worrled about
your wll'e and klds?
Don't leave.
The way thlngs are now,
some people-- Not me, mlnd you...
...but some people mlght say
you're leavlng her hlgh and dry.
Some people would be
Ignorant on the facts.
Some people wouldn't know that
as far as the pollce are concerned...
...Skyler Is a blameless vlctlm.
Get It off your chest.
The phone call was a smart move.
Kudos to you.
Odds are It was recorded.
It'll play great for a Jury.
It mlght even buy her a mlstrlal.
In a year and a hall'. Untll then,
If they don't have you, they go after her.
There's no polnt. She knows nothlng.
Well, too bad.
She's got nothlng to trade.
I hate to be a downer here...
...but there are two DEA agents mlsslng,
presumed dead.
Thlnk the feds wlll let that go
because you hlt the ejector seat?
Flrst thlng they're gonna do...
...they wlll Rlco
your wll'e and klds out of the house.
That condo ls gone.
Your bank accounts, they're I'rozen.
Her plcture's probably on TV rlght now,
next to yours. Who's gonna hlre her?
-Money's no problem.
-Well, I don't mean to contradlct you...
...but gettlng It to her, lmposslble.
The I'eds are praylng
that you'll make contact.
The Internet, the phone, It's all tapped.
Hey, Mlke was no dummy.
But every tlme he trled to get
hls nest egg to hls granddaughter...
...It ended up In Uncle Sam's pockets.
So you propose what?
Stay. Face the muslc.
I mean,
how much tlme have you got left?
You walk In wlth your head held hlgh...
...be the John Dllllnger ol'
the Metropolltan Detentlon Center.
How bad Is that?
And you brlng a barrel
full of drug money.
Maybe that soothes
some troubled waters.
Maybe they let your I'amlly stay
In the house.
After all, the house predates
the crlmlnal enterprlse.
God, you thlnk I want to run?
Thls Is the last thlng that I want.
Thls-- Thls changes nothlng.
What I do, I do for my I'amlly.
My money goes to my chlldren.
Not Just thls barrel. All of It!
I'm golng to klll Jack
and hls entlre crew...
...and I'm gonna take back what ls mlne
and glve It to my chlldren.
And then, and only then...
...am I through.
Do you understand?
Everythlng good?
Del'lne 'good.'
You're set. Tlme to go.
You'll be a llttle longer.
I'm stlll worklng on transportatlon.
Change of plans.
He's comlng wlth me.
-No. No, that's not--
-We're golng together. I can use hlm.
I'll glve you two a mlnute.
Hey, I'm a clvlllan.
I'm not your lawyer anymore.
I'm nobody's lawyer. The I'un's over.
From here on out, I'm Mr. Low-ProI'IIe.
A douche bag wlth a Job
and three palrs ol' Dockers.
If I'm lucky, month from now,
best-case scenarlo...
-...l'm managlng a Clnnabon In Omaha.
-You're stlll part of thls...
-...whether you llke It or not.
-Sorry. I don't thlnk so.
You remember what I told you?
It's not over untll--
It's over.
Do you want us to cuff her now?
Would that make you feel better?
Your cllent admlts to....
Her day of reckonlng Is now.
--by the tlme thls goes to trlal.
Is she even llstenlng?
Mrs. Whlte?
Are you I'ollowlng all thls?
Do you understand
what's happenlng here?
Yes.
I understand.
I understand I'm In terrlble trouble.
I understand that you wlll use
everythlng In your power...
...agalnst me and my chlldren unless--
Unless I glve you Walt.
But the truth ls,
I can't glve you what you want.
I don't know where he ls.
All rlght, go and dlscuss thls
wlth your lawyer here.
Rack your braln.
And hope you can come up
wlth somethlng we can use.
Four-seventeen?
Four-seventeen. No actlvlty.
Ma'am, Is there anybody else
In the house?
What about your son?
II' I go look In hls room,
am I gonna see hlm?
He's not gonna pop out
and surprlse me?
ll' thls guy takes hls hand away,
are you gonna scream?
He's at hls I'rlend's house.
He's been there all week.
Please, please, don't hurt my baby.
-Please-- Please.
-Ma'am.
We got a lot of respect
for your husband.
There's Just somethlng
that we gotta stralghten out.
Okay, we know that you've
been taIkIng to the pollce...
...and that's okay. You gotta do that.
But you've seen some people.
LIke that lady
who came Into the car wash.
The one wlth the black halr.
You sald anythlng about her?
You sure about that?
I dldn't.
The pollce don't need
to know anythlng about her.
Okay, ma'am,
I'm gonna need you to say It.
lwlll not...
...say anythlng about her. Ever.
I swear.
Okay.
When we leave,
you're not gonna go...
...runnlng to those
pollce oI'I'lcers out front?
Okay.
Because you really
don't want us comlng back.
Sure.
Don't. Stay where you are.
We'll talk llke thls.
Okay.
So that thlng that we talked about...
-...I went to Mr. and Mrs. Whlte's house--
-You don't have to say the name.
Sure. And It went really good.
I mean, the message was recelved
loud and clear.
The message? Yeah.
Look, I know you dld your best.
IJust thlnk--
HI. What can I get you?
Chamomlle tea wlth soy mllk, please.
The person we're dlscusslng
saw my face.
You're not Western Unlon.
We can't Just settle
for you sendlng messages.
Really, If you'd been there,
I thlnk you'd see It dll'l'erent.
We threw a real scare Into her.
She seems llke a nlce lady
watchlng out for her klds.
So you're not golng to have
a problem wlth her.
-I can pretty much guarantee It.
-I wlsh I had your certalnty...
...but I'm not llke you and your uncle.
I'm Just--
I'm not used to thls klnd ol' rlsk.
We're gonna have to take a break.
l have so pounds vacuum-packed
and ready to go.
And I wlsh you all the luck
In the world wlth It.
It's 92 percent.
I'm sorry?
Nlnety-two percent.
-Truly?
-Tested It twlce.
And It's blue, Just llke bel'ore.
NInety-two. That's Helsenberg level.
He's not wlth you?
Well, next best thlng. Plnkman.
They're looklng I'or Plnkman.
Well, they're not golng to I'lnd hlm. He's
wlth us and he's not golng anywhere.
Ms. Quayle, thls Is what your guys
In Europe have been begglng I'or, rlght?
IJust thlnk we work together good.
We make a good team.
lthlnk It's klnd ol'...
...mutually good.
NInety-two percent.
Mr. Lambert,
welcome to New Hampshlre.
All rlght.
Let's have a look at thls place.
You got about a month's worth
of food on hand.
Most of It's canned goods,
but there's steaks In the freezer.
You got a generator outslde,
works on LP.
Ought to be enough In the tank
to last the wlnter.
It's only 15 amps, but that ought to do
for the llghts, the TV, and the freezer.
That's a wood-burner.
Ought to warm the place up
pretty good.
Plus you can cook on It.
On the TV front,
the receptlon's pretty much nll.
You got some mountalns In the way.
Weather's rlght, you mlght
be able to catch Montreal...
...but mostly you'll be llmlted to DVDs.
Mr. MagorIum's Wonder EmporIum.
Two coples.
I'm not much of a movle guy.
I'll make a supply run next month.
You want somethlng else to watch,
put It on the llst.
Supply run.
Fltty thousand dollars
for a trlp to Costco.
It's rlsk.
And rlsk Is what you're paylng me for,
not tollet paper.
Rlsk and a 44oo-mlle round trlp.
Mr. Lambert...
...my cllents and I don't usually have
an ongolng relatlonshlp.
Normally you and I would have already
gone our separate ways...
...but you're you.
-Where's the phone?
-No phone.
Up here, Ice storms equal servlce calls,
equal you In cuffs.
-lnternet?
-Same deal.
Also satelllte, cable TV,
drop phone, car.
You want news,
I'll brlng the Albuquerque papers.
Whatever you need,
Just put It on the llst.
Put It on the llst. Yeah.
Look, I have buslness to conduct.
Your buslness Is your buslness.
My buslness ls keeplng you
out of custody.
You are the target
of a natlon-wlde manhunt.
Your face Is all over TV.
You are the hottest cllent
l have ever had, by far.
It stands to reason
you've got to keep out of slght.
And what's keeplng me
from walklng out that gate?
Nothlng.
There's a llttle one-horse town
elght mlles down the hlll.
There's not a thlng
on God's green earth...
...that I can do to stop you
golng down there.
All I'm saylng ls...
...lf you leave thls place,
you wlll get caught.
And I gotta tell you...
...II I flnd out that
you've left the reservatlon...
...I won't be comlng back.
That Is for my own safety.
You understand?
Sure.
Know how to work the stove?
-The flue can be trlcky.
-Yeah, I got It.
You pald good money for thls.
You got two acres up here,
lots of woods, nlce, warm place.
Seems to me Just the spot for a man
to rest up and thlnk on thlngs.
If you look around, It's klnd of beautlful.
You've been very helpful. Thank you.
See you In a month.
Tomorrow.
Oh, so you're Just too good
to eat wlth the rest of us, huh?
-lt's not for me.
-Damn, man, serlously.
That's not my chocolate chlp, Is It?
You're gonna spoll hlm.
Hey, you awake?
Yeah.
We had some Ben S Jerry's.
There's peanut butter cup
and AmerlCone Dream.
l dldn't know what you llked,
so I got you some of each.
There you go.
So that batch that you Just cooked
was 96 percent.
Klnd of flgured you deserved
a llttle somethlng.
Thanks.
Well, better get some sleep.
Tomorrow's gonna be a blg day.
Got a whole new batch.
-Hey, Todd.
-Yeah?
Would you mlnd
leavlng the tarp off tonlght?
Well, mlght get cold.
No, I don't mlnd. l]ust....
IJust wanna see the stars.
Sure. Okay.
Thanks.
Well, good nlght, Jesse.
nght.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Come on, bltch.
Go ahead! Do It!
Just klll me now and get It over wlth,
because there's no way...
...l'm dolng one more cook
for you psycho fucksl
-Yes?
-Hl, ma'am. How you dolng tonlght?
You're Andrea, rlght?
How can I help you?
You know Jesse Plnkman?
nght? Well, I'm a frlend of hls.
My name's Todd.
I'm sorry to bother you so late,
but It's nlce to meet you.
How Is Jesse? Is he okay?
Yeah, he's okay.
Actually, I brought hlm wlth me.
Jesse's here?
Yeah, he's rlght over there
In that truck.
Where?
Just so you know, thls Isn't personal.
Whoa, hey, settle down.
Settle down.
Hey, remember.
There's stlll the kld.
I brought you a couple of
cases of Ensure.
Maybe put a llttle welght on you.
Jesus.
I can barely read thls.
Almost forgot.
Wlthout a prescrlptlon, I had to take
an educated guess and shotgun It.
One of these ought to come close.
Dld you check on them?
ls Skyler In a better place?
No, she's stlll at that place
off of Eubank.
Klds are both stlll wlth her
for the moment.
There's no court date yet.
The news was taIkIng about
a grand Jury, but they dldn't say when.
I saw her publlc defender on TV.
Looks llke a deer In the headllghts.
Thlnk I got socks older than hlm.
What are they dolng for money?
She's dolng taxl dlspatch, part-tlme.
Leaves the baby wlth a nelghbour
when she goes In.
I saw her shopplng one tlme.
She looks pretty good.
And she's uslng her malden name.
I wouldn't take that personally,
under the clrcumstances.
Those worklng for you?
Oh, yeah.
I took a run by your old house.
The auctlon's stlll pendlng.
They put a fence up around It.
They put up a fence?
Seems llke the place got to be klnd of
a tourlst attractlon. Klds breaklng In.
The nelghbours complalned,
so the bank put up a fence.
You ready?
Yeah.
Sorry about last tlme.
It should go better now.
I watched a couple of YouTube vldeos.
It's all about flndlng the veln.
lee It to me. I'll do It.
Here, you do It.
Make a flst. Tlght. There we go.
All rlght, It's Just....
thtle stlck.
That's It. Okay. Hey.
Pretty good. There you go.
Thlnk I had worse my last physlcal.
lwlll see you on....
Let's see.
Afternoon of the 15th.
Stay a llttle longer?
Yeah, I got a long trlp ahead of me.
Two hours?
I'll glve you another $10,000.
Please.
Ten thousand.
One hour.
Cards?
All rlght, well....
The game wlll be seven-card.
I'll deal, slnce you are encumbered.
One of these days,
when you come up here...
My money over there.
What happens to It then?
What If I ask you
to glve It to my famlly?
Would you do It?
If I sald yes...
...would you belleve me?
You wanna cut the cards?
A klng.
Two klngs.
Flynn WhIte to the prInpraI's
ofﬁce, please.
I'm sorry to pull you out of class.
It's your aunt Marle.
It sounds very Important.
-You can take It In here, okay?
-Okay.
Here he ls.
Thank you.
Hey, Aunt Marle.
What's--? What's golng on?
Hold on a sec, honey.
Look at those numbers for Denver.
ThIngs haven't gone theIr way....
Son, It's me. Please, don't let on.
Carmen's nearby, rlght?
She cannot know.
Son, are you there?
Yes.
It's so good to hear your volce.
Son, the thlngs that they're saylng...
...about me....
I dld wrong.
I made some terrlble mIstakes.
But the reasons were always....
Thlngs happened that I never Intended.
I never Intended--
Llsten, son, we don't have much tlme.
ls Louls' famlly stlll
at 4040 Newcombe?
Son, your frlend, LouIs Corbett...
...does hls famlly stIII IIve
In that same place up on Newcombe?
-Yes.
-Okay, good.
Okay, he's a good kld.
He's llke you. He'll understand.
I'm sendlng LouIs a package.
Now, It's addressed to LouIs,
but It's for you...
your mother and your sIster.
There's money lnslde.
About $100,000. Okay?
I thlnk.
It was all that I could ﬁt Into the box.
It has to be a secret.
If anyone says a word,
the pollce wlll take It.
I wanted to gIve you so much more.
But thls Is all I could do.
Do you understand?
Son?
Can you hear me?
Do you understand?
You want to send money?
Yes. Good.
So you'll talk to Louls, rlght?
You kIIIed Uncle Hank.
-You kIIIed hlml
-Llsten. Walt. Walt, son.
-No. What you dld to Mom--
-PIease--
You asshole.
You kIIIed Uncle Hank.
Llsten to me.
You've got to llsten to me.
Just shut up. Just stop It. Stop It.
I don't want anythlng from you.
I don't glve a shlt.
-You need thls money.
-You kIIIed Uncle Hank.
-You kIIIed hImI
-Your mother needs thls money.
-It can't all be for nothlng.
-What you dld--
-Please. Please.
-Just shut up. Shut up.
WIII you just--? Just leave us alone.
You assholel
Why are you stlll allve?
-Why won't you just dIe already?
-Please--
Just-- Just dle.
Wagner hasn't had to be
really stellar tonlght.
Made solId saves
back In the ﬁrst perIod.
You know, Mlchael, that's probably--
Golng back, look at Wagner's numbers...
you know, It seems llke he's one of
the last goalIes In the league.
They don't wanna
put pressure on thls guy.
KevIn Granato looks to make a move,
had the puck taken.
Denver comes back out
the other way.
--by Graham Melanson off Rycroft.
Who else?
Boy, he's been all over the Ice tonlght.
DEA, Albuquerque DIstrIct OI'I'Ice.
How may I dIrect your call?
I'd llke to speak to the agent...
...In charge of the Walter Whlte
Investlgatlon.
Who may I say Is callIng?
Walter Whlte.
Hello? Hello?
SIr? SIr, are you stlll there?
--thIs Is not just a goalIe that's
out there, It's a whole team.
Two forty-nlne remaInIng
In the thlrd perIod.
You ready for that drlnk now?
Dlmple Plnch. Neat.
You got It.
--and Melanson
wlth a good look makes the save.
That's why you need good, solId
breakout passes.
Matt Peterson-- WIn the draw, Englehart
wIns the draw, back to Peterson...
...goes behlnd the net, makes a terrlble
breakout pass, goes rlght to Hackard.
He just wlnds up, puts It on net here.
Turnovers, turnovers.
When you get turnovers
In the oﬂenslve zone, chances happen.
Hopefully It won't happen agaIn.
Turnovers generally--
-I wasn't sure you'd come.
-I'm not stayIng--
-Madam, Is thls transfer good on the--?
-Darker than a normal rose--
For us, It's always been
scIence ﬁrst, and--
Walt, would you--? Would you--?
Would you go back, please?
-ShamWows--
-More ofa by-product.
-There.
-Exactly.
-What, thls?
-Yes.
But just yesterday, your charlty...
...the Gretchen and Hum Schwartz
Foundatlon...
...announced a $20 mIllIon grant...
...for drug-abuse treatment centres
throughout the Southwest.
CharlIe, the Southwest Is our home...
...and we couldn't just Ignore
what's golng on In our own backyard.
But I'm sure you're aware that there
are people who suggest other motlves.
Andrew Ross SorkIn
of The New York Tlmes...
...wrote a column suggestlng...
...that the grant was
a klnd of publIcIty manoeuvre...
...to shore up the stock prIce
of Gray Matter Technologles...
...because of your assocIatIon
wlth Walter Whlte.
-Well, that's not exactly the way--
-To cleanse yourselves, so to speak...
...of havIng a methamphetamlne kIngpIn
as cofounder of your company.
CharlIe, I'm glad you brought that up.
I have to belleve that
the Investlng publlc understands...
...we're taIkIng about a person
who was there early on...
...but who had nothlng to do
wlth the creatIon of the company...
...and stlll less to do wlth growlng It.
So, what was Walter Whlte's
contrIbutIon?
You know, to be honest... Honey?
-The company name.
We came up wlth It
by combInIng our names.
"Schwartz" means "black. "
-Black plus whlte makes grey.
-Hence Gray Matter Technologles.
Exactly. As far as I can recall,
hls contrIbutIon beglns and ends there.
There are contInuIng reports
of blue methamphetamlne...
...consIdered hls sIgnature product
throughout the Southwest...
...and some evIdence
of reachlng as far as Europe.
So my questIon Is,
Is Walter Whlte stlll out there?
No, he's not.
You sound very sure.
I am.
I can't speak to thls Helsenberg
that people refer to...
...but whatever he became...
...the sweet, klnd, brIllIant man...
...that we once knew long ago,
he's gone.
But to be absolutely clear....
Pollcel Handsl Show us your hands.
Show us your hands.
What's golng on?
Let's see your hands!