The city's called Duke
The state's called New Mexico
Among the gangsters
The gringos' fame is inflated
'Cause of the new drug they created
They say the colour ls blue
And the quallty pure
Thls potent drug's runnln'
Through the clty
And no one could stop It
If they wanted to
The cartel's runnin' hot because
They weren't getting respect
Talkin' 'bout some ”Heisenberg"
Who owns the market now
No one knows the man since
They've never seen his face
The cartel's 'bout respect
And they ain't forgiving
But that homey's dead
He just doesn't know it yet
Heisenberg's fame has got
Down to Michoacan
From way far away
They want to taste that meth
That blue stuff has crossed the border
Now New Mexico's Iivin' up to its name
Looks just like Mexico
In all the drugs lt's hldlng
Except there's a gringo boss
And he's known as ”Heisenberg"
The cartel's runnin' hot because
They weren't getting respect
Talkin' 'bout some ”Heisenberg"
Who owns the market now
No one knows the man since
They've never seen his face
The fury of the cartel
Ain't no one escaped it yet
But that homey's dead
He just doesn't know it yet
Nltrogen bonds to oxygen,
whlch In turn....
You do know what a bond is?
A strong force of attraction.
Covalent bonds, ionic bonds.
The coming together of atoms
and molecules to form compounds.
No?
Chemical bonds
are what make matter matter.
Bonds are what hold
the physical world together.
-What hold us together.
-Yeah. Yeah. No, I got It.
Your test score says otherwise.
It tells me you don't get it at all.
Yeah, but, I mean, 58. I was close.
What Is 'close'?
There's no "close" in science, Barry.
There are rlght answers
and wrong answers.
"Close" didn't put men on the moon.
Yeah, but I'm Just saylng, Mr. Whlte,
two polnts?
Look, if I don't pass chemistry,
I have to go to summer school.
And, I mean, I really studied.
Like, really, really studied.
lee, all nlght, hard.
And, I mean, I'm so into chemistry
for, like, the concepts.
Ijust think I might have, you know,
the attention deficit....
Couldn't you please
Just let thls sllde?
Don't bullshit a bullshitter.
The answer Is no.
Next tlme, apply yourself.
Yo. lfl know you, leave a message.
Are you ducking me, or what?
This makes the third time.
Look, I will be leaving this phone on
for another 15 minutes, so call me.
Oh, and by the way,
that thing we talked about, the....
When I said, "Handle it."
Well, don't. Just let it go.
All rlght.
Come on.
Jesse, open the door.
I know you're home. Your car ls here.
Come on. Hey.
Can I help you?
No. Thank you.
Well, I'm the manager, so can we stop
with the pounding, please?
You're the manager?
Yes. Yes, you can help me.
Absolutely.
I very much need to get inside here,
so if you have a master key....
-You have a key, rlght?
-Yeah, I have a key.
Look, the person who lives here...
...lt's Just very Important
for me to see hlm.
-And you knocked, rlght?
-Yeah.
He didn't answer?
Whlch means...?
-Look, I'm hls father, all rlght?
-You're Mr. Jackson?
Yes. That's me. Walt Jackson.
And you are...?
-Jane.
-Jane. Very nlce to meet you, Jane.
Now, if you wouldn't mind....
Mr. Jackson,
I'm happy to let you use my phone.
-Wanna call hlm?
-No.
As I sald, lwould Ilke
If you let me Inslde here...
...so that I can check on
my son's well-belng.
You understand?
Look, whatever's going on
between the two of you is family.
I don't get involved in family.
Jesse doesn't want you In,
you're not gettlng In.
Perlod.
Sorry.
Come on In, Dad.
-Thanks.
-You okay?
Yeah.
'Jesse Jackson'?
Do you even...?
Oh, I see you have a telephone,
at least.
You know, that blinking thing
I've been calling you on?
Whatever, man.
-Hey, give me my-- Give--
-I will break this. I will break this!
Damned druggie idiot.
Is this what you've been doing...
...the whole tlme
I've been trylng to reach you?
-No. I've been taking care of business.
-What business?
What business?
The business you put me on, asshole.
What, you already forgot?
Thls buslness.
Does that log your memory?
Son of a bltch.
-You dldn't actually--?
-Hey, you sald--
You sald, 'Handle It,'
so, you know, I handled It.
When I said, "Handle it,"
I meant fear and intimidation.
I meant get your money back.
I never meant--
-0h, dldn't mean to H" somebody?
-Nol
Well, too late, yo,
because dude's dead.
-0h, God.
-All rlght? Way dead.
-0h, and, hey, hey, hey. Here.
Here's your money.
Yeah, 4660 bucks. Your half.
Spend it in good health,
you miserable son of a bitch.
I didn't say I killed him.
Tell me what happened.
Dude's wife crushed his head
with an ATM machine.
-Crushed hls--?
-Crushed hls head...
...wlth an ATM machlne
rlght In front of me.
I mean, crushed it like....
Oh, my God, the sound...
...lt's stlll In my ears.
You know, and the blood,
Ilke, everywhere.
lee, there was so much,
you would not belleve.
Man, will you just please give me--?
Just give me my weed, all right?
It helps with my nausea.
...you did not kill anyone?
Does anybody think
that you killed anybody?
I called the cops.
You called the cops?
Yeah. You know, I called,
and l spllt, you know?
And then they came In
and busted her.
God, she was--
She was so zapped out of her mInd.
You know? It's....
She dId It for, Ilke, nothlng.
I mean, he told her she was a skank,
but, yo, I mean, she was a skank.
She couldn't ldentlfy
her left ass cheek.
She was so zonked.
And she had this....
God, she had this kid.
LIsten, I'm a "ﬁle fuzzy
on the mechanlcs here...
...but could you not stop this woman
from killing this man?
Look, she had a gun on me,
all rlght?
Yeah, my gun, okay? Mine.
Go ahead, say it. Say it.
No, l aln't no Tuco or Krazy-a.
I can't run a crew.
Come on. Come on. Point made, man.
Point made. Yes.
Yo. lfl know you, leave a message.
-Hey, lt's Badger, man.
-What are you doing?
-Don't use your real name.
-What? That isn't my real name.
Okay.
Yo, we got those pants you wanted.
Thirty-two large, right?
We got them just for you, jefe.
Let's do some business, yo.
So are you gonna
get back up on that horse?
You get on. All right?
I just want to forget. I just....
Sorry.
Hey.
Hey, what's up with that?
Jesus Malverde,
patron saint of Mexican drug dealers.
Well, yeah, hell,
I know who It Is, okay?
Scumbags kneellng down
praylng to hIm:
'Please, Senor Salnt.
No DEA, please.‘
I'm Just-- I'm Just saylng,
why's he on your desk?
Going after neo-Nazis,
you don't wear swastikas, right?
-Sun Tzu.
-Son who?
Sixth-century Chinese general.
Wrote The Art of War.
'If you know your enemy
as yourself...
...you'll flght wlthout danger
In many battles.‘
nght on.
-Glad to have you onboard.
-Thanks.
-Everybody getting you settled in?
-Oh, yeah, yeah. Great group of guys.
And gals. And gals.
Guys-- Guys and gals.
Good. You couldn't have
picked a better time to arrive.
We're about to put a big dent
in the cartel. Right, Vanco?
Yes, slr.
Yo, bro, check it out.
It's a satellite picture of you farting.
'Fat Man and thtle Boy.‘
Sounds Ilke you two.
I got your fat man in my pants, bitch.
-Hey, watch It.
-It aln't real, dumb-ass.
Just watch It, Is all.
You watch It.
I'm Helsenberg.
You're Heisenberg?
Yeah, I remember you.
You were the cook.
Let's get this over with.
Where's Jesse?
-Busy.
-Hey, that's cool.
Totally cool.
Hey, hey--
It's all there, man. Every dollar.
Case you wanna, like, count it.
-Here?
-l'm Just saylng....
Just saying, like, we cool, yo.
AIn't got no confuslons
and Interpretatlons...
...as to who we work for.
And that's church, yo. For real.
What have you heard?
DId Jesse really...?
I mean, did he really...
...squash that dude's head
with an ATM machine?
Word.
Who's saying that?
Damn, man, it's all over town.
Everybody's like, "Whoa, snap."
Usually I gotta chase dudes down
for their money...
...but today everybody's paying up.
True that. Serious.
But, Ilke....
You didn't hear that from me.
Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Very good, Ms. Whlte.
We'll consider your application
and let you know.
Thank you.
I'd just like to mention
that l have worked here before.
Really?
When are you due?
-Several months.
-Congratulatlons.
I see. Accounting Department.
You left us four years ago?
Famlly.
We'll definitely let you know.
Thank you for coming by.
Actually, may I see Ted Beneke?
l-- I think he'll remember me.
Mr. Beneke's very busy today,
unfortunately.
You know, if it's okay, I'll just--
Skyler. Oh, my God, look at you.
Hey, Ted.
-Come In, come In.
-0kay.
No calls, Margaret, thanks.
Come on, sit down right here.
Okay. Thank you.
-You look great.
-0h, yeah, yeah.
Boy or gIrl?
Or are you keeplng It a secret?
Oh, It's a "ﬁle glrl.
We're very exclted.
I'll bet. One of each.
How's Walt Jr.?
Oh, 10th grade,
and he's just growing like a weed.
He's-- He's taller than I am now.
Yeah. I'm bettlng 6'3', 6'4'
by the tlme he's fInIshed.
And, wow, handsome. Oh, my God.
Speaking of movie stars,
those can't be the twins.
Oh, yeah. Yep. That's them.
-They're gorgeous.
-Yes, they are.
And they know It.
I'm in real trouble there, huh?
Yeah.
So the big office, huh?
-Yeah.
Welrd, Isn't It?
lstill think of it as my dad's.
Me too.
I'd like to think he'd be proud.
Last year was our best year yet.
Yeah, he'd be proud.
Walt? How's he doing?
Oh, he's-- He is doing great.
Yeah. He's plugging away.
-Great. He's stlll teachlng?
-Yeah.
-You tell hlm l sald hello.
-I wlll deflnltely do that.
To be honest, Ted,
l dldn't just stop by to say hello. I....
l was applying for the data-entry job.
Skyler, you were, Ilke,
our go-to bookkeeper.
Yeah. Well...
...the economy, you know, so....
Well, you, data entry?
That'd be a mlstake.
How about...
...get your old job back?
We're expanding, and, well,
between you and me...
...the whole department's
pretty much of a mess.
Your work would be cut out for you...
...but we could use your help.
Okay.
All rlght. Now, thls Is our terrltory,
rlght? Currently.
Hey. Hello.
-Yeah, man. Current. Whatever.
-Now, look at thls.
Here, here, here and here.
What does that look like to you?
Opportunities. Golden ones.
That's what that looks like.
No, look.
Look, It's an entlre clty full of buyers.
Now, why aren't we exploiting that?
-Because it's not our territory?
-Because we lack initiative.
-Inlt|atlve.
-Yes.
You need to employ more dealers.
Double, trlple your crew.
Those three I met?
They should each have three, six, nine
sub-dealers working for them.
Exponentlal growth,
that's the key here.
It's not our terrltory, man.
Yo, you follow me here, huh?
We go rolllng Into
these nelghbourhoods...
...other crews ain't gonna take kindly,
you understand?
Sure, they won't like it...
...but I say they're not gonna
do a thlng about It.
-No. LIsten, Jesse--
-No.
Jesse.
The game has changed.
The word is out that you are a killer.
-What are you talking about?
-Apparently, it's all over town.
Somebody crossed you,
you got angry...
...you crushed their skull
with an ATM machine.
-That's not how It happened.
-Who cares...
...as long as it's our competitors
who believe it and not the police?
-Oh, my--
-No, don't you see how great thls Is?
Look, you-- You are a....
Jesse, look at me.
You are a blowfish.
-What?
-A blowflsh. Thlnk about It.
Small In stature,
not swlft, not cunnlng.
Easy prey for predators...
...but the blowflsh
has a secret weapon...
...doesn't he? Doesn't he?
What does the blowflsh do, Jesse?
What does the blowflsh do?
-I don't even know--
-The blowflsh puffs up.
The blowflsh puffs himself up
four, five times larger than normal.
And why? Why does he do that?
So that It makes hlm IntImldatIng,
that's why.
IntImldatIng.
So that the other scarler flsh
are scared off.
And that's you. You are a blowfish.
You see, it's just all an illusion.
You see, it's nothing but air.
...who messes wlth the blowflsh,
Jesse?
-Nobody.
-You're damn rlght.
-l'm a blowflsh.
-You are a blowflsh.
-Say It agaln.
-l'm a blowflsh.
-Say It Ilke you mean It.
-You're a blowflsh. That's rlght.
-Yeahl
Blowfishing this up.
Hello?
The SkyMalI.
Give me the SkyMalI, would you?
Vanco...
...new guy don't speak Spanlsh.
What's up?
Hey, whlte boy,
better learn EspaIIol, huh?
This ain't Branson, Missouri,
know what I'm talking about?
You know what? I'll teach you.
It means, "Let's make a deal."
So go ahead. We're waiting.
Okay.
nght here.
'ltem SS4G:
Yankee Stadium final season
commemorative baseball...
...hand—signed by Derek Jeter."
Vanco, write this down.
Oh, man, watch out.
"GGIOOZBG: large-size floor runner."
Look at that, huh?
It's a rug you put on the floor...
...except for It looks Ilke
a hundred-dollar blll.
I love them. Get me 20 of them.
I'm gonna put them all over my casa.
We'll get you three.
-No, you glve me 10.
-Flve.
Hey. How about you stop
jerklng us off here?
Where's the meet?
When's It goIng down?
Whlte boy don't Ilke
let's make a deal, huh?
White boy's gonna kick your ass,
you don't stop wasting time.
Schrader....
Hey, white boy. My name's Tortuga.
You know what that means?
Well, if I had to guess,
I'd say that's Spanish for "asshole."
Tortuga means "turtle." That's me.
I take my time, but I always win.
Oh, wait. That reminds me.
I seen this earlier. Lookit.
Thls Is awesome, homes.
nght there, look at that.
'The tranqull tortolse
garden sculpture.‘
Definitely two of those, huh?
Check it out, huh? Good likeness.
Hank's doing great down there.
He's making inroads.
I'm sure he is. He's a hero, after all.
So you gonna go down to El Paso?
Please. It's Third World enough
around here.
They keep him busy every second.
He's already got some
bIg operatlon golng.
Some hush-hush deal
he couldn't tell me about...
...except It's on the other slde
of the border.
Wow, that sounds exciting.
He's being safe, right?
Yeah.
He says he's mostly rldlng a desk.
Which, between you and me,
is just the way I want it.
Speaking of riding desks...
...got myself a job today.
You dId not.
As bIg as you are?
-Thank you.
-You know I just mean....
Where? With who?
Well, someone willing
to work around that, apparently.
You dId not.
Is Mr. Grabby-Hands stlll there?
Marle, that was one tlme
at a Chrlstmas party.
And he was so drunk,
he was practically slurring his words.
-Just what you want in an executive.
-And he apologised profusely.
Plus he's married with a family.
I'm sure he doesn't wanna get sued.
It will not happen again.
ls money that tight?
Yeah.
You know we can always help out.
No, Marle.
You know Walt. He would just....
-Speak of the devll.
-Hey. HI, Marle.
How are you? What's up?
Nothlng much.
How's thlngs wlth you?
-Good. Good.
-H|, honey.
-Dinner will be about an hour and--
-Oh, thanks, sweetie.
-Everythlng okay?
-Everyth|ng's perfect.
Thls Is Ralsln Bran,
not Ralsln Bran Crunch.
So? Same thlng.
Not the same thing.
I'll tell you what, why don't you
do the grocery shopping?
And then you can get
whatever you want. Great.
lt's-- It's not that hard, Mom.
It says 'crunch' on the box.
You're pushlng It.
-Morn|ng.
-Morn|ng, honey.
-Hey, Dad.
-Hey.
Dad, notice anything?
Is there a funeral today?
-A funeral?
-WeII--
-Oh, Chrlst, do I look that bad?
-No, no, no.
Mom got a job.
A job? Why?
Well, do I need to get out
the chequebook and show you?
No, I.... Do you thlnk It's a good Idea
In your condItIon?
No, no. The doctor said I can work
up until I go into labour.
And It's just an offlce job.
I'm just slttlng on my butt.
Where?
I'm back working
in the Accounting Department.
Skyler, what about the welding fumes?
Isn't that why you had to quit...
-...In the flrst place?
-They've gone green slnce then.
They have some kind of
green welding or something.
l dldn't smell anythlng
when l was In there.
Didn't Mr. Beneke pass away?
Yeah.
Who's running things?
Ted. The son.
Anyway, I have got to go.
I don't wanna be late
my flrst day back.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye.
Okay.
-W|sh me luck.
-Good luck.
Bye.
Hey.
You left your cave.
Yeah.
lwas-- I'm missing my TV.
Thinking maybe I'd hit Costco.
You know,
snag a bIg-ass wIde-screen.
Yeah.
What you drawing?
That's good.
Make a hell of a tat.
That's the plan.
Really?
I work part-time, down at ABQ Ink.
nght on.
I used to do a little of that.
You used to be a drawer too, huh?
What stopped you?
You know, just....
So tell me something.
What kInd of tattoo artlst
has no tattoos?
That's way too big a commitment.
Hey, man. You're Pinkman.
You're the man!
Everybody's been talking about you.
Yeah.
Right on, man. Keep it real.
'Plnkman,' huh?
Yeah.
I thought your name was "Jackson."
Well, your snltch
Is really earnlng hls nlckname.
Are we...?
Are we just on mahana time?
They'll show.
Yeah? Why Is that?
You got more catalogues
for hlm to clean out?
Maybe a little Sharper Image
or Pottery Barn?
What the hell are they thinking?
Sending us some loudmouth
who doesn't speak the language?
Politics, man. Politics.
Supposed to be some hotshot hero.
I say it's a bunch of crap.
Hero for Albuquerque, maybe.
Maybe it don't take much up there.
Hey, somethlng
I need to know about?
What? Oh, that? No, man.
We were just singing your praises.
Glad to have you.
Welcome aboard.
Hey, is that your guy?
Hey, lthink that's your guy.
What the hell
Is he doIng down there?
Schrader, where you going?
We need an evidence bag, right?
A pretty big one.
What's the matter?
You act Ilke you never saw...
...a severed human head
on a tortolse before.
Hey, welcome to--
My leg.
--headed by Werner Heisenberg,
were also undertaken during the war.
The game has changed, yo.
This is our city, all right?
All of it. The whole damn place.
Our terrltory.
We're staking our claim...
...that we sell when we want,
where we want.
Now, we're gonna be klngs,
understand?
Well, I'm gonna be king.
You guys wlll be prlnces
or dukes or somethlng.
-I wanna be a knlght.
-But flrst thlngs flrst.
We gotta get more dealers.
You know, foot soldiers, right?
Now, they'll be working for you.
You're worklng for me,
and they're worklng for you.
You follow me?
Layered, like nachos.
Exponential growth.
Now, that's success
wlth a capltal S.
Straight up, straight up.
For shlzzle.
Frigging awesome.
Well, we're set.
Our boys are ready.
Gonna be some mad cheddar, yo.
Cheddar, Mr. White.
Fat stacks, dead presldents,
cash money.
Gonna own thls clty.
We're not charging enough.
What?
You corner the market,
then ralse the prlce.
Oh, hey, Ted. Come on in.
-Looks Ilke they got you all set up.
-Yeah. It's perfect.
lam close enough to the bathroom
that I don't have to waddle far.
And that's very nlce.
-I figured that might be a deal-breaker.
-Yeah.
LIsten, l....
I wanted to thank you
for havlng me back.
You don't have to thank me.
I need you.
Wow, Ted, It's a "ﬁle early
for wIne, Isn't It?
Oh, damn. It's grape juice.
Been making the girls
breakfast in the morning.
Hey, how is Denise doing?
We split up, about a year ago.
I'm sorry.
She's definitely happier now.
I guess I am too, most days.
-Together slnce hlgh school.
-Yeah.
-I remember that.
-Anyway....
I don't know, people change.
Yes.
Anyway, Ijust wanted
to welcome you.
Welcome you back. And....
I'll see you around
the vendlng machlnes.
Okay.
We should have lunch one day.
LIke old tlmes.
Sure.
Oh, hey.
Hey, yourself.
So Ilsten. My....
My name Is not really
Jesse Jackson.
It's Jesse Pinkman.
And that guy you met...
...he's not my dad.
You're not gonna kIck me out,
are you?
Because I actually really like it here.
I don't make It my buslness
what you do.
So long as you don't do it here.
So, hey, I got thls kIck-ass
new flat-screen.
Wanna see?
It's got that thing where the blacks...
...are, Ilke, you know,
really, really, really black.
And the Dolby six-point-whatever.
So it'll really rock the house.
But I'll, you know....
I'll keep it way down, of course.
I don't know what the hell
Is taklng so long.
Come on, come on.