More.
Another.
Caroful, senor.
Hot day Ilka today...
...too much all In the machlna...
...can cause It to blow a gasket.
There are two klnd: of men
In thl: world.
Thou who drlnk...
...and those who pour.
Shut up and ﬁll my glass.
Hay, you two.
You, you.
I used to be Just Ilka you.
Worked dlrt tor the man
tlll my hand: bled.
But no more.
Because I learned that a man
can never drlnk hla I'lll...
...by waltlng In llne tor the tap.
Llaten to hlm.
He can teach you aomethlngl
Hey, how you dolng, boas?
Good to see you, my I'rlend.
You know, I never pegged you
for such a deep thlnker.
I keep thlnklng I should wrlte a book.
Maybe, maybe....
So, what brlnga you to thla
burro'a aaahole of a town?
I knew I would ﬁnd you here.
Don't you have aomethlng to dellver?
Cuttlng It cloae, aren't you?
Lot: of tlme.
Tortuga may be slow out of the gate,
but he always--
Flnlahea I'lrat.
Yea, I know.
Just llke your nameaake.
l llke the way you talk, Tortuga.
Yeah?
You've got such a way wlth worda.
They Now llke a waterfall.
l llke that about you.
I'm so atupld.
l mlaaed your blrthday.
No, I feel terrlble.
So bad I came all the way here
to thla burro'a aaahole...
...to glve you your present.
Preaent?
Come on, boaa.
No need to go through the trouble.
Forget It, I wanted to.
l have It for you In the back.
-Back there?
-Yea. Come. Follow me.
It's perfect!
Do you really llke It?
I love It!
What a great pet It wlll make.
Thank you, boaal
Excellent.
Let me algn It for you.
Let me algn It...
...'For the blg talker.'
He'a atlll breathlng.
Well, by the look: of hlm,
he has no Idea how close he came.
I'm aaaumlng Saul Goodman
doesn't need to know.
Mum'a the word.
Son of a bltch.
Hang on, baby.
Hello.
Walt? Are you In the house?
0h, hey, Skyler. Yeah, It's me.
What? What the hell
are you dolng In there?
No, no, you're not back, Walt.
You're not back.
Get-- Get out of there.
-Well, It's my house too, Skyler.
.N°..
I'm ataylng. End of story.
-We had an agreement.
-I dldn't agree to anythlng.
Now, look, Just come on lnalde
and we'll talk thla through, okay?
No. No. There'a nothlng to talk about.
I am not comlng In there
untll you get out.
Well, ault youraell'.
Walt.
Walt?
What la wrong wlth you?
-Skyler, l have every rlght to be here.
-No, you don't.
You don't llve here anymore.
We're gettlng a dlvorce.
-I don't agree to a dlvorce.
-Well, It's not up to you.
It you don't get out of here rlght now,
I'm gonna call the pollce...
...and I'm golng to tell them
everythlng.
I mean It, Walt.
There's the phone.
lt'a rlnglng.
Albuquerque Pollce Department.
Operator number 314.
How may I help you?
Albuquerque Pollce Department.
Yea, I want to report a dlaturbance,
pleaae.
No, no, It's not--
It's not exactly, lt'a....
It's a domeatlc laaue.
Okay.
They're connectlng me.
nght hand to God, lwlll tell them.
Do what you have to do, Skyler.
Thla I'amlly la everythlng to me.
-W|thout It, I have nothlng to lose.
-Flne.
Yea. My name la Skyler Whlte.
I need pollce aaalatance
at my home rlght away.
My aoon-to-be-ex-huaband
broke Into my houae...
...and I need an ofﬁcer to come
and remove hlm.
lt'a 308 Negra Arroyo Lane.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
They're comlng.
-Dad'a here?
-Great, he'a home.
-Dad.
-Hey, aon.
How are you?
Are you back for good?
-Why are you home ao aoon?
-l'm not.
Hey, I am atarvlng.
How about a grllled cheeae?
-Sure.
-You want one too?
Walter, your dad and l
have aomethlng we need to dlacuaa.
When your aandwlch la ready,
I'll brlng It to your room.
Mom, can't It walt?
I haven't aeen Dad In, llke, I'orever.
-Walter?
-How waa achool?
-lt waa good.
-Yeah? Homework?
-No, not really.
-Not really? What doea that mean?
So are you gonna be
at work tomorrow?
Yeah, that'a the plan.
Hello, ma'am.
We were called about a dlaturbance?
lt'a more of a treapaaalng altuatlon,
really, but....
Yeah, that waa me.
You called the copa on Dad?
I came home from work
and he waa back.
He had Juat moved back
Into the houae.
And I aaked hlm to leave,
but he won't llaten. l]uat....
I want hlm out.
I want hlm out of the houae.
Okay, Mra. Whlte, there'a a couple
queatlona I need to aak you.
lt'a very Important
you anawer honeatly.
-Dld he atrlke you?
-No.
-Haa he ever hlt you?
-No. Thla la not about vlolence.
Thla la about treapaaalng.
-About hlm belng here agalnat my wlll.
-Okay. Treapaaalng.
-You're dlvorced, then?
-No, worklng on It.
-nght now, were aeparated.
-Legally aeparated?
There'a not a court order,
It that'a what you mean.
But we've been llvlng apart
for almoat two weeka, glve or take.
I changed the locka.
lan't that breaklng and enterlng?
Whoae name la on the tltle
to the houae?
Both of ua. lt'a Jolntly owned.
We can't arreat a man for breaklng
Into hla own houae.
Not wlthout a court order
requlrlng he ataya away.
Unleaa he'a threatened you
or the klda.
No. Not phyalcally.
But havlng hlm In the houae la Juat....
lt'a not a good thlng. Excuae me.
I got her, honey.
Come here. Here we go.
You hungry? You hungry?
Here we go.
That waa It.
-l'm aorry, oI'I'lcer. Where were we?
-Dlaagreementa.
Yea, well, we've had our ahare of that.
I haven't.... I haven't been
the moat attentlve huaband lately.
Mra. Whlte, would thla be eaaler
II' we atepped outalde tor a mlnute?
No. Nope. I'm I'lne rlght here.
I'm gonna level wlth you, ma'am.
It you want hlm out of the houae,
you'll have to help me.
la It poaalble maybe
he'a broken any lawa that you know of?
Anythlng at all. Anythlng that
we could work wlth here, Juat tell me.
Even If lt'a Juat a auaplclon,
I can work wlth that.
I'll get hlm out of the houae for you.
What'a your take on all thla?
lt'a my mom'a I'ault.
She won't even aay what my dad dld
and lt'a becauae he dldn't do anythlng.
I don't know why
ahe'a belng thla way.
My dad, he la a great guy.
Son, lt'a not your mom'a I'ault.
Mra. Whlte.
I'm aorry, ma'am.
There'a no legal baala...
...I'or ua to remove your huaband
from the houae.
Next tlme you feel thlnga
are gettlng out of control...
...you ahould call thla number.
lt'a the I'amlly hotllne.
I'd really look Into
aome counaelllng.
Beat of luck to you I'olka.
Llaten, thank you, ofI'Icera.
We're aorry.
Why you gotta--?
Why you gotta do thla to Dad?
Junlor, walt, come on.
Don't blame your mother for thla.
Sorry.
Welcome home.
He llvea. Happy houaewarmlng, kld.
-Don't look ao glad to aee me.
-Thanka.
lntereatlng decor. lt'a aubtle.
The whole mlnlmallat thlng never
really blew my halr back, but hey.
So how are you dolng?
Staylng clean?
Good. I waa klnd oI' worrled
that you were back to old hablta...
...alnce l dldn't hear from you,
you know.
You reallae how atupld It la
to Ignore your counael'a phone calla?
What II' I waa trylng to warn you...
...that the DEA waa gonna klck down
your door? What then?
Why don't you apare me the aermon
and get to why you're here?
Falr enough.
Remember the other day...
...when I brought up the Idea of you
gettlng back In touch wlth your partner?
Well, I klnd of wanted to
re-I'loat that boat.
I'm not auggeatlng you
youraell' get back to cooklng.
I mean, you belng In rehab and all.
I only want you to convlnce
the maater chef to do hla thlng.
So, what do you aay?
-Sure, man. Whatever.
-Okay. Whatever what?
I mean, you gonna call hlm?
l aald I'll handle It.
Now, bounce, wlll you? Pleaae?
Flnal thought.
Look at thla place. You're houae-poor,
you got no bankroll.
It you get the maeatro cooklng agaln,
I'll make It worth your whlle.
Call hlm.
If you're trylng to aell me aomethlng,
I've got four worda for you:
"Do Not Call Ilat. "
However, If you're cool,
leave It at the beep.
Schrader.
Yea, alr. Yeah, what'a up?
Yeah?
That'a great newa, alr. Thank you.
Yeah, yeah, abaolutely,
you can bet on that.
Hey, llaten, thanka agaln, alr...
...I really appreclate you atepplng
to the plate. Thank you.
So you gonna keep me In auapenae
or what? What'a the good newa?
Merkert called In a couple of I'avoura.
El Paao wanta me back.
Hey, man, congrata, man.
That'a I'antaatlc.
Thank you.
Gentlemen. Welcome.
Thank you for comlng.
Any dll'l'lculty at the border?
The day I can't get acroaa the border
la the day l retlre.
Pleaae, come In.
l apologlae that lt'a not
wheelchalr acceaalble.
My apologlea, Guatavo.
OI' courae,
you ahould have been advlaed.
lt'a your terrltory,
you had a rlght to bleaa the order.
But....
We had no reaaon to belleve
the man waa of concern to you.
So you're In bualneaa wlth
thla Helaenberg.
I don't know hlm by that name, but yea.
I've made no aecret ol' the fact that...
...l have alwaya done bualneaa
wlth certaln local manul'acturera.
You and I,
we atlll make money together.
lt'a never affected our relatlonahlp.
Don Salamanca had a
nephew named Tuco.
Yea, I knew of hlm.
Then perhapa you know Don Salamanca
mentored hlm In the bualneaa.
Thought of Tuco aa a aon.
When Don Salamanca waa no longer
able, Tuco took over for hla uncle.
He waa a key man In our
organlaatlon north of the border.
He waa loyal.
Thla Helaenberg, Walter Whlte...
...he waa one of Tuco'a local auppllera.
Untll he betrayed Tuco.
So now you aee,
blood muat be repald by blood.
Tuco'a coualna here...
...they have the rlght
to exact vengeance.
The Salamanca famlly, the cartel...
...everyone atanda ahoulder
to ahoulder on thla.
Gentlemen.
I feel your loaa deeply.
Pleaae accept my condolencea.
l have no laaue wlth
your rlght to vengeance.
But I am preaently engaged In
bualneaa wlth thla man.
When our bualneaa la done...
...he wlll no longer be
of any concern to me.
Untll then...
...I need hlm allve.
I don't tell you how to
fry your chlckena, Guatavo.
You ahould really leave mattera
of my organlaatlon'a polltlca to me.
Do I not run my own terrltory?
Of courae you do.
And I wlll advlae them to be patlent.
But I recommend you flnlah your
bualneaa wlth the man qulckly.
Or you rlak loalng the
good gracea of the cartel.
That would not be wlae.
And thoae boya lnalde...
...I cannot guarantee
that they wlll llaten.
They are not llke you and I.
If you're trylng to aell me aomethlng,
I've got four worda for you:
"Do Not Call Ilat. "
However, If you're cool,
leave It at the beep.
If you're trylng to aell me aomethlng,
I've got four worda for you:
"Do Not Call "at. "
However, If you're cool,
leave It at the beep.
If you're trylng to aell me aomethlng,
I've got four worda for you....
Sweetheart. I'm aorry. I'm aorry.
lt'a okay. lt'a okay, my glrl.
Yea, lt'a okay. lt'a okay.
Mama'a got you.
I've got you. Yea. Yea.
Skyler? Want aome help?
Skyler, can I uae the bathroom?
-What do you mean? Agalnat your wlll?
-Yea.
Very much agalnat my wlll.
He Juat-- He ahowed rlght back up.
And he doean't want a dlvorce.
Won't even conalder It.
I called the pollce on hlm.
-So cloae to what?
-Nothlng. Never mlnd.
Skyler, I can't advlae you properly
If you don't glve me all the facta.
Underatand, I'm bound
by the attorney-cllent prlvllege...
...to keep everythlng you tell me
a aecret.
I can't tell a aoul
unleaa you authorlae me to.
Even If lt'a aomethlng Illegal?
Eapeclally If lt'a Illegal.
I'm your lawyer, not the pollce.
My Job la to protect you.
My huaband makea meth.
Methamphetamlne.
-Your huaband'a a drug dealer?
-A manufacturer, technlcally.
They.... They call them cooka.
I looked It up on the Internet.
Thla la my advlce,
and you ahould take It:
Sue your huaband for dlvorce
lmmedlately.
Let me go to the pollce
and tell them what you Juat told me.
I'll go In ex parte to get a
reatralnlng order from the court today.
If he comea anywhere near you and
your chlldren, he'll go atralght to Jall.
No queatlona aaked.
Thla la a no-bralner.
lt'a the beat thlng for you
and your famlly.
I can't.
I can't do It.
I don't want my aon to flnd out
that hla father la a crlmlnal.
l]uat....
-I can't do that to hlm.
-In the end, It may not be up to you.
Drug dealera have a way
of gettlng caught.
Walt haa lung cancer.
Hla treatment bought hlm aome tlme.
But the doctora,
they all aay that aooner or later....
I can't aee why
lahould lay all thla on my famlly...
...when thlnga may...
...reaolve themaelvea on thelr own...
...wlthout anyone elae knowlng.
Man, dld l loae a bet or aomethlng?
-What are we dolng In thla ahlthole?
-Relax, wlll you?
Relax? Thla la the klnd of place
you get knlfed.
-We ahould have went to Chlll'a, man.
-All rlght, already. Jeaua.
Outback Steakhouae. lt'a not too late.
They got that Bloomlng Onlon.
What'a wrong wlth aplclng thlnga
up a llttle?
Thla aplce looka llke lt'a been through
a couple of guya already.
So when you headed back down
to El Paao?
You know. Between all the packlng,
erranda, gettlng the ducka In a row...
-...maybe a week or two.
-Week or two?
Come on, man.
I'd be dylng to get back In the actlon.
lt'a not llke
there'a nothlng golng on up here.
What are you talklng about?
Aln't Jack golng on up here.
lt'a qulet aa hell.
I'm gonna hlt the head.
Thoae two over there.
lthlnk they're holdlng.
Man, In thla place,
the bartender'a probably holdlng.
-All rlght.
-What you dolng?
Calllng A.P.D., what do you thlnk?
Slnce when can't we handle
a couple dlrtballa?
Come on, man. Courteay call.
What If Vlce la runnlng
aome klnd of undercover op?
Screw It. lt'a your turn to pay.
-Where you golng?
-Gotta take a leak.
Jeaua, get youraelf aome Flomax.
Stand up.
You got a problem wlth ua, bltch?
Your move.
DEA. Don't move.
Go out and tell my partner
to get hla aaa In here.
If you're trylng to aell me aomethlng,
I've got four worda for you:
"Do Not Call Ilat. "
However, If you're cool,
leave It at the beep.
If you're trylng to aell me aomethlng,
I've got four worda for you:
"Do Not OaII--"
The number you have reached,
149-4985...
...In area code 505 la no longer--
Skyler.
Can we talk?
ASAc wanta to aee you.
And?
We were hanglng back,
aaw a deal go down.
I went outalde to call It In.
You atayed to keep an eye
on the auapecta.
That'a when they attacked you.
What I dldn't tell hlm la that
you left your gun under the aeat...
...before you went back lnalde.
I've done a terrlble thlng.
But I dld It for a good reaaon.
ldld It for ua.
That la college tultlon
for Walter Jr...
...and Holly 18 yeara
down the road.
That la health lnaurance
for you and the klda.
For Junlor'a phyalcal therapy,
hla SAT tutor.
lt'a money for grocerlea...
...for gaa...
...for blrthdaya
and graduatlon partlea.
Skyler, that money la for thla roof
over your head...
...the mortgage you aren't
gonna be able to afford...
...on a part-tlme bookkeeper'a aalary
when I'm gone.
-Walt, l--
-Pleaae. Pleaae.
Thla money, I dldn't ateal It.
It doean't belong to anyone elae.
I earned It.
The thlnga I've done to earn It...
...the thlnga that I've had to do...
...I've got to llve wlth them.
Skyler...
...all that I've done...
...all the aacrlflcea that l have
made for thla famlly...
...all of It wlll be for nothlng
If you don't accept what I've earned.
Pleaae.
I'll be here
when you get home from work.
You can glve me your anawer then.
Hey, Sky.
-Hey, aome coffee?
-Yeah.
That report'a looklng real good.
I llke how It looka.
Are your klda home?
It'a herel It'a herel
Everybody, come on Inl Lookl
Hey, Mra. Whlte.
Hey, Loula.
Hey, thanka for havlng me
over for dlnner.
Sure.
Hey, Skyler. I'm cooklng dlnner.
Pot roaat. Could you...?
So how waa your day?
Excellent.
I hope you don't mlnd, l lnvlted Loula
to atay for dlnner tonlght.
You know, aa a thank-you for drlvlng
Walter Jr. to achool for ua.
We've been klnd of abaent...
...but, ltell you,
Loula really pltched In.
Look, IJuat wanna aay that I feel good
about our talk thla mornlng...
...and I'm very eager
to hear what you're thlnklng about...
...about what we talked about.
But, you know,
whenever you're ready, of courae.
Honeaty la good. Don't you thlnk?
I fucked Ted.
Boya, dlnner.
-lced tea?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Loula?
-Yea, pleaae.
All rlght.
I want you boya both
to eat your aalad, okay?
-Okay.
-I know nobody llkea aalad...
...but lt'a good for you.
-Thanka, darllng.
-Thank you.