Yo, so, what's next?
We walt.
We don't got Ilka alght more
anal thlng: m gotta do tlrst?
The raactlon has begun.
Yoah, I know. So how long?
Well, If m had a truzor, the condanaed
llquld would cool more qulckly...
...becauu, of course,
thla la an exothormlc reactlon...
...whlch moan: 'glvlng oft haat.‘
And our daalrod product |a....
Put me Into a coma, why don't you?
What dld you Just say?
What? What? Nothlng.
No, no, no. Not In hora.
le0 I'm an ldlot.
Yeah. lee you're an ldlot.
God. Jesus. God.
Shut up.
Bogdan. Bogdan say: I'm not
dolng the recelpta rlght.
Well, he's got a bug up hla butt.
He's got a atlck up hla butt?
He's got a bug up hla butt
about the recelpta, anywaya.
So anyway, he'a lnalatlng that l--
He'a demandlng that I stay...
...and look over hla ayatem...
...and I cannot get out of It.
Yeah.
-Hello.
-Hl, honey. It's me.
-Hey, you. What's golng on?
-Nothlng much.
lwaa Juat calllng
to say I'm sorry...
...but I'm gonna be late tonlght.
Bogdan. He's got a bug up hla butt.
That's okay. I wasn't plannlng anythlng
apeclal l'or dlnner, ao....
In fact, you could take plty on us
and brlng a plzza home.
They're havlng a two-l'or-one
at Venezla'a.
At thla polnt,
I could eat a whole one by myself.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
I can plck up a plzza.
Hopel'ully Bogdan
won't keep me too late.
He better not. Trust me, he doesn't want
to plea off a hungry pregnant woman.
-What'a that sound?
-I just sold your favourlte plece.
The hldeoua crylng clown.
Yeah, and I got 9 bucks
more than I pald for It.
Shows what I know about art.
Hey, what do you thlnk about Holly?
Do you llke It?
lthlnk I really llke lt.
Holly. Yeah, It's nlce.
Let me thlnk about It.
Juat l'eela rlght, you know?
It's my new tavourlte.
Well, It's a l'ront-runner, for sure.
Llaten, l was thlnklng, maybe we can
have a llttle l'amlly tlme thla weekend.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
You know, Just take a drlve.
The almost tour of us.
Maybe we can head up
the Turquolse Trall...
...stop at Tlnkertown,
maybe grab some lunch ln Madrld.
Oh, my God.
We haven't been there In l'orever.
-I know.
-Yeah.
So why don't we just do that?
Take a llttle break?
Sold. Sounds fun.
Holly. It's growlng on me.
Yep. Me too.
All rlght, well, I had better go
and get thls In the mall.
Why don't you call me
when you're on your way home?
-W|ll do. Love you.
-Love you too.
Whoa, slmmer down there, sparky.
What the hell dld we Just walk Into?
Hey, Uncle Jack,
I don't see Jesse Plnkman.
He was rlght here before.
-Anybody got eyes on Plnkman?
-No.
What do you l'lgure? He maybe
headed down that gully there?
That's the way I'd go.
Frankle, Lester, go l'lnd hlm.
Jack.
These guys are DEA.
Nol Jack, nol
Jack! Jack! Jack!
No! No, don't!
Jack, don't. No.
No, Jack, Jack, Jack! Jack, nol
-Jack, no. Don't klll hlm.
-Back It up.
-Don't klll hlm, Jack.
-Get back here.
The hell not? He's DEA.
No, he's l'amlly.
Say agaln?
He's my l'amlly.
He's my brother-ln-law.
Dldn't cross your mlnd
to maybe tell us...
...you had a DEA agent
for a brother-ln-law?
-Dld you know about thls?
-I called you off, remember?
-I told you not to come.
-Well, It seems to me we dld you a solld.
-You weren't supposed to be here.
-Too late now.
How's about you telllng me
what was golng down out here?
You and your brother-ln-law
don't seem to be gettlng along too well.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't concern you.
We Just wasted hls partner here,
and he's wearlng a bullet...
...so, yeah, I'd say It does concern me.
Thls ls between hlm and me.
-No cavalry comlng?
-No.
-You bet your ass the cavalry's comlng.
-No, no, no! Jack--
Jackl No, the DEA
doesn't know about thls.
Not yet.
Nothlng can change
what Just happened...
...but you can walk out of here allve...
...ll' you Just promlse us
that you'll let thls go.
Yeah, I thought as much.
Sorry, man. Just no scenarlo
where thls guy llves.
No, no, no, llstenl l have money!
l have money!
It's burled out here. It's....
It's 680 mllllon.
Elghty mllllon.
So that's what got
thls party started, huh?
But thls money of yours
won't do me much good In prlson.
You can go anywhere.
You can do anythlng. Thlnk about It.
You can have any future that you want.
Jack.
Elghty mllllon.
And all you've got to do...
...ls let hlm go.
That's a hell of an offer.
What do you thlnk, l'ed?
Would you take that deal?
It's Hank.
How about It, Hank?
Should I let you go?
My name Is ASAc Schrader.
And you can go fuck yourself.
Hank, llsten to me.
You gotta tell hlm.
You gotta tell hlm now
that we can work thls out.
Please. Please.
What? You want me to beg?
You're the smartest guy I ever met.
And you're too stupld to see...
...he made up hls mlnd
10 mlnutes ago.
Do what you're gonna do.
Pretty specll'lc dlrectlons.
Most people tell me to be somewhere,
they say, 'West on the 40...
...thls or that exlt, second gas statlon
on the lett.‘ You know?
Thls here? Thls Is a whole other story.
Yeah.
Look at thls.
They even brought a shovel.
Jack, no slgn ol' Plnkman.
All rlght.
Says thls Is It rlght here.
What's that? A barrel?
Couple barrels?
-Jesus.
-Hell, yeah!
Oh, Jesus. Would you look at that?
-Goddamn.
What are you waltlng l'or?
Yeah, boss. Hell, yeah.
-Let me get on thls slde.
-Get that out of there, man.
Okay. Pull a barrel off the truck
and load It In the Chrysler.
-Serlously?
-Jack.
That's llke 10 or 11 mllllon rlght there.
You sure you wanna do that?
You gonna make me say It agaln?
Go, go. Chop, chop.
Jesus, what's wlth all the greed here?
It's unattractlve.
Hey.
I'm leavlng you a barrel.
Boys are gonna load It for you.
You got the keys to these cuffs?
I'm sorry for your loss.
My nephew here, he respects you.
He would never l'orglve me
It thlngs went another way.
Also you caught me In a good mood.
So here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna get In your car...
...and you're gonna drlve out of here,
all rlght?
No hard l'eellngs.
Understand me?
We square?
Hey, man, I gotta know we're square,
or we're gonna have to go the other way.
Plnkman.
You stlll owe me.
It you can l'lnd hlm, we'll klll hlm.
Found hlm.
Get off me!
Get off!
Good to go?
Hey, Uncle Jack.
Well, he was out here wlth those l'eds.
nght? Worklng wlth them. Should we
maybe l'lnd out what he told them l'lrst?
Because, I mean, he had
to have told them some stuff...
...that mlght not be too good for us.
And I'll bet we could
get It out of hlm back home.
I mean, I can do It.
Me and hlm, we got hlstory.
And then, you know,
we'd take care of the Job after that.
Works for me. Work for you?
-Let's go, pal.
-No.
Walt.
I watched Jane dle.
l was there.
And I watched her dle.
I watched her overdose
and choke to death.
I could have saved her.
But I dldn't.
That truck belong to you?
It does.
I'd llke to buy It.
It's not for sale.
Hey, Walt, It's me.
Just thought I'd try you agaln.
We were Just wonderlng
when you thought you'd be back...
...so Just glve us a call
whenever you can.
Bye.
Hey, Aunt Marle.
Hey, sweetle.
Haven't seen you for a whlle.
What have you been up to?
Oh, you know. Thls and that.
Your mom and I need to talk,
so thought I'd stop by.
Well, I wlsh you'd called l'lrst.
Thls Isn't the best tlme.
Well, Flynn looks llke
he can hold down the tort.
Why don't we go Into your ofï¬ce?
I got lt.
Okay, honey. Thanks.
-Marle, l have nothlng to say.
-Well, I do.
So you can Just slt there and llsten.
I got a call from Hank.
He arrested Walt three hours ago.
It's over.
'Dead to rlghts'
l belleve Is the expresslon.
Hank and Steve Gomez are worklng
wlth a former assoclate ol' Walt's...
...Jesse Plnkman,
whom I know you know...
...and Plnkman has supplled them
wlth everythlng they need.
Hank ls booklng Walt as we speak.
And I, for one, could not be happler.
I almost dldn't come here.
Chrlst, I barely even know
who you are...
...and I sure as hell don't know
II' I can ever trust you agaln.
And then I thlnk about
how you were so upset wlth Walt...
...and how you wanted
the klds out of the house...
...and all of thls makes me belleve
that there has got to be hope for you...
...that whatever he dld to you
can be undone.
All I know, all I have been
I'orclng myself to remember...
...Is that you are my slster.
And so I'm here.
-Marle--
-Everythlng changes now.
And you have got to prepare yourself.
Hank wlll help you as much as he can.
I know he wlll.
And I wlll support you through thls.
But I have condltlons.
lee me every slngle copy
of that obscenlty...
...that the two of you made
to dlscredlt Hank. That DVD.
Every slngle copy.
You understand me?
Answer me. Do you understand me?
Yes.
Now dry your eyes
and get Flynn In here.
You are golng to tell hlm everythlng,
and I mean everythlng.
He deserves to know
the truth from hls I'amlly.
-Not a bunch of unll'ormed strangers.
-No. No. No, he cannot know.
You tell hlm, or I wlll.
There's no way around thls.
He needs to know,
and he needs to know now.
Look, I gave you what you wanted.
Come on, please.
Hey, please.
-I told you where to I'lnd the tape, okay?
-Yup.
Hey, Just go.
Just go there.
Just go to hls house and get It.
-We're on It.
-Get It!
No one else knows about It.
Just me and hls partner.
-0kay.
-No one else knows, I swear!
Let's cook.
You're completely out of your mlnd.
-lt's the truth.
-It Is, Flynn.
Then both of you
are out of your mlnds.
You're full of shlt, Is what you are.
Both of you.
II' thls ls true, then how could you
keep thls a secret?
I mean, why?
Why would you go along?
I'll be asklng myself that
for the rest of my llI'e.
So you're saylng all thls tlme
you were lylng about thls?
I mean, so you're saylng you're a llar.
You Just admltted It.
So were you lylng then,
or are you lylng now?
Whlch He Is It?
Flynn, honey, your mother
ls telllng you the truth.
nght here, rlght now. Belleve It.
You know what? Thls ls bullshlt.
Thls ls bullshlt.
-Baby--
-I wanna talk to Dad.
Your dad's In custody.
You can't talk to hlm tor a whlle.
-l'm calllng Uncle Hank.
-l've trled. He's not answerlng.
He's probably In the thlck of It
wlth your father.
Honey, I know thls Is a lot
to process, Flynn...
...but It you could Just breathe,
Just try to breathe...
-...and Just trust--
-Really? Really? Try to breathe?
Oh, my God.
Just take the klds home, okay?
Go home and regroup.
I'll stop by later.
Flynn?
Could you put
your seatbelt on, please?
Please. It's not safe.
You're shlttlng me, rlght?
It all thls ls true
and you knew about It...
...then you're as bad as hlm.
Whose truck Is that?
Dad?
Llsten, I need you to come lnslde
and pack rlght now.
Mom, Aunt Marle, they sald
that you were arrested?
-No, Just--
-You're some klnd of drug dealer?
No, Just come lnslde, please. Now.
Come lnslde. Come on.
-Dad, stop. Just talk to me, please.
-0ur prlorlty rlght now Is to pack.
-Uncle Hank, they sald he arrested you?
-I wlll dlscuss all of thls later, okay?
-Just tell me what--
-Just llsten to me!
Go Into your bedroom now,
grab anythlng Important.
You understand? Go. Now.
Both of you. Go.
Walt.
Why are you here?
Skyler, please,
wlll you Just go get your thlngs?
For you and the klds. Now.
Thls Is our prlorlty.
Hank had you In custody.
He wouldn't Just let you go.
-Where Is he?
.|..
-Where's Hank?
-l....
-l negotlated--
-Negotlated?
-Yes.
-What does that mean?
It means we're I'lne, okay?
We are. We're I'lne.
Everythlng ls gonna be I'lne...
...but we need to leave rlght now.
-All rlght? Can we do that?
-What happened?
Where Is Hank?
Why do we need to leave?
I need both of you to trust me.
nght now, okay?
Please, Just work wlth me here...
...and l promlse l wlll explaln
everythlng later, okay?
Where Is Hank?
Skyler.
l have $11 mllllon In cash
rlght outslde.
We can have a fresh start.
Whole new llves.
All we have to do Is go.
We have to go rlght now.
That's all we have to do.
You kllled hlm.
You kllled Hank.
-What?
-No, no, no.
-You kllled hlm.
-No, no, no!
l trled to save hlm.
Uncle Hank ls dead? In
-It can't be true. It Just can't be true.
-Just stop, please.
Everythlng ls gonna be okay.
Everythlng's gonna be I'lne, l promlse,
but we need to leave rlght now.
Dad, what's golng on? Talk to me.
Just stop for one second.
-Look, I told you to get your thlngs.
-Stop walklng away.
-There Is no tlme.
-Tell me about Uncle Hank.
-No, Just drop ltl
-But what's wrong wlth you?
-We're golng. We're golng rlght now.
-You have to tell me. Dad, walt.
What happened to Uncle Hank?
What--?
Get out.
Skyler, l promlse you,
we wlll I'lgure thls out.
-Enough.
-Mom, what are you dolng?
Skyler, put the knll'e down, please.
-l promlse you, everythlng--
-Don't say one more word.
Get out of here now.
Skyler--
Get out!
Stop It! Just stopl Just stopl
-Let go! Let go!
-Get away from us!
Just stopl Stopl
Dad, stop It! Stopl
Mom, stop It.
Stop, Dad. Stop It now. Stop.
Stopl Just, please, stop!
Stop It! Stopl Stop It!
What the hell ls wrong wlth you?!
We're a I'amllyl
We're a I'amlly.
What are you dolng?
Yeah, I need the pollce.
My dad, he pulled a knll'e on my mom.
He attacked her. He's dangerous.
lthlnk he mlght have kllled somebody.
Yeah.
He's stlll here.
Yeah, he's stlll In the house.
We're at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane.
308 Negra Arroyo Lanel
You've gotta come qulck.
Hurry, hurry. Oh, God, no, no!
Oh, my God. No.
-Walt, nol Waltl
-Moml
Walt, please, no!
Walt, nol Let her go!
You can't take her!
Let her go, please! You can't take her!
Let her go! Waltl
Walt, please, no!
Walt, nol Walt, pleasel
Walt, nol
Walt, please, no!
Walt, pleasel
Please, stop! Waltl
Say, 'Da-da.'
Da-da. You say, 'Da-da'?
There. Get rld of that
stlnky old dlaper, huh?
Don't be sad.
Where's your belly button?
There. Now, don't you feel better?
You're all nlce and dry.
That feels good? Oh, I know.
You were so wet and so cranky,
but now you feel better, don't you?
Next order of buslness
Is to get you a brand-new car seat.
Won't that be nlce, Holly?
ConI'lrmlng the abductlon.
Amber Alert. Holly Whlte.
Female, 18 months.
Blond halr, blue eyes.
Was last seen wearlng
a plnk and whlte Jacket, plnk pants.
Abductor Is the I'ather....
He was In handcuffs.
Hank had hlm In handcuffs.
Bald head, goatee,
gold, wlre-framed glasses.
Are you expectlng a call?
HI, you've reached the Whlte famlly.
Please leave a message.
Skyler, It's me. Plck up. Plck up.
-That's hlm. That's my husband.
-I need you to plck up the phone.
Start a trace on the landllne.
-The number's 505-177-8987.
-I know you're there, so plck It up.
Skyler, you hear me?
-Need the locatlon of an lncomlng caller.
-Answer the pho--
Walt, where's Holly?
Are you alone?
No pollce?
Where are you? Where's Holly?
-WaltI
-What the hell ls wrong wlth you?
Why can't you do one thlng I say?
-What?
-Thls Is your fault.
Thls Is what comes of your dlsrespect.
I told you, Skyler.
I warned you for a solld year.
You cross me,
there wlll be consequences.
What part of that
dldn't you understand?
You took my chlld.
Because you need to learn.
You brlng her back.
Maybe now you'll llsten.
Maybe now you'll use your damn head.
You know, you never belleved In me.
You were never grateful
for anythlng l dld for thls famlly.
"Oh, no. Walt. Walt, you have to stop.
You have to stop thls.
It's Immoral. It's Illegal.
Someone mlght get hurt. "
You're always whlnlng and complalnlng
about howl make my money...
...just dragglng me down,
whlle I do everythlng.
And now--
Now you tell my son what I do...
...after I've told you and told you
to keep your damn mouth shut.
You stupld bltch.
How dare you?
I'm sorry.
You have no rlght...
...to dlscuss anythlng about what I do.
What the hell do you know
about It anyway?
Nothlng. lbullt thls.
Me. Me alone. Nobody elsel
You're rlght.
You mark my words, Skyler.
Toe the llne...
...or you wlll wlnd up Just llke Hank.
Walt.
Tell me what happened.
Where Is Hank?
Please.
We need to know.
You're never gonna see Hank agaln.
He crossed me.
You thlnk about that.
Famlly or no.
You let that slnk In.
Walt.
I just want Holly back.
Please, Walt.
Just come home.
I've stlll got thlngs left to do.
Hey.