[WIND WHISTLING]
[MOTORCYCLE REWING]
[TRAIN HORN BLARES IN DISTANCE]
[J'J'J']
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hay, man, look at the sad lack
I found moplng around the lobby.
Hay. Ha, ha.
HANK: Ho, hey, thorn, Walt.
How you dolng, buddy?
Good.
Lllten, I'm sorry to drop In on you
out of the blue.
No, no, no.
If It's a bad tlmo, I could--
No. I'm Just klnd ol' uttllng
Into the now dlg: here.
What do you thlnk, huh?
Wow. It I: very nlco.
Yoah. Congratulatlon: agaln.
Yoah.
We're all very proud of you.
Oh, well, thanks.
My day: of chaelng dlrt-balle I: over.
But I'll tell you what, belng a boss,
own klnd ol' grlnd,
you know what I'm aaylng?
Uh, steve, would you mlnd If...
I've gotta run aomethlng by Hank,
It It's all rlght.
Yeah. Yeah, hey, aomebody'a
gotta go chase the bad guys.
Walt, It's a pleasure aeelng you agaln.
Thanka agaln, steve.
Appreclate lt.
Sure.
Hey. Look
at that.
Jeaua, Walt.
0h.
That'a nlce. Let me see that.
Yeah.
Wow, that's beautll'ul.
Was It a blrthday preaent?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, not really.
I bought It for myself.
0h.
Hey, well, have a seat.
Thanka.
Unh. New car, new watch.
Ah. Good for you.
Wlth all the curveballa
that were thrown at you thla year,
you deserve to treat yourself.
Ha, ha.
I mean, as long as you got
the money to spend, that la.
So how'a Sky?
Actually, she went to work
thla mornlng.
She wanted to.
She aald she needed to, you know,
keep her mlnd occupled, and...
That's good. Great, actually.
Yeah.
I mean, as long as you're all rlght
wlth her belng on her own and stuff.
Yeah, well, you know,
I'm rlght there wlth her
moat ol' the tlme.
And Marlano klnd ol' keep: an eye
on her when I'm not, so...
Good.
Yeah.
And what about the whole Idea
of talklng to somebody?
You know, Marle goes off about Dave
llke he's a rock star ahrlnk, you know?
They come In llke zomblea, out
llke larka, you know what I'm aaylng?
That's great. Actually,
she already found someone.
Yeah. Peter...
Um...
Hm. I don't know why
I'm drawlng a blank
on hla last name. Peter...
Anyway, he's out In Rlo Rancho.
He'a supposed to be top-notch.
Good, good. I'm glad you're
on It. That's not aomethlng
you wanna let teeter.
No. No, you don't. You don't.
Um... Hank, IJuat, uh...
I wanted to thank you and Marle
l'or watchlng the klda.
Oh.
No, lt'a-- It really la--
No, It's nlce of you,
and I'd llke to come by tonlght
and see them, If that's all rlght.
Of course. What do you mean?
You don't have to ask that.
It's great havlng them.
They're great klda.
l appreclate that.
Somethlng else
on your mlnd there, Walt?
Walt, feel free to,
you know, ahem...
[VOICE BREAKING]
Skyler doesn't love me anymore.
And I don't know what to do,
Hank. I don't.
She says that I'm
a bad Influence on the klda
and, uh, that I'm not...
Not good for them.
Aw, Jeez, Walt.
No. Uh--
She thlnka I'm a bad I'ather.
I'm sorry.
Hey, I mean, Sky and you
got your Iaauea,
but, uh, that there, that's...
That'a...
I'm not an expert on parentlng or
anythlng, but from where I'm alttlng,
IJuat don't see It, you know?
lthlnk you're great wlth the klda.
You're a provlder,
a role model, you know?
Hell, the gut: you showed
golng toe-to-toe wlth cancer,
that alone, that's an Inaplratlon
to me, you know?
No, I've made mlatakea, you know?
Yeah. Uh, yeah, I know.
Llaten, I'm gonna get a coffee.
You want a coffee?
Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
I'm gonna have a cup of coffee.
I'm gonna glve you a moment
to Just get It together there. Um...
You want, uh,
cream and sugar?
Yeah, yeah. Hank, I'm sorry.
That-- Cup of coffee, rlght?
All rlght.
Just take a moment.
Take a moment.
[SNIFFLES THEN SIGHS]
[J'J'J']
You know, you two
are really great together.
Take It from me, buddy,
It's always darkeat
Just before the dawn.
Yeah.
[J'J'J']
What Ia thla place? What Ia thla place?
What are we dolng here?
MIKE: Get me the table.
LYDIA: I can't be here.
My daughter, my llttle glrl,
she's gonna be home soon.
What? What are you dolng?
Mlke, Mlke, Mlke...
MIKE: Shut up!
lee me her phone.
All rlght, Lydla.
My frlenda here don't know you
llke I do
so they are very klndly
glvlng you one last chance.
There's your acrlpt. Study It.
In about 30 seconds, I'm gonna dlal
Agent Schrader on your llne here
and you're gonna pass along
thla lnformatlon
and then we'll see what we see.
But here are the rules:
If you yell for help, try to glve the man
aome klnd of coded meaaage
or otherwlae tlp hlm off,
I am gonna pull out my platol
and shoot you In the head.
Same goes for panlcklng,
breaklng down Into teara.
Remember how
you llke to do that?
If It happens thla tlme,
I am golng to pull my platol out,
and I am golng to shoot you
In the head.
Look at me, not at them.
Lydla, look at me.
If you make Schrader auaplcloua
In any way,
any way at all,
tell me what's gonna happen next.
You'll pull out your gun and shoot me.
And where wlll I shoot you?
In the head.
In the head. That'a rlght.
And It's a platol, not a gun.
I'm expectlng preclalon here.
We up and runnlng?
Yeah, um... Computer's aet.
MIKE:
Okay, Lydla.
If you ever needed to glve
the performance of a llfetlme,
It's now.
[LINE RINGING]
You're up.
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]:
ASAC': ofﬁce.
HI. Lydla Rodarte-Quayle
calllng for Agent Schrader.
I'm sorry. What's thls regardlng?
Madrlgal Electromotlve.
Lydla. Rodarte. Quayle.
Hank, Lydla Rodarte-Quayle
on llne one.
Hank Schrader.
How can I help you, Me. Quayle?
Well, thla Ia klnd of an odd, uh...
It's Just that l was In our warehouse,
aupervlalng a ahlpment of chemlcala
when l notlced a devlce on the bottom
of one of our barrel: of methylamlne.
A devlce?
Yeah. I guess you'd call It that. I mean,
I'm certalnly no expert,
but It looks to me llke aome klnd of a...
A tracklng devlce or a GPS.
So l was Juat wonderlng
If maybe your people put It there.
Not that It's any of my bualneaa, but
the last thlng I wanna do Ia Interfere
wlth a law enforcement operatlon
or a atlng,
or whatever you call It.
So, I don't know,
maybe you could
glve me some guldance?
Uh, well, I'll tell you what.
Set that barrel aalde for me,
If you would,
and I'll look Into It
and get back to you.
And In the meantlme,
mum'a the word, all rlght?
Yeah. All rlght. Sure thlng.
Okay, great.
Thanks for the call, Ma. Quayle.
Bye-bye.
Hey, Gomey, come here, would you?
Yeah?
Hey, man.
HANK [OVER COMPUTER]:
You know anythlng about GPS trackers
on a methylamlne barrel?
Madrlgal Houston, I'm talklng about.
GOMEZ:
Nope. Nobody from my team
planted anythlng, Why?
HANK:
Oh, I don't know. I ﬁgured as much.
All rlght. Thanks.
I know what you're thlnklng,
but I dldn't do It.
I'm telllng you, I dldn't plant that thlng.
Shut up.
And there you have It, llke l sald.
All rlght. So now what?
It's not the DEA's, so Schrader's
probably thlnklng some crew planted It,
looklng for a weak spot
to pull a helst.
He's gonna send a team
over to that warehouse.
He's gonna wlre It out the wazoo.
Bugs, cameras, the whole nlne yards.
So the warehouse Is too hot.
Her supply Is useless to us now.
It depends on how fast Schrader
can get hls guys there.
We're 900 mlles closer, after all.
I say we keep llstenlng,
suss out how much tlme we have.
If It's at least 12 hours,
then we head down there,
use her securlty code
to galn access,
and we take every barrel we can.
U-Haul can only take
slx or seven before
the suspenslon glves out.
It's a stopgap. But rlght now,
It's the best we can do.
[WHISPERING]
Well, what about her?
MIKE:
You two drlve the
barrels back tonlght.
I'll deal wlth her.
No! No, no, no.
You're maklng a mlstake.
Thls was not me!
I swear to God I dldn't do It!
I don't know. Sounds llke
she's telllng the truth to me.
She has a gun to her head, kld.
Everyone sounds llke Meryl Streep
wlth a gun to thelr head.
I'm sorry, Jesse.
You're the one who wanted
to put It up to a vote.
It's two agalnst one.
No. No! You can't klll me!
Come on!
I swear I dldn't do anythlngI
HANK:
JanIce, glve me Doughty
In the Houston ofI'Ice, wIII you?
JANICE:
You got It.
Hank Schrader for Mr. Doughty.
He's on the flue.
HANK:
Hey, Erol. Please tell me you guys
dldn't do somethIng as IamebraIned
as put a GPS tracker on the outsIde
of a barrel of methylamlne.
One earmarked for the
Madrlgal warehouse In Houston?
EROL:
Um... Who's askIng?
DId someone ﬁnd them?
HANK:
Jesus. Are you shIttIng me?
SInce when do you put a GPS tracker
on the outsIde ofa barrel?
EROL:
We dldn't have tlme to go In
wlth hazard suIts, Hank.
They were about to shIp.
We epoxIed them to the bottom.
They were well-hldden.
HANK:
Oh, really? Well, not well-hldden
enough. How many barrels you tag?
EROL:
All of them. All the ones
headed to the warehouse, anyway.
HANK:
ChrIst. All rlght. Well, sIt tIght.
Let me ﬁgure out how to play thIs.
Next tlme, a "ﬁle communIcatIon ﬁrst,
all rlght?
EROL: Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
Asshole.
Aslde-- Aslde from the fact
that we almost kllled thls woman,
all of those barrels are already marked.
We solve the problem we can.
Thls has not changed the equatlon
one Iota for her.
Oh, come on! You are not serlously
stlll conslderlng kllllng me?
I saved you! If It weren't for me,
we'd all be In ]all rlght now.
I hate to say It,
but she's rlght, Mlke.
She saved our asses
by flndlng that thlng.
She Is savlng herself.
She's a loose cannon.
lam telllng you, she wlll
turn a gun or a badge on us
the flrst chance she gets.
The woman put a hlt out on me.
Serlously?
Walt. A hlt? What? lee the mafla?
Yeah, llke the mafla.
Hey! You stlll need methylamlne,
don't you? nght?
You wanna talk methylamlne?
Then tell your partner to stop
threatenlng me, and let's talk.
Talk about what? You heard.
You can't even get us
a slngle barrel.
Who sald anythlng about barrels?
I'm talklng about an ocean
of the stuff.
Just glve hlm a mlnute,
would you?
Trust hlm.
'Trust hlm.'
[MIKE OHUOKLES]
WALT:
Okay. So, let's hear It.
Not wlthout a guarantee that once
I tell you how to get what you want,
I won't be kllled anyway.
Flne. You have my word.
Not good enough.
Ha. Look, lady--
Do you have chlldren?
That has nothlng to do wlth thls.
It's not a trlck questlon.
Why don't you Just answer It?
Yes, I have chlldren. So what?
You thlnk that somehow
because we're both parents
that I won't let my partner
do what's necessary?
Swear on thelr llves.
Uh, what?
Swear on your chlldren's llves
that I won't be harmed.
Otherwlse, how can I trust you?
Look, you're
a smart buslnesswoman.
You understand the concept
of leverage.
Please don't patronlse me. I hate that.
You have none.
But trust has to work
both ways, Lydla.
Is It true that you
put a hlt out on Mlke?
Yes.
Why?
l was scared.
Of Mlke?
Not at flrst.
There are men who used to work
wlth Gus Frlng In custody now.
Nlne of them. They know
everythlng about me. Everythlng.
Some of them even know about you,
assumlng you're the master chemlst
they're always talklng about.
And If It's these nlne
that you're worrled about,
why put the hlt on Mlke?
I had no cholce.
I'm not golng to prlson and have
my daughter ralsed In a group home.
Do you have any Idea
what those places are llke?
I gave hlm a llst of names
but Instead of handllng It,
he's protectlng them.
So I hlred someone else.
At that polnt, there was no optlon
but to add Mlke to the llst.
Thls ocean of methylamlne
that you clalm
you can get your hands on,
how much are we
talklng about, llterally?
How does 24,000 gallons sound?
Once a week, on a Wednesday,
a frelght traln leaves
the Port of Long Beach
loaded wlth Industrlal chemlcals.
There's always at least one tanker car
full of methylamlne
whlch we Import from
a manufacturer In Guangzhou.
The traln travels east
through Arlzona,
stops at a rall yard
outsIde Flagstaff
where It gets broken down
and rebullt. But the methylamlne
always moves on,
destlned for our pestlclde concerns
In Texas and Oklahoma.
Whlch means that It passes
rlght through your home state.
There's a remote three-mlle stretch
here In McKInley County.
That's where you do It.
That's where we
do what exactly?
Get your methylamlne.
lee, rob It? lee Jesse James?
LYDIA: You want the stuff?
I'm offerlng you enough
to flll a swlmmlng pool.
You are offerlng us a qulck trlp
to prlson. That's what I'm hearlng.
Stopplng a traln, post 9I11?
You have any Idea how many alarms
that'll set off between here and D.C.?
None, If you do It rlght here.
If a frelght traln Is stopped In translt,
anywhere other than
the usual yards or depots,
absolutely, a slgnal wlll alarm
the FRA and the TSA Surface Dlvlslon
at the Department of Homeland
Securlty. But what you don't know,
and I do, because my ]ob requlres me
to keep track of my buyers' shlpments,
thls Is dark terrltory.
What's that?
LYDIA: Traln-speak for an area
of no contact.
It's a dead zone.
No automated supervlslon system,
no alarms, no contact wlth control.
What about cell phones?
Crew could Just call the cops.
LYDIA: No cellular elther.
I'm telllng you,
It's the perfect place.
You'd have tlme enough
to stop the traln,
slphon off as much methylamlne
as you can carry,
get away before the pollce are called.
Walt a mlnute. Walt a mlnute.
Assumlng we can stop
a movlng traln,
how do we know we have the rlght
one? And whlch tanker car Is whlch?
I can't belleve that they would
advertlse thelr contents.
Once the traln
gets rebullt In Flagstaff,
a flnal manlfest gets uploaded
to my company's server.
I'll have It for you sometlme
between mldnlght and 2 am.
That'll glve you at least
slx hours of lead tlme.
Keep In mlnd, I'm taklng a huge rlsk
supplylng thls lnformatlon.
I expect to be pald.
Heh.
We can talk percentages later.
MIKE:
You know what thls means,
don't you?
We've gotta off the crew.
How do you flgure?
If we don't, the englneer's
gonna call the cops
as soon as he gets out of the
dead zone. It's only three mlles long.
We're way out In the boonles.
I don't care If It's In the Gobl Desert.
Once they get word,
the FBI and Homeland Securlty
are gonna swoop down wlth choppers
on us so fast, It'll make our heads spln.
And there Is no hldlng
In that open country.
How many In the crew?
Just two. An englneer and a conductor.
MIKE:
Assumlng there are
no securlty guards.
No guards. It's not llke
we're carrylng nuclear warheads.
Walt. Two guys.
Can't we ]ust tle them up
or somethIng?
And then what? Even If we
wear a mask, we're leavlng
two wltnesses behlnd.
Bottom llne, l have done thls
long enough to know
that there are two klnds of helsts:
Those where the guys
get away wlth It,
and those that leave wltnesses.
[LYDIA SOOFFS]
lee me a break. You guys
were gonna murder me.
I thought
you were professlonals.
Can you say 'ASAC'?
'ASAC.' Can you say that?
Say, 'ASAC Schrader.'
If those turn out to be her flrst words,
I wlll beat you wlth my shoe.
Don't llsten to hlm, Holly.
Aw, I'm Just telllng It llke It Is, babe.
Boss man.
I'm the boss man.
Say, 'Boss man.'
Am I the boss man? I'm the boss.
Hey, that better be somethIng from
a boob Instead of some fake soy crap.
Yeah, yeah.
My llttle glrl
Your llttle glrl.
deserves the real McCoy.
[CRYING]
Oh. No. See?
Okay.
She doesn't want It.
No, she wants me.
She wants me.
Yeah, my llttle glrl,
because I'm not glvlng her back.
Yeah, I know.
What about Emo McGee?
Has he come out
of hls room today?
Barely.
When he does,
he barely talks.
Yeah, well, what do you expect,
you know?
Hls parents treat hlm
llke he's a baby there.
[HOLLY OOOING]
[FRIDGE DOOR OPENS
THEN CLOSES]
Flynn, do you want me to
heat up some of that lasagne
to hold you over tlll dlnner?
Hey, I plcked up Heat on Blu-ray.
Wanna watch It wlth me later?
No. And you can keep
talklng about me now.
[noon CLOSES]
MIKE:
Well, If no one else Is gonna
offer an oplnlon, lwlll.
We do It the old-fashloned way.
We hlt skld row, the Crystal Palace,
all the halfway houses,
scrounge up about
a dozen skells, put them
to work smurflng cold pllls.
You mean swltch back
to a pseudo cook.
You're the chemlst. Admlttedly,
It's gonna cut down on our output.
lee a factor of four or flve.
It also means
that we wlll eat $00,000
we ]ust Invested
In our new lab equlpment
whlch Is only good
for a P2P cook.
You know, I don't have to do
the math to know
that we'd be maklng
a fractlon of the proflt.
And maklng less money
Is better than maklng nothlng.
Oh, yeah, Mlke? Well,
why don't you tell us why?
Why Is maklng nothlng
not an optlon?
Walter--
Let me tell you why.
It's because of your nlne guys
In lockup, rlght?
You broke It, you pay for It.
And we've talked about thls
plenty already.
Well, maybe we better
talk about It a llttle more
because what It sounds llke
you're telllng me, Mlke, Is that
from now on
we have no cholce but to
do thls plddllng pseudo cook
so that we can pay back
your guys.
Or else what? Or else they're
gonna rat on us, and we
end up In prlson.
Yeah? And It sounds llke
what you're telllng me, Walter,
Is that you wanna
do thls helst,
even If It means kllllng
a couple of Innocent men.
That what you want?
Heh.
You know, I don't know why
you Inslst on puttlng words
In my mouth here.
What If we can rlp off that traln,
and no one ever knows It got robbed?
[WIND WHISTLING]
Maybe.
Just maybe.
[OAR DOOR CLOSES]
It'll come from that dlrectlon.
Seven seventy-flve.
Elght hundred.
[JESSE OHUOKLING]
Oh. Elght fourteen.
Wow. Walt a mlnute.
It's perfect.
Yeah, we do It here.
We do It rlght here.
How are we looklng, Mlke?
All clear.
WALT:
Copy that.
Go down, go down.
You got It. That's good, Fernando.
[TRUCK BEEPING]
Hey.
Thls one.
nght.
JESSE: You good?
Yeah.
What's your name agaln?
Todd.
Todd, on the day, are you
gonna be able to make thls cllmb?
Yes, slr.
I'll be ready.
All rlght.
You mlnd If I ask you a questlon?
WALT: No. Go ahead.
Well, I get why we want the tank
for the methylamlne.
But why thls other one
for the water?
Well...
Jesse, It's your Idea.
You wanna flll hlm In?
It's all about the welght, yo.
The tanker we're gonna hlt
gets welghed when It
gets loaded In Long Beach
and then agaln
when It's unloaded In Texas.
If the welghts don't match,
the traln company's
gonna know It got robbed.
Okay.
JESSE:
Boostlng methylamlne from a traln
ls, llke, a major rap.
The polnt Is, no one other than us can
ever know that thls robbery went down.
Nobody. You got It?
Yeah. Absolutely.
Are you sure?
Yes, slr.
JESSE:
Wlth all that sald,
the whole thlng relles on us
replaclng the welght of
methylamlne we steal wlth
the same welght In water.
TODD:
So they'll never know
we hlt them. Cool.
Aqueous methylamlne Is water-based,
yet It welghs sllghtly less than water.
We wlll be removlng
a thousand gallons of methylamlne
from the tanker car
but replaclng It wlth about
nlne-tenths of that volume In water
whlch comes to 900.24 gallons.
Actually, Jesse,
let's make that an even 920
to account for splllage and
whatever wlll remaln In the hose.
Yeah.
How we dolng, by the way?
Uh, elght flfty. We're almost there.
All rlght.
Won't they flgure they got robbed,
gettlng watered-down methylamlne?
Well, out of 24,000 gallons,
It'll only amount to about
four percent dllutlon, so...
But, yes, you're rlght.
They wlll notlce.
At whlch polnt,
they wlll blame Chlna
for sendlng
a marglnally weaker batch.
Damn, you guys thought
of everythlng.
SKYLER:
Flynn.
Flynn, open the door.
Just come out and talk to me.
WALT JR.:
I'm staylng. That's all I have to say.
What's golng on?
You got what you wanted, that's what.
Congratulatlons.
It's me. Open up.
Come on, Junlor.
I'm not gonna ask twlce.
What?
You know what.
Are you serlously klcklng me out
of my own house?
Are you serlously dolng that?
We are not klcklng you
out of anywhere, son.
We love you. And thls Is your house
as much as It Is ours.
But your mom and I need some tlme
alone, and you know that.
We explalned that to you.
You haven't explalned ]ack shlt.
You want me out?
Explaln to me why.
Why do I have to go
to Uncle Hank's?
lee me the exact reason
or I'm not golng anywhere.
Thls Is not gonna be a debate.
What's golng on?
Why can't anybody tell me anythlng?
I want one good reason.
Because we're your parents
and you're our chlld.
That's reason enough.
Now, please, do as I ask.
It'll pass. He'll understand.
Don't start, Walt.
I won't change my mlnd
about you.
Even
Well, I don't accept that.
You're my wlfe.
I'm not your wlfe,
I'm your hostage.
But slnce you Inslst
on keeplng me lmprlsoned,
I'll make you a deal.
lwlll launder your money,
I'll keep your secrets
but the klds wlll stay
at Hank and Marle's
where they have
a chance of belng safe.
lthlnk you've seen
too many movles.
Our chlldren
are not In danger.
Just a couple of days ago,
you told me that a man
held a gun to your head.
You sald It llke It
was a polnt of prlde.
There's nothlng you can say
that'll convlnce me
there won't come a day that
somebody wlll knock on that door,
looklng to harm you or me
or all of us.
And when that day comes,
the chlldren cannot be here.
You agree to that,
and l wlll be whatever klnd of
partner you want me to be.
Okay.
By the way,
you're vlsltlng a theraplst
from Rlo Rancho. Peter.
Last name Is up to you.
SKYLER:
Out burylng bodles?
Robblng a traln.
[J'J'J']
[PHONE KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
WALT: Yeah?
It's me.
I've got It.
JESSE:
Okay, Mr. Whlte,
everythlng's set.
[TRAIN HORN BLARING
IN DISTANCE]
[J'J'J']
[TRAIN HORN BLARING
IN DISTANCE]
[J'J'J']
Hey, WallaceI Up aheadI
KUBY:
Stop the traln nowI
[HORN BLARING]
StopI
Stop the tralnI
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
[BELL RINGING]
[J'J'J']
Jesus. Thank God you guys
weren't asleep at the swltch.
It'd be llke pancake clty out here.
Aw, man.
Hey, you belleve thls?
I mean, shlt flre
and save the matches.
Talk about bum luck.
Hey, man, I'm sorry to
put you guys out llke thls.
What's the trouble wlth It?
No clue. I was ]ust drlvlng
down the road.
All of a sudden, the old cow
]ust bellled up and dled on me.
Elther one of you guys know about
englnes? Oh, of course you do.
That's why they call you
an englneer, rlght?
All rlght.
Thlnk It's, uh...
Thlnk It's In there
or somethIng.
You thlnk?
Yeah.
Probably a pretty good bet.
When was the last tlme
you changed the oll?
I don't know, man.
l]ust drlve It.
Now. Go, go, go.
We're on.
[J'J'J']
[GRUNTS]
[TOOL WHIRRING]
[snuurmc]
Good?
Yeah.
[LIQUID FLOWING]
ENGINEER:
It looks good up here.
Now, hold up. There It Is.
lthlnk thls Is the one.
CONDUCTOR: We good?
ENGINEER: Yeah.
Hey, you wanna get In there,
glve It a whlrl?
All rlght,
let me glve It a try.
[J'J'J']
Ready?
Ready.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Nothlng?
Try agaln.
Nothlng.
All rlght. Uh...
Maybe If
we all pushed?
All rlght. It's worth a try.
Any other Ideas,
you Just shout them out.
Not at the moment,
I don't.
You comlng?
So far, so good.
lee me a status.
We're at 300 gallons
and countlng.
Water Is golng...
[PUMP WHIRRING]
Water's golng In now.
We're golng wlth water now.
[LIQUID SLOSHING]
Good?
Yeah.
All rlght.
One, two, three.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
You dld remember
to put It In neutral, rlght?
Yeah, man. lee me a llttle credlt.
Uh-oh.
You sure you're not
out of gas?
I got a full tank here.
ENGINEER:
Thls doesn't make any sense.
Everythlng looks good.
Oh.
CONDUCTOR:
Why don't we Just keep golng over It?
There's gotta be
somethIng loose somewhere.
Damn, buddy. Plcked a hell
of a place to break down.
I know, rlght? Crazy.
Hey, you know anythlng
about englnes?
Not a whole lot. I can push you off
the tracks at least.
Oh, gee, I wouldn't want you
to mess up your rlde.
I'll go slow. Won't get a scratch.
You'll screw up
your nlce shlny bumper.
Hey.
We're runnlng late because of you.
The man sald It was no problem.
Come on already.
And thank you, by the way.
Yeah, yeah. Absolutely, pal.
Thanks.
[J'J'J']
Jesus. Walter, we've got
a Good Samarltan on the scene.
You pull your guys
off that traln rlght now.
We're not done yet.
The track Is clear, Walter.
l sald get out of there.
Thank you, mlster. Much obllged.
Glad we could work that out for you.
Yeah, no problem.
You want a rlde Into town?
KUBY:
Yeah. Yeah. Thanks.
Walter, they are back
In the locomotlve.
If you do not abort rlght now,
you are gonna get us a" busted.
[J'J'J']
Ready?
Yeah.
[BELL RINGING
THEN HORN BLARES]
Mr. WhlteI
HeyI
Hold ItI Hold It steadyI
Close It of" Close It offI
[BELL RINGING]
WALT:
ToddI Get of" Get off!
[PANTING]
[WALT LAUGHING]
Oh...
Yeah, bltchI
Oh.
We dld It.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, my...
WALT: Okay, okay. Nlce ]ob.
JESSE: YeahI Oh.
[WHIRRING STOPS]
[LAUGHS]
[MOTOR WHIRRING SOFTLY]
[J'J'J']