[J'J'J']
You guys dldn't tall me
thl: stuff smell: Ilka cat plu.
Man, shlt happens, huh?
Unhl
[J'J'J']
TODD:
l man, I'm sorry, but I had to do It.
Obvloully,
l guns: you no It dlﬂ'arant.
Somo of you.
But I dldn't no
any othor cholco.
l'vo bun thlnklng
about thla all day,
golng ovar It In my haad
and It was the only way.
JESSE: Huh.
Well, It's not Ilka l wantod to.
The kld was on a dlrt blko.
Ho could've Just--
Ho could've gunned It
and bun gono boforo m
even had a chance to bllnk.
We never would've caught hlm.
I thought on my feet. I saw a threat,
and I took care of It.
A threat?
The kld was wavlng at us.
He wasn't golng anywhere.
He was saylng hl.
Yeah, but you don't know that.
Yeah, I do.
He dIdn't know what he'd seen.
I dIdn't want to take that chance.
The whole polnt oI' thls
was no one was supposed
to know we were there.
People weren't supposed to
know anythlng got robbed.
How could we let
the kld go?
He made us.
II' I hadn't done what I dld,
the mlsslon would've I'alled.
I'm real sorry.
I really am, but I...
But dld I make a mlstake, Mr. Whlte?
Because to me, you know, respectl'ully,
l was looklng out for the team.
ldldn't want to klll hlm.
You gotta belleve that.
At the end of the day,
It was hlm or us,
and I chose us.
And I would do It agaln.
Okay, look, uh...
Todd, why don't you step
outslde tor a few mlnutes
so we can talk thls through.
Of course. Yeah, you guys talk.
But I Just want to make
sure that you know that
my prlorlty ls thls buslness.
Okay. That's ﬁne, Todd.
Thank you.
I want to be
a real part of thls.
All rlght? It you could Just
see that. I'm motlvated
and I've got connectlons.
My uncle's got hls hookups In prlson
who I thlnk could be a real help
to us It...
[noon SHUTS]
Okay. That dude? Wack Job.
Let's Just stlck to the facts here.
JESSE: Facts? Oh, okay.
How about the fact
that he shot a kld?
A kld that he dIdn't need
to shoot.
Well, the boy had seen us.
And, no, It dIdn't look llke
he knew what he was seelng.
But what II' he told somebody?
What II' he Just mentloned It
In passlng?
We can't know what someone--
Exactly. We can't know,
because Rlcky Hltler there shot hlm.
We, us three, should've had
a dlscusslon about It.
We would've I'lgured It out.
But that dlckhead Just went ahead
and made the cholce for us.
Is that how we do buslness now?
I understand you're upset.
And what was that crap about hls
uncle wlth the prlson connectlons?
It's Just some bullshlt
lntlmldatlon move. Come on.
It's true, though.
He does have some connectlons.
ls thls a problem?
No. It's nothlng to be concerned about.
It came up In the background
I dld on hlm.
Dldn't worry me then.
He's Just I'lexlng.
All rlght.
It seems to me that
we have three optlons here
and none of whlch are Ideal.
One, we I'lre Todd.
Yeah.
I'm not a fan of thls optlon,
seelng that he knows way too much
about thls buslness at thls polnt.
And we'd most llkely have to pay hlm
to keep qulet.
And God only knows
we've got enough of that golng on.
Two:
We dlspose oI' hlm.
Whlch leaves us optlon three.
We keep hlm on payroll.
Put hlm back on tentlng houses,
settlng up the lab and so forth.
We keep hlm close,
under our control.
Now, optlon three
would be my cholce.
Shall we vote?
MIKE:
I vote three, kld.
You're stlll In.
nght on. Thank you so much.
You guys totally made the rlght--
The next tlme you brlng a gun
to a Job wlthout telllng me,
lwlll stlck It up your ass sldeways.
You understand?
Yes, slr.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Hey, boss. What's up?
l was Just In the nelghbourhood.
Anythlng golng on?
No. He's Just hanglng out
wlth hls granddaughter.
Well, Isn't that sweet?
Here, let me see.
It's a dead drop.
AGENT: What?
GOMEZ: A dead drop.
He Just stashed somethlng
underneath that trash can.
erte the tlme down.
Roll on It.
Looks llke he's leavlng.
Anybody comlng for It?
Nope, not that I can see.
Nobody In slght.
Could be hours.
Could be.
What do you want to do?
HANK [ON RECORDING]:
It's not my fault that Martha's got
hls pantles In a twlst.
It's an HR Issue, Janlce.
[RECORDING FAST-FORWARDING]
I read the report.
I'm calllng agaln because that's
the wrong case ﬁle number.
All rlght? I don't know what klnd of
shoddy stan--
[RECORDING FAST-FORWARDING]
Flrst off, eracle Whlp
Is not mayonnalse, okay?
"Looks Ilke It" doesn't equal
"tastes Ilke It. "
Secondly, every tlme It's Ilke
they gotta slather an entlre jar--
[RECORDING FAST-FORWARDING]
--bastard's screwlng wlth us now.
How'd he make you? What'd you do?
GOMEZ:
We honked our horns
and yelled "yoo-hoo. "
What do you mean, what dld we do?
Thls guy Is sllppery as hell.
He's been throwlng every tall
we put on hlm.
The guy's a pro.
HANK:
Yeah, well,
even pros make mlstakes.
One of these days, our pal
Ehrmantraut's gonna sllp up.
Just gotta be there when he does.
Teenagers. Sometlmes you
Just want to strangle them. Heh.
How's It golng?
Oh, you know.
Well, thls llttle munchkln,
I could Just keep her forever.
She Is Just the sweetest
llttle baby ever born.
Yes, she ls.
Oh.
I don't see much of Flynn.
That car of hls keeps hlm
pretty busy.
Yeah.
More lmportantly,
how are you dolng?
I'm okay.
How's the therapy?
I know Dave helped me
so much when l was golng
through my llttle...
How's your guy? Um...
Peter.
He's, um-- Yeah, he's good.
ll'eel Ilke I'm maklng progress.
That's great.
You know,
you Just keep worklng through It.
[SKYLER WHIMPERING]
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
Honey. Babe, what Is It?
It's okay. It's all rlght.
Why don't you let me take Holly,
and then we'll talk about thls?
No.
Okay. All rlght, that's I'lne.
Then how about you Just talk to me?
Just tell me what's golng on.
IJust...
I need to make the rlght declslon.
I need them to be safe.
The klds?
They're sale. 01' course they are.
IJust mlss them so much.
IJust want to be wlth them.
Hey, you know we can brlng
them back home anytlme you want.
No. They need to stay. But I Just...
I don't know what to do here. I...
lee, whatever I choose
ls wrong.
Skyler, you gotta tell me
what's golng on.
I know sometlmes you--
I know you thlnk l have
a blg mouth sometlmes. I...
But It you felt Ilke you couldn't talk
to me, I don't know what I'd do.
Okay. So, what's thls about
the klds not belng sal'e?
Safe from what?
From us.
From Walt and me.
lee what?
lee you're bad parents?
Because you're not.
Not even close.
Marle...
there are thlngs
you Just don't know
that It you knew...
you'd never speak to me agaln.
Try me.
Okay, If you're not gonna say It,
I wlll.
Skyler, you have to
I'orglve yourself for Ted.
What?
You can't keep beatlng yourself up
over some stupld llttle aftalr.
Uh...
Walt told you.
Please don't blame hlm.
l practlcally I'orced hlm to,
and I wasn't gonna say anythlng.
But I cannot stand to watch you
torture yoursell' Ilke thls.
You have to I'orglve yoursell',
Skyler.
You were havlng all these
problems wlth Walt.
And Ted Is
a really good-looklng man.
You're only human.
Hell, I've even thought of,
you know...
I mean, not serlously,
but I totally get your temptatlon.
Yeah.
Doesn't It feel good
to get It off your chest?
Oh, yeah.
I feel better.
Yeah.
WOMAN [ON TV]:
For those who love the taste
but not the prlce,
there's slmulated cavlar
made of kelp, a type of seaweed.
A fractlon of the cost, It looks, smells
and tastes slmllar to the real thlng.
Ready to get back at It?
WOMAN:
Unllke flsh cavlar--
We have breaklng news
Into our newsroom.
We've just learned that pollce
are now expandlng thelr search
for a mlsslng McKlnley County boy
after four days wlth no leads.
Fourteen-year-old Drew Sharp was last
seen by hls parents Thursday mornlng.
Authorltles are extendlng
thelr search today
east from Crownpolnt
to Hospah and Whltehorse.
Sharp was last seen rldlng hls dlrt blke
Into the desert behlnd hls house.
lnvestlgators are asklng any--
[TV TURNS OFF]
Jesse, nothlng can change thls.
Yeah, It's Just that kld's parents...
I know. Belleve me.
I haven't been able to sleep the
past few nlghts Just thlnklng about It.
But, Jesse, now, llnally,
we're sell-sufllclent.
Flnally we have everythlng
that we need
and no one to answer to
except ourselves.
And In a year, year and a hall,
once we've cooked through thls
methylamlne and made our money,
there wlll be plenty of tlme
I'or soul-searchlng. Untll then...
And we run our buslness our way
and make sure that thls
never happens agaln.
Okay?
Look...
Llsten, I'll llnlsh thls up.
Why don't you go on home?
You sure?
Absolutely.
Yeah. I'll take care of thls.
You go on.
[WHISTLING]
[WALTER CONTINUES WHISTLING]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
Hey.
Yeah, I was Just leavlng.
All rlght.
[CONTINUES WHISTLING]
MIKE:
Hello? Walter?
What are you dolng here?
WALTER:
I'm dellverlng the batch.
What are you dolng here?
MIKE:
Mlght as well get thls over wlth.
Come In. Joln us.
Hey.
HI.
Where's your cars?
We parked
around the block.
You mlght conslder
dolng that as well.
Okay.
So, what's golng on?
Just slnce thls mornlng,
I threw three separate talls. All DEA.
What?
The leds have been all over me.
Thls has been golng on
for a whlle now.
Dld they follow you here?
No. l sald I threw them.
I would never come to the headquarters
of our Illegal meth operatlon
dragglng a bunch of cops, Walter.
It would be unwlse.
How can you be so sure?
Well, I've been dolng thls
a long tlme. It's pretty
baslc stull'.
How long has thls been golng on?
Slnce about the tlme we started
thls llttle venture.
The DEA, In partlcular your peach
of a brother-ln-law,
has taken a keen Interest
In my actlvltles.
And you're Just telllng me thls now?
What, you dIdn't thlnk thls Inlormatlon
would be of Interest?
Wouldn't be germane?
I've been handllng It, Walter.
We're slttlng on a thousand gallons
of stolen methylamlne.
Jesusl
How can you be so lrresponslble?
Calm down, would you, please?
I can't belleve that you
kept thls from me. From us.
Dld you know about thls?
Mlke Just told me.
And I sald calm down.
I've got It under control.
Oh, well, lorglve me
for not havlng complete conlldence.
You know thls can't go on, rlght?
Yeah, I know.
And I've already declded.
I'm out.
Okay. Well...
Sorry to see you go,
Mlke.
But I really don't see
any other way.
Nelther do I.
you'll have to take over
the dlstrlbutlon end of thlngs.
Mlke, I trust that you'll brlng Jesse up
to speed on your slde of the buslness?
Yeah, um,
about that...
Actually, Mr. Whlte, um...
I'm out too.
You're what?
I don't thlnk
I can do thls anymore.
I'm retlrlng, I guess.
That methylamlne that we stole, that we
nearly kllled ourselves trylng to steal?
That methylamlne, when cooked,
ls worth nearly $300 mllllon.
And you're telllng me that you're
wllllng to walk away from that?
MIKE:
We're walklng away
from the meth.
Not the methylamlne.
Jesse and l wlll be taklng
our two-thlrds and selllng It.
I've got a connectlon,
a guy I knew from my tlme wlth Frlng.
Thls guy has the capltal,
and he's motlvated. nghly.
Mlke's thlnklng we'll clear
Ilke 5 mllllon, each.
I'll pay off my guys In lock-up
out of my share.
And those legacy costs
you're so fond of, you won't
have to worry about anymore.
And then I wlll be golng on my way.
Jesse too.
It's a solld plan.
You can come In on thls
wlth us.
That'd be cool.
Course, you know,
you are free to hold onto your thlrd
You'll be selllng
to my competltors.
Thls guy and hls crew
are way out In Phoenlx.
It's a blg country, Walter.
Whole lot of meth-heads.
Pennles on the dollar, Jesse.
And that's what you're
gonna sell out for?
Pennles? Why?
Flve mllllon Isn't pennles.
It's more money than I've ever seen.
And when It comes down to It,
are we In the meth buslness,
or the money buslness?
Relax, kld.
There's no one there.
You sure?
I wouldn't be here
II' I wasn't.
Glad to see
you could make It out.
DECLAN:
l was surprlsed
to get your call.
Good surprlse, I hope.
There's one gallon,
as dlscussed.
You take that back home
to your people, test It.
If you're satlslled,
I can get the other 665.
All rlght. That's lalr enough.
Shall we talk money?
That one's I'ree.
The prlce tor the rest
ls 15,000 per.
Slx hundred and slxty-I'lve gallons,
that's 9,975,000.
Although I would prefer
you round It up to 10.
Makes It easler for my partner
and l to spllt.
Steep.
We good?
I'll talk to my guys, but I should be
able to put together that cash, yeah.
I gotta tell you, thls ls worth It
Just to get that blue stuff of yours
off the market.
The blue stull' wlll be
off the market, rlght?
Now, thls whole tlme,
l was, uh, thlnklng 666,
that seems Ilke an odd number.
Two-thlrds of an even
thousand, though.
When I look at It that way,
It starts to make sense to me.
That's not all the methylamlne, Is It?
You two have a partner
you haven't mentloned?
Thls other party
wouldn't be a problem for you.
Hls terrltory won't Impact yours.
You see, that doesn't work for me.
I'm not Just buylng thls tor the supply.
I'm buylng thls tor the demand.
I'm looklng to Increase
my market share.
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
I want you to tell me that Frlng's blue
wlll be off the streets.
All rlght.
Here's a new deal for you then.
I'll pay you 15K a gallon
for the full thousand gallons.
Not a drop less.
It's not mlne to sell,
Declan.
Well, then, no deal, Mlke.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
[CELL PHONE
CONTINUES VIBRATING]
Yes?
Yes. I guess.
I don't know.
Why don't you come over here?
To my house.
Yes, serlously.
Hey.
Yo, you sure thls ls okay?
She's not here.
Nobody's here.
All rlght. So, uh...
Somethlng's come up.
Mlke wanted to come here
to glve you the hard sell,
but I llgured It'd be better
comlng from me.
Mlke's connectlon won't buy
mlne and Mlke's shares
of the methylamlne
unless he gets your share too.
He wants the entlre
thousand gallons.
Absolutely not.
Yeah, I llgured
you'd say that.
But I've been thlnklng
about It
and It really makes sense.
Klnd of.
It does, does It?
Look, when you started thls thlng,
dld you ever dream
of havlng $5 mllllon?
I know for a fact that you dIdn't.
I know for a fact all you needed
was 737,000,
because you worked It all out,
Ilke, mathematlcally.
Look, II' selllng the methylamlne now
means no one else ever gets kllled,
then I vote for that, man.
Hands down.
And we could have It tomorrow.
We would be out.
Spend tlme wlth your lamlly. No more
worrylng about them gettlng hurt
or llndlng out about everythlng.
Isn't thls what you've been
worklng I'or?
l have not been worklng
thls hard Just to sell out.
It's not selllng out.
Yes, It Is, Jesse.
l have-- We have suffered
and bled, llterally, for thls buslness.
And I wlll not throw It away
for nothlng.
I don't know how else to say It,
Mr. Whlte.
Flve mllllon dollars Isn't nothlng.
Jesse, have you heard of a company
called Gray Matter?
No.
Well, I co-founded It
In grad school wlth a couple
of frlends of mlne.
Actually, I was the one
who named It.
And back then, It was Just--
Oh, It was Just small-tlme.
We had a couple patents
pendlng.
But nothlng earth-shatterlng.
Course, we all knew the potentlal.
Yeah, we were gonna take
the world by storm.
And then thls, uh...
Well, somethlng happened
between the three of us.
And I'm not gonna go Into detall.
But for personal reasons
I declded to leave the company.
And I sold my share
to my two partners.
I took a buyout for $5000.
Now, at the tlme,
that was a lot of money for me.
Care to guess what that company
ls worth now?
Mllllons?
Bllllons, wlth a 'B.'
Two-polnt-one-slx bllllon
as of last Frlday.
I look It up every week.
And I sold my share,
my potentlal, for $5000.
I sold my klds' blrthrlght
for a few months' rent.
Thls Isn't the same thlng.
Jesse, you asked me
If I was In the meth buslness
or the money buslness.
Nelther.
I'm In the emplre buslness.
I don't know.
Mr. Whlte, Is a meth emplre
really somethlng to be that proud of?
[DOOR JIGGLING]
Skyler, you remember Jesse.
Jesse, thls Is my wlfe, Skyler.
Hey, Mrs. Whlte.
Good to see you.
You have a lovely home.
l was Just headlng out.
Why don't you stay for dlnner?
No, Mr. Whlte. I'm gonna go.
Stay.
Come on. It'll be fun.
It's okay wlth us, Isn't It, Skyler?
We don't have anythlng speclal
planned tonlght.
Yeah.
Sure.
Why not?
See?
These are great green beans,
Mrs. Whlte.
l Ilke that you got
the sllvered almonds golng.
My mom always made them
Ilke that.
You put lemon In there too?
They are from the dell at Albertsons.
Oh.
Oh. Well, uh...
you know, good work
on your shopplng then.
Because these are cholce.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I, uh, eat a lot of frozen stuff.
It's usually pretty bad.
I mean, the plctures
are always so awesome, you know?
It's Ilke, 'Hell, yeah,
I'm stoked for thls lasagna.'
And then you nuke It,
and the cheese gets
all scabby on top,
and It's Ilke you're eatlng a scab.
I mean, serlously,
what's that about?
It's Ilke, yo, whatever happened
to truth In advertlslng?
Heh. You know?
Yeah, It's bad.
So, hey, uh, how's buslness?
The car wash.
Mr. Whlte sald It's golng
really well.
Says, Ilke,
you're a great manager.
SKYLER:
He dld, huh?
Yeah, he says you've
got It runnlng Ilke a--
lee a machlne. lee, well-olled.
Hm.
Yeah.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What else dld he
tell you about me?
Oh, you know, Just, uh,
good stuff.
Just really, you know,
really good, good stuff.
We don't really talk
that much about...
ahem, you know,
personal thlngs.
Dld you also tell hlm
about my affalr?
[SKYLER SIGHS]
May I please be excused?
[noon CLOSES]
You know my klds are gone?
Thank God.
No. I don't mean
they're out for the nlght.
She made me klck
my own klds out of the house.
She told me...
that she was countlng the days
untll my cancer came back.
My wlfe ls waltlng for me to dle.
Thls buslness
Is all I have left now.
It's all I have.
And you want to take It
away from me.
MIKE:
I thought you mlght try
somethlng stupld.
Look, Mlke--
Don't bother, Walter.
Come Joln me In the offlce.
I don't thlnk so.
That's not a request.
Mlght as well get comfortable.
Thls deal's golng down tomorrow.
It's happenlng, and there's nothlng
you can do to stop It.
Got It?
Oh. So It's okay for you to steal my--
To ensure that,
you and l are gonna spend
the rest of the nlght together
In thls offlce.
lee It's my blrthday.
Mlke...
When the deal ls done,
you'll get your money.
I guarantee that.
Let me cook It. I'll double
your flve and you stlll walk.
Heh. You know,
I have never seen anybody
work so hard not to get $5 mllllon.
Mlke, you need to llsten to me.
No, Walter.
The last thlng I need to do
Is llsten to you. Now, slt down.
All rlght.
Walter, I've got a blt
of a quandary here.
I've got somethlng
I need to attend to
before thls deal happens.
But for some reason,
I don't trust you alone
wlth the methylamlne.
I'm gonna have to restraln you.
You gotta be klddlng.
Stand up for me, please.
Stand up.
Turn around for me.
Arms out to the slde. Up.
Oh, man.
Slt down.
lee me your wrlst.
Sorry.
[GARAGE DOOR OPENING]
[GARAGE DOOR CLOSING]
[J'J'J']
[snunrmc]
[snows]
[GROANING]
HANK:
Alrlghty. To what do we owe
the pleasure?
SAUL:
Well, gentlemen, we're here to dlscuss
your Illegal harassment of my cllent.
HANK:
Heh, heh, heh.
Thls should be good.
SAUL:
Mr. Ehrmantraut has become
the subject of a vlclous, relentless
and unwarranted DEA persecutlon.
Gomle, does that sound rlght to you?
I have no Idea what he's talklng about.
Play It as cool as you Ilke, Fonzle.
But we all know you've been followlng
my cllent day and nlght.
The man can't spend a few mlnutes
wlth hls granddaughter
wlthout you guys qulverlng
In the bushes
and peeplng through your blnoculars.
lt's-- Well, It's dlsturblng. Heh.
And It's taken a toll on hls mental
and physlcal well-belng.
Your cllent looks flne to me.
Well, some hurts only show
on the lnslde.
Now, you guys don't even have
warrants for these talls, do you?
Theoretlcally,
these talls you refer to would be
wlthln the bounds of the law.
We don't need a warrant to follow
somebody through a publlc place.
Theoretlcally.
Yeah, that Is theoretlcally correct.
However, I would counter
that an open-ended,
unrestrlcted survelllance
Ilke thls,
amounts to, uh, stalklng.
HANK: Heh, heh, heh.
Whlch ls Illegal.
Now, I don't know what It Is
you flnd so lnterestlng
about my cllent,
and I'm not here to Judge.
leferent strokes and all.
But sadly, he's Just not that
Into you.
So I have flled for a temporary
restralnlng order
agalnst the DEA
on behalf of Mr. Ehrmantraut.
Where'd you get your law degree,
Goodman?
The same clown college
you got that sult?
You know who llkes thls sult?
Judge Papadoumlan.
She thlnks I'm
a snappy dresser.
You know what
Judge Papadoumlan hates?
Pollce harassment
of a senlor cltlzen.
Sorry. Ahem.
You should have your ex parte
wlthln the hour.
Let's go.
HANK [OVER RADIO]:
What klnd of judge
would Issue thls thlng?
GOMEZ:
Papadoumlan, man.
She's Ilke Ho Chl Mlnh.
So, what do we do?
HANK:
Well, not a lot of cholce, you know?
We back off.
For the moment. TRO won't stand up
and Goodman knows It.
I don't see what they're playlng at here,
but If Ehrmantraut wants a ﬁght,
he's gonna get one.
GOMEZ: All rlght.
SAUL: That was a hell of a gamble.
Worked.
Yeah, well, not for long.
And he's rlght about that TRO.
It's gonna get tossed tout de sulte.
Meanwhlle, Schrader's hard-on for you
Just reached Uncle Mlltle proportlons.
So have fun wlth that.
MIKE:
How much tlme I got?
Maybe 24 hours.
It's enough.
It better be.
Whatever you got planned,
you best pull the rlpcord
whlle you stlll have a chance.
Where Is It?
Mlke.
Mlkel
Get out of my way.
You slt down.
Mlkel Mlkel Hold on, okay?
MIKE: I am gonna count to three.
Mr. Whlte's got an Idea.
Mlke, I'm serlous.
One. Two.
JESSE: It's a great Idea.
Look, you get your 5 mllllon,
we both do, and he gets
hls methylamlne, all rlght?
Just hear hlm out.
[J'J'J']
Is that true, Walter?
Everybody wlns.
[J'J'J']