You are not how I remambor you
from class. I moan, Ilka, not at all.
Dude, thl: Isn't even 7 grand, all rlght?
My guy want: 85.
Thl: I: all the many I hava
In the world.
You are a drug dealar. Negotlato.
Buy the RV.
We start tomorrow.
Work It, work It, baby.
Yo, thla la alck, brother.
Totally. God.
Yo, Joan, I got than two ï¬ne ladle:
who wanna partlclpato.
-You got the funds?
-0h, I got the funds. Hay.
Would you ladloa Ilka to meat
my fat atack?
Get In hora.
Come on.
Hey. ye. yo.
Yo, you got champagno?
None of that cheap atufl'.
I want the axpenalvo ahlt.
Don Pbrlgnon.
It's 400 a bottle.
on, wall, In that caaa,
I'll only hava two.
Oh, and I want tha tall, aklnny glaaaaa.
l Ilka thoaa aklnny glaaaaa.
That's what Jamaa Bond drlnka.
Motoa, I'm all about that.
Yo, Jaaaa, man, I gotta aak.
-Whara dld you gat all tha chaddar?
-Muat ba movlng mad voluma.
It's funny.
You wanna know what's funny?
-What'a I'unny?
-Thla old duda, ha gava It to ma.
-What?
-Ha gava It to ma.
lt'a hla antlra llI'a aavlnga.
-What? Why?
-Bacauaa ha'a a dumb-aaa. That's why.
Oh, God.
Yaal
All rlght, llvlng larga, playara.
Thank you. Yo, thank you.
-Thank you.
-That waa....
Awaaoma, bro.
Latar.
Oh, man.
Oh, I'm so daad.
I only got.... 0h, damn.
I only got, Ilka, 1400.
Wafl'la Houaa? Yaah.
Suppoaad to uaa that duda'a monay
to buy an RV.
-What do you want wlth a RV for?
-Bacauaa, llka....
Navar mlnd.
Jaaua.
Now I gotta, Ilka, laava town
or changa my ldantlty or aomathlng.
Guy'a blackmalllng ma.
Ha'a got, Ilka, a crlmlnal mlnd, yo.
RV, yaah?
I can hook you up, bro.
I can totally gat you an RV.
-No, l naad It today. Now.
-No problam. Lat'a go.
You'ra talllng ma
you can gat ma an RV?
For 1400, at 6 In tha mornlng?
nght on.
No, It's, Ilka,
a no-paparwork-typa daal.
Plaaaura dolng bualnaaa wlth you.
Coma on, wa gotta bounca.
-What?
-For raal, yo. Gat It out of hara.
Oh, my God, I lova thla I'loor.
Thla I'aala I'antaatlc.
Can you control tha tamparatura?
Yaah. Thara ahould ba a awltch
rlght naxt to you thara.
It's a tharmoatat.
Tad, thla haa gotta ba...
...tha moat amazlng lnvantlon avar.
I know. Contractor talkad ma Into It.
Saamad klnd oI' axtravagant, but....
I gotta tall you, onca you try It,
you can't go back.
I can navar I'lnd anythlng
In thla Bulck.
You know, you could laava
a law thlnga hara It you want.
-Why don't you go gat your dad?
-Sura.
Hay, Dad.
-Dad?
-Yaah.
Wanna coma to dlnnar?
Yaah, I'll ba rlght thara.
You'ra not llatanlng to ma.
I don't know.
Yaah, rlght, Ilka you don't know.
-What dld IJuat say?
-lea ma tha phona. lea It.
lea you dldn't maka aoma daal
bahlnd my back.
Correct. I dld not.
lwaa alttlng at a atopllght...
...mlndlng my own bualneaa,
when the man-- The man....
The kld threw a bag of money
through my wlndow.
Whatever, man.
You owe me that money.
-Let me talk to hlm.
-I owe you?
I owe you nothlng.
And I wlll get to the bottom of thla.
Trust me.
Truat you? Truat you?
That's a good one.
Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do.
You wanna talk about truat, Jeaae?
Let's talk about truat.
I told you not to cook my formula,
and you went ahead and dld It anyway.
Because I never aald I wouldn't cook It
because It aln't youra. lt'a oura.
Plural, bltch.
You dld not have my permlaalon.
All I know la I got half the money
I'm due...
...and you got the rest.
Eacalatlng. You're eacalatlng.
You know what? Eacalate thla.
My math, my money!
I wIII be a one-man glass factory.
I wIII rock that RV 24--
lt'a buttoned up tlght.
Can't see a damn thlng.
l aln't I'eellng It.
No amoke, no small, no waste.
There's no cook.
Could be they're aettlng up.
I heard movement lnalde.
I say we call It a nlght,
come back wlth a search warrant.
I'm not lettlng thla aucker
out of my alght.
There'a gotta be a way.
There's gotta be a way....
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you dolng?
-No, no, no.
-What the hell are you dolng up there?
Are you some klnd of a pervert?
Yeah,
because we were here last year.
Sorry. I appreclate....
Golng after the bad guys.
I'm sorry and enjoy the rest
of your vacatlon. Okay?
Go back to your trallera.
Everythlng'a okay.
Guy'a VFW. He'a cool.
We're gonna check out a couple more
and call It a mornlng.
-0kay, what do you say?
-Can't. Gotta get home.
Why, you leave your ball:
In your wll'e'a purse or what?
Gotta pack.
Where you headed?
Texaa.
Hey there.
Hank?
Can I come In?
-Hey, babe.
-Hey.
-How dld It go laat nlght?
-Good.
Catch the bad guys?
-Want me to make you some breakfast?
-No. I'm....
I'm headlng back out after thla.
Now? You worked all nlght.
Get some sleep, Hank.
Thoae RVa aren't golng anywhere.
They're recreatlonal vehlclea, Marla.
That's what they do.
You know what I mean.
I spoke wlth Blanca.
She aald
that Steven'a golng to El Paao?
Yeah.
l was Juat wonderlng
how you feel about that.
-I turned It down. End of story.
-Good. Good.
Jeaua, God know: I'm relleved.
I needed some tlme here because
I'm deep Into thla lnveatlgatlon...
...and couldn't do both...
...ao I made a Judgement call.
You know that you can talk to me
about thlnga, rlght?
You don't have
to go through thla alone.
Do you ask me whlch lead blb
to put on someone...
...beI'ore you nuke them?
Jeaua, Marla.
I made a declalon.
I'm not golng through anythlng.
Dolng my Job.
A condo In Georgetown. I know.
It you would let me I'lnlah,
lwaa golng to lay...
...l'd Ilka to be Included. That's all.
Don't you worry about my career.
My career la Juat I'lne.
Dld you not wanna go?
I don't blame you. l]uat--
-Aren't you late for work or aomethlng?
-Mter what happened...
...It would make perfect sense
for you to not wanna go back.
I'm onto some Important atufl'
rlght here, rlght now.
And Mexlco doesn't have a damn thlng
to do wlth It. Anyone who doubt: that....
I mean, I'm dolng
some actual good out here...
...and all I get
are these bullahlt accuaatlonal
What, everyone thlnka
I'm Jerklng off on thla thlng? Flne.
But I'm onto aomethlng. I know It.
You understand me?
You hear me?
What exactly la thla?
I'll tell you what I thlnk It la.
A ploy.
A ploy to get me cooklng agaln.
And an obvloua one at that.
How do you mean?
A: II' I would aerloualy belleve
you would hlre an addlct.
Jeaae Plnkman? Recoverlng or not.
You vouched for hlm prevloualy.
I took you at your word.
No. No, no, no. Let me be clear.
Let me be perfectly clear.
Jane was capable of worklng
under my aupervlalon.
Truatlng hlm wlth a solo venture...
...well, that's qulte another matter.
How he could poaalbly
produce anythlng...
...other than a medlocre product
at beat.
I am told hla product
was more or Ian conalatent...
...wlth the quallty I had come to expect.
More or Ian?
More or Ian? Really?
Boy, that la the....
Talk about aettlng the bar low.
Except you don't do that,
eat the bar low.
Therefore,
what conclualon am I left to draw?
That you belleve l have some
proprletary klnd of aelflahneaa...
...about my own formula.
Some sort of overweenlng prlde,
I suppose...
...that you thlnk
almply overwhelma me...
...clouda my Judgement.
-But It doesn't.
-Abaolutely not.
l almply respect the chemlatry.
The chemlatry must be respected.
l apologlae for belng ao tranaparent.
Would you take a drlve wlth me?
I'd Ilka to show you aomethlng.
HI. la everythlng okay?
She'a already flnlahed an antlra bottle,
but aha atlll aeemed hungry.
Then aha fell asleep.
But I waa thlnklng I'd glve her another
when aha wakea up.
Yeah, yeah, abaolutely, abaolutely.
-Fatten that baby up.
-IIIIIII do.
Waa that It?
So where are you? Are you at work?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm at work.
I shouldn't be much longer.
-Ia that okay?
-You know I love my llttle pookuma.
You can leave her wlth me
for the next 18 yeara...
...aa far aa I'm concerned.
Great. Thanka, Marla.
Are you aura you're okay?
Sweetle, what Ia It? Come on.
-lt'a Hank.
-Hank? What about hlm?
I don't know how to talk to hlm.
I don't know what to aay to hlm
anymore. I don't know how to....
Ever alnce El Paao, ever alnce--
Maybe before....
Yeah. God knowa
he went through a lot down there.
People blown up rlght In front of hlm,
blood everywhere...
...and laat week,
El Paao aald they want hlm back.
Yeah?
He'a not golng. stave Gomez
la golng In hla place...
...and I don't know
how I feel about that.
Well, he'a certalnly a lot aafer up here,
lan't he?
Of course, and! want hlm aafe.
But I can't tell what he wanta.
He won't talk to me.
He hardly even comea home.
He worka all day, all nlght.
Barely eata, barely apeaka to me.
It'a Ilka aomethlng'a
eatlng hlm away from Inalde.
He'a Juat not the aame. He'a not.
Faclng death, It changea a peraon.
It haa to, don't you thlnk?
l gueaa you've notlced
a change In Walt.
Pleaae.
What la thla?
Your new lab.
My God.
Thorlum oxlde for a catalyat bed.
Look at the alze
of thla reactlon veaael.
0h, lt'a got....
lt'a gotta be 1200 lltrea.
Where--? Where--?
How dld you know
how to put thla all together?
I had excellent help, aa wlll you.
Qulte a lot of plannlng went Into thla.
I would aay ao.
The laundry upatalra,
I've owned It for yeara.
It recelvea large chemlcal dellverlea
on a weekly baala...
...detergenta and auch.
There la nothlng auaplcloua
about It...
...and my employeea, to be aura,
are well-tralned, truatworthy.
The flltratlon ayatem
la atate of the art.
It wlll vent nothlng
but clean, odourleaa ateam...
...Juat aa the laundry doea...
...and through the very aame atacka.
I need 200 pounda per week
to make thla economlcally vlable.
You would chooae your own houra,
of courae...
...come and go aa you pleaae...
...ao long aa the quota la met.
Sorry.
The anawer la atlll no.
l have made a aerlea
of very bad declalona...
...and I cannot make another one.
Why dld you make theae declalona?
For the good of my famlly.
Then they weren't bad declalona.
What doea a man do, Walter?
A man provldea for hla famlly.
Thla coat me my famlly.
When you have chlldren,
you alwaya have famlly.
They wlll alwaya be your prlorlty,
your reaponalblllty.
And a man.... A man provldea.
And he doea It
even when he'a not appreclated...
...or reapected...
...or even loved.
He almply beara up, and he doea It...
Any chance
we could grab a qulck blte?
Thal place around the corner'a
pretty good.
I really gotta head home.
All rlght, raln check, then.
She aald It waa the tofu.
Whatever. She'a atlll cute anywaya.
Great dlnner, Mom.
Can I be excuaed?
To do homework
or to play vldeo gamea?
I can multltaak.
Yeah.
You wanna take her?
lee me aomethlng, Andy. Come on.
Welded onto the back of a houae.
Well, that'a claaay.
Chrlat.
Okay. Okay, thanka.
Hey, Janlce. Janlce.
That the laat one?
Sorry, Hank. That'a all DMV had.
Twenty nlne early '80a Boundera
reglatered In New Mexlco.
-Could you check agaln?
-Now?
-Can I do It after the party?
-Janlce, l'm....
I'm dead In the water here.
Okay, I'll check.
Hey, how are you guya dolng?
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna clean It
really good, I tell you.
All good.
-Gomey.
-Yeah.
Tlme for the llttle blrd to fly the neat,
huh?
The rlght guy for the Job alnce
the bean-apeak comea natural and all.
Wanna know how to aay
'get bent' In Spanlah?
Juat don't go natlve on me, all rlght?
Hey.
Here.
Know your enemy and all.
-Flght the good flght, brother.
-I wlll.
Who got a drlnk around here?
Your hunch waa rlght. One more RV.
DMV aald the reglatratlon
waan't renewed...
...but than they reallaed It waa never
flled aa non-operatlonal or deatroyed.
No pollce report, alther.
IJuat don't know what the hell
I'm dolng anymore, you know?
lt'a Ilka I'm paralyzed...
...llke If I take a atep
In any dlrectlon...
...l'm gonna make
a apectacular mlatake.
God, I could go
for a glaaa of wlne about now.
You wanna go to--?
Sorry, never mlnd.
Anyway...
...breaklng newa la
I am aleeplng wlth my boaa...
...and I don't know why.
Yep.
That'a a Ila. I do know why.
I mean, he'a a lovely guy.
He'a a really good peraon...
...but, I mean,
lt'a not Ilka we're ever gonna....
Somehow,
and I can't actually belleve It...
...but my antlra famlly
aeea me aa aome aort of....
My own alater, my brother-ln-law.
My teenage aon...
...tella me I'm a bltch.
And you aay tell hlm the truth.
Tell hlm about hla father...
...but I can't.
Even
How could I?
And thla man that I'm aeelng,
you know...
...aa wrong aa I know It la...
...aa much aa I know I'm probably
dolng It to make Walt leave me...
...lt lathe only thlng In my day
where I don't feel...
...drownlng.
So he knowa about thla other man?
Yeah.
So then he'll algn?
Walt aaya he'a not golng anywhere...
...ao that'a a really brllllant
gamblt on my part. Yep.
He keepa money In the houae.
Your huaband, the drug dealer?
How much money?
l dldn't count It. lt'a heavy.
A bag, where he keepa It.
Are you aaklng my permlaalon
to apend thla money?
No. God, no. l]uat--
No, I'm Juat, you know....
I'm Juat trylng to Juat talk It through.
That'a....
Let me Juat aay
that I'm half aa quallfled...
...and twlce the prlce of a theraplat.
There la nothlng to dlacuaa here.
I'm Juat aaylng, you know?
We have a hlatory.
He'a the father of my chlldren...
...and maybe what he dld, he--
He dld It for the famlly. nght?
Well, gueaa what.
That la one enormoua load
of horae ahlt.
Okay.
I'm golng to apell thla out
aa almply aa I can for you.
You are a fool to atay In that houae
one mlnute longer.
If your huaband won't leave,
than you go.
You are now an acceaaory
after the fact.
You, your chlldren,
you could loae everythlng you own.
Do you underatand?
All courteay of thla crlmlnal
you refuae to dlvorce.
-l dldn't marry a crlmlnal.
-Well, you're marrled to one now.
How'a about we run through thla
one more tlme...
...eapeclally where I do the talklng,
you don't aay Jack?
Oh, I'm gonna aayJack.
I'm gonna aay plenty.
What dld we aay about eacalatlng, huh?
Who'a got your back here?
Me, all rlght?
I'm golng to take care of thlnga.
Hey, what are the parametera
of thla aobrlety thlng you got golng?
-What do you mean?
-Can you take a Xanax?
Becauae I got a drawer full of them.
I get them from my 'chlropractor.'
Vletnameae, 5-foot tall.
She adJuata you to 'completlon.'
Her name'a Klm Nu Suong...
...aa dellcloua aa It aounda.
l ahould glve you her card.
Hell wlth thla. I'm out of here.
He'a here.
Hello, Walt. Good to aee you.
Pleaae, have a aeat here.
Mr. Plnkman, If you wlll.
You're late.
Gentlemen, If we could come
to aome accommodatlon here now.
There'a alwaya a way
to oll everyone'a lock.
Thla young man la prepared
to offer you a aweetheart of a deal...
-...for dolng preclaely nothlng.
-Really?
Ten percent of all future proflta
from hla aolo venture.
That'a money you get pald
for walklng down to the mallbox.
Conalder It a geature of reapect
for your valuable contrlbutlon...
...to the bualneaa thua far.
I'm aura you'll agree that'a falr.
That'a charlty, la what that la.
I do all the work.
He alta around on hla fat aaa
Judglng people.
Eacalatlng. Stop.
So there'a that,
but than there'a one amall detall.
Clearly a mlatake waa made
on the part of our mutual aaaoclate...
...when he pald you half
of Jeaae'a earnlnga.
He muat not have reallaed that you two
had come to a partlng of the waya.
Take It. It belonga to you.
You're damn rlght It belonga to me.
I knew I could count on you boya
to play nlce. That'a--
-That almoat brlnga a tear to my eye.
-En]oy It.
Spend It In good health.
That la the laat money
you'll ever earn In thla bualneaa.
What the hell la that
auppoaed to mean?
Well, I hate to break It to you, Jeaae,
but our mutual aaaoclate...
...waa only ualng you to get to me.
What are you talklng about?
See, he needa aomeone
wlth expertlae...
...aomeone who knowa
what he'a dolng.
In other worda, he needa me.
You're talllng me
you're cooklng agaln?
Yeah.
Let'a aaa, how ahould I put thla?
You're out.
Walt, hold on there.
What waa the offer, If I may aak?
lt'a three mllllon
for three montha of my tlme.
You're gonna need that money
laundered. I mean, of courae.
What waa our deal before?
Seventeen percent.
That'a a ahade hlgh.
Let'a aettle on an even 15.
That'a a nlce round number.
Flve percent.
-Fourteen'a falr.
-Flve.
-Th|rteen.
-Twelve. For old tlmea' aake, 12.
-Flve.
I'm a reaaonable guy.
lt'a a ahort-term deal.
Ten even, but I can't go any lower
and atlll reapect myaelf.
Flve.
What In the hell Juat happened?
You're my lawyer, not hla.
That'a the way of the world, kld.
Go wlth the wlnner.
You thlnk thla wlll atop me
from cooklng?
Cook whatever you Ilka.
Aa long aa lt'a that rldlculoua
Chllll P or aome other dreck...
...but don't even thlnk
about ualng my formula.
Juat try and atop me, bltch.
-Yea?
-Hl there, Mra. Ortega?
-Yea.
-Hl, I'm Hank Schrader.
I'm wlth the Drug Enforcement
Admlnlatratlon.
We're lntereated In an RV that'a
reglatered to your name and addreaa.
-Do you have an RV?
-l dld.
It waa atolen montha ago.
Stolen, huh? Yeah.
Well, then I'm curloua aa to why
the theft waa never reported.
I'm not aeelng any recorda
of It wlth the pollce or the DMV.
IJuat dldn't get around to It.
May I aak why?
I mean, lt'a a great way
to get the famlly together...
...for an affordable vacatlon.
It muat've been a blow
when It went mlaalng.
It waa.
Do you have any ldaaa at all
who mlght've taken It?
l dldn't want hlm arreated.
He ran wlth a bad crowd,
but he waa never a bad peraon.
I thought he could turn
hla llfe around.
Who are we talklng about,
Mra. Ortega?
My aon.
I'd really Ilka to apeak wlth hlm.
He'a paaaed away.
He waa ahot two montha ago.
-What waa your aon'a name?
-Chrlatlan.
Chrlatlan Ortega.
Waa hla nlckname Combo?
Thanka for thla.
I really appreclate It.