Operation Icebreaker.
-How we liking that?
-We never used that before, did we?
-lan't that the name of a breath mlnt?
-What?
-|ce Breakers, right? Breath mint?
-Nobody's gonna think that.
Gonna be thinking about some ship
in the North Pole breaking ice.
Says you. I'm gonna be thinking
Operation Breath Mint.
I'm thinking Operation Breath Mint every
time you and me are on a stakeout.
Your breath can knock a buzzard
off a shit waggon.
All right, Operation TBD.
Thanks for nothing, Gom.
Anyway, say hello to
Domingo Gallardo Molina.
A.k.a. Krazy-8. Way smarter
than your average cheese eater.
I turned him out when he was street,
but this dude's like The Jeffersons...
-...movlng on up.
-Every dealer he'd throw at us...
-...he'd end up snaking their customers.
-Turns out he's missing, presumed dead.
Found his car out in the boonies.
Last guy he ratted out
was none other than his cousin...
...Em|l|o Koyama.
You thinking the cousin found out
and took revenge?
Could be, turns out he's missing too.
And normally I'd say
someone did the world a favour.
But our snitch's car, turns out
we find two grams of meth in it...
...we take It to the lab,
they come back...
...they tell us It the purest
they've ever seen.
Ninety-nine-point-one percent.
Our chemist is blown away.
Said he couldn't do better.
Worse yet, it didn't come out
of some super lab in Mexico...
...we're thinking this was cooked
here in the Land of Enchantment.
Car was abandoned
at what appears to be a cook site.
This Is the only other thing
left behind.
We're sending it off to Quantico,
see if they can pull something off it.
Meantime, our guys swabbed the filter
element and found the same 99.1 meth.
So be on notice.
We got new players in town.
Now, we don't know who they are,
or where they come from...
...but they possess
an extremely high skill set.
Me, personally...
...I'm thinking Albuquerque
just might have a new kingpin.
Jesus, Walt,
you're burning the shit out of them.
Damn It.
Hey, Sky, you got any more chicken?
Emerll, here,
Is gonna need a fresh pack.
All right, looking good.
Is this low-fat mayonnaise
In the coleslaw?
I don't know, it's store-bought.
Okay, Hank, you need another beer?
Does the pope shit in his hat?
Yeah, I don't think that he does, Hank,
and I think everybody would like it...
...if you'd stop saying that.
-Marle, some more wine?
-l'm all right, thanks.
-All right.
-Hey, I want a beer.
Yeah, I want Shania Twain
to give me a tuggy.
Guess what. It ain't happening either.
-How about some more soda?
-Yeah, sure.
Honey, do you need anything?
-No, Walt, thank you.
-0kay. Be right back.
-No.
-What, are you kidding me?
You look like
a damn movie star, man.
Girls gotta be lining up left and right.
-Tell him how good-looking he is.
-He's adorable.
He doesn't wanna be fricking adorable,
he wants to be hot.
See what I'm talking about?
That's female perspective.
-She's supposed to say that.
-Look, a guy doesn't gotta look like...
...you know, Charlton Heston--
I'm talking Moses days.
--to get a girl, all right?
You Just gotta have...
...confldence.
Confidence and persistence.
Okay? That's what I'm talking about.
I kept bugging her for a date,
she kept saying no.
What, I asked you, like, 50 times?
Yeah, it was before they tightened
the stalking laws.
Anyway, how about your dad here?
That there's a good story, Walt.
-Tell him how you met Skylar.
-Mom was a waitress in Los Alamos...
...and Dad said that thing to you.
Well, actually, your mother
wasn't a waitress...
...It was a summer Job,
and she was the hostess...
...and she also worked
the cash register.
And I used to go in there a lot because
it was close enough to the lab...
...where I could ride my bicycle.
And once I noticed her...
...it got to be so that I would only go in
when I knew she was working.
When it was slow,
she would lean against the counter...
...dolng her crossword puzzles,
but kind of hiding It...
...pretendlng that
she was still working...
...and once I caught on to that...
...I would do crossword puzzles while
late my grilled-cheese sandwich.
It got so that every day at lunch...
...we would both be doing
The New York Times crossword puzzle...
...10 feet from each other.
And eventually...
...I caught her looking over at me...
...so I began saylng:
"Excuse me, 14 across,
seven-letter word for whatchamacallit...
...may I ask what you wrote down?"
And, well, that got us talking...
...and, boy, I tell you,
I was terrible at those puzzles.
I don't think that I finished
even one of them.
But your mother
would do them In Ink.
Very smooth.
I bet you didn't think
your old man had it in him, huh?
But that's what I'm talking about,
that's persistence, you see?
Once you set your cap
for something...
...or somebody,
you gotta Just, you know....
-Skylar.
-Mom, are you all right?
Hey, hey.
Honey, It's okay.
What's the matter?
What Is It?
Ask him.
What's she talking about?
Walt?
l have cancer.
Lung cancer.
It's bad.
Ask him how long he's known.
-I guess a month, maybe.
-0h, for God sakes, Walt.
We're just sitting out there having
a cookout like nothing's going on.
He made me promise
not to tell anybody.
Christ, these last 48 hours.
And it's the weekend, so I couldn't
even get his doctor on the phone.
Buddy, why--? I mean, why wouldn't
you wanna tell anybody?
Walt, don't you see
everybody just wants to help you.
We're family.
We get through these things together.
And I don't get, you know, lung cancer?
How can that happen?
-You don't even smoke.
-You know, I'm thinking...
...that this goes back 20 years,
maybe...
...to the applications lab, all those
chemicals they had you working around.
We always took
the proper precautions.
One time you complained that
they didn't give you the right kind of...
...I don't know, some kind of
ventilation hood or something...
-...and then the headaches.
-Honey, It wasn't that.
How do they think
they can get away with this?
-We should hire a lawyer.
-Okay, so first let's deal with this.
Okay, so,
what's the next step for Walt?
Certainly a second opinion, right?
Right. Right, absolutely.
Okay, so first thing tomorrow,
I talk to my radiologists...
...we find you the best,
the oncology dream team.
That's good. That's good.
Yeah.
Yeah?
-Yeah, okay.
-0kay.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go check on Walt Jr.
...If I can talk hlm Into,
I don't know, Joining us.
I really didn't mean for him
to find out that way.
Walt...
...whatever happens...
...I hope this goes without saying...
...but whatever happens...
...I want you to know that...
...I'II always take care of your family.
Yo, check out these fake Pop-Tarts.
-These are mad tlght, yo.
-No, thanks, man, pass.
Your loss. These are from, like,
Canada, or something. Imported.
Hey, yo, what happened
to your hallway, man?
-Dld, like, the ceiling fall down, or...?
-0h, yeah...
...no, man,
lthlnk the house Is Just settllng.
You know,
It's been cavlng In left and right.
Hit me In the eye.
-lt's bananas.
-Yo, my pops could fix you up...
...he's, like,
a contractor or something.
Yeah? Yeah, right on,
I should grab that number.
Say, Jesse,
you still cook a little crystal?
Could be, yeah.
You know, from time to time.
I heard you lost your partner.
Didn't he get locked up?
No, man, he's out.
His cousln balled him out.
lthlnk he sklpped town
or something.
I don't know about any of that,
I've Just been...
...klnd of doing my own thing
these days, so....
But you maybe
got some crystal, man?
Because I could seriously go for a bowl
right now, you know, take the edge off.
-Hell, yeah, Sunday night bowl, yo.
-All right.
Well, maybe it just so happens...
...that I just recently cooked
the best batch ever.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah. Came up
with this whole new recipe.
It's more like a formula.
It's, like,
way, way more chemically--
Shit, you know,
It's just the bomb, so....
But, you know, I don't know,
I've been thinking lately...
...I'II just lay off of it for a while...
...because lately it's been
kind of making me paranoid, so....
You know, for, like,
health-wise, just lay off.
Yo, if you're not into sharing, man,
just tell us to piss off, it's cool.
-We don't need no soap opera.
-Yeah, man, whatever.
No, no, it's all good, you know.
I'm just saying,
hey, I got plenty of pot.
Yeah, I think I'll bounce, man.
Yeah, sounds about right.
Hey, yo, yo. Hey, homes, I'm joking.
Okay, I'm totally joking with you.
You kidding? Sit down.
Best scante ever.
Grab that plpe.
Okay, there.
Shlt.
Walt, do you need some help?
Oh, no, I'm fine, honey. I'm fine.
Just prlvacy.
Thanks.
I'm right outside if you need me.
Okay.
Yeah, any time on Friday
Is absolutely flne.
Thank you so much
for working us In.
Can I just put that on a credit card?
Great. Perfect.
Okay, so we will see you at 10:45
on Friday morning.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Oh, yes.
Honey...
...the best oncologist, I mean,
not even just in New Mexico...
...but one of the top 10
In the entire nation...
...his name is Dr. Delcavoli...
...and we see him on Friday.
I mean,
Marie really came through for us.
She had her boss call, and....
Okay, this Is good.
From here on out, things are gonna--
What's that we're putting on
a credit card?
It's just a deposit kind of thing.
-How much of a deposit?
-lt's $5000.
Flve thousand?
Jesus.
What's that, just to start? I mean...
...just to tell me
what I already know?
Walt, he's not in our HMO, okay?
So be it, we'll figure it out.
Come on,
don't get hung up on money here.
-We can always borrow from Hank.
-Absolutely not.
No, Ijust....
We're not gonna do that.
Well, maybe we can ask your mom.
Have you even called her yet?
Walt, regardless, you're gonna have to
tell her about this...
-...I mean, I'm willing to do It, but In
-l'll call. I'll call.
Okay, look...
...I don't even want us
thinking about money.
Money is not the issue here.
-lt's not.
-I know. I know.
It's not.
-Okay.
Okay.
I'll take care of the deposit.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'll borrow it from my pension.
Damn It!
Hey. Hey, pal, what's up?
Oh, yeah, no, I thought I heard mice.
Boy, that's all we need, huh?
So, what's up, pal?
What the hell's wrong with you?
-What?
-You're actlng all....
You're....
You're all....
Why are you actlng so weird?
-Son.
-You're acting like nothing |s going on.
Oh, no, please. Please, please, no.
Hey, no, heyl
-Heyl
-Put that douche bag on the phone.
Oh, come on.
Hey, am I gonna have to
come down there and whup your ass?
And let me tell you something else,
I'm not doing this for charity, right?
I'm the best he's got.
He knows It, I know It...
...I expect to be paid to a level
commensurate with--
I said, "Dave, do you think 40 grand
is a proper bonus?"
That's less than 10 percent
of what I booked this quarter.
I'm not gonna sit here
and be disrespect--
Oh, he's shitting bricks.
Oh, you know he ls.
Yeah, that man lives In fear.
I'll go across town--
Hell, I could go anywhere.
Hoffman, Gordon Bradley, or Sorcher.
Even Goldberg-Wayne. They'd make me
a partner for walking in the damn door...
-...that's how ecstatlc they'd be.
-Next customer.
Hells, yes, brother man.
Dude, you should check this chick out.
Who? No.
Stacey's a cow.
We're talking major
barnyard boo-hog.
Roll her in flour and look for
the wet spot before you hit that, man.
That kind of stink does not wash off.
-S|r?
-nght.
Slr.
Oh, yeah?
-Sorry. HI.
-Oh, totally.
-Hi. What can I do for you today?
-Which dude?
-That dude that looks like a lizard?
-Next In line.
-And he llmps like some leper.
-l'm sorry, lwould llke...
-...a cashier's cheque...
-Grosses me out.
...in the full amount...
...made out to Oncology Partners
of New Mexico, please.
Oh, that's O-N-C-O-L-O-G-Y.
Yeah, you got It.
I don't understand
why they're forcing you...
...to choose between
plccolo and oboe.
You show so much promise
with both.
They can't have any
switching between woodwinds.
No matter how they divide it up,
someone would be left out.
-Rules are rules, I guess.
-Sure, rules are rules. I'm all for that.
But I'm telling you,
you really shine on that oboe.
You have real talent,
and I'm not just saying that.
Thanks.
What about Mr. Pemberton?
Is he giving you enough
individual attention?
I'd say so.
He tries to talk to each one of us...
...at least once during every practise.
-That's good. Feedback's important.
-It's key, Ithink.
Hey, so how was soccer practise?
I think that was in our backyard.
Who's there?
What the hell are you doing out here?
Hey, Dad.
Hey, Mom.
Jake.
Got new patio furniture.
Right on.
What do you think it could be?
God knows I'm no expert.
I don't know. Uppers, downers?
Your guess is as good as mine.
I think we should check his arms
for needle marks.
Do we let him stay?
The Presbyterian Church
has those meetings.
So maybe on condition, you know?
If he agrees to attend.
I just don't know what to tell Jake.
-Hey.
-Hey. Good evening.
Well? Sleep well?
What time's--? What time is dinner?
In about an hour.
You know,
I could wash those clothes If you like.
They look a little lived in.
No, that's cool. Maybe later.
We are not doing this again.
We said we'd lay down the law,
we lay down the law.
We just have to be
consistent about It.
Hey.
You're not taking the bus?
All right. Well, listen.
Give me maybe another 20 minutes,
and we'll get out of here.
-All right.
Yeah, good.
You know, I just think that...
...thlngs have a way
of working themselves out.
When did you get this?
Last May at the year-end assembly.
They gave me that one too.
The one on the end.
Environmental Consciousness
Award.
What's that mean? What, you,
like, recycle cans and shit?
I contacted
The Albuquerque Journal...
...and asked what chemicals
they use to bleach their paper.
-Wound up writing an article about it.
-Right on, little bro.
Making mad inroads
with the business community.
All right.
Now, hey, remember...
...not all learning
comes out of books.
Look at you.
You know, we should--
We should hang out more often.
You know, just kick back and chill.
I mean, If you ever, like,
I don't know, need advice.
Because, you know, I've been--
I've been through it all. For real.
Yeah, man, you-- You play the flute?
-lt's a plccolo, actually.
-Dude, play some Jethro Tull.
Hey, guys, how we doing in here?
We're good.
-Jake?
-Yeah. Flne, Mom.
Well, that's good. That's great.
You know, what the hell?
You see this?
What am I,
some criminal or something?
-Whatever.
-Whatever?
What, you think that's okay?
Like, "Oh, we can't let that scumbag
warp the mind of our favourite son."
I'm the favourite?
Yeah, right.
You're practically
all they ever talk about.
Oh, snap.
Awesome.
-Yeah?
-Yo, man, It's me.
Hey, listen. You know that product?
You got any more of that?
No, man, okay?
I'm done giving out freebles.
You want charity,
go ask the Salvation Army.
No, no charlty. No.
I got this cousln,
he's got him some rich frlends.
These dudes are In town,
they're looking to party.
And your stuff is, like, so sweet.
So, what do you say?
You up for making some fat stacks?
Because they'll buy
everything you got.
Yes. Yes. Okay.
Oh, you can't be serious.
What the hell are you doing here?
Yo, I waited till the ball buster left.
I mean, no offence.
Who sent you, huh?
-You wearing a wire?
-Hey. Jesus.
-You settlng me up?
-Homo.
A wire? You want a wire?
I got a wire.
Speak Into the mike, bltch.
What the hell's wrong with you?
A wire.
Jesus.
-So who did you tell about...?
-Nobody. What, are you nuts?
Then why are you here?
I don't know.
To, llke, touch base.
Touch base?
Yeah, you know.
What they call a debrief.
Maybe we could, like--
Thought we could debrief.
Debrlef?
Wow, that's--
That's what you think we need,
debrlef?
Yeah, after what happened,
it just seems like the thing to do.
Kind of, you know, talk about it.
I mean, we can't talk to anybody else.
Anyway, that and I wanted to--
Wanted to, you know...
...tell you how much everybody digs
that meth we cooked.
Everybody digs the meth we cooked.
Seriously. I got dudes that would give
their left nut for a little more.
-Great.
-l'm just saying, I mean, If you ever...
...you know, saw your way clear...
...to, you know,
you and l cooking a little more....
Get the hell off my property.
-What? I'm just saying.
-Go. And don't come back.
All right.
All right, you know what?
Four grand.
Your share from selling that batch.
That's why I'm here.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Hey, I didn't smoke It all.
Non-small-cell adenocarcinoma.
Stage 3A, which means it's spread
from the lung to the lymph nodes.
There's no denying it's very serious.
But lt-- ls lt--?
It Is...
...curable?
I prefer the word "treatable."
But the treatments we have
at our disposal can be very effective.
Without making any promises,
I can tell you that the specific course...
...of radiation and chemotherapy I'm
going to suggest has been successful.
In certain cases, it's prolonged a
patient's life and resulted in remission.
What about the side effects?
Well, they can be mild
to practically non-existent.
Or they can be pretty darn awful.
It varies from patient to patient.
Typically, there's hair loss...
...which begins a couple of weeks
after the start of chemotherapy.
You may find yourself unusually
fatigued, not much energy.
You won't want to get out of bed.
You may lose weight due to reduced
appetite and certain intestinal issues.
Muscle aches and pains,
gums will get sore and bleed.
And, of course,
there's the possibility of nausea...
...although we'll prescribe an
antiemetic and try to counteract that.
Possible kidney or bladder irritation.
You may wind up with
increased bruising and bleeding.
There are maybe sexual symptoms.
Your skin may become dry....
Got anything to say?
What do you know about that?
-Nothlng.
-Well, that's not gonna fly this time.
How many chances
have we given you?
How many times have we
sat right here...
...and had the same conversation
over and over again?
Where you look us in the eye
and you plead ignorance?
And you play on our emotions...
...and tell us anything and everything
you think we want to hear...
...just so we'll give you
another chance.
And It makes us feel like fools.
Every time.
Enough, Jesse.
We are not going to have this
In our house.
We need you to leave.
Thanks for not telling on me.
You think I could have it back?
It's skunk-weed anyway.
The Alr Force ls aware
of the wldely-held bellef...
...that some of these
could be ﬂylng saucers from--
You know,
this Is actually very hopeful.
Nothlng concluslve
In the evldence...
...but probing and digesting
of information about UFOs...
...continues unceasingly.
Did you hear me?
I said this Is really
very, very hopeful.
Defence Command in
Colorado Springs issued an order--
So can I call them
and tell them you'll start next week?
Even as they did so,
the military wondered whether...
thelr sclentlﬂc know-how
and thelr best weapons...
...would be effective in any battle
of the Earth versus the flying saucers.
I just think that we need to discuss it
a little more, that's all.
What is there to discuss?
You're gonna get the best treatment,
and he's the best.
Well, there's the money discussion.
I think-- No, $90,000 out of pocket.
-Maybe more.
-There's a way, Walt.
There's flnanclng...
...there's instalment plans.
I could always go back to work.
-Walt, there's always a way.
-All right.
Skyler, say that there is a way.
And we spend all that money, and....
Am I supposed to leave you
with all that debt?
No. Honey.
I just don't want emotions ruling us.
Maybe treatment isn't the way to go.
Then why don't you just fucking dle,
already?
Just give up and die.
Come on, move your ass.
Name of the guy? You'll like him.
Yeah, dude, I'm not worried.
I got the best fricking attorney.
I would not want to be
on the other side of this one.
He's got this little team of ninjas, too,
that go out and do forward operations--
He's got crap on people.
What the hell?
-What?
-Don't go near It, buddy.
What--? What are you doing?
Call somebody. Call the fire people.
Yeah. I have a flre....
I don't believe this.
Do you know how much I paid for that?
Why are you doing this?