You want me to open the doors?
Here. The keys. Take them.
Why you talklng?
Gambling destroyed my life.
Me, my family, everything I loved.
It was Ilka a robbery,
only I was the thlaf.
It's amazing the stories you tell
yourself to justify it.
The lies that lead you
to just one more hand, one more spin...
...one more roll of the dice.
This is our deal, okay? Marie, no.
You guys are not llftlng a flngar.
I mean It.
Yeah, we're bringing everything. 80--
This is not up for debate, okay?
Great.
Sweetie, don't worry. We're not
gonna say one word about the bills.
We Just wanna brlng everyone
up to speed.
All right, I'll see you soon. Bye.
Tonight's the night. No turning back.
Well....
Okay. Let's do thla.
Okay. So first, I assign point values.
Correlate to the effect of removal.
-You're gonna apllt the elghta?
-8kyler, pleaae.
Now, the mathematical principle
known as the Kelly Criterion...
...upon whlch l devlaed
my own strategy--
Not dissimilar to the MIT system--
Walt, you're not teaching them.
-You wanted me to be thorough.
-Play. You're taking too long.
You don't think it behoves me
to be able to explain any of this?
lt behoves you to be a pro, that's all.
That's the fiction. So, chop-chop.
Don't chop-chop me.
Now, we both know
that the flrat declalon...
...la whether or not to apllt
or to surrender.
On eights. Split them.
Good on both.
Next decision is whether
to double down or not.
-Wh|ch you should be dolng.
-On an 11, yea. Double.
Okay, thla hand over here,
we have a soft 18.
The final decision is whether or not
to hit or to stand. Hit it.
-Becomea a hard 15.
-Dealer has a nlne.
I see that.
Hlt It.
Okay, let's see what I got.
And 21.
-Damn.
-Yup.
Okay, the key thing to remember here
is that it's not about any one hand.
The key la the number of hand:
per hour.
Let's go agaln.
Zero, mlnua one, 0.6.
Okay.
-Walt.
-lt'a not as If I don't know how to play.
I certainly more than understand
how to count cards.
Let's just keep going.
No, you know what?
I'm In recovery, remember?
I shouldn't even be playing.
And that is the fiction
that we should be sticking to.
You know what?
You're rlght. Yeah.
Okay.
We're not leavlng anythlng to chance.
All rlght. Let's get started.
Got a lot of....
-Walt. We got a lot of ground to cover.
-What is this?
We have to get our story straight.
We've gotta be on the same page.
-A scrlpt?
-Bullet polnts.
Bullet points? We got a novella.
This is smart. You really wanna try
to sell a DEA agent some...
...full-of-holes story
about how we suddenly...
...have enough money
to buy a car wash?
-Am I supposed to memorise this?
-We need to practise.
-We need to be word-perfect.
-W|th|n reason.
We need this story to be solid...
...and sympathetic
and, most of all, completely believable.
The story that you already told Marie.
You think that she hasn't told Hank?
Come on, thls |s Marle
we're talklng about here.
No, she hasn't. She hasn't.
Hank thinks his insurance is paying
for everything.
Marie's not telling him
we are paying his therapy bills.
-And nelther are we.
-And why Is that agaln?
-Really?
-If we have the gambllng story...?
Did you take money, Walt?
You remember Gretchen and Elliot?
I seem to recall that
you'd rather sell drugs than take help.
-F|ne.
-Marle wlll tell Hank In her own tlme.
And at least we'll have lald
the groundwork.
And comlng clean wlth Hank
and Junl--
Appearing to come clean
will be the best thing for everyone.
We talked about this.
-Okay? We agreed about thls.
-Yes, we dld. It's just....
What?
Never mind. Just--
Okay. So I really think we should
tag team the narrative, okay?
We'll each be responsible for certain
portions of the story and then we can--
We can hand off so we don't leave
anything out, and it'll seem natural.
Okay. So I'm gonna launch
wlth the excltlng news...
...that we are buying a car wash.
The next logical question
Hank will probably ask is:
"Where are you getting the money?"
To which I'll say:
We wanna tell you the whole story.
It's a doozy...
...so hold onto your hats.
Do you llke that?
Sure.
lt accomplishes two things. It keeps
it light while letting them know...
...to expect something big.
Yeah. No. It's a doozy.
Okay. Anyway, that's where you will
take over, starting with your diagnosis.
Pages one and two. Okay. And it's--
It's pretty much gonna run parallel
to the truth, which makes it easier.
But just make sure
to really hlt the cancer.
Really touch on the fear and despair.
It's good to remind them
and to get their sympathy.
We want them to understand why
you could do something so stupid.
Now, after that, per pages three
and four, after you say:
"Gambling became an addiction
and I just couldn't control it."
-Do you see that?
-Yes.
In the middle. Okay.
I put in that line about robbery,
from the GA meeting. That was good.
So next, l'll chime in about how
it affected our marriage...
...starting with the confusion, the
deceit, why we couldn't tell anyone--
I'm terrlbly, terrlbly ashamed
of my actlons.
-Yeah.
-Two 'terrlbly's?
-lt's to show contrition.
-Well, I just wouldn't use that word.
I would never say
the word 'terrlbly.‘
Phrase it however you want. Okay?
You're jumping ahead. Now--
And why--?
And why am I so ashamed?
Do I really need to answer that?
l was, and am,
provldlng for our famlly.
-Let's just pick up where we left off.
-l'm weak, I'm out of control.
This makes me look like crap.
This has to be a warts-and-all story.
That's how we'll sell It.
We both look bad.
How do you look bad exactly?
Where Is the 'I slept wlth my boss'
bullet polnt?
I can't seem to find that anywhere.
For a flred schoolteacher
who cooks crystal meth...
...l'd say you're comlng out
pretty much ahead.
I don't llke It.
I don't want Junlor thlnklng less of me.
At least you won at gambling. I'm the
bitch mom who wouldn't cut you slack.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
that I put you through all of thls.
How's that sound?
Two 'sorry's.
I believe we were on page five.
So after you say how very sorry you
are, in your own words, of course...
...we're almost to the end.
And then I say how proud lam of you
forjoining a 12-step programme.
And this is where I think we should
enact how we're feeling, you know?
Just a suggestion. You might
look down at the floor with remorse.
What? You don't have to mean it.
You just stare down at your feet,
Walt, okay?
Then I'm gonna....
l was thinking of taking Marie's hand
and saying something emotional like:
It's such a relief to tell you.
We're glad we have a strong famlly
to help us.
That we can all support each other.
And then maybe I'll tear up a little.
I don't know. We'll just have to see
what happens in the moment.
You're gonna cry on cue?
-I said, I don't know. Maybe.
-When you dab your eyes...
...you gonna do It
wlth your rlght hand or your left?
-One tear? Two tears? How many?
-This has to be convincing.
Especially to Hank.
I'm doing the best I can here, Walt.
And yes, I'm thorough.
Maybe lying doesn't come
as easily to me as it does to you.
-Guysl Come on In! HII
-Hey.
-Good to see you!
-Hey, you llttle punkl Hey.
-Hey.
-Great to see you.
-How you dolng?
Look at my llttle prlncess.
She's gettlng blg.
-Yeah. And heavy too.
-Is that actual food l'm smelling?
l mlght get an
honest-to-God meal here?
-You look good.
-Thank you, sweetheart.
Your Aunt Marie, she's cute,
but she could burn water.
You are so hilarious.
Show the boys your rock collection.
-We're gonna get organised.
-lt'll be 20 minutes.
-You have a rock collectlon?
-lt's a mlneral collectlon.
Just somethlng I've--
You wanna see It?
-Sure.
-All rlght. Let's go see It.
-Oh, hey, let me--
-Hey, no. l-- I got It.
Come on, guys. It's down the hall here.
Now, that one there, that's rhodonite.
Okay? lt's manganese inosilicate.
Cool. What makes It be
all plnk llke that?
Well, that's the manganese part. Okay?
lt oxidises, you know, like rust.
Manganese can have
an oxldatlon state...
...of between mlnus-three
and plus-seven...
...which takes it through a range
of colours. Purple, green, blue.
But its most stable state is plus-two,
which is usually pale pink.
Exactly. Whatever the hell he said.
Anyway, you get the idea.
Yeah, It's lnterestlng.
lnterestlng stuff, that. Really.
Oh, hey. Yeah, give me that.
lee me that flle, wlll you?
You gotta check thls out.
I've been working on something here.
I'm doing a little consulting.
You know, welghlng In on a case
for A.P.D.
Put that In for me.
Put that In over there.
Hank, what Is thls?
It's not a dead body?
Oh, no, no, no. Nothlng llke that.
No.
Thls Is good. Ready?
Let me get It golng here.
Look at thls guy.
Look at--
Oh, man.
You can't make thls stuff up.
Who Is thls?
That, my friends, is Albuquerque's
public enemy number one.
It's such a relief to finally tell you.
We're just so glad that we have
a strong family to help us through this.
That we can all support each other.
Jesus. I don't even know where to--
Holy shlt.
Yeah.
Walter H. White.
Man of hidden talents.
Dad, you're such a stud.
How much did you win exactly?
-Dad?
-I don't thlnk l have exact flgures.
It's enough to-- After taxes, of course,
to buy the car wash.
Maybe even pay for...
...a couple of halfway reasonable
college educations.
Damn, Dad, why'd you quit?
I can totally get a car
for my blrthday now, rlght?
Son, I'm terrlbly, terrlbly
ashamed of my actlons.
Would you excuse me, please?
I need to use the restroom.
Walt?
Heyl
Sorry.
-Thought you mlght have fallen In.
-No, no, ljust....
Hey, man, that was some big stuff
back there.
No, we wanted to be thorough, so....
Yeah, well, it was quite a tale. Couldn't
have been easy to, you know...
...talk about.
You know, Walt, if you....
You can always bend my ear, right?
I mean, if you ever need to talk...
...or just blow off some steam,
I'm here.
Not going anywhere, so....
Thanks, Hank.
Same goes for me, you know. If you
ever wanna bounce anything off me...
...I don't know, casework,
anythlng, really.
Sometlmes just talklng
somethlng through...
...you know,
really can make a dlfference.
We're definitely not talking bathtub
crank here. This is a big-ass operation.
You know, hundreds of pounds a week.
Maybe more.
So who is this person?
What do you know about him?
Other than he's deader
than a Texas salad bar...
...and has a decent set of pipes?
-l'd say he's my guy.
-Your guy?
There's this mystery man I've been
chasing for the better part of a year.
Cooks the purest meth that me
or anyone else has ever seen.
Goes by the name of Heisenberg.
Yeah. Pretty weird, huh?
I looked him up. It was one of these
physic-- One of Hitler's guys.
You know, a physicist named
Werner Heisenberg. Real cute, huh?
I figure with a handle like that,
my guy's gotta be some sort of....
Some sort of an egghead. No offence.
And here we go.
Gale 'Major Tom' Boettlcher.
Anyway, I just wanna see If I'm,
you know...
...not barking up the wrong tree,
chemically speaking.
As far as I can make out, he's writing
about a phenylacetone cook, right?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. That's pretty rare these days...
...but it does jibe
with the blue stuff I've been tracking.
"Two sticks dairy-free soy margarine,
two-third cup turbinado sugar."
It's a recipe for vegan s'mores.
There's all kinds of crazy crap in there.
Yeah, llke, you know,
top-ten recumbent blcycles...
...indoor composting tips.
All right next to the mother
of methamphetamine syntheses.
Thls guy was a....
Man, he was a real character.
Yeah, he seems unique.
Yeah. Let me show you somethlng.
lee It here.
nght here at the....
nght here at the top It says:
'To W.W.
My star, my perfect sllence.'
W.W.
I mean, who do you figure that is?
Woodrow Wilson?
Wllly Wonka?
Walter White?
You got me.
W.W.
Wait a minute. Let me see this...
...for a second,
because I thlnk I remembered....
Here.
Yes.
Yeah.
'When I Heard
the Learn'd Astronomer.‘
Learned.
And from time to time
Look'd up in perfect silence at the stars.
It's a poem by Walt Whitman.
Your W.W.
You freaking brainiac.
I must have skipped that day
in school or something.
I been chasing my tail about that one.
Bet you're right.
-Well, I'm glad I could be of help.
-Yeah.
Walt Whitman.
So you thlnk thls Gale person
Is your Helsenberg?
Yeah, lthlnk so. Yeah.
God, I wanted to get this guy.
It looks llke you dld.
No, I mean, you know, me personally,
you know?
I wanted to be the one to slap
the handcuffs on him, that kind of shit.
Popeye Doyle waving to Frog One.
If I recall, at least from the flrst
French Connection...
...Popeye Doyle never actually
caught hlm.
Yeah, I guess me
and old Popeye, huh?
Day late and a dollar short.
-What about the person who killed him?
-A.P.D.'s problem, not mine.
-Any leads?
-My buddy Tlm says...
...they got some flngerprlnts
they're trylng to ID.
Eyewitness saw a person of interest.
Might get lucky there.
Somebody knows something.
They'll track the shooter eventually.
Jesse.
What's up?
I need to talk to you.
Okay.
Would you stop doing
what you're doing, please?
I'm not done, yo.
And that dude's next.
-What the hell? What is wrong--?
-We have business to discuss.
So dIscuss. Jesus.
Let go of me.
Gale's murder is being investigated.
And I have it on good authority that
they found fingerprints at the scene.
Not mlne.
-We done here?
-No, we are not done here.
What If they are yours?
How can you be so sure?
Because I'm here. Your brother-in-law's
got such a hard-on for me...
...if the cops found my fingerprints--
If the cops found my prints
within five blocks of that place...
...they would've plcked me up
by now.
What about the casing?
-Oh, my God.
-Or caslngs?
How many tlmes
dId you shoot hlm, anyway?
Jesse, did you pick up the casings?
Did you pick them up?
Yeah, well....
Listen, we gotta go over this
step-by-step, everything.
Tell me exactly what happened
from the moment you got there.
-I got In, I got out.
-No.
No, I need to know specifics.
Now, we'll start from the beginning.
Jesse, I need you to concentrate.
Thls Is very Important.
DId you knock or rlng?
Knock or rlng?
Knock.
Good, good. That's very good.
Now, llsten.
Assume that Gale answered the door.
What happened after that?
Did he recognise you?
Did you say anything to each other?
Did you walk into the room or did you
shoot him right then and there?
What?
-Who wants to make a hundred bucks?
-Yeah.
Look, the kid's probably right.
If they had anything on him,
he'd be locked up already.
What about my brother-in-law?
He suspects Jess--
Hell, he knows Jesse is involved
in the sale of blue meth.
That was Hank's one-and-only lead.
What if he puts two and two together...
...and he goes after Jesse
for the murder?
Goes after hlm how,
on hls Rascal scooter?
That perhaps sounded insensitive.
But if he goes after him,
I'll sue his ass for police brutality...
...harassment,
assault and 16 other thlngs.
No, history those two have together,
being what it is...
...gotta figure your brother-in-law's
smart enough not to go down that road.
Goose egg. Bubkes.
That's what the cops got.
I wouldn't worry about it.
Yeah, what else should I
not worry about, Saul?
Should I not worry that Gus plans to
murder me at the first chance he gets?
That my drug-addicted partner doesn't
seem to care whether he lives or dies?
You should see hls house.
It's llke skld row.
He has actual hobos living there.
Now, how long before Gus decides
that he's too big of a risk?
Jeez, I got Mike,
that grunting, dead-eyed cretin...
...sucker-punching me in the face.
I've got Gus wielding a box cutter.
I mean, Western Unlon,
message recelved.
Let me ask you.
When did this stop being a business?
Why am I the only person capable
of behaving in a professional manner?
No, any way you sllce It,
everyone Is In danger.
I mean, how can I protect anyone?
My family, Jesse, myself?
My name never comes up
with those guys, does it?
And meanwhile, we're buying
this stupid car wash.
Oh, yeah.
That shlp has saIIed, bon voyage.
We are committed.
We already told our family about it.
And now Skyler,
I'm sure she belleves--
She needs to believe
that everything is neat and tidy.
And she's telling herself that
I work in this nice, quiet little lab...
...wlth a whlte lab coat
and a pocket protector...
...and when my contract is up,
I'll just simply hang it all up...
...tip my hat and walk away.
Oh, God.
How dId everythlng
get so screwed up?
Yeah, you do have a little
shit-creek action happening.
You know, FYI,
you can buy a paddle.
Thls Is a last-resort,
back-pocket klnd of thlng...
...but if you really gotta protect
yourself, disappear....
There's a guy who can make it happen.
They call him a "dissapearer."
For a substantial fee,
and I do mean substantial...
...you and your loved ones can vanish.
Untraceable.
I mean, he sets you up
wlth a whole new llfe.
What, llke a wltness protectlon
klnd of thlng?
Beyond. I mean, off the grid.
New identities, new everything.
No one would ever be able to trace you.
Now, be clear. This is an end game,
if you get my meaning.
I mean, there's no coming back.
So you want his card?
God, there's gotta be something else
that I can do.
Some way to keep everything
from spiralling out of control.
Well, from what you told me...
...it sounds like Pinkman is first up
in the imminent-demise department.
Gus won't rlsk
lettlng the pollce flnd Jesse.
I know him. He won't.
I'm not kidding. If you really
think about it, you can't even see it.
How can you know how bad
radio frequencies, microwaves...
...and cell phones are getting you?
You could be strolling
through security at the airport--
Hey, wake up, bitches.
You get waved through a full-body
x-ray scanner.
Next day, you could be dead or dying
from all the radiation they say is safe.
But there's no way it could be.
It has to deliver a concentrated dose.
Enough to penetrate clothes.
The accumulated amount could be
dangerous to susceptible individuals...
-...especlally from a rural area.
-Yo.
The ozone layer is already thin
because of the cow farts.
-YoI
-Oh, hey.
Make sure there's plzza here
when I get back.
-All rlght? Enough for everybody.
-Oh, yeah.
I can do that. I can definitely do that.
Not a problem.
I can get the stuff, the pizza and stuff.
But as far as the flnanclal sltuatlon,
you know....
-Just hang on. Hang on.
-Yeah, yeah.
And you know,
the concentrated doses...
...it's gonna fuck with your bone
marrow and it's gonna mess up....
Because-- Because especlally
If you have cancer.
You know, because if you gotta get
a bone-marrow transplant...
...your odds are 60 percent.
You got a 60 percent chan--
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Get some dipping sticks too, yo.
Yeah, I can deflnltely get
dlpplng stlcks.
All right. I can get them.
Hey, smoke it up, bitches.
Gotchal
Wake up.
What's up?
What's up with your ear?
Downstairs. Now.
Where is everybody?
I invited your guests to leave.
Know who this is?
-Nope.
-You ought to.
He's been at your house
for three solld days.
Okay.
He stole your money.
That $78,000 or so look familiar?
-Thls Is It?
-That's It.
Okay. Thanks.
Wanna know what's next for
Little Miss Pissed-in-His-Pants?
-No.
-You sure, now?
-Yep.
-Don't even wanna take a wlld guess?
You're gonna kill him.
Is this the part where
I'm supposed to beg you not to do it?
Oh, please, please.
And then what?
I'm supposed to promlse,
cross my heart...
...to stralghten up and fly rlght
or toe the HM...
...or some other crap
that I'm not gonna say?
Is that what your little show here
was all about?
You're on thin ice, you little shithead.
You know that?
You aln't gonna smoke
that dude In there.
You know how come I know?
Because you went through the trouble
of putting a blindfold on him.
I'm going back to bed.
Let yourselves out.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
-How's the ear?
-Mendlng.
What can I do for you?
It's Plnkman.
He's become increasingly incautious.
He's a rlsk. A lIabIlIty.
I know he and Walter come as a team
and that Walter won't like it...
...but something's gotta be done.
You gotta be kidding.
Hey, it's me. Wait for the thing.
nght.
Thls Is message number three.
You'd better be ready in two minutes,
because I am right outside your door.
Jesse.
Jessel
Damn It.
Hey, it's me. Wait for the thing.
Oh, great.
Jessel
Thls Is perfect.
You are a pIece of work,
you know that?
Jesse?
Jesse.
Hey, it's me. Wait for the thing.
Where Is he?
Gonna ask where we're going?