Hore': my resume.
l moan, technlcally It says
'currlculum vltaa'...
...whlch l thlnk I: more profaulonal,
but, you know...
...same thing, pretty much.
That's" Wow, grant.
This position truly is a
no-experience-necessary kind of thing.
And it doesn't really say it here...
...but I havo a solid background
In sales.
I'm pretty much a self-starter, so....
-That'e excellent, but--
-Excellent.
ljuet...
...I really feel I could be a major...
...major asset to your sales force.
I'm thinking there's
a little misunderstanding.
This isn't actually a sales job.
I mean, I'd be happy to consider you
for a sales position...
...but all our agents
need to be licensed...
...have at least two years
on-the-Job experience...
...and usually a college degree.
What you'll be doing is more like...
...advertlslng.
Hey, Jesse.
Hey, man.
Yo, man.
-What up?
-Badger?
Where you been keeping yourself?
Yeah, you too.
Thanks.
Yo, why would you wanna do
this lame-ass job, anyway?
I mean, no offence.
Because I'm on probation, yo.
I gotta prove to the man
I'm rehabilitated.
Upstanding citizen, all that shit.
It's really good exercise too.
You can't just stand there,
you have to spin the arrow.
There's all these moves
you have to learn, like "the helicopter."
Yeah. See, yeah?
That one's a bitch.
I'm not very good at it yet.
You really opened my eyes
to the possibilities.
-Yeah.
-Hey, anyways...
-...thanks for the toke.
-Any time.
Speaking of which...
...you think you could maybe
hook me up with some crystal?
No, I've been out of the business
for a while.
Actually, now thinking about retiring.
-What? No.
-Yeah.
That stuff you made is unbelievable.
It was pretty awesome.
Retirement?
I can't be hearing this.
No, man, I had this partner
who was helping me cook.
I mean, I was doing
most of the work...
...but he was an asshole, so.
Anyway, I mean, pseudo's getting
harder and harder to come by and--
Yo, I can hook you up
with some pseudo.
Major pseudo.
I got channels, bro.
We could partner up.
No pressure.
Just think about It, all right?
Oh, shit. I gotta go.
Yo, this way to savings.
Save your dollar bills, y'all.
Blg savings
This way and save
Come on! Save some money.
It's a stupid glft.
No, it isn't. He'll love it.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Dldn't the Invitation
even say 'no glfts'?
-Walt.
-What?
We have to go.
I know, I'm not complaining.
Yes, you are.
Look, we need this.
We've been through a lot
lately. Okay?
Jesus, guess we didn't get
the 'belge' memo.
We're okay.
Yes, I look like I'm wearing
a prom dress from 1985.
Honey, you look fine.
Walt, this is the only thing
I could find that fit me.
God, would you look at that.
The invitation said "no gifts."
So? Come on.
Sir, I'll take that for you.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Oh, look, there's Elliott.
Oh, come on, let's go say hello.
Elliott.
Walt.
You made It.
Happy birthday.
-Wouldn't mlss It for the world.
-Skyler.
HI. Oh, that's right.
Great to see you.
You look beautiful, as always.
Well, these days a little more big
than beautiful, but....
Of course, congratulations.
That was such great news.
-Thank you.
-Gretchen, look who's here.
It's been ages.
Oh, it's so good to see you.
It's really good.
Skyler, welcome. Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's really nice to be here.
-When are you due?
-In about 10 more weeks.
And actually, we recently found out
that It's a girl.
-0h, that's so wonderful.
-Yeah.
Yeah, we've been thinking about it
for ourselves.
Yeah, thinking about it.
0h, hey, by the way...
...securlng that patent
was Just amazing.
I mean, the work
that your company |s do|ng....
Congratulations to both of you.
-Hard work and a lot of luck. A lot.
-Yeah. Oh, well, now.
Elllott.
Excuse us, we gotta say hi.
Make yourselves at home,
we'll catch up.
Sure, sure. Okay.
-0kay.
-So glad you're here.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
John, Missy. How are you?
Shall we?
Walt?
I thought that was you.
Farley.
Long time no see.
-Thls |s Walter White.
-Hello.
Back at Caltech, he was--
You were Just a master
of crystallography.
I remember this one time we were
stuck on this protein problem...
...for weeks.
...and you had one word for us....
Synchrotrons.
It was synchrotrons, yeah.
They generate pure and more complete
patterns than x-ray beams.
Data collection
takes a fraction of the time.
This is the White in Gray Matter.
-Tell them, Walt.
-0kay.
Well, back when Elliott and l
were in grad school...
...we came up with the name.
Schwartz, black. Walter White.
So together they became
Gray Matter Technologies.
-Cute, huh?
-So you run the company with Elliott?
No. No, that's Gretchen and Elliott.
Yeah, yeah. You know,
I gravitated toward education.
What university?
Oh, wow, it's a Stratocaster.
Not Just any Strat.
That's one of Clapton's.
No way.
"To Elliott, sorry about the buckle rash,
Eric Clapton."
Thank you. This is beautiful.
-Why Is he doing this?
-Beautlful.
What is he, like, 8 years old?
Here, honey.
Thanks.
Oh, this is from Walt.
-0h, God.
-lt's okay.
Hey.
Let's see what we got.
Yum Good Ramen.
This is what Wait and I lived on...
...for 10 months straight...
...whlle we were working
on our thesis.
Sold them down at Ralstow's
in the hardware isle.
Right next to the-- What was it?
-Sterno. Yeah.
-The Sterno.
Yeah, ten for a dollar ninety-nine.
To this day,
I am convinced these noodles...
...were responsible for our success.
This was our lifeblood.
Man, where'd you find these? I thought
they'd been outlawed years ago.
I love It.
Thank you, Walt.
Well.
For the man who has everything.
-No, no, no.
-It was.
-No, you remember the fat guy.
-Yes.
We used to call him Snot Trough.
He had that thing under his nose.
-What do you call that thing?
-That was Dobkins.
That was the same guy
who always smelled like chocolate milk.
-It was.
-No, no, no.
It wasn't Dobkins, it was....
Anyway, I swear to Christ,
he used to iron those patches...
...onto the elbows
of his members-only Jacket...
...because he thought it made him
look distinguished.
-Dldn't It? I thought lt--
-No.
Oh, God.
Well, here's to Snot Trough.
-To Snot Trough.
-Wherever you may be.
Do you remember the professor who
used to hate Robert Wilhelm Bunsen?
Yes. All you had to do
was mention the Bunsen burner...
...and he was off on a rant.
"Oh, he didn't invent it."
Do you remember the waving?
"He just improved it," you know.
It was easy to kill 15 minutes.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
I miss this, Walt.
Yeah. Me too.
Listen, we ought to get together
more often.
Skyler and I would love
to have you and Gretchen...
...over for dinner sometime.
Oh, sure, yeah, absolutely.
But, you know, what I mean is that
you and I should work together again.
-Are you gonna teach high school?
-No, no, no, seriously.
What's stopping us?
Wait a minute, Elliott,
what are you--?
Are you asking me to come work
for you at Gray Matter?
Yeah, why not? You'd fit right in.
You're brllllant,
you got a ton of experience.
Well...
...I wouldn't really know
where to begin.
God, you have no idea.
I spend my days just drawing out
atoms on the chalkboard...
...and trying to get these kids to learn
the periodic table.
Look, I understand.
You're a little rusty,
but you're not seeing the upside here.
We could really benefit
from a new set of eyes.
You know when you've
been trying to crack some problem...
...for months on end,
you get tunnel vision.
One guy thinking outside of the box,
you may be exactly what we need.
Well, listen, Elliott, it--
The offer Is very appealing,
It really ls, I thank you.
But there's....
There's something you should know.
l have some personal issues.
Look, there's nothing
we can't work out.
Well, yeah, but...
...lt's complicated.
We can help you.
We have excellent health insurance.
The best.
Hey, did you try those
prosciutto-wrapped flgs?
They were, like, wow.
They were just--
I must have had about 30
of those suckers.
Oh, and the seafood table,
did you see that?
They had lobster tail,
they had crab legs, like, shrimp.
They had....
-Walt.
-What the hell did you say to Elliott?
-What?
-You told him about the cancer...
...didn't you? Didn't you?
I can't believe It.
Okay, we were talking,
he asked how you were doing...
...and lam sorry, but I don't have
the best poker face these days...
...where that's concerned.
He knew something was wrong
with you, and he pressed me.
He pressed you? Come on.
Walt, when it came right down to it...
...I didn't know what to do
but tell him the truth.
The truth? Well, how about
you just said, "He's fine," huh?
You could have said that. "He's fine."
It would have been done.
I don't like the way you're talking.
I don't like the way you talk
about private affairs...
...to people who are not
even In our lIves anymore.
Well, what exactly did he say to you?
-He offered me a job.
-What?
Yes. Kind of like some flg leaf,
you know.
Some face-saving bullshit...
...that allowed me
to generously accept his charity.
And then when I turned that down,
he flat out...
...offered to pay for my treatment.
Which is exactly what
you expected him to do, didn't you?
-Walt.
-Dldn't you?
-No. I did not put him up--
-Please. Come on. Come on.
Okay, what did you say?
Walt?
What do you think I said?
Why? Wait.
-Ready to go?
-l'm taking the bus.
Okay.
Bye, honey.
Hey, dude. Are these bullet holes?
No, man. Those are for,
like, you know...
...ventllatlon.
Cool.
Nlce setup, huh?
-Man.
-Thls Is nothing, man.
I used to have, like,
twice as much glassware...
...until my dumb-ass ex-partner drove
us into a ditch and wrecked most of it.
Big-ass beaker, huh?
Hey, wait, wait, no, that's--
Yeah, that's a boIlIng flask.
This Is a beaker.
Here's a Griffin beaker.
Here's a volumetric beaker.
Here's an Erlenmeyer flask.
You got--
You really know your shit.
It's just basic chemistry, yo.
...you got something for me?
Hells, yeah.
Okay.
We're in business.
Right on, Badger.
Dude, check this out.
Jesus.
-What are you bringing that for?
-Huntlng.
We might see javelinas.
Are you gonna help me or what?
Hey.
Badgeﬂ
Yeah, buddy. Yeah.
Let's see the money.
Here.
I need flve each.
Come on, two more.
Here.
What about him?
Are you kidding?
He looks younger than us.
Whatever.
What about that guy?
No, he looks like a businessman.
So what?
So, businessmen
are always In a hurry.
They're always, like, going
to some meeting or something.
Seriously, he's just gonna say no.
Hey, hey, this guy.
This Is our guy.
You're up.
Why do I have to do it?
Give me the crutches
and I'll go do It.
Shlt.
Excuse me, hey...
...we forgot our IDs,
and we were wondering...
...If you could do us a favour
and buy us a six-pack?
You know,
what you're asking Is Illegal.
No, It's not.
Yeah, It Is.
Oh, shit.
Guess you win the jackpot.
This Is not how I wanted to spend
my night off.
Consider this your first
and last warning.
-Yes, sir.
-You're lucky you got a good dad, here.
The other guys had to run.
I couldn't talk my way out of it.
Not cool, man. Not cool.
What, you never tried to buy beer
when you were my age?
I'm talking about you calling me
and not your father.
How do you think
that'd make him feel?
I don't even know what to say to you.
Just go.
l'll deal with you later.
Where's Walt?
I haven't seen him since this morning.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Listen, do me a favour, all right?
Don't tell him about the kid.
He's just a teenager
trying to score some beer.
You know...
...growlng palns.
I mean, he finds out his dad's sick,
he starts acting out, you know?
First the pot, then this.
The pot?
-You told me the kid was smoking.
-That's what Skyler told me.
-I mean, you may as well have.
-I wasn't talking about Walter, Jr.
l was talking about Walt.
Excuse me?
He admitted it.
He said he liked it.
Walt?
Shlt.
I didn't think he had it in him.
-lt's like he's not himself lately.
-Yeah.
...why would anyone in their right mind
choose not to do treatment?
Especially when
It's completely paId for.
Why is he doing this?
You know what we need to do?
What we really need to do
is sit him down, all of us...
...and get everything out
on the table.
-You mean an Intervention?
-No, no.
Just a family meeting.
Where everyone
can voIce their concerns...
...and be heard.
You are a genius, bro.
This cankenstein is unreal.
When we get back,
I'm gonna burn that suit...
...because we're gonna
make some mad dough.
It's not right.
What do you mean,
It's not right?
It's cloudy.
It's not supposed to be cloudy.
Okay, that last time, it was glass.
So what? Cloudy, not cloudy?
It looks good enough to me.
Walt, walt.
Yo, what are you doIng?
Are you out of your mind?
I totally would've smoked that.
It's not for you,
It's for our customers.
They're gonna demand
a certain standard.
What? What--? What are you--?
-What?
-We'll just do It agaln.
Until we get it right.
Walt.
Please have a seat and join us.
-We can do better.
-Don't you fucking think about it.
-Hey.
-Come on.
Three entire pounds
of pseudo wasted.
Do you know how long
I had to spIn that sIgn?
-Get off me, psycho.
-Hellcopter, bltchl
Asshole.
Open the door.
Come back here, you bitch!
I'm gonna mess you up!
This Isn't funnyl
I really need to understand
your thought process...
...because clearly I don't.
I feel that this decision
you've made...
...lt's not In the best Interest
of our entire family.
-Look, Skyler--
-Not yet, please. l--
l have the talking pillow.
Everybody gets to speak their minds,
remember?
And then you'll get your chance.
Money has always been
an issue for us, I'll give you that.
But now that Elliott is more than willing
to pitch in--
Wait, I know, I understand
that it's hard for you to accept help.
Maybe it's the way you were raised.
But, honey...
...lt's okay to lean on people
now and again.
You need this treatment.
And nothing can stop you
from getting It...
...except you.
-Am I allowed to respond?
-In a minute.
I think we need
to go around the cIrcle first.
Hank, would you like to start?
Yeah. Okay, well....
-What I would say Is--
-Take the talking plllow.
All right, look, buddy...
...I know I don't get to
tell you this enough...
...but I care about you.
A hell of a lot.
And this cancer thing....
Let's just-- Let's face it, you know,
you were dealt a shit hand.
But...
...sometimes your luck can change.
I mean, I can't tell you how many times
lwas-- I started with a shit hand...
...and I ended up with a, you know,
a full house. Okay?
I mean, the key ls,
you gotta hang In there.
Man, you gotta keep placing your bets,
keep placing your bets.
-...what the hell are you saying?
-Please, Marie, let him talk.
That's what we're here to do. Please.
All right, look at it this way, okay?
It's the bottom of the ninth,
bases are loaded...
...you're up.
But you got a bum arm, right?
There's no fricking way
you're gonna hit a homer, okay?
So you can either let the pinch hitter
take the bat...
...or you can hold on to your pride
and lose the game.
You get what I'm saying?
You got your pride, man.
I get It, okay? I get It.
But this Daddy Warbucks
wants to chip in, man.
I'm with your old lady on this one.
I say take the money and run, man.
Somebody wanna take this thing?
Here.
Yes, Waiter--
Walter, Jr., I'm sure that you have
about a million things to say, probably.
And now is your chance.
Go ahead. Just let it all out.
This Is bullshit.
-All right, come on.
-lt's all right.
lt--
Talk.
Tell your dad how you feel.
-l'm pissed off.
-Tell him.
I'm pissed off.
Because you're being....
You're--
You're a pussy.
You're, like, ready to give up.
You're-- God.
What if you gave up on me, huh?
This here...
...and you're scared
of a little chemotherapy?
Me, personally...
...I think you should do
whatever you wanna do.
What?
You told us to be honest
about our feelings.
Walt's the one with cancer,
It's his decision.
It's not up to any of us.
-Why In hell would you do this?
-Hey, hey.
I wasn't planning
on agreeing with Walt.
After sitting and listening
to you all talk about his future...
-...llke he has no say In lt--
-He's not gonna have a future...
...if he doesn't get treatment.
lam a medical professional.
l x-ray people In treatment
every day.
I see them every day.
And you know what?
Some of them
are absolutely mIserable.
-Marle--
-l'm sorry, but It's true.
And some of them don't wanna spend
their last weeks or months...
...being picked at by doctors.
But they got talked Into It
by their families.
Can I get the pillow back?
I agree with Marie.
-Thank you.
-Hank--
What? Maybe Walt wants to die
like a man.
I don't want him to die at all.
That's the whole point of this.
So either help or leave.
Skyler, ljust wanted
to do you the courtesy...
...of giving you my honest opinion.
You know, Marle,
this Is not debate club.
-This is my husband's life--
-I made one simple observation--
-And it's like you-- How dare you--
-Okay, so we disagree--
Ladlesl Marlel
This Is so stupid.
All right,
I've got the talking plllow now.
Okay?
We all, In this room...
...we love each other.
We want what's best for each other,
and I know that.
lam very thankful for that.
But what I want--
What I want, what I need...
What does that mean?
Sometimes I feel like I never
actually...
...make any of my own choices...
My entire life...
...It just seems I never...
...you know, had a real say
about any of It.
Now, this last one, cancer...
...all I have left Is
how I choose to approach this.
Then make the right choice, Walt.
You are not the only one it affects.
What about your son?
Don't you wanna see your daughter
grow up? I just....
Of course I do.
Skyler, you've read the statistics,
you....
These doctors...
...talking about "surviving"...
...one year, two years,
like it's the only thing that matters.
But what good is it to just survive
if I am too sick to work?
To enjoy a meal?
To make love?
For what time I have left...
...I wanna live in my own house.
I wanna sleep in my own bed.
I don't wanna choke down
30 or 40 pills every single day...
...and lose my hair...
...and lie around,
too tired to get up...
...and so nauseated
that I can't even move my head.
And you.
Cleaning up after me.
And me? What--?
Some dead man,
some artlflclally-allve--
Just marking tlme.
And that's
how you would remember me.
That's the worst part.
So that Is my thought process,
Skyler.
I'm sorry. ljust....
I choose not to do it.
All right.
'All right' what?
I'll do the treatment.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay.
The lady from the billing office...
...said they usually bill
the insurance company directly.
But since our HMO's not paying for it,
we can pay up front with a credit card.
Oh, and then Elliott
will send a cheque.
I will take care of it.
Walter White?
Yes.
Okay.
-All right.
-Okay.
-See you In a minute.
Okay.
Elllott.
Wait, it's Gretchen.
Oh, hey.
Hey, Gretchen, how are you?
You know, it was really great seeing
you two the other day, you know.
Wow, what a party.
Elliott told me about the cancer.
I'm so sorry.
Well, you know...
...It Is what It ls, I guess.
I don't know what to say.
Except, I'm always here for you.
Both of us are.
We wanted you to know that.
Yeah, well, thank you.
Walt, Elliott told me that he'd offered
to pay for the treatment.
You have to accept.
That money,
as far as we're both concerned...
...that belongs to you.
Even the name of our company,
It's half yours.
Wait?
Is this about you and me?
Gretchen, I really appreciate
the offer.
I do. But we're fine.
As it turns out,
the insurance came through after all.
...I am covered. And....
We", and, anyway,
i really appreciate it, i really do.
Thank you.
Good. That's good news.
You know,
that really was a great party.
-Keep In touch, okay?
-Sure. Sure, and...
...thank you for calling.
YoI
Wanna cook?