Why?
Why I: thl: stlll under dllcuulon?
I don't Ilka hlm.
I don't care who he knows.
We're Iuppoud to trust
hlm wlth our products.
Blg Ganerallulmol
Blg try cook I: more Ilka It.
The 'Chlckon Man.‘
You wlll do what you want.
But you havo my vote.
Nevar trust a South Amarlcan.
Dlrty, dlrty paoplo.
He broke my toyl He broke my toyl
He was Just havlng tun.
You'll get ovar It.
No! I hate hlm! lwlsh he was doad!
Marco.
Grab your old unclo a bear,
would you?
No, no. A cold one.
Thls Is what you wantcd.
Your hrothcr dcad. nght?
You're golng to havc to
try hardcr than that...
...ll' you want to savc hlm.
How much longer do you thlnk
he has down there?
One mlnute? Maybe more? Maybe less?
Famlly Is all.
Hey, you got nothlng on me, yo.
All rlght, you can call my lawyer,
Saul Goodman.
Talk to my lawyer, all rlght?
You hear me? I got nothlng to say.
I told you, you can call my--
Chrlstl
You got my cell phone number,
my wll'e's name! How dld you do It?
Talkl Who you worklng wlth?l
Yes, slr.
If you're ready to talk...
...they wanna get a statement.
Your slde of what happened here.
Or we can hold them off
tlll another tlme.
Maybe you wanna talk to a lawyer.
There It Is.
Yo, Adrlan.
Rocky called,
he wants hls l'ace back.
Come on, I gotta cheer you up.
You see that?
That's your get-out-ot-Jall-l'ree card.
You understand
get-out-ot-Jall-l'ree card?
I mean, Just bllnk once
If you're l'ollowlng.
The DEA's worst nlghtmare
Is that face out In publlc.
They'll have to steer a wlde berth
of young Master Plnkman...
...l'or tear of the PR poop storm
that wlll raln down on them...
...ll' thls story ever gets out.
I mean, thls beatlng?
Best thlng for you.
You're home free.
Good, rlght?
nght.
Oh, my God.
You're now the cute one of the group.
Paul, meet Rlngo. Rlngo, Paul.
Thls ls-- l--
Jesse, l'm-- I am so sorry for thls.
Thls should not have happened.
But It dld.
No thanks to you.
But the plan dld work.
We would've been locked up rlght now
If we dldn't lure hlm away. But thls--
Thls-- I Just--
I never saw thls comlng.
What"?
What happens now?
I'll tell you what happens now.
Your scumbag brother-ln-law
ls l'lnlshed.
You understand?
lwlll own hlm when thls ls over.
Every cent he earns...
...every cent hls wll'e earns...
Anyplace he goes...
...anywhere he turns...
...l'm gonna be there...
...grabblng my share.
He'll be scrubblng tollets ln TIJuana
l'or pennles...
...and I'll be standlng over hlm...
...to get my cut.
...and when he crawls to sleep
In whatever rat hole ls left for hlm...
...after I shred hls house down.
lwlll haunt hls crusty ass...
...l'orever...
...untll the day...
...he stlcks a gun up hls mouth...
...and pulls the trlgger...
...Just to get me out of hls head.
That's what happens next.
My advlce:
That's probably
not a good strategy.
They're scared of you rlght now.
They want nothlng to do wlth you.
But It you hlt them...
...they're forced to hlt back hard.
I mean, they wlll turn over every rock
hlther, thlther and yon...
...untll someone spllls the beans on you
and anyone assoclated wlth you...
...present company Included.
Yes, lthlnk what Saul ls saylng
makes a lot of sense.
Jesse, move on wlth your llI'e.
Leave It behlnd, all of It.
Nothlng changes...
...once I walk out of here.
I get myself a new RV
and go start cooklng agaln.
How exactly do you thlnk...
...you're golng to get away wlth that?
They wlll catch you.
-So what?
-What?
l have a get-out-ot-Jall-I'ree card.
Hey, I may have overstated
the power of your face.
Not thls.
II' the cops catch me...
...l glve them
what they want the most.
You.
They nab me...
...to glve up the great Helsenberg...
...and hls mllllon-dollar drug rlng.
You're my free pass...
...bltch.
You're so sure.
Look, II' he dldn't glve up my name
whlle Hank was beatlng hlm...
...he's never golng to talk.
What do you thlnk that was, a bluff?
He wants your brother-ln-law.
And there's gonna be lawyers...
...creamlng thelr Underoos
for a case llke that.
I'd take It myself If It wouldn't
cause so much collateral damage.
And hlm cooklng agaln?
Hey, when, not If, he gets caught,
and he's faclng 20 years...
...what'll he do then? Belleve me,
there's no honour among thleves.
Except for us, of course.
He'll come around.
And If he doesn't...
...there may come a tlme
to talk optlons.
Optlons?
I'm convlnced
Mr. Plnkman was Involved...
...In the manufacture and dlstrlbutlon
of phenyl-2 methamphetamlne...
...speclflcally what we call
the blue meth.
l tracked hlm to a scrap yard...
...where he stored
an early-'80s camper...
Whlle waltlng for a warrant
to search thls vehlcle...
...whlch l belleve to be
a rolllng meth lab...
...l recelved a telephone call...
...telllng me my wlfe Marle
had been Injured In an accldent.
Upon hearlng the news...
...I left Mr. Plnkman
and hls vehlcle to tend to my wlfe.
Arrlvlng at the hospltal, I learned
the emergency call was a hoax.
My wlfe, fortunately, was unharmed.
So I lmmedlately went back to
the salvage yard, but the RV was gone.
Most llkely destroyed on slte.
And It was at thls polnt you drove
to the home of Jesse Plnkman?
Agent Schrader needs to get home...
...get some rest.
That's flne. But Just to conflrm,
you're taklng the Flfth here?
Yeah, that's correct.
Okay. Well...
...we Just wanna glve you all
a heads up.
Mr. Plnkman ls presslng charges
In thls matter.
He's glven a detalled verslon
of events as he sees them.
The word of a meth head.
We know all about hls hlstory.
We're well aware,
but toxlcology on Plnkman....
Hls blood ls clean, he's not uslng.
The kld ls even refuslng hls
doctor-ordered paln meds...
...far as we can tell.
...where do we go from here?
A couple of gentlemen
from OPR wlll come down...
...probably tomorrow mornlng.
Janlce wlll glve us an exact tlme.
And you men wlll be contlnulng
your lnvestlgatlon, so....
-Thanks for your tlme.
-nght. We Just--
We need one more thlng.
A photo of Agent Schrader's hands.
For the record.
Yes, of course.
Bandage off, If you would.
0n the table ls flne.
Flat on the table. That's flne.
It's all gonna work out.
You've been too good to them
for too many years.
I hope It goes wlthout saylng we're not
talklng to anybody about thls, okay?
Okay.
Marle...
...who?
Do you have a mlnute?
Sure.
I guess crlme does pay.
I don't suppose you Just came by
to Insult me.
No. We need to talk.
You heard about Hank?
About what happened
wlth thls Jesse Plnkman?
Yes, I know.
Whatever Hank was lnvestlgatlng...
...hlm trylng to flnd an RV...
...Is there any danger...
...that could lead back to you?
Why would It?
ls thls why you're here?
I'm here to talk about Hank.
You know what's gonna happen to hlm
If thls Plnkman presses charges?
Hank could lose everythlng.
I thought maybe...
...there's a way you could help hlm.
How?
Contact Plnkman.
Get hlm to drop the charges.
I don't know what klnd of relatlonshlp
you plcture me havlng wlth thls person.
-l'm not asklng.
-He was-- He's-- He's not my frlend.
-lt's not as If we were even close.
.|'m..
I'm not asklng.
But there must be somethlng
you could say.
Isn't It even worth a try?
Hank Is your famlly.
Not currently.
What?
l sald, not currently.
I'm late. I have to go.
l was startlng to get worrled.
Car trouble.
Oh, that's a bummer.
You should call me next tlme.
I'll plck you up.
No sandals today?
IJust thought....
A blt more professlonal.
Well, everythlng Is on track.
We got our dlstlllate.
Just waltlng to--
Let's get our trays ready.
-CIean, no molsture.
-Done.
Is our...?
Our solvent flltered?
I thought you mlght ask that.
That's good.
Hand In glove,
that's what we strlve for.
You know, thls mlght be the beglnnlng
of a beautlful frlendshlp.
So you the gentlemen?
Lucky you boys caught me,
I got a load to plck up In Memphls.
I can hammer It out In about 15,
but there's thls glrl, Lolly. Maybe Fran.
She's got thls fetlsh,
she llkes to get peed on.
l was hoplng to see her tonlght
but she wants to sleep before 10...
...so I wanna wrap It up here ASAP
because trafflc can be a wlld card.
Thlng ls, women who llke to get peed on
tend to be from the warmer cllmates.
You'd thlnk the ones In colder zones
would be more lncllned.
Maybe It's a shock
If the body's not accllmated...
...but, you know, I leave that
for smarter mlnds than me.
Sclence Is a mystery.
Well, take a gander.
Prlces are negotlable.
Buylng In bulk gets you a dlscount.
I'm runnlng a speclal on these honeys.
JHPs. Hollow-polnt bullets,
known as Black Death. Check It out.
lee that?
So sweet, you wanna llck It.
Nlckel-plated brass caslng,
Lubalox coat.
Sucker has slx razor claws
that expand upon Impact:
Shred your mama's head
llke a cabbage.
Keep It. On the house.
But I been wlndJammlng enough.
Tell me what you're looklng for,
what It Is you need.
Vests.
Vests? Hell, yeah, we got vests.
nght here.
Sleek, comfortable, thermally bonded,
non-Interwoven Kevlar flbre.
Stop a bullet llke a soft wang agalnst
a Quaker glrl. Aln't gettlng through.
And llghtwelght? So llghtwelght,
you'll forget you're wearlng It.
They work?
Sure as shlt, they do.
I don't leave home wlthout It.
What the hell?
You broke my freaklng rlb,
you manlac son of a bltch.
You're welcome!
What temperature dld you set here?
Here?
Statlon flve, 75 c.
Elght-flve.
I wrote It down. You sald 75.
-I wrote It.
-Well, you wrote It wrong.
That's not what I sald.
It's always been 85.
Not 75. Not 95.
Elghty-flve.
Thls ls chemlstry. Degrees matter.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
Great.
You're sorry, meanwhlle...
...you've Just brewed so gallons
of useless sludge. Congratulatlons.
Just dump It. Dump It all.
Thls batch ls rulned.
You look nlce.
I look llke a TV weatherman.
You want a coffee?
l squeezed some orange Julce.
You want a glass of orange Julce?
I'm all rlght.
What are you gonna tell them?
Here's what you'll tell them.
He attacked you.
-He attacked me?
-He swung at you wlth somethlng.
-Swung at me?
-He attacked you wlth a plpe.
A plpe.
It happened fast. He reslsted arrest
and muscle memory klcked In...
...and you had to dlsarm hlm.
Muscle memory.
Happens all the tlme. Years of tralnlng,
your body acted faster than your braln.
You had no cholce but to hlt hlm.
-You had to flght back.
-Marle, Marle, Marle.
I'm not gonna go In there and lle.
It's some lowllfe degenerate
versus you...
...dolng the Job you're supposed to.
Why should you be the one
who pays...
...for dolng the rlght thlng?
Oh, baby, It wasn't the rlght thlng.
It's not what the Job Is.
I'm supposed to be better than that.
And you made one mlstake.
No, It wasn't one mlstake. I've been--
I've been...
...unravelllng, you know?
I don't sleep at nlght anymore.
l freeze.
l freeze up.
My chest gets all tlght.
I can't breathe.
Just--
Ever slnce that Salamanca thlng.
I mean, Tuco Salamanca.
If ever a scumbag deserved a bullet
between the eyes....
It changed me.
And I can't seem to control It.
l trled to flght It.
But then...
...El Paso.
And It's Just gotten worse.
What I dld to Plnkman...
...that's not who I'm supposed to be.
That's not me.
All thls...
...everythlng that's happened, In
I swear to God, Marle,
lthlnk the unlverse...
...ls trylng to tell me somethlng...
...and I'm flnally...
...ready to llsten.
I'm Just not the man I thought I was.
lthlnk I'm done as a cop.
Now, thls Is not an easy declslon,
but It Is one that l have to make.
I'm sorry.
Thls whole Gale sltuatlon, he's--
He's Just not worklng out.
Yes, now.
It may sound unorthodox...
...but I thlnk our flrst best optlon...
...ls Jesse Plnkman.
Hello?
No, look. There's a shorthand
that exlsts between us...
...experlence together...
...at a level that, qulte frankly,
I'm Just never golng to reach wlth Gale.
Look, Mr. Frlng...
...when I accepted your offer,
I was told the lab ls mlne.
And I know best how to run It.
Thank you.
Yes, lwlll. l wlll.
Okay. Goodbye.
Llsten, somethlng's come up.
l thlnk It's a good opportunlty.
There's been a Job openlng.
I need a new lab asslstant.
I already dld my tlme.
Why don't you Just go get yourself
a monkey?
I don't want a monkey.
I want you.
Oh, gee, thanks.
Well, not Interested.
I got my own thlng golng on.
And nlce try, savlng your asshead
brother-ln-law.
That's not why I'm here, Jesse.
There's more.
It's more than an asslstant.
Partners.
We'll be partners agaln.
Spllt everythlng flfty-flfty,
Just llke before.
One-polnt-flve mllllon dollars each.
-I don't thlnk you heard--
-I heard you flne.
Let me understand thls.
You're turnlng down
one and a half mllllon dollars--
I am not turnlng down the money.
I am turnlng down you.
You get It?
I want nothlng to do wlth you.
Ever slnce I met you...
...everythlng I've ever cared about...
Rulned, turned to shlt...
...dead, ever slnce I hooked up
wlth the great Helsenberg.
l have never been more alone.
l have nothlngl
All rlght? It's all gone!
Get It?
No, no. Why--?
Why would you get It?
What do you even care,
as long as you get what you want?
nght?
You don't glve a shlt about me.
You sald l was no good.
I'm nothlngl
Why would you want me, huh?
You sald my meth ls lnferlor, rlght?
nght? Hey, you sald my cook
was garbagel
Hey, screw you, man!
Screw you.
Your meth ls good, Jesse.
As good as mlne.
Yeah.
FIfty-flfty.
Yes, flfty-flfty.
Okay.
Partners.
And thls Is the statement
you want to glve?
Yes, slr.
-Hank, you don't have to do thls.
-No, l--
So we understand
If we wrlte It up llke that, you'll slgn It.
That's the way It happened.
I accept the consequences.
In the llght of these facts...
...as of thls moment,
you're suspended wlthout pay.
l have to ask you to hand over
your badge and your gun.
Yes, slr.
Schrader.
Yes, slr?
IJust wanted to tell you somethlng.
And you dldn't hear It from me.
Don't want you to get your hopes up...
...but the word In the plpellne ls
Plnkman Isn't presslng charges.
-Why not?
-Who the hell knows?
Maybe you have a guardlan angel.
It went flne.
Well, flne means what It means,
yeah.
I'll tell you all about It
when I get home, okay?
Yeah. It's--
Yeah, It's Just--
I don't know, baby, IJust thlnk--
lthlnk we may be okay. Yeah.
Okay. I love you too.
-Schrader.
-I need you to llsten very carefully.
Two men are comlng to klll you.
Come agaln?
They're approachlng your car.
You have one mlnute.
I don't get the gag, Jagoff.
Who Is thls?
They're comlng.
Hello?
Hey, ll--
Gomey, I don't know what that call was,
but It's dumb even by your standards...
...so call me when you get thls.
Flnlsh hlm.
Jesus.
Too easy.