[FLY BUZZING]
[BUZZING]
Mr. Whlte?
Hallo?
[BUZZING]
Mr. Whlta,
the car's bun dealt wlth, Ilr.
No one talled you?
No, I stayed off the maln struts
and kept chocklng, so...
Jon ask any quutlonl?
I told hlm RVJob, Just Ilka you uld,
and he totally know.
It's pretty cool the way they do that.
They Just turn a car Into a cube.
So should we deal
wlth thla other thlng now?
Yeah.
Sure.
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
I don't want to talk about thla.
Okay.
It had to be done.
All rlght.
I need to talk to you.
In prlvate.
So, what's the story?
You get to Mlke?
Mm-hm.
He get out late?
All rlght.
Well, what about
those nlne guya ln Jall?
I mean, they got no reason
not to talk now.
So, what do we do?
'We'? Who'a 'we'?
There la no 'we,' Jeaae.
I'm the only vote left,
and I'll handle It.
[DOOR CLOSING]
[J'J'J']
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
My cllent wlll aupply lnl'ormatlon
relatlng to the organlaatlon,
dlatrlbutlon and productlon ol' Frlng'a
methamphetamlne enterprlae.
We expect all charges to be dropped,
and Dennla not only walk: out of here
a free man,
but also recelvea blanket Immunlty.
[CHUCKLES]
For what he'll be I'urnlahlng,
thla deal la plenty I'alr.
[SCOFFS]
Beat I'd be wllllng to do
la queen tor a day
and reduced chargea.
All charges dropped.
Queen for a day and a I'lve-k.
That's the beat you're gonna get.
No way. Guya, come on.
You can be a I'alry prlnceaa,
for all I care.
Where you golng?
Shopplng for someone who can tell me
aomethlng I don't already know.
Hey, hey.
I got plenty you don't know.
HANK:
You seem a llttle conl'uaed.
Thla here la a buyer's market.
I got elght other aaaholea
Juat llke you, tour of them
wlthln 100 feet from here.
I also got Dan the lawyer,
who'll glve me the money
and Ehrmantraut.
So aettle In, Dennla.
Enjoy your new home.
I'm gonna go rattle aome cagea.
[DOOR OPENS THEN OLOSES]
[noon OPENS]
So?
Maybe you should order aomethlng.
Do you want a coffee or aomethlng?
Not Just now.
lthlnk thla would play better
If you ordered aomethlng.
lthlnk thla wlll play Juat flne,
and I'm not thlraty.
So let's take a look at the Hat.
Lydla, you've come all thla way.
You do have the Hat?
Yea, I have It.
Good.
It's Just not wrltten down.
And why la that?
It's In my head. Safer there.
Then I suggest you plck up a pen.
Not Just yet.
It was my underatandlng
that attendlng to these nlne namea
waa preclaely what you wanted.
Ten name: now.
Ten, countlng the lawyer.
Yea. Ten, countlng the lawyer.
So, what, am I not tylng up loose end:
for our mutual beneflt?
You're tylng up loose ends,
and I don't wanna be one of them.
l glve you that llat,
I've aerved my purpose.
Then maybe I'm Just one more person
who know: too much.
So you put that llat In my hands,
and In your mlnd,
l Immedlately Juat murder you,
Just rlght here In thla reataurant?
No. Not rlght here. Of course.
Here In thla publlc place, Immedlately?
That la not--
Llaten, Lydla.
You made me promlae
on my chlldren'a llvea
that l guaranteed your safety.
From Mlke.
You guaranteed
I'd be safe from "Ike.
There's no way he'd ever go for thla,
you gettlng rld of hla guya.
You wouldn't be dolng thla, the names,
If Mlke were atlll a factor.
Yeah. That's what I thought.
What do you want, exactly?
Becauae If you don't want
to glve me that llat
then I've truly got no use for you.
I can grow your bualneaa
exponentlally.
Juat glve me the Hat.
I can do that by helplng you
expand Into a larger,
hlghly actlve, hlghly profltable
marketplace.
What do you know
about the Czech Republlc?
The Czech Republlc?
Dld you know there's a hlgher demand
for meth there than anywhere
In Europe?
Flve percent of It: 10 mllllon people
whlch la roughly the populatlon
of the Southwest
from western Texas to Phoenlx,
are ualng meth.
You keep your market here,
but by addlng overseas sales,
you can more than double
your current proflta.
And I checked. The average purlty
la only about 60 percent.
They've never seen
anythlng llke your product.
You'll blow thelr halr back.
Shlpplng lnternatlonally
aeema llke courtlng dlaaater.
Not If you're Madrlgal.
Madrlgal la under lnveatlgatlon
by the DEA.
The restaurant dlvlalon, moatly.
We've got 46,000 employees
spread across 14 dlvlalona.
And once Mlke'a people are no longer
a factor, thlnga ahould tldy up nlcely.
Thla la what I do, you understand?
Move thlnga from polnt A to polnt B
all over the globe.
One-polnt-two mllllon
metrlc tons a month
and all of It rlght at my flngertlpa,
a laptop cllck away.
The Czech Republlc...
Who's on the other end?
People I ahlp to regularly.
People I've worked wlth for years.
Profeaalonal and very amenable.
I'm very careful who I work wlth.
And If thla la such a slam dunk,
then why dldn't you pltch It to Frlng?
l dld. He aald yea. We were
In the flnal atagea of worklng It out
when aomebody kllled hlm.
You don't thlnk Gua Frlng
bullt hla dlatrlbutlon network
all by hlmaelf.
There are conalderable advantagea
to dlveralflcatlon of dlatrlbutlon,
llke puttlng 6000 mllea
between you and your product.
At 25 pounda a week, I'm eatlmatlng
you'll groaa about 2 mllllon.
lee me 10 pounda to atart,
and we'll aee how It goea.
All rlght.
Now, wlth Frlng,
my end waa gonna be 30 percent,
whlch l belleve la more than falr.
Okay.
Truat me, If you do thla--
Lydla, learn to take yea for an anawer.
Now, flrat thlnga flrat.
Shake on It?
We're golng to make
a lot of money together.
[DIALLING]
Todd, lthlnk It'a tlme
I meet your uncle.
MAN 1:
No Iron plle.
There'a too many muacle-heada
flexlng thelr ahlt. Too many eyea.
MAN 2:
Okay, ao no chow llne, no yard.
MAN 1:
Well, gonna keep It almple.
MAN 2:
Paaa-byea.
MAN 1:
Yeah. Hallwaya,
ahower room, cella.
The eaay atuff.
MAN 3:
l aay we go wlth a rlot.
Our boya get It done In a rlot.
MAN 1:
No, no, no. No chaoa.
I don't want the goon aquad rolllng In
and ateallng our ahot, you know?
Thla haa gotta be faat and qulet.
Juat boom, boom, boom.
You know what I'm aaylng?
Yeah.
Surglcal.
Surglcal. That'a what It'a gotta be.
So how many guya we got at "DC?
Three, countlng Shattuck.
And he makea the achedule now
ao we can put who we need
where we need them.
All rlght. So MDC'a covered.
What about the reat?
We need 6 block In Valencla, rlght?
Our guy'a on the nlght ahlft.
JACK: Have hlm pull a double.
No.
Hla aupervlaor'a got
aome hard-on about OT.
Have hlm awltch wlth aomebody.
Juat get It done.
Regardleaa, you know, we got
enough guya In Valencla rlght now?
Mlght have to hlre out.
You hlgh?
Mlx blood wlth chuntaroa?
No way.
JACK: No.
There'a no need. We got enough.
Hlttera aln't the problem. It'a that
ahort walklng wlndow after lunch.
KENNY: Mm-hm.
Yeah. It'a gonna be tlght.
Real tlght.
I gotta be atralght wlth you, man.
Taklng out all theae guya la doable.
But hlttlng them
In three aeparate Jalla
all wlthln two mlnutea?
I mean, whacklng bln Laden
waan't thla compllcated.
Where do you auppoae
theae come from?
I've aeen thla one before.
I wonder,
are they all In aome glant
warehouae aomeplace?
Hey.
It can be done,
Juat not the way you want It.
It can be done exactly how I want It.
The only queatlon la,
are you the man to do It?
Flgure It out.
That'a what I'm paylng you for.
[CHUCKLES]
[TICKING]
[NAT KING OOLE'S
'PIOK YOURSELF UP' PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
I Take a deep breath I
J' Duat youraelf off I
I And alert all over agaln J'
[GRUNTING AND YELLING]
J' For when my chln
la on the ground I
J' I plck myself up
Duat myself off I
[YELLING AND GRUNTING]
I And alert all over agaln J'
I Don't Ioae your conﬁdence I
[GRUNTING]
I Be grateful for a pleaaant trlp J'
I And plck youraelf up I
J' Duat youraelf off I
[GRUNTING]
I And atart all over agaln J'
J' Work Ilke a aoul Inaplred J'
J' TIII the battle of the day la won I
J' You may be alck and tlred J'
I But you'll be a man, my aon J'
J' WIII you remember the famoua men J'
I Who had to fall to rlae agaln? J'
I So take a deep breath I
[GRUNTING]
[ALARM BLARING]
J' Duat youraelf off I
I And atart all over agaln J'
Yo, what'a golng on, man?
What'a that alarm?
What'a happenlng?
Ohl Whoal
What are you dolng, man?
No, man, pleaael
J' WIII you remember the famoua men J'
I Who had to fall to rlae agaln? J'
Ball came In my dlrectlon,
batter wouldn't even bother runnlng.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[WHISPERS INDISTINOTLY]
Excuae me a aecond.
Couple more photoa.
J' Duat youraelf off I
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
I And atart all over agaln J'J'
Yea?
JACK:
It'a done.
New detalla have emerged
In the apate of [all deatha
that rocked central New Mexlco
three daya ago.
Aa of yet, no namea of vlctlma
have been releaaed
but authorltlea contlnue to Inveatlgate
what appeara to be
a carefully coordlnated
aequence of attacka
that occurred wlthln mlnutea In
three dII'I'erent correctlonal facIIItIea...
la It okay If I turn thla off?
Oh, aure.
I don't want the newa on rlght now.
Hank Juat pulled up,
and he'a not In the beat mood.
Oh, all rlght. I'll get out of your halr.
Okay.
HI, honey.
Dlnner wlll be In about an hour.
And I thought we could have
that chlcken you Ilke.
Or we could order Chlneae.
Sure.
Here we go.
That fun? Play wlth your toya?
I'll aee you In a llttle blt, okay?
See you In a llttle blt.
Hey, Hank.
l waa Juat gettlng ready to leave.
Somethlng to drlnk?
Um-- Yeah, aure. Thanka.
Perfect.
Rocka, rlght?
Rocka, yea.
[HOLLY BABBLING]
Been thlnklng about thla aummer Job
I uaed to have.
Oh, yeah?
Back In college, I'd apend my daya
marklng treea In the wooda
wlth thla
Thla orange apray can.
Marklng treea?
Yeah. Crewa would come In later
and flnd the treea l tagged
and cut them down.
Flrat, you go In
and you mark locatlona
for akld tralla and landlnga.
Then you chooae apeclflc treea
all wlthln a aelected grld.
Every day,
plck up where I left off.
Oh, It aounda nlce,
belng out In the wooda all day.
No, It waan't ao great.
I got aunburned.
There were moaqultoea.
IJuat wanted to make a few bucka.
Buy beer.
Been thlnklng about that Job
more and more lately.
Maybe I ahould've enjoyed It more.
Tagglng treea la a lot better
than chaalng monatera.
l uaed to love to go camplng.
[TOMMY JAMES 5 THE SHONDELLS'
'ORYSTAL BLUE PERSUASION'
PLAYING]
I Look over yonder J'
I What do you aee? J'
J' The arm Ia a-rIaIn' J'
J' Moat deﬂnltely J'
J' A new day Ia comln' J'
J' Whoo-hoo J'
J' People are changln' J'
J' Aln't It beautlful? J'
J' Whoo-hoo J'
J' Crystal blue persuaslon J'
J' Better get ready I
J' Gonna see the IIght J'
J' Love, love Is the answer I
J' Whoo-hoo J'
I And that's all rlght J'
I So don't you glve up now I
J' Whoo-hoo J'
I So easy to ﬁnd I
I Just look to your soul I
I Look to your soul I
I And open your mlnd J'
J' Crystal blue persuaslon J'
J' Mm-hm J'
J' It's a new vlbratlon J'
J' Crystal blue persuaslon J'
J' Crystal J'
J' Blue persuaslon J'
J' Maybe tomorrow I
I When he looks down I
J' On every green ﬁeld I
J' Whoo-hoo J'
I And every town I
I All of hla chlldren J'
J' In every natlon J'
J' There'll be peace and good I
J' Brotherhood J'
J' Crystal blue persuaslon J'
J' Yeah I
J'AhaJ'
J' Crystal blue persuaslon J'
J' Crystal blue persuaslon J'J'
WALT JR.: Thls way.
SKYLER: Here, baby glrl.
Come see your brother.
There you go, sweetle. That's It.
Oh, my God! Look at her go!
Good Job! Good Job!
WALT JR: Over here. Peekaboo.
Thls way.
SKYLER: Let's go see your brother.
Let's get hlm.
WALT JR.: Where'd you go?
I can't see you. Where'd you go?
There you are!
[SKYLER & WALT JR. LAUGHING]
You're really good wlth her.
[HOLLY OOUGHING]
Come here, my baby glrl.
You're gonna be a handful,
aren't you? Yeah.
Mama's gonna get her exerclse.
Hey, do you wanna watch a movle?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, Louls. Um, ahem.
One moment. Uh...
Uh, nothlng. Heh. What's up?
Tsk. Oh, well.
[SIGHS THEN OHUOKLES]
It's so nlce to see you
smlle agaln.
I mean, you seem good.
Yeah. I'm hanglng In there.
To see you laugh Ilke that
Just now...
It's such an Improvement,
don't you thlnk?
I don't-- I don't really...
Uh...
We've been thlnklng,
Hank and I, that It may be tlme
to take the klds home.
It's been almost three months,
rlght?
Almost three?
Um...
Does Hank not want--?
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, God. No. No.
Hank's crazy for these klds.
You know that.
It goes wlthout saylng,
we love havlng them.
And we're always here for you
and wanna help you
any way that we can.
But...
We're startlng to worry
that maybe...
Maybe we're enabllng you.
Sweetle, you've had
a lot on your plate
and you and Walt have had a lot--
So much to contend wlth.
I'm so proud of you
for golng to therapy.
You know that, rlght?
It can be so helpful,
such a good tool.
And I'm very, very proud of you
but In
We...
Maybe at thls polnt,
the best way to help
repalr the famlly
would be to repalr the famlly,
you know?
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[WATER LAPPING SOFTLY]
Take a drlve wlth me.
Here. I'll get It.
Walt.
Thls Is It.
Thls Is what you've
been worklng for.
I rented thls place and I started
brlnglng It here because
l dldn't know what else to do.
I gave up countlng It.
I mean, I had to.
It was Just so much, so fast.
ltrled welghlng It.
lflgured one blll of any denomlnatlon
welghs a gram.
There are 454 grams
to a pound, but...
There's a varlety
of denomlnatlons, so...
How much ls thls?
l have no earthly Idea.
I truly don't.
IJust stack It up,
keep It dry,
spray It for sllverflsh.
There Is more money here
than we could spend
In 10 llfetlmes.
l certalnly can't launder It,
not wlth a hundred car washes.
Walt,
I want my klds back.
I want my llfe back.
Please tell me.
How much ls enough?
How blg does thls plle have to be?
[WHIRRING]
[J'J'J']
[CLICK]
[MECHANICAL HUMMING]
[noon OPENS]
Owl Aw, shltl
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[KNOCKING]
Hey.
Um, I hope I'm not dlsturblng you
or anythlng.
l trled calllng, but--
Yeah. No, I tossed all my burners.
Mm. And you dldn't answer
your home llne.
It's dlsconnected.
Well, um, unplugged.
I mean, dld you leave
a message, or...?
Uh-- No.
So, what's up?
No, l was Just In the nelghbourhood,
so I thought I'd drop by and say hello.
You wanna come In, or...?
Uh... Sure. Thanks.
You know, I'd offer you
a beer or somethlng
but, you know, I'm out.
No, no. No, I'm flne, thanks.
You dldn't wlnd up movlng, I see.
Dldn't have to.
Saul told me what you dld.
Anyways, um, I'm not In Jall.
You aren't elther, so there you go.
There was no other optlon, Jesse.
It had to be done.
I'm not comlng back.
So why are you here,
exactly?
It's funny, I...
I saw a Bounder the other day.
Bounder?
Yeah.
Our RV? A Bounder?
Oh. Oh.
Heh.
Oh, you saw the same one
as ours?
Yeah. Well, I mean,
wlthln a couple of years, I guess.
Early '00s.
It was certalnly In a lot better shape
than our old hunk ofjunk.
Much nlcer palnt Job.
No bullet holes In the door.
Yeah. That thlng
was a nlghtmare, huh?
Yeah. It was prlmltlve.
You know, whenever
I hlt a red llght, I used to pray
It wouldn't crap out on me.
Yeah.
And then, suddenly,
It would sometlmes have that...
That screechlng sound
Just out of the blue
Ilke we hlt a pack of cats.
Power-steerlng belt.
That's what that was.
You know, I always had thls...
Thls whole system.
Strategy to not let It Idle too low.
Remember that tlme we ran out of gas
comlng back from a cook?
Ah. The gauge.
It always sald half-full.
You walked three mlles wlth a Jerrlcan
whlle l walted on the slde of the road,
praylng the whole tlme
that no cop would show up,
no Good Samarltan.
We had money.
Why'd we keep It?
Why dld we have to have
the world's shlttlest RV?
lnertla?
Yeah.
lnertla.
So, hey, you know, I gotta get golng.
Me too.
I'm meetlng frlends.
I gotta get golng as well.
I left somethlng for you.
[CAR DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
[J'J'J']
[ENGINE STARTS]
[PANTING]
[noon OPENS]
[noon CLOSES]
Hey.
I'm out.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
MARIE:
Wlth some blg earrlngs,
It could be really nlce.
Perhaps some blg hoops.
HANK: I do Indeed.
MARIE:
I feel Ilke I want to mlx It up
wlth my halr thls summer.
I don't know, Ilke colours--
HANK: I don't know. Colns.
WALT:
Dld you have a coln collectlon?
MARIE:
I've heard It's very therapeutlc.
HANK:
Colns and baseball cards.
Those were the ones.
You can play around wlth It,
take them In and out.
Not enough hours In the day,
rlght?
There's not enough hours.
MARIE: My halrstyllst told me
to take prenatal vltamlns.
SKYLER:
For your halr?
He sald they work,
so I flgured why not?
Oh, Flynn, could you put some more
sunscreen on Holly?
Yeah. Is It over there?
Yeah, It's rlght here.
WALT JR.: Okay.
Especlally for a home brew, though.
Paba-free. That's good.
I don't know why It would be bad.
Yeah. Me nelther.
Oh, do you--? I used to squeeze
lemon Julce In my halr.
You remember that?
You wanted to be
a beach bum so badly.
You and your stlff halr.
Stlff? Whose stlffy? What?
Hey, hey.
[LAUGHING]
l was Interested
to see you get Into that.
It's Ilke chemlstry.
Borage oll ls supposed to be good.
Better than flaxseed?
I don't know.
That's cool. I Ilke your style.
There Is no Chrlstmas.
Maybe I should brew up a batch.
Ooh. Schraderbrau?
Yeah.
SKYLER: I vote yes.
I second that.
Well, there you go. It's unanlmous.
Well, who am I to fly In the face
of publlc demand, rlght?
[CHUCKLES]
HANK:
All rlght. Uhn.
Anybody want anythlng?
You want anythlng?
No, I'm good. I'm good, thank you.
Yeah? All rlght.
Does It look glossler?
Do I have a halo?
How's she dolng?
She's good.
Yeah? Try not to put any
of the sunscreen on her flngers.
HANK:
"To W.W. My star,
my perfect sllence. " Heh.
W. W. Ha-ha.
I mean, who do you flgure that Is?
Woodrow Wllson?
Wllly Wonka?
Walter Whlte?
[CHUCKLES]
You got me.
[J'J'J']