MAN [IN GERMAN ACCENT]:
[m GERMAN]
[MAN SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
[noon OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES THEN
FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[m GERMAN]
[IN GERMAN]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[J'J'J']
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
TROMEL [IN GERMAN]:
[KNOCKING LOUDLY]
KUNST [IN GERMAN]:
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[KNOCKING]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[DEVICE WHIRRING]
[KUNST SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
[FLUSHING]
[J'J'J']
JESSE [OVER PHONE]:
Honest to God,
It's starllng lo drlve me crazy.
WALT: Don't.
JESSE: It keeps me awake.
I lay there lhlnklng, "Where I: ll?
Where dld I! go?"
And I just" I can't" I have no Idea.
WALT: Jesse, Iook.
Doesn't I! make sense
that I! wound up In the Iab?
JESSE:
I thought about that a Iot.
But I just don't see how.
WALT:
WeII, Iook. You had the pack
In your pocket of your jacket, rIght?
JESSE: Yeah.
WALT: Your jacket was In your Iocker.
So maybe the charette
fell out of the pocket
and wound up In the Iocker,
and now It's a" burned up.
It's gone.
JESSE: Yeah.
But I don't know that, you know?
I can't ever know for sure.
WALT:
We", took, dId you check your house?
DId you--? Maybe It's
somewhere In your house.
JESSE:
No, man.
I've Iooked everywhere, okay?
WALT: Your car? You check your car?
JESSE: No.
WALT: Thorougth?
JESSE: It's not In my house.
It's not In my car.
The more I thInk about It,
there's no way It fell out In my Iocker.
Somebody's gonna ﬁnd It
on the street.
WALT: You don't know that.
JESSE: Somewhere where I dropped It.
Some Innocent person,
some kId maybe, even.
They're gonna pIck It up,
and It's gonna--
WALT: You're workIng yourseIf a" up.
JESSE: Oh, my GodI
WALT:
You've gotta get ahoId of yourseIf.
I'II tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna come over there.
And together, we're gonna took
for thIs thIng. AII rIght?
JESSE:
Yeah.
[WHITEY'S 'STAY ON THE OUTSIDE'
PLAYING]
J' CouId've been, shouId've been
One, two, three I
I But recentIy
SomethIng has happened to me I
J' EverythIng aIways came easIIy
But today I woke up and felt nothIng J'
J' CouId It be fInaIIy fIndIng out I
I That there's absolutely nothIng
Worth shoutIng about I
J' Faced wIth the choIce
Of just IosIng my voIce J'
J' I'd rather shut up and say nothIng J'
J' A" the rIght peopIe
Seem squeaky cIean J'
I We", a" the rIght peopIe
Mean nothIng to me I
J' CreepIn' and cheatIn'
To stay on track I
I after one hand
And put a anfe In your back I
J' NotIced that somethIng
Is terrIny wrong I
I When they offer the world I
I Then they turn and they're gone I
I They knew from the start
You could never beIong J'
J' You came from the outsIde
You'II stay on the outsIde J'
I If you're askIng for answers
You're In the wrong pIace J'
J' There's absquter nothIng
Worth tryIng to say I
I Just watch where you waIk
And who's In your way I
I And stand up for the outsIde
Stay on the outsIde J'J'
[WHIRRING]
What the hell Is that?
My Roomba.
I already checked It.
When?
lee a week ago.
Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay. Easy, easy. Take lt--
Careful. Let me see.
Is It stlll Intact?
Yeah. Good.
Good. No worrles.
Let me get rld ot thls.
What luck.
[TOILET FLUSHING]
WALT:
Whoo.
Well, I don't know about you,
but I, for one, could use a beer.
You have any?
Jesse?
[SOBBING]
I almost shot you.
Hey, hey, now...
I almost kllled you all because...
Llsten.
It was Just a mlsunderstandlng,
that's all.
I don't know what's wrong
wIth me, Mr. Whlte. l--
Hey.
[SOBBING]
I don't know howl could be so stupld.
Stop that now. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
I'm so sorry.
Shh.
It's okay. It's okay.
Llsten to me.
What happened, happened for the best,
you hear me?
And I wouldn't change a thIng.
You and l workIng together,
havlng each other's back.
It's what saved our llves.
I want you to thInk about that
as we go forward.
Go forward where?
[MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER TV]
MAN [OVER TV]:
Stlllwell, steady as you go.
Wlllle, note the tlme.
Captaln, I'm sorry,
but you're a slck man.
I'm rellevlng you as captaln of the shlp
under artlcle 184.
Oh, God.
CAPTAIN: I don't know
what you're talklng about.
Helmsman, left 180.
Mr. Kelth, what do I do?
You're the ofﬁcer on the deck.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
I told you to come left.
Now come left, and fast.
MAN:
I'm sorry, slr, but you're not lssulng
orders on thls brldge anymore.
I've relleved you.
I take full responslbll--
WALT:
Thanks for seelng us.
We're here to talk partnershlp.
Partnershlp?
Yes. Equal. Three ways.
You, Jesse and me.
Partnershlp In what?
Well, we flgure we're gonna start
cooklng agaln.
You know, we flgure, why not?
WALT:
There's no denylng the popularlty
of our product.
There's a market to be ﬁlled
and currently no one to flll It.
JESSE:
A lot of money to be made.
WALT:
And obvlously, Jesse and l
have manufacture covered.
But there's stlll dlstrlbutlon,
support, loglstlcs, that sort of thIng.
For Instance
we'll need a steady supply
of precursor.
Wlth your experlence
and connectlons,
you would be a great help.
Mm-hm.
Granted, there's a lot of work ahead.
There's a lot of rebulldlng.
And, no doubt,
our proflts wlll be smaller.
At least at flrst. But each of us
wlll recelve a larger cut.
Owners, not employees.
Thanks, but no, thanks.
WALT:
Mlke, I know you don't care for me.
We've had our Issues, you and I.
But I would suggest
that you leave emotlon
out of thls declslon.
You...
are trouble.
You are a tlme bomb,
tlck, tlck, tlcklng,
and l have no lntentlon
of belng around for the boom.
Well, sleep on It.
Maybe you'll reconslder.
In the meantlme, we're presslng on.
Mornlng.
Hey, why aren't
you upstalrs?
I came to see If you needed any help.
Yeah, well, I don't.
Well, I can see that, man.
It's outstandlng.
Yeah. I'm workIng
on It, here.
Not exactly runnlng marathons,
you know.
Yeah, when dld your couch-shaped
ass ever run any marathons?
I'm proud of you, brother.
Yeah.
So how many Krauts we got?
Enough to Invade Poland.
Came In thelr own 65,
Just llke Oprah has.
G5, yeah?
Mm-hm.
Is that one where the wlngs
go up llke that?
lthlnk they all do that.
They all have that?
Anyway, we got two U.S. Attorneys
In the house.
Blg dolngs.
Your name keeps comlng up.
Yeah? Hey, glve me a hand here,
would you?
Just a llttle blt there. Thanks.
MAN:
I hlred Peter Schuler In 1992.
Almost slngle-handedly,
he grew our llttle restaurant dlvlslon
Into an Industry leader
and a source
of great personal prlde.
I am shocked and saddened
by hls death
and outraged by the damage
hls actlons have wrought
upon my grandfather's company.
[SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
Alleged actlons.
An Innocent man
does not klll hlmself.
My people and l are here to help.
To your Investlgatlon,
I pledge Madrlgal's full cooperatlon
and transparency.
I confess I have my selflsh reasons.
l belleve Peter Schuler
was a lone anomaly.
But If that Is not the case,
I want to know It
Just as you do.
HANK:
So when you gonna announce It?
I don't know.
As I'm walklng out the door
wIth my blg cardboard box.
Can't do that. You know damn well
we're gonna throw you a blg party.
Damn stralght.
We're talklng a blowout.
Outstandlng pollce work, Hank.
If only I'd llstened.
But I guess the damage was done.
It's not rIght,
them puttlng thls on you.
Somebody's gotta go under the bus.
Ramey's a good man.
He'll do rIght by you.
Besldes, thls offlce
practlcally runs Itself.
Bullshlt, It does.
SIr.
What's wIth that A.P.D. thlng?
The electromagnets?
They're thlnklng
It's about Frlng's laptop.
A couple of days before It happened,
desk sergeant gets a call
from a 'postal lnspector'
quote, unquote,
wantlng to know
where they keep the thIng.
And he told them? Jesus.
Anythlng left of the laptop?
Do we look that lucky?
l sneaked a peek before A.P.D.
took It out of Frlng's offlce.
The whole thlng was encrypted. They
wouldn't have got anythlng anyway, but...
So Hector Salamanca kllled Frlng.
But who gave Salamanca
the bomb?
Whole lot of questlons
and not much
In the way of answers.
Yet.
The A.P.D. dld flnd
some of Frlng's flnanclals.
That Just mlght lead to somethIng.
I had hlm out to my house.
Fourth of July.
We cooked out In the backyard.
My son shucked the corn.
My daughter cut up potatoes.
Frlng brought sea bass.
Every tlme l grlll It now, I make
a llttle foII pouch, Just llke he showed me.
That whole nlght, we were laughlng,
telllng storles, drlnklng wlne.
And he's somebody else completely.
mm In front of me.
nght under my nose.
[MAN SINGING INDISTINCTLY
OVER STEREO]
HI. What can I get you?
LYDIA: Just tea. Chamomlle.
Oh, sorry. We don't have chamomlle tea.
LYDIA:
Then some sort of bergamot,
not Earl Grey.
l llke soy mllk Instead of dalry.
We don't have soy mllk
or any sort of bergamot.
Wow. You're really runnlng me
through my paces here.
Well, Engllsh breakfast, I guess.
We have Llpton's.
That's pretty much all we have.
I would llke a cup of hot water, flltered,
If posslble, and a sllce of lemon.
I'm assumlng
you don't have stevla?
Never mlnd. I brought my own.
You comlng to me,
or am I comlng to you?
Face forward. We'll talk llke thls.
I guess I'm comlng to you.
[GRUNTS]
Take a breath, wlll you?
Thls place Is safe.
No one's gonna see you here.
My God. Duane, thls Is so-- Thank you.
How dld I not see you slttlng back there?
So welrd. Heh.
You want anythlng else, Mlke?
No. I'm good, Fran. Thanks.
how about
we lose the sunglasses?
I feel llke I'm talklng
to Jackle Onassls here.
There you go.
Breathe In, breathe out.
Drlnk your whatever.
[MACK OWEN'S 'SOMEBODY JUST
LIKE YOU' PLAYING OVER STEREO]
Who kllled Gus?
Haven't I told you
not to worry about that?
Now, what do you want from me,
and why Is It so Important?
What's thls?
A llst of 11 names.
Okay.
You know them all.
Those 11 men--
And I thInk you know thls, Mlke.
Those 11 could slnk us,
you and me both.
Where are we golng wIth thls?
No speclflc... I'm Just polntlng out facts.
These men--
Your men, yours and Gus',
they were on the payroll,
very publlcly.
They trace back to Pollos, the laundry,
to Madrlgal.
They're gonna get plcked up
by the pollce. When they do,
and threatened,
and there's only one way out--
And I'm not saylng all of them, okay?
All It's gonna take Is two or three,
or even one.
But there's always a weak llnk.
But they're gonna talk.
At least one's gonna talk about you,
me, and that's all It's gonna take.
These are the 11 I know of,
but I'd love your Input.
I never met your chemlst, for Instance.
I'd love your Input.
You want me to klll
every man on that llst?
That's a leap, what you Just, uh...
No, l dldn't say that.
But If you thInk that'd be wlse...
Oh.
You're scared, aren't you?
Yeah.
You're very upset, whlch I'm gonna factor
Into my response here.
These are my guys,
and they are solld.
Understand?
What about Chow at the warehouse?
Dldn't you have to shoot hlm
through the hand?
Thlnk that dldn't stlck In hls memory?
What about Dennls at the laundry?
They're sure to plck hlm up.
They already have.
They plcked hlm up last nlght.
My guys are solld.
l vetted them wIth great care
and Frlng made sure
they were well compensated
In the event of a sltuatlon such as thls.
They're pald to stand up to the heat,
keep thelr mouths shut,
no matter what.
And they wlll.
I don't know what movles
you've been watchlng,
but In the real world,
we don't klll 11 people
as some klnd of
prophylactlc measure.
Look at me
and say you understand.
I understand.
I get It.
So we're off that very sllly Idea?
Drlnk your hot water.
Hm.
I gotta go.
Dld you have enough?
Yeah. I'm good.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Bye, blg brother.
Say bye to Mom for me.
lwlll. Have a good day.
You too.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Skyler.
Hm.
Hey.
The car wash opens In 15 mlnutes.
Marlano can open
for me today.
Hey, how about you get up, huh?
Come on.
A shower wlll feel good.
Hey, Chow.
How you holdlng up?
Okay.
You know, they...
They talked to me.
You can't smoke In here, Chow.
HANK:
Thanks for comlng down.
Have a seat, Mr. Ehrmantraut.
Am I saylng that rIght?
Close enough.
Once more, you're walvlng your rIght
to have an attorney present?
Correct.
Could you state that
to the camera?
I'm walvlng my rIght
to have an attorney present.
Okay, then.
We Just have a few questlons.
You're currently employed
by the Pollos Hermanos chaln.
Is that correct?
Yes, I am.
What do you do there?
Corporate securlty.
Yeah.
What's that?
lee guardlng the speclal sauce?
l conduct employee
background checks.
l oversee loss preventlon.
At a fast-food restaurant,
that's a full-tlme Job?
We have 14 locatlons.
So, yes, It's a full-tlme Job.
Yeah, well, If I were you,
I'd start sendlng out those resumes.
It says here
you're a prlvate lnvestlgator?
Where you IIcensed?
New Mexlco, Arlzona, Utah.
Every state where we operate.
Colorado?
You have some restaurants there, rIght?
Colorado doesn't requlre IIcensure.
Llcensed to carry a ﬁrearm?
Concealed carry? Yes, I am.
Whlch states?
It'd be qulcker to mentlon
the states In whlch I'm not.
And If we pulled your CCPs,
everythlng would be In order?
I'm guesslng you've already done that,
so you tell me.
You strlke me as a former cop.
Am I rIght?
Where at?
Phlladelphla.
Phllly.
[CHUCKLES]
The Clty of Brotherly Love.
Turns out we know some folks there
and they told us that your tenure
as a pollce offlcer
ended somewhat, uh, dramatlcally?
You wanna talk about that?
Not partlcularly.
Yeah, me nelther.
See, I'm more Interested In why Gus Frlng
declded to put a guy llke you
In charge of hls corporate securlty.
I mean, glven your hlstory,
dolng background checks
on plmple-faced fry cooks.
Seems llke overklll.
What else you do for Frlng?
He must've needed help
runnlng that drug emplre of hls, no?
Drug emplre?
Flrst I'm hearlng about that.
I don't know anythlng about that.
We have a guy that could
put you In that underground lab,
and he'll testlfy to It. So from
here on out, thls can go hard or easy.
So what's It gonna be?
Forget your handcuffs?
I'm confused.
Am I under arrest here, or am I not?
You wanna state that
for the camera?
You are not under arrest, currently.
Agents, do you have
any more questlons for me?
Because you've got me very stlrred up
wIth all these false accusatlons.
If I'm not under arrest,
I'd prefer to leave.
Oh, well...
I suppose we could talk about
the $2 mllllon
In your granddaughter's name.
Yeah. It seems Frlng had all these
secret offshore accounts
that he would deposlt money Into.
lee, well, an even dozen of them.
And they're all In the names
of certaln people on hls payroll.
The manager of the laundry,
um, a couple guys from
the Pollos dlstrlbutlon centre.
There was the owner of a chemlcal
warehouse, a bunch of others.
You know, guys that must've been
gettlng pald off the books.
Anyway, one of the names
was Kaylee Ehrmantraut.
Ten years old
and Just cute as a button.
Yeah. Two mllllon and change
we found on deposlt for her.
Way more than anybody else.
Now, my partner here,
he took one look at that and sald:
'Shlt, man. Thls flfth-grade glrl Is the
muscle behlnd Frlng's entlre operatlon.‘
l sald, 'Whoa, whoa, hey, partner,
slow down there.
Maybe It was actually
her dear old granddaddy.‘
lmpresslve, no?
That, tsk, level of Inslght?
He's not Impressed, Gomey.
Perhaps he's plcturlng
all that money golng bye-bye.
Yeah, well, I mean, the government's
gonna take every last dollar, unless...
Here's the thlng, Mlke-- Or Mlchael?
Mr. Ehrmantraut.
HANK: Here's the thlng, Mlke.
Lucky, you dldn't touch that money.
I cannot say the same
for the other 11 on the llst.
One of your guys
Is gonna roll
and then we'll deflnltely remember
the handcuffs.
Now, before that day comes,
you can do yourself a solld.
You can tell us what you know,
you can tell us
who's stlll out there,
and If we llke your story,
good thlngs can happen.
Kaylee mlght be able
to keep some of that money.
Maybe.
So what do you say?
I don't know anythlng
about any money.
I don't know what you're talklng about.
WALT:
Flrst order of buslness
Is to flnd a new place to cook.
Before anyone says If,
no more RV's.
I don't know.
The crystal shlp dld pretty good for us.
WALT:
The 'crystal shlp'?
Yeah. That's what I called It.
Well, I'll admlt, It held Its own
as a starter lab
but It was too dark, too small,
not to mentlon It could've broken down
at any moment.
Saul, flnd us someplace safe
from prylng eyes.
Securlty agalnst detectlon
Is paramount.
But I don't wanna drlve too far.
No more 50-mlle treks
to some lndlan reservatlon.
In town Is trlckler. I mean, you got
a lot more of your prylng eyes.
If Gus can manage It,
then so can we.
Precursor. Where are we wIth that?
We're good on everythlng
except, uh, methylamlne.
No surprlse.
It's dry as hell out there.
What If we swltched back
to a pseudo cook?
WALT:
Absolutely out of the questlon.
Jesse, there Is methylamlne out there.
I know It.
JESSE:
Yeah, but what If there's not?
Because there Isn't.
I mean, really.
There Is.
Have falth.
Can I offer a thought?
[SAUL SIGHS]
Say a guy wlns the lottery.
Ten mllllon bucks.
The very next day,
what's the one thlng he does not do?
He does not go buy another
lottery tlcket, rIght?
He counts hls lucky stars,
and he salls off Into the sunset,
whlch, seems to me,
and all due respect,
some advlce you two mlght take.
What lottery dld l wln, exactly?
Hey, you're allve.
I mean, as far as I'm concerned,
that's the lrlsh sweepstakes.
I'm allve, and I'm broke.
Countlng the money that I owe Jesse,
I'm about 40 grand In the hole.
Does that seem llke an acceptable
stopplng polnt to you?
There Is gold In the streets
Just waltlng for someone
to come and scoop It up.
But me, I should qult now.
Jesse, too, I suppose, huh?
Wow.
I got you thls tlme, kld.
Hey, how come you get two,
and I only get one?
Hmm?
Oh, what are you gonna--?
That one's mlneI
Green Is beatlng orange.
No. Ahh.
Plnk Is beatlng your yellow one.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Ha-ha-ha. Oh.
l glve up, baby.
You're too good.
Yeah?
CHOW:
It's me. You got a mlnute?
Yeah. A mlnute. What's up, Chow?
The DEA,
they call me to come back.
Say they want to talk more.
I'm sure they do.
Dld you call your lawyer?
Yeah, but, Mlke,
the DEA take all my money.
I need It.
I need my money.
You understand.
What do you want me
to do about It?
I don't know.
I don't know. We gotta talk.
Not on the phone.
Can you come to my house?
All rIght.
You glve me two hours.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[WHIRRING]
[SOFT THUDDING]
[THUDDING CONTINUES]
MIKE:
Chrls.
I'd llke you to drop your gun
where you stand
and then turn around very slowly.
Come on over
and all next to Chow.
[GRUNTS]
How much
was she gonna pay you?
Ten thousand a name.
How far dld you get down the llst?
Just Chow.
l flgured I'd start wIth you.
For you,
she was gonna pay 30.
I'm really sorry about thls, Mlke,
but I needed the money.
Those feds,
they took It all, man.
Are you ready?
Llsten, Mlke--
NANNY:
Kllra, come and have some cookles.
KIIRA: It's a cookleI
It's a cookle, yesI
Let's go. Uh-huh.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Let's count.
[BOTH SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[BOTH CONTINUE
SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[SENSOR BEEPS]
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
LYDIA:
Well, look at thls.
What are you dolng?
Hey, MommyI
What are you dolng stlll up?
Hey, yourself. lee me a klss.
She sald she wanted to wall for you.
She does, huh?
Well, who's the adult here, Delores?
Tell me she ate her dlnner, at least.
DELORES: Oh, yes, she ate everythlng.
She ate her peas, her carrots.
Do whatever It takes to keep them
out of here, or they dle.
DELORES: A whole lot.
Understand?
KIIRA: Yep.
DELORES: That's rIght, my glrl.
Delores, I'm gonna take a bath.
Put KIIra to bed and then go on home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
DELORES: Really?
You don't want me to wall for you?
No, you go home. Thank you.
SI, Mlss Lydla.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Mommy, you gonna come
say good nlght to me?
Yeah, honey.
After Mommy takes a bath.
Okay.
Love you.
DELORES:
Mommy's very tlred,
so let's go to bed.
[GASPS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Don't hurt my daughter.
I won't have to unless you scream.
You know why I'm here?
What are you waltlng for?
The nanny to leave.
If you have anythlng to say to me,
now's the tlme.
[SCOFFS]
Two good men dled because of you.
Don't shoot me In the face.
Please. I don't want my daughter
seelng me llke that.
Your daughter won't see you.
She wlll. She'll flnd me.
She never sleeps through the nlght.
Nobody's gonna flnd you.
Walt. What?
No. She has to flnd me.
Lower your volce.
She has to flnd me.
You want your 5-year-old daughter
stumbllng across your dead body?
I can't dlsappear.
She has to know I dldn't leave her.
She has to know that.
Keep your volce down.
I don't care what you do.
I'll scream, and I'll keep screamlng.
My daughter's not thlnklng
l abandoned her!
Shut up and calm down.
I don't care.
You have to promlse me.
[SENSOR BEEPS
THEN DOOR CLOSES]
Promlse I don't dlsappear.
[J'J'J']
Can you stlll get your hands
on methylamlne?
Methylamlne, Lydla.
Can you stlll get It?
Maybe.
Why?
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Yes?
MIKE: You stlll plan to move forward?
Yes, we do.
I've reconsldered.
[WALT SIGHS THEN GRUNTS]
WALT:
Well, you mlssed a good meal.
The lasagne came out very well,
If I do say so myself.
I wrapped some up for you
If you'd llke some later.
[WALT EXHALES]
You know, It gets easler.
l promlse you that It does.
What you're feellng rIght now,
about, uh, Ted...
EverythIng.
It'll pass.
[WALT SIGHS]
When we do
what we do for good reasons...
then we've got
nothIng to worry about.
And there's no better reason
than famlly.
[J'J'J']