That was nasty, man.
Hallo, Carol.
-Sho': so cute.
-I know, Isn't the?
She takes amr har mothar.
Well, thank goodness for that.
Okay, evarybody,
alnce you were so good...
...and you ate all your d|nner,
everybody.
la aweetle hungry?
Sweetle, pumpkln ple,
thla one'a for you. That one'a for you.
She's got a lot more ha|r than you do.
Yea. You wear that so well. You do.
Look at what I have. Speclal one for you.
Oh, my God...
...Skyler. I'll take the plnk one.
It's a plnk one.
-Skyler.
-I know, rlght?
Well, actually, they were my Idea.
You are all welcome.
-You are the devll.
-0h, my gosh.
Hey, buddy. Ready for a cold one?
-Not leellng 100 percent.
-0h, I hope It's not aomethlng you ate.
No, no. l]uat--
We have Pepto, Uncle Hank.
Yeah.
No, I'm good, In
lthlnk we need to shove ofl'.
-Yeah, okay. Yeah, yeah.
-0kay.
Sorry, Skyler, I hate to leave--
No, no. Don't worry about It.
I have help.
And by that, she means me.
-That I: correct.
-Holly can help.
-Let'a go send them on thelr way.
-Yeah.
-Let'a say goodbye to auntle and uncle.
-Been too long.
-Say, 'Bye, auntle.'
-Bye, aweetle, bye-bye.
You know, It's been about 100 year:
alnce we've been bowllng.
-Then how about Thuraday nlght?
-0h, that sound: great.
Thank you for havlng ua.
-Yeah, abaolutely. Take care of hlm.
-Hey. You okay to drlve?
Yeah.
All rlght, well, feel better.
Say, 'Bye, Uncle Hank. Bye-bye.‘
'Bye, Uncle Hank. Bye, Aunt Marle.‘
All rlght, let's get started on
those dlahea. Come on.
-You.
-No, you.
-Waahlng, okay?
-l'll dry. You waah.
-You're a good waaher.
-Hello, Carol.
0h, hl, Walt.
Europe.
I can't belleve lt.
Were you there when she aald that?
Yeah.
You okay? Your atomach okay?
-Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm llne.
-0kay.
God, Jesus, Europe.
I Just--
And, you know, where they were
three or four month: ago.
She was talklng about It
llke It was a second honeymoon.
-We need to go to Europe. We could go.
-Yeah.
Have It be llke a bualneaa trlp,
you know?
It could be Italy. To Lake Como....
Hank? Hank?
Hank? You okay?
Oh, my God. Hank?
Hank? Hank?
-No. Are you okay?
-l'm good.
Call an ambulance!
Okay. You okay?
Just take a breath. Yeah.
Oh, God, aweetle.
-An accldent. It happens.
-l'll make the appolntment.
-All you have to do I: show up.
-For what?
Three hours In the emergency room,
all for nothlng.
All they dld waa rule out a heart attack.
-What It It happens agaln?
-It won't happen agaln.
How can you know that?
You can't say what It was.
Marle, baby. I'm okay. I'm llne, trust me.
Dlacuaalon over.
-And do not tell Skyler.
-What? Why?
Just don't.
There'a nothlng to be
embarrassed about. Hank?
Lula.
Enrlque.
Okay.
Here you go. There'a compllmentary
coffee lnalde. Have an A-1 day.
Alr l'reahenera are hlgh-margln, rlght?
At 30 cent: wholeaale? Yeah.
nght. So I'm thlnklng
we reorganlze the dlaplay.
Separate the food acenta
from the nature acenta.
I mean, doea bubble gum belong
anywhere near ocean apray? No.
And plne Ia atlll
our blggeat aeller, rlght?
So maybe we move that over to the cash
reglater, by the 5-hour Energy drlnk.
-Sure. That'd be llne.
-Yeah, yeah.
Come here.
Speaklng of the bualneaa...
...the story come: ﬁrst.
The story la, I: that we are
car wash ownera, pure and almple.
But If our story I: that
the car wash Ia aucceaal'ul...
...then what do aucceaal'ul
car wash ownera do?
They buy more car washes.
Llaten.
Skyler, you'll be launderlng
that money for years.
Wouldn't two be better than one?
Well, there's Gentle Handa
over by Klrtland. I do love that locatlon.
I'll thlnk about It.
Yeah. nght, rlght. To be contlnued.
Okay.
Good mornlng. Welcome to A-1.
Just the regular, pleaae.
Well, we're havlng a apeclal
on hand wax, 21.99...
...Il you're Interested
In gettlng rld of those water apota.
Just the regular Ia llne.
Okay. Well, there's compllmentary
coffee lnalde whlle you're waltlng.
Have an A-1 day.
Pleaae glve thla to your car wash
profeaalonal, and have an A-1 day.
Slxty-elght percent. And falllng.
Good mornlng.
May I have your tlcket, pleaae?
I knew there would be a drop In quallty,
but 68 percent?
Thla I: not what I agreed to.
I left a vlable operatlon.
The rest was up to you.
-May I have your tlcket, pleaae?
-l'm only aaklng for a few days...
...a week at moat. Call It a tutorlal.
That's the standard waah.
le thla. Get the ahlp back on course.
We'll make It worth your whlle.
That'll be 14.95, pleaae.
Llaten, thla la a compllcated altuatlon.
There are a lot of movlng parta.
None of whlch are my concern.
You're puttlng me In a box here.
You know what could happen.
Agaln, none of my concern.
There's your change, and If you'll hand
thla to your car wash profeaalonal.
And have an A-1 day.
-Llaten--
-lt'll only be a few more mlnutea.
There's some compllmentary coffee,
If you llke.
What's up?
Juat wonderlng
who waahea a rental car.
Walt, who was that?
She's a former bualneaa aaaoclate...
...who want: me to go back.
And I won't.
Enrlque, thla one'a flnlahed.
Get out of here.
Excuse me?
Never come back here.
Do you understand me?
-Hey.
Oh, thanka.
You golng In today?
Good. You know, stay out of there
tlll you're sure you're better.
-Yeah.
-Stay home, reat...
-...don't even thlnk about work.
-Okay.
-All rlght? I'll see you later.
-All rlght.
-Mornlng, Mrs. Schrader.
-Hey, guys. What's golng on?
Dropplng these off.
Where'd you llke them?
Brlng them around
to the garage, guys. I got It.
Have a good day.
You too.
Boss, Janlce sald to tell you a few
of them mlght not have Indexes.
We could glve you a hand
sortlng through them.
No, I got It, thanks.
All rlght.
-Well, see you, boss.
-Okay.
Okay....
Dude, you are trlpplng. I'm not dead.
I'm on the starshlp Enterprlse,
macklng on Yeoman Rand...
...thIe the Andorlan wlth the dlsruptor
Is back on Talos IV, or whatever.
What do you thlnk
all those sparkles and shlt are?
Transporters
are breaklng you apart, man.
Down to your molecules and bones.
They're maklng a copy.
That dude who comes out on the other
slde? He's not you. He's a colour Xerox.
So you're telllng me every tlme
Klrk went Into the transporter...
...he was kllllng hlmself?
So over the whole serles,
there's, llke, 147 Klrks?
At least. Dude, why do you thlnk
McCoy never llkes to beam nowhere?
Because he's a doctor, bltch.
Look It up. It's sclence.
I ever tell you about
my Star Trek scrlpt?
-Star Trek scrlpt?
-Yeah. I gotta wrlte It down, Is all.
The Enterprlse
Is flve parsecs out of ngel XII.
Nothlng's golng on.
Neutral zone Is qulet.
The crew Is bored,
so they put on a ple-eatlng contest.
The whole crew's In the galley.
They're eatlng tulaberry ples.
-Tulaberry?
-Tulaberr|es, from Gamma Quadrant, yo.
-That's Voyager, dude.
-Okay, blueberrles, then.
-They're eatlng blueberry ples...
-Better.
...as fast as the repllcator
can churn them out:
Flnally It's down to Just three:
Klrk, Spock and Chekov.
Okay, Spock always wlns these thlngs.
How Is Spock gonna beat Klrk, yo?
Spock's llke a toothbrush.
Look at Klrk. He's got room to spare.
Spock has total Vulcan control over hls
dlgestlon. You wanna hear thls or not?
-Yeah. Yeah, go.
-Okay. Flnally, Klrk...
...he can't take It anymore. He yorks.
Now It's Just down
to Chekov and Spock.
But Chekov, you see, he's got a whole
fat stack of quatloos rldlng on thls...
...and he has flgured out a way to wln.
He's got Scotty back In the Transporter
Room locked In on Chekov's stomach.
Every tlme Chekov eats a ple,
Scotty beams It rlght out of hlm.
-Where's he sendlng them? The tollet?
-Space.
There's blueberrles Just floatlng
out there, frozen, because It's In space.
And Chekov Is Just
shovelllng them Into hls mouth...
...and Spock's llke, 'I can't belleve
thls Russlan Is defeatlng me.'
Meanwhlle,
Scotty's In the Transporter Room...
...flddllng wlth levers
when Lleutenant Uhura comes In.
She's got, you know, her blg polntles,
and Scotty's flngers are all sweaty.
-No.
-Chekov screams.
He sprays blood out of hls mouth.
Scotty beamed hls guts Into space.
No way.
Hey, man, where you golng?
You're mlsslng the best part.
Just flll thls out, brlng It back to me.
You know you can't
smoke that up In here.
Yeah, Jesse Plnkman's
out here smoklng pot.
lee me a break, man.
Plnkman. He'll see you now.
Woody Harrelson, llve and In person.
Pull up a bong and take a seat.
Hey, I'm klddlng about the bong.
Don't be dolng that.
Sorry to keep you on Ice out there, kld.
If I'd known It was you....
Well, that Francesca,
I've warned her before.
One more tlme
and It's back to the DMV.
So are we on our own today?
Barn door open.
Barn door?
So how Is the maestro?
Thlngs have been qulet on thls end.
I haven't seen hlm.
Just as well, probably.
That whole thlng In the Jalls.
I mean...
...when they start to whack lawyers,
that's when I draw the llne.
Thls goes to Kaylee Ehrmantraut...
...and that goes to
Mr. and Mrs. Albert Sharp...
...315 East Pueblo.
It's up In Whlte Horse.
It's 2 and a half mllllon each. Total of 5.
Mr. and Mrs. who?
Drew Sharp's parents.
Drew Sharp? That's the kld on TV?
The mlsslng--?
So but why would you--?
Scratch that. I don't know,
and I don't wanna know.
The thlng Is, what those folks want
Is to know what happened to thelr boy.
A sack full of cash on thelr doorstep?
That's Just gonna ralse more questlons.
Kaylee Ehrmantraut?
That's Mlke's granddaughter?
-So thls Is Mlke's money?
-lt's mlne.
It's your money. Okay. And you're
glvlng It to Kaylee Ehrmantraut...?
It's what Mlke wanted.
So you and "Ike,
you've been In touch?
So we're Just talklng about charlty?
Yeah.
Okay, look, you know, shelllng out
money to the ex and her llttle boy...
...l klnd of get It. I mean, klnd of.
But thls, thls Is a brldge too far.
I'm sorry to say, kld...
...but you're stlll gonna be
two mlracles short of salnthood.
Brass tacks.
Okay, my Job Is to advlse...
...and my advlce ls, come on, already.
Mlke left one step ahead
of the boys In blue.
You better belleve
hls famlly's on the radar.
A couple mllllon bucks shows up,
they're gonna snatch It.
The feds have already taken
Kaylee's money twlce.
-What, are you golng for a hat trlck?
-l'll freaklng do It myself, Saul.
No, no, no! lwas Just thlnklng out loud.
Enough bullshlt, Saul.
Are you gonna do thls or not?
Yes, yes. Absolutely. I llve to serve.
And, kld, you mlght wanna thlnk about
cleanlng up a llttle, gettlng some rest.
-You've looked better.
-Just get It done.
You know who thls Is?
Don't hang up on me.
Yeah, there's a problem.
There's 5 mllllon of them
here In my offlce.
No, no, don't. Just hold on to It.
Yes.
Ye--
Calm down.
I'll handle It.
Deja vu, huh?
Jesus.
All rlght, look...
...you wanna talk me through thls?
What you were thlnklng?
What you asked Saul to do.
I mean, come on.
It's Just nonsenslcal.
Do you--?
Do you have any explanatlon at all?
-Blood money.
-What?
It's llke you sald.
It's blood money.
l sa--?
Jesus. Okay, yes, all rlght. l sald that.
But It was In the heat of the moment.
I was trylng to wln an argument.
All rlght? And I was wrong.
Thls Is your money.
Come on, you've earned It.
Drew Sharp.
That Is a terrlble memory,
no doubt about It.
But, son...
...you need to stop focuslng
on the darkness behlnd you.
The past Is the past.
Look, nothlng can change
what we've done.
But now that's over.
You're out.
And so am I.
That's rlght. I'm done.
I've been out for about a month.
But there Is nothlng left
for us to do except to try...
...to llve...
...ordlnary, decent llves.
Why Kaylee Ehrmantraut?
She needs someone looklng after her.
Mlke Is perfectly capable
of looklng after hls own granddaughter.
I don't thlnk so.
I don't thlnk he Is capable.
I don't thlnk he's comlng back.
What--? What are you saylng?
You dolng what you dld...
...offlng Mlke's guys?
If he was out there...
...you'd have to look over your shoulder
for the rest of your llfe.
And that's not how you do thlngs.
So I thlnk he's dead...
...and l thlnk you know that.
I don't know that.
I don't.
Llsten to me.
I dld not klll Mlke.
The last tlme that I saw hlm, he had
hls bag, the one that I brought hlm.
And he got Into hls car,
and he drove away.
And for all I know, he's allve and well.
And If--
If he does come back and he doesn't
understand why I had to do what I dld...
...well, then, that's on me.
Jesse?
I need you to belleve thls.
It's not true. It's Just not.
So he's out there?
He's okay?
Yes.
Mlke Is flne, wherever he ls.
We both know
that he can take care of hlmself.
And he's certalnly capable
to provlde for hls own famlly. Okay?
Jesse.
I need you to belleve me.
Yeah.
lee you sald.
He's allve.
Yeah.
Mlke's allve.
Absolutely.
You've got to have a counsellor.
Are they brlnglng In someone new?
I don't know. Maybe she'll be back.
What If she's not? What are you
supposed to do?
What's Louls gonna do?
He's not worrled.
Oh, yeah, sure. What's there to worry
about? It's only college, rlght?
nght.
College. Nothlng more Important.
Oh, you know,
Uncle Hank's stlll not feellng well...
...so bowllng's off tomorrow nlght.
-Really?
-Really.
So you're spared
a nlght out wlth the famlly.
You do not have to look
so happy about It.
I'll be rlght back.
So If bowllng's off,
can I get a late curfew?
Are you gonna turn off the llght?
Have you seen Leaves of Grass?
My book.
Walt Whltman.
Dark green hardcover.
l dldn't even know we had that.
You don't thlnk Junlor...?
You're klddlng, rlght?
Well...
...lt'll show up.
What's wrong wlth Hank?
It's a stomach bug, sounds llke.
He hasn't been to work all week.
Well, good nlght.
nght.
Mlster. Can you help me out?
Spare some change?
Hey.
Come back.
Yeah. You. Come here,
I got somethlng for you.
Here.
Take It.
Just take It.
Yeah.
Anythlng you want us
to tell Steve Gomez?
Says he's worrled about you.
Yeah. Tell hlm I already
got two grandmas.
Llsten, tell everybody
more work and less worry.
-Guess we better hlt It.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
-Hey, guys.
-Walt.
-How are you?
-Good to see you.
How you dolng?
Well, you know, I can't complaln.
How's your son's arm?
I was thlnklng about that.
-Back to 100 percent. Golng to dlstrlct.
-Gonna be excltlng. Thls Saturday?
Thls Saturday mornlng.
lthlnk flrst pltch Is at 10 am.
-Yeah, yeah. It'll be fun.
-Should be a blg crowd.
Guys, you're stlll on the clock here.
Let's go.
-See you, Walt.
-See you, Artle. All rlght, Scott. Be well.
-They're good guys, huh?
-Yeah, they're good guys.
-Well, It's good to see you up and about.
-Yeah.
-How are you feellng?
-Well, you know. I've been better, but....
-Yeah.
-Have you--?
Dld you get to see a doctor? I mean...
...when one of these thlngs
lasts more than three days...
-...you really should get that checked.
-Yeah, no, I dld, and I'm flne...
...l'm, what they say,
on the upswlng, you know?
-Good. Good to hear.
-Yeah.
When I heard you weren't
golng In to work, In Well....
Looks llke you have the work
comlng to you.
Perks of belng the boss, huh?
You know.
How's--?
How's thlngs at the car wash?
-Good.
-Yeah?
Yeah, really good.
Hey, dld you have
any of that potato salad?
-I don't know. Maybe. Maybe.
-Yeah, I mean, no one else got slck...
...so you probably
shouldn't worry about It.
Well, Skyler wlll be very happy
to hear that you're feellng better.
Whlch remlnds me,
I better get back to It.
If there's anythlng I can do....
Feel better.
You know...
...you're gonna laugh,
but I have to ask you about thls.
Belleve It or not,
I found thls on my car.
I mean, It looks Just llke the GPS tracker
that we used on Gus Frlng, doesn't It?
Back when we were tracklng hlm,
Just the two of us.
You wouldn't know anythlng about thls,
would you, Hank?
You okay?
I gotta say, I don't llke the way
you're looklng at me rlght now.
It was you.
All along, It was you!
You son of a bltch.
You drove Into trafflc
to keep me from that laundry.
Calm down.
That call I got, telllng me Marle
was In the hospltal...
...that wasn't Plnkman.
You had my cell number.
You kllled 1o wltnesses
to save your sorry ass.
-Llsten to me.
-You bombed a nurslng home.
Helsenberg. Helsenberg.
You lylng, two-faced sack of shlt.
Look, I don't know where thls Is
comlng from, Hank, but Just--
I swear to Chrlst...
-...l wlll put you under the Jall.
-Take a breath, okay? Llsten to yourself.
These wlld accusatlons, they could
destroy our famlly. And for what?
You don't glve a shlt about famllyl
Hank, my cancer Is back.
Rot, you son of a bltch.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
I wanna beat thls thlng, I do.
I'm back on chemo,
and I am flghtlng llke hell.
But the truth Is, In slx months,
you won't have someone to prosecute.
But even--
Even If somehow you were
able to convlnce anyone...
...that l was capable
of dolng these thlngs...
...you and I both know I would
never see the lnslde of a Jall cell.
I'm a dylng man...
...who runs a car wash.
My rlght hand to God,
that Is all that I am.
What's the polnt?
Have Skyler brlng the klds here.
And then we'll talk.
That Is not golng to happen.
I don't know who you are.
I don't even know who I'm talklng to.
If that's true...
...If you don't know who I am...
...then maybe your best course...
...would be to tread llghtly.