Skylar, I'm 50....
Marie. Oh, Christ, Marie. How...?
Oh, God. Oh, thank God.
Is she beautiful?
Yaah, I'm Itarlng at brake llght:
on the 40.
Some accident up ahead.
Christ! Today of all days, huh?
No, no, no. Let her rut.
I'll be there as soon a: I can.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Skyler White?
-307.
-Thank you.
Skyler, I'm so sorry. I'm just....
Are you okay?
Meet your daughter.
Hi there, girl. Hi there, Holly.
Congratulations, Walt.
0h, Ted, I'm sorry,
I didn't no you here.
Oh, Ted drove me here. Thank God.
I mean, this little bundle ofjoy
of ours was practically on rails.
Halfway here I thought
he was gonna have to pull over...
...and deliver her himself.
Well, that--
I'm glad It didn't come to that.
Yeah. Thanka, Tad.
No problem at all.
Well, let me get out of your way here
so you two can--
You three can be alone, okay?
Listen, take it easy, Sky.
-I really can't begin to thank you.
-Don't think anything of it.
It's my pleasure.
Congratulation: again.
-Thank you.
-She'a beautiful.
Okay. I'll talk to you soon.
Okay. Take care.
Bye.
Are you okay?
-la everything okay?
-Everythlng la okay.
| just wish you'd been here.
-Where'a everyone else?
-Downatalra.
Hank and Marie
took Junlor for dinner.
He has been such a trouper.
He even changed his first diaper.
-No.
-Yeah.
Dld he?
Honey, la there anything
that I can do for you?
-Anythlng at all?
-Actually, yea.
I left my overnight bag
at home this morning.
| just think you get it in your head,
C-section. You know?
But I'm Just so glad,
the way It all worked out.
Doing it natural instead.
It just couldn't have gone any better.
Let me go get your things.
And I'll get my stuff too, okay?
-l'll spend the night.
-0kay.
I was in the shower, hey.
l overalept.
I'm running late, but I'll be there.
Yeah.
Baby, I gotta go.
Okay.
Somebody broke in.
Oh, no. No, no, no!
Come on.
Oh, God.
Oh, Chrlat.
This week was tough.
Tougheat yet.
You know why?
I knew this day was coming.
-My birthday.
-Your re-blrthday?
Yeah. As it got closer, it got worse.
l was scared ahltleaa
I wouldn't make It.
I really didn't think I would.
Called in sick three days in a row.
I know my boss was pissed.
I guess I don't really care.
| just didn't wanna see anybody.
You guys know how that is.
All it would take is one friend...
...and I'd be out
ripping and running again.
But I made it. I really made it.
I got one year clean to the day.
You look tlred.
Your eyes are kind of red.
-You getting enough sleep?
-Actually, no.
I'm working on this
really complex new tat.
-Yeah?
-A guy want: his whole back done up.
Him on his chopper with, like,
flames all around.
I keep showing him the design,
he keeps asking for changes, like:
'lee me more muaclea.
Give me more flamea.‘
And I'm like, 'A:
This ain't the Sistine Chapel.
And B: l have enough trouble
working around your zits."
I really wish you wouldn't
work at that place.
You need to avoid
those type of people.
I know and I do.
It's mostly college kids
and airmen from Kirtland.
It's actually really corporate.
Thank you.
So how'a your Job?
Oh, you know. Same old, same old.
Dolng backup training
on my day: off.
God, they're hiring anybody now.
I mean, no experience at all. It's scary.
You aeelng anyone?
You?
What about that guy next door?
What do you mean?
Well, he seemed to have
some expectation...
...of you introducing me to him.
He knows you own the place.
Yeah.
Dad, he's our tenant.
End of story.
Why would I get Involved
with a tenant?
Okay.
There you go.
Oh, yea.
Oh, isn't she beautiful?
Ijuat think she's the moat
beautiful baby ever.
Yeah. And why not?
Good atock.
I'll get It.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hello. Hello?
Nobody'a there.
Oh, well.
Beat you.
-Hello.
-Hey, man.
on, M, Carmen.
Juat Carmen.
-Come on. Hurry up.
-So you heard, huh? Yea, yea.
Good newa.
Oh, ahe'a juat ao beautlful.
Well, Holly.
Seven pounds, 3 ounces.
Everybody is doing just fine.
You junkie imbecile.
What are you calling this number for?
lam trying to tell you, man.
Laat nlght,
aomebody broke In my place, yo.
-I got robbed.
-What?
Yeah. Somebody,
they got all of our atuff. Okay?
All of It.
You get me, Mr. White?
The blue stuff. It's, like, uncanny.
They knew exactly where to look.
I mean, say something, man, all right?
Yell at me or something! Come on!
Mr. Whlte.
Oh, no.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Hank, come on.
People are starving to death out here.
All right. I just had to get a beer.
Flnally.
All right, guys. Here we go.
We got mlld, medium
and may callente.
I got dibs on the breast.
-Los Pollos Hermanos?
-Oh, yeah, seriously. You gotta try it.
lthlnk thla jolnt glvea KFC
a run for their money.
That baby is hungry.
Give me that baby.
Oh, aweetle, yea.
Do you have any coleslaw in there?
Oh, no, no, no. Come on. Jeez, Sky.
-Not at the table. We're eating.
-Hank, it's only a breast.
-lt'a my alater-ln-law'a breaat.
-Oh, you are ao provlnclal.
Hank, remember the day...
...when you were talking to me
about childproofing?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. What are you thinking?
A fence or a cover?
Yeah. No, well, actually, I was
thinking more of an alarm system.
They've got these new systems that
are now sonar systems that would--
Anything falla Into It,
It aeta the alarm off.
Oh, nlce.
-Wow, that aounda expenalve.
-Well, yeah.
-But for the baby, I mean....
-Well, why don't....
Why don't you let Marie and |
get that for you?
-Abaolutely.
-No, no. Thank you.
No, no, pleaae.
I'll be back at work aoon.
We'll take care of it.
Back at work soon?
Since you're acheduled
for aurgery...
...| just thought it might be a good
idea to have some money coming in.
Well, Skyler, we need to think
about what's best for the baby.
And I think having her mother around
for at least the first few years....
Money-wlae, we'll manage.
l promlae you that.
What? You guys got, like, a printing
press in the garage churning out 50s?
Mom'a even talking
about me getting a job.
That's right. Everybody pitches in.
Why don't we ever get Chinese?
I'll get her.
Yea. Good glrl.
That'a a good girl.
My little girl, huh?
Hey, do you wanna see something?
Come here.
Oh, I know, I know.
Yeah.
Hey.
You wanna aee what
your daddy did for you?
Let me ahow you.
Here. Come here.
Wanna aee?
That's right. Daddy did that.
Daddy did that for you.
This place looks exactly the same.
Why don't you have computers
and shit? It's the 20th century.
What the hell are you doing here?
-Get out.
-No. You took the ataah.
I heard all thoae meaaagea,
flgured It out.
You figured it out, huh?
Well, congratulations, Einstein.
You left me to freak out all day long
like I dropped the ball or something...
-...and you were the one who took ltl
-Shut up.
You lower your voice.
"Like you dropped the ball"?
When have you ever
not dropped the ball, Jesse?
Blasted out of your mind
on whatever the hell that was.
What was that, heroin?
Jeaua.
l was on my day off, man.
What I do on my day off--
'Day off'?
We were on call, you junkle.
On call for the blggeat deal
of our llvea.
| just managed to pull it off by the
skin of my teeth, no thanks to you.
And you made me miss
the birth of my daughter.
Son of a bitch.
How much?
-How much what?
-How much did you get for the deal?
One-point-two million.
Six hundred thousand each.
Four hundred and eighty thousand.
Saul's cut is 20 percent.
All right.
So where'a my money?
What?
You are joking, right?
If I gave you that money...
...you would be dead
lnalde of a week.
Man, look, I'm off the heroin.
I didn't even like It anyway.
It made me alck.
And the.... And the meth.
You know, I could take it or leave it.
l'm clean, Mr. White.
For real.
Prove it. Pee in that.
-How gay are you, aerloualy?
-Pee In It.
They're aelllng teatlng klta
at the drugatorea.
If you are clean,
lwlll give you every laat dlme.
No, huh?
Well, I guess, until then
you'll just have to depend...
...on the klndneaa of atrangera
to get high.
That and your little junkie girlfriend.
Not on her tummy, Walt.
I'm not putting her on her tummy.
I'll put her on her side.
Do you wanna hold her back?
-Yeah.
-nght there.
Juat In caae ahe decldea
to do a little aplt-up...
...l'm gonna roll up a nice clean towel
like this and put it under.
Hammacher Schlemmer
makes a proper one of those.
-lt'a hypoallergenic.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, I think a towel will do.
Skyler, what la It?
Your son. He is just unbelievable.
Come see what he did.
-I told you it's not ready yet.
-Honey, just show it to them.
My God, son. That's wonderful.
Flynn.
Thla la beautlful.
SaveWalterWhite.com.
Well, I, for one,
am telling everybody.
Wait a minute. You're not asking
for money, are you, son?
Yeah. That's the whole idea.
Louis helped me set up
a PayPal account and everything.
-See?
-But we can't aak for money.
Walt.
Okay.
I appreciate it. I really do.
Show me what else you put on.
Thla waa all hla Idea.
He worked ao hard on It.
-Juat let him help.
-Skyler.
lt'a-- You can't aak him
to take It down.
-lt'll cruah hlm.
-Skyler, lt'a charlty.
Why do you say that
like it's some sort of dirty word?
Thla la lnaane.
l have so much cash on hand...
...that I actually count it
by weighing it on my bathroom scale.
And yet, I can't spend it.
I can't tell my family about it.
All of whom think that I am
right on the edge of bankruptcy.
I mean, lt'a--
lt'a lnaane.
Well, I gueaa that'a why
gangatera had molla.
What?
Haven't you ever seen White Heat?
Yeah, I've seen White Heat...
-...but I don't see how that pertains.
-Maybe you need a moll...
...more than a wife
who you can't trust with your secrets.
-Juat--
-What good la money...
...that doean't apend?
The tree falla In the foreat....
You know, you get the point.
So communicating is out?
Out.
Let's see. What else is there?
There's always,
"Hey, I found a big bag of money...
...down by the railroad tracks."
No? No? Works for me.
Uncle Murray.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah,
'Oh, many la the happy memory...
...of Uncle Murray
bounclng me on hla knee.
We loat track of
the old pervert yeara ago...
-...but he kicked It, left me mllllona.‘
-No, no.
It cannot be blind luck or some
imaginary relative who saves us.
No, I earned that money, me.
And now my aon created
hla own webalte...
...SaveWalterWhite.com,
soliciting anonymous donations.
Do you have any idea
how that makes me feel?
Yeah, look at that.
lt'a got PayPal and everything.
Cyber-begging. That's all that is.
Juat rattllng a little tln cup
to the entire world.
Yeah, there'a no deep-aeated
laauea there.
Walter, I'm looking at the answer here.
It's staring me in the face.
-Do I have to apell It out for you?
-I know. I know.
You're thinking that I should be
funnelling money...
...lnto my aon'a webalte,
but abaolutely not.
lam not going to have
my family think that some...
...mystery benefactor saved us.
Not aome myatery benefactor,
alngular.
That would raise too many questions.
However--
Stay with me here.
I got a guy, who knows this guy,
who knows this Rain Man-type.
He lives with his mother
in her basement in Belarus, all right?
So good luck extradltlng
hla fat Ruaalan aaa.
Walt. He'a a hacker-cracker
extraordlnalre.
Thla guy can hljack
random deaktopa...
...all around the world, turn them
into zombies that do his bidding.
For lnatance, he can make It
ao 20- or 30,000...
...little donations come in
from all over the U.S. and Canada.
Ten, 20, 50 bucks a pop...
...all paid In full, nice and neat,
untraceable...
...from the good-hearted people
of the world to Mr. Walter H. White...
...cancer aalnt.
I'm getting a warm and fuzzy feeling
just thinking about it.
He'a an aaahole, that'a what.
Alwaya judglng me.
Not too much.
I mean, like, who is he, right?
I mean, first off, I taught him.
Alwaya acting like
I'm hla lndentured aervant.
Now the cotton.
Needle?
-I don't underatand why you need him.
-Exactly.
My point exactly.
Flat against your skin
so it doesn't wiggle around too much.
How much doea he owe you,
anyway?
Four hundred and eighty.
Oh, hell, I'd be mad too
if somebody owed me 500 bucks.
Four hundred and eighty thousand.
What?
Thouaand.
Not on your back,
In caae you throw up.
On your side. Sleep on your side.
And she's all like:
"Don't preach to me." And I'm like,
"Baby, I'm not preaching to you.
I'm talking about baalc aurvlval,
you know?
I'm converalng
about life and death.‘
I mean, thla here,
what we've been doing...
...hell, Becky knows.
Dad?
loverslept. I'm on my way.
Dad, walt.
Dad, it's not what it looks like.
Dad, will just wait? Let me--
Just talk to you for one second.
Dad?
Dad, no. No, atop It!
Don't touch him, Dadl
-Dad, atop. Dad, let him go!
-Son of a bitch.
Dad, no. Stop It!
Stop It, Dadl Stop It!
-Get away from me, man. Back off.
-Jeaae.
-Jeaae, nol
-Back off!
-Okay, everybody just calm down!
-What's with you, yo?
-Because l'll seriously bust you up.
-You miserable little smackhead.
-Get the hell out!
-Hey, I pay my rent, bltchl
All right? I got civil rights.
Dad, nol Okayl
Jeaae, come on.
Pleaae, no. Come on.
I pay my rent.
You're going back to rehab.
Today. Now.
Look, aa It ao happena,
we were juat....
We were juat talking
about that now.
-Yeah?
-Yeah, I waa gonna tell you, okay?
-lf you would juat let me.
-Elghteen montha.
You have been clean for 18 months,
Jane. Why? Why do you do it?
l backalld, okay?
Like, what?
What, you think I'm proud of this?
Like I do it on purpose?
Lylng to me...
...shacking up and using
with this scumbag, this loser.
It takes one to know one.
His name is Jesse. You don't know
the first thing about him.
We talk about rehab every night.
lt'a hla Idea.
You talk about rehab?
Well, gee, isn't that wonderful?
Thank you for not being judgemental
24 hours a day.
Because that's exactly what I need,
to be judged all the time!
Okay.
You know what you need?
I'll tell you what you need.
What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-I am calling the police.
-Dad. Dad, no, don't.
-Come on. Come on!
...of love and understanding.
Maybe what it takes
is you drying out in a jail cell.
Yes, I would like to report drug use
in a building that I own.
-Dad. Daddy, no.
-No. It's ongoing. lt's illegal activity.
-l'd like to talk to aomebody.
-Daddy.
-Would you connect me, please?
-Fine, we'll go to rehab.
I could care leaa
about him going to rehab.
-I want you In rehab.
-l'll go flrat thlng tomorrow.
Not tomorrow. Today.
l have to call into work.
l have to stop the newspaper.
The last time I went, my houseplants
died because you didn't water them.
Daddy, pleaae?
Albuquerque Pollce.
How may I dIrect your call?
Tomorrow.
Hello?
I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
Tomorrow.
I don't know.
ljuat think
If we had enough money...
...nobody could make ua
do anything.
Oh, juat let It rlng.
No, I'm gonna go see who it is.
lt'a okay, Holly.
lt'a okay, aweetle.
Good luck with that.
But I'm sure he'd be glad to,
you know, write some--
You know, actually, here he is
right now. So hold on a second.
-What?
-lt'a one of your....
One of your old students
wants a letter of recommendation.
Oh, okay. Thanka.
Oh, honey,
lthlnk the baby la gettlng hungry.
-Thla la Walter Whlte.
-Hello, Walter Whlte.
I'm aorry.
I'm having a little trouble recalling--
lt'a Jane.
You know, of Jesse and Jane.
Jesse's ”junkie girlfriend. ”
Oh, yea, yea. Of courae.
It really haa been a long time.
Get aomewhere
where you can talk.
Sure. Yea.
I am looking Into that aa we apeak.
How the hell did you get this number?
Did Jesse give it to you?
All Jeaae wanta
la what'a coming to him.
No more, no leaa.
What are you talking about?
Four hundred and eighty thousand.
-He told you about the money.
-He told me everything.
So, what la thla?
What, aome kind of blackmall
or aomethlng?
Thla la me telling you
to do right by Jeaae.
Bring him what you owe him.
I don't call that blackmail.
I call that you getting off your ass,
and being a decent human being.
Well, I call it blackmail.
Dlalllng my number.
Talking to my wife.
And what's your end of this?
How much heroin
does a half a million dollars buy?
For your information,
lam holding Jesse's money for him...
...and be M" recelve
every Iaat dollar of It.
He will, not you...
...at a time when | see fit.
But I will not contribute
to hla overdoae.
Now you tell him, if he gets clean--
-lf you both get clean--
-You know what?
I take that back. This is blackmail.
Because what I know about you,
high-school teacher...
...turned drug dealer,
with a brother-in-Iaw in the DEA...
...that would make one hell ofa story.
National news, I'll bet.
Do right by Jesse tonight
or I will burn you to the ground.
Shlt.
He's a high-school teacher. What's
he gonna do, give you a B-minus?
Send you outalde
to clap the eraaera?
You wouldn't really go to the copa,
would you?
We won't have to. He'll pay.
And what if he doesn't?
Jesse, it's your money.
You're in the right here. He's in
the wrong. He's not stupid. He'll pay.
What la It, really?
You don't want
your half a million dollara?
You wanna renounce your earthly
possessions and become a monk?
No, lt'a juat,
I'm not the kind of dude who rolla.
And by extenalon, you know,
neither are you.
I mean, he's my partner.
I'm your partner.
The Iargeat land anImaI
In all the planet...
...IIvea In a tIghtIy ant
matrIarchaI aoclety...
...Ied by the eldeat female
In the herd.
Close your eyes and go to sleep.
She is finally asleep.
What you doing,
learning about elephanta?
Oh, honey, we're out of diapers.
Would you mind going out?
Jeaae.
Not you.
Nice job wearing the pants.
How do I know she'll keep quiet?
l gueaa you don't.
You'll never hear
from either of ua agaln.
You're not seeing straight, Jesse.
You are making a mistake.
-Do you know what this is?
-|t's a whole lot of cheddar.
Thla la freedom.
Thla la aaylng,
'I can go anywhere I want.
I can be anybody.'
Who do you wanna be?
Where do you wanna go?
South America? Europe? Australia?
-Is New Zealand part of Australia?
-New Zealand is New Zealand.
Right on.
I say we just move there, yo.
I mean, you can do your art.
Right? Like, you can paint, like,
the local castles and shit.
And I can be a bush pilot.
Yeah. New Zealand.
I can get behind that.
But I guess I'm good anywhere
as long as it's the two of us.
But first, we gotta get clean.
And not becauae
anybody la telllng ua to.
-We do thla for ua, right?
-Yeah. Abaolutely. For ua.
All this here, we're not gonna
just shoot this up our arms, Jesse.
We're not.
Hell, no. No, no, no.
We're better than that.
We're way better than that. I say....
I say we flush what we've got left
and we start tonight.
Yeah, we can do that.
Deflnltely.
What can I get you?
Give me a Fat Tire draught, please.
Damn It.
Hey, honey.
No. I don't know what to tell you.
Three stores I've been to so far,
and not one of them have it in stock.
Well, do they have
to be dlapera for newborna?
What If we went up a alze
and juat kind of....
All right, all right. No, I understand.
All right. No, I'll just keep looking.
l'm pulling into Wal-Mart now, so....
Yeah. Okay. Love you.
Thank you.
Well played.
They found water on Mars.
They have Indeed.
Don't know what to do
with that Information...
...but, hey, God bleaa them,
they found It.
Oh, well, actually...
...they theoretically can separate
the hydrogen from the oxygen...
...and process that into providing
fuel for manned space flights.
Ostensibly, turning Mars into
a giant gas station.
So lt'a a....
Yeah. We live in an amazing time.
-To water on Mara.
So, what did you have? Girl or boy?
-thtle glrl.
-That'a nlce.
-Thanka.
-Congratulatlona.
Thank you.
-l have a daughter.
-Yeah?
How old?
Old enough to know better.
Twenty-seven next month.
-You have other klda?
-Juat the one.
I've got a 16-year-old boy.
Well, he'a almoat 16.
Jeez. Oh, there's a spread, huh?
But he helps out, though.
He'a even changlng aome dlapera
now, ao....
It's more than I managed to do
when l was his age.
Kids today grow up faster, I think.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, maybe so.
So, any advice?
Having a daughter. Any advice?
No, not really. Just love them.
Juat-- Yeah.
I mean, they are who they are.
Yeah.
I've got this nephew.
Thla nephew who la--
I mean, he'a an adult.
But you can't infantilize them,
you can't live their life for them.
But atlll, I mean,
there la that fruatratlon.
You know, that....
God, that frustration
that goes along with, you know:
"Yes, as a matter of fact, I do know
what is best for you, so listen."
But of course, they don't.
I mean, what do you do
with someone like that?
Famlly?
Yeah. Famlly.
You can't give up on them. Never.
I mean, what else is there?
Jeaae, lt'a me.
Jesse, | just wanna talk.
Jeaua.
Jeaae.
Jeaae, wake up.