In the "tile vlllage where I was born,
We moved at a slower pace...
y...el fell a" the rlcher for It.
There, my two uncles were known for
and wlde for their dellclous cooking.
They seasoned thetr zesty chlcken...
...ustng only the freshest herbs
and splces.
People called them
Los Pollos Hermanos...
"The Chlcken Brothers. "
Today, we carry on thelr tradltlon...
...ln a manner that would make
my uncles proud.
The ﬁnest lngredlents are brought
together wlth lovlng care...
...then slow-cooked to perfectlon.
Yes, the old ways are stlll best
at Los Pollos Hermanos.
But don't take my word for lt.
One taste and you'll know.
Two-oh-one-polnt-slx.
Jesus, serlously.
Better over than under.
Over by a pound and a halt.
I thought you were all, Ilke, preclse.
Whatever.
We'll Just save It out tlll next week.
We shlp It as Is.
What, are we runnlng a charlty?
Come on, man. We're gonna take It out.
Leave It. One batch, one shlp.
stop compllcatlng thlngs.
Why are you purposely glvlng hlm
tree meth?
These bltches are bleedlng us
enough already.
You are pald extraordlnarlly well.
-Why can't you Just appreclate that?
-Yeah. Hey, I been crunchlng numbers.
-Oh, you've been crunchlng numbers?
-Yeah.
And I don't gotta be a mathematlclan
to tlgure out...
...that thls deal you made ls bullshlt.
-We both earn--
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
A mllllon and a halt each.
What's he gettlng, huh?
Say he's wholesallng at
40 large a pound.
That's probably hlgh.
ngh. What, for our stuff?
That's what I was gettlng.
All rlght, look,
say he's gettlng 40 a pound.
All rlght, 200 pounds a week
for three months.
And, Ilke, what happens at the end
of the three months? Look, whatever.
Two hundred pounds a week
for three months. That's 2400 pounds.
Twenty-tour hundred
tlmes 40,000 |s--
And I swear to God,
I double-checked thls Ilke 10 tlmes.
NInety-slx mllllon dollars.
All rlght? NInety-slx mllllon.
NInety-slx to our three.
That Is messed up, yo.
That Is so messed up.
-Falrness-wlse, I can't even--
-Jesse.
You are now a mllllonalre
and you're complalnlng?
What world do you llve In?
One where the dudes who are actually
dolng all the work aln't gettlng tlsted.
What Is golng on wlth you lately?
What's happened to you?
Hang on, can't we Just--?
Hey, we gotta hash thls out.
Hey, what's more Important
than money?
These thlngs they laughlngly
call plllows...
...I would not glve them
to prlson Inmates.
You want me to go ask for another?
No, Just remlnd me to brlng hls
from home.
They're not movlng hls legs enough.
Hey, everybody.
HI, Marle. Is It okay It I vlslt?
Yeah.
Hls colour looks good.
Gomey, Is that you?
Buddy, yeah, It's me.
That's you, Gomey?
Yeah, Hank. I'm rlght here.
Come here. Closer.
-What Is It?
-CIoser.
Asshole.
Man, he got you good.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm glad to see you stlll have
your twlsted sense of humour.
Hey, check thls out.
I got somethlng
that'll make you feel better.
Been keeplng an eye on that blue meth
of yours. Slx, seven weeks, nothlng.
Then all of a sudden, boom,
It's popplng up everywhere.
Look at the new locatlons.
Texas, Nevada, up In Farmlngton.
Even rlght here In town.
A teener here and there, you know,
strlctly street-level amounts.
Man, It's crazy.
How exactly Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
Because you were rlght.
You're the only one that
saw thls comlng.
Well, three cheers for me.
Thls thlng doesn't do a damn thlng.
Hank, It's probably stlll on lock-out.
It's been an hour, rlght?
I'm hurtlng here.
I could use some meds.
I'll go tlnd somebody.
Hey, no more shop talk.
Sorry.
l dldn't see It comlng.
What? Damn rlght, you dld.
No, l dldn't see shlt.
Day late and dollar short, as usual.
The only reason I'm even breathlng...
...ls I got a warnlng call.
A warnlng call? What do you mean?
One mlnute
before they attacked me...
...somebody called my cell
and told me to expect It.
A volce scrambler.
Could have been anybody.
Marle's got my phone somewhere,
It you want to run the Incomlng.
Not that you're gonna learn anythlng
worth knowlng.
I don't get It. Cartel hlt?
-Who would have called to warn you?
-I don't know.
Oh, Jesus.
-Come on already.
-Okay.
Skyler, I had nothlng to do--
Are we sate?
Yes.
Are you safe?
Absolutely.
Jesse?
What about you?
Face looks better.
How's It all golng?
Anythlng you wanna tell us about?
What, llke my Interestlng llte?
One day pretty much bleeds
Into the next.
Been worklng a lot.
-Got a Job.
-Job Is good.
It's In a Laundromat.
It's totally corporate.
Corporate Laundromat.
It's, llke, rlgld. All klnds of red tape.
My boss Is a dlck.
The owner, super dlck.
I'm not worthy to meet hlm,
but everybody's scared of the dude.
The place ls full
of dead-eyed douche bags...
...the hours suck and nobody knows
what's golng on, so....
Sounds klnd ot Katkaesque.
Yeah.
Totally Katkaesque.
Majorly.
From the u.s. attorney In Santa Fe.
Very nlce.
You've got all these nlce tullps
and baby's breath.
Oh, and thls ls chrysanthemum.
That looks llke chrysanthemum.
-Yeah.
-Look at these, Hank.
-Aren't they beautltul?
-Beautltul.
Wow, look at the slze ot thls basket.
It's got so many goodles In It.
Look, chocolate-covered pretzels
and cheese stlcks...
...and some fancy deslgner ollves.
You had me at cheese stlcks. You're
gonna have to tlght me for those, Hank.
'Get well and best wlshes
from Ted Beneke...
...and all the folks
at Beneke Fabrlcators.‘
Wow, he glves you all thls tlme off
and now thls.
-Get me a Job there.
-I know. He's great.
Boss hall of fame. I don't see anythlng
here from Klelnman.
They're gonna have to get
on the stlck.
-How's everybody dolng today?
-Good. We're good.
-How are you?
-l'm very good.
HI, Hank. Just gonna do
a qulck perlpheral response, all rlght?
-See where we're at.
-Moment of truth?
Yeah, I wouldn't call It that.
All rlght, let's Just take a look here.
All rlght.
All rlght, now I want you to tell me
It you can feel thls.
All rlght.
How about thls?
Okay.
How about now?
Do that one agaln, would you?
nght there?
-Yeah, yeah, I feel a tlngle.
-Okay, on a scale of one to ten...
...ten belng your normal level of teellng
and one belng no teellng at all.
Oh, I don't know.
-Four?
-Okay, tour. Okay.
And how about there?
Yeah. A slx.
Okay, good. And here.
Yeah, stlll there. A llttle less.
-A three.
-Okay.
All rlght, good.
Thank you very much, Hank.
Dld good.
So thls ls good news, rlght?
Oh, yeah, detlnltely.
It looks llke some nerve tunctlon
ls returnlng.
Oh, thank God.
All rlght, so when do we get hlm
walklng agaln?
Marle, It's Important
that we manage our expectatlons.
We're talklng about months
of very hard work.
And even then,
the odds, they're not great.
But you can't know for sure.
-No.
-When does he start physlcal therapy?
We've sent the paperwork
to your Insurance.
It's hlgh-prlorlty. We should have
pre-authorlsatlon In the next few days.
Certalnly by early next week.
Next week?
No, that's not gonna do It.
I've looked Into thls.
And the sooner physlcal therapy
beglns, the better hls chances are.
He needs dally sesslons.
Isn't that rlght?
-Well--
-Actually...
...your plan's treatment programme
covers tour sesslons a week.
Actually, she asked the doctor.
Plan-wlse, four treatments a week
Is talrly typlcal.
And the theraplsts In your network
are mostly tlne.
Mostly tlne. Okay, well,
there's a rlnglng endorsement.
Look, It Hank had more physlcal
therapy wlth better theraplsts...
...wouldn't It be more llkely
he would walk?
It's very hard to say, Marle.
Is the health plan's way
medlcally Justltlable? Sure.
Is It absolutely optlmal?
You know, screw It.
I'll make sure he gets what he needs.
They can relmburse me.
Mrs. Schrader, I get your trustratlon.
Really, I do.
But my best advlce Is stay
In the network. Don't go out of pocket.
Physlcal therapy Is Just
the beglnnlng.
We're talklng nurslng care,
modltlcatlons to your home...
...occupatlonal therapy,
medlcal equlpment.
It could run Into the hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
So what?
We're Just supposed to compromlse
on hls care?
Well, It you don't follow
the Insurance company's procedures...
...they may never pay you back.
I've seen patlents and thelr tamllles
go bankrupt waltlng to be relmbursed.
Who Is the best physlcal theraplst
that you know?
I can glve you some names.
But they're not llkely to be
on your plan.
To hell wlth the plan.
There he ls. Flnally.
I went ahead and started wlthout you.
Ladles, thls Is Jesse-san.
He's In for the full treatment.
Hey, klck off your shoes. Lay back.
-ExI'ol|ate.
-Maybe later.
Where's the maestro,
out parklng the mlnlvan?
Do I look llke hls shadow?
Who cares where he's at?
What am I dolng here?
Well, I was gonna have you two
tllp a coln.
But slnce the genlus can't be bothered,
today's your lucky day.
Look around, klddo. It's all yours.
What?
-Th|s?
-Yeah.
You are now the owner
of thls tlne establlshment.
-For free?
-Free?
Oh, ladles, cover your ears.
No, not free.
Look, hey, thls Is a squeaky-clean,
hlghly proﬁtable--
At least potentlally.
--local lnstltutlon looked upon wlth
favour by the Chamber of Commerce...
...Better Buslness Bureau.
At $312,000, It's a steal.
Three-hundred-and-twelve thousand?
On the lnslde, It's the best money
laundry a growlng boy could ask for.
Walt, walt, walt. Hey.
Ladles, thank you. Thank you.
Good Job. Come back here.
Slt. Come on, come on.
Humour me here for a second.
Now, you know you need to launder
your money, rlght?
Do you understand the baslcs of It,
placement, layerlng, Integratlon?
l aln't buylng no damn nall salon,
so Just forget It.
Don't you want to stay out of Jall?
I mean, you wanna keep your money
and your freedom.
Because I got three llttle letters
for you: IRS.
If they can get Capone,
they can get you.
Hey, look. Here's you, rlght?
Plnk, Plnkman. Get It?
Okay, here's your cash.
You're out on the town.
Yeah, you're partylng hearty.
You're knocklng boots
wlth the chlcky babes. Oh, who's thls?
It's the tax man.
And he's looklng at you.
Now, what does he see?
He sees a young fellow
wlth a blg fancy house...
...unllmlted cash supply and no Job.
Now, what Is the concluslon
the tax man makes?
-l'm a drug dealer.
-Wrong.
Mllllon tlmes worse.
You're a tax cheat.
What do they do?
They take every penny...
...and you go In the can
for felony tax evaslon.
What was your mlstake?
You dldn't launder your money.
Now, you glve me your money, okay?
That's called placement.
Hand me that llttle thlng-- Bln.
Thls Is the nall salon, rlght?
I take your dlrty money and l sllp It
Into the salon's nlce clean cash flow.
That's called layerlng.
Flnal step, lntegratlon.
The revenues from the salon
go to the owner. That's you.
Your fllthy drug money
has been transformed...
...Into nlce, clean, taxable Income...
...brought to you by a savvy Investment
In a thrlvlng buslness.
So you want me to buy thls place
so I can pay taxes.
I'm a crlmlnal, yo.
Yeah, and If you wanna stay a crlmlnal
and not become, say, a convlct...
...maybe you should grow up
and llsten to your lawyer.
nght, so you can get your 5 percent.
No, that's 17 percent.
I heard you say 5.
You sald It rlght In front of me.
Yeah, that was for your partner.
It's prlvlleges of senlorlty and all.
But for you, It's the usual,
17 percent and that's a bargaln.
Hey, what? You-- Hey, l|sten--
Come on, I'm talklng to you about
your future here. Llsten to reason.
How Is your brother-In-law?
He'll llve.
Walter, you seem troubled.
How can I help you?
I asked to see you In order
to clear the alr.
There are some Issues that could cause
a mlsunderstandlng between us...
...and l thlnk It's In our best Interests
to Just lay the cards on the table.
That's the best way to do buslness.
My brother-ln-law,
moments before he was attacked...
...someone called to warn hlm.
l belleve that same person
was protectlng me.
Those two men, the assasslns...
...l belleve l was thelr prlme target.
But that somehow, they were steered
away from me to my brother-ln-law.
Because of thls lnterventlon...
...I am allve.
And yet I thlnk that thls person...
...was playlng a much deeper game.
He made that phone call
because he wanted a shootout...
...not a sllent assasslnatlon.
In one stroke,
he bloodled both sldes...
...set the Amerlcan and Mexlcan
governments agalnst the cartel...
...and cut off the supply
of methamphetamlne to the Southwest.
If thls man had hls own source
of product on thls slde of the border...
...he would have the market
to hlmself.
The rewards would be enormous.
We're both adults.
I can't pretend I don't know
that person Is you.
I want there to be no confuslon.
I know I owe you my llfe.
And more than that...
...I respect the strategy.
In your posltlon...
...I would have done the same.
One Issue whlch troubles me...
...I don't know what happens
when our three-month contract ends.
What would you llke to happen?
You know why I do thls.
I want securlty for my famlly.
Then you have It.
Three mllllon for three months.
That was our agreement.
Extended annually, 12 mllllon a year.
Call It 15.
Open-ended.
Would that be agreeable?
Part of the reason we talk about what
gets us rlled up In our dally llves...
...Is to help each other put a flnger
on what our relapse trlggers mlght be...
...head off our dlsease before
It comes back.
So, anyone?
Free IIcence to bltch and moan.
How often do you get that?
Jesse, last tlme, you seemed down
about your Job at the Laundromat.
Let me ask somethlng. If you had the
chance to do anythlng you wanted...
...what would you do?
Make more green, man. A lot more.
Forget about money.
Assume you have all you want.
I don't know.
I guess I would make somethlng.
lee what?
I don't know If It even matters...
...but work wlth my hands, I guess.
Bulldlng thlngs, llke carpentry
or brlcklaylng or somethlng?
I took thls vo-tech class In hlgh school,
woodworklng.
I took a lot of vo-tech classes,
because It was Just a blg Jerk-off.
But thls one tlme, I had thls teacher
by the name of...
...Mr. Plke.
I guess he was llke a Marlne
or somethlng before he got old.
He was hard of hearlng.
My project for hls class...
...was to make thls wooden box.
You know, llke a small--
Just llke a--
lee a box, you know, to put stuff In.
So I wanted to get the thlng done
as fast as posslble.
l flgured I could cut classes
for the rest of the semester...
...and he couldn't flunk me as long as I,
you know, made the thlng.
So I flnlshed It In a couple days.
And It looked pretty lame,
but It worked...
...you know,
for puttlng stuff In or whatnot.
So when I showed It to Mr. Plke...
...for my grade...
...he looked at It and sald:
'Is that the best you can do?‘
At flrst I thought to myself,
'Hell yeah, bltch.
Now glve me a D and shut up
so I can go blaze one wlth my boys.‘
I don't know.
Maybe It was the way he sald II, but...
It was llke he wasn't exactly
saylng It sucked.
He was Just asklng me honestly,
'Is that all you got?‘
And for some reason,
I thought to myself:
'Yeah, man, I can do better,‘
so I started from scratch.
I made another, then another.
And by the end of the semester,
by llke box number flve...
...I had bullt thls thlng.
You should have seen It.
It was Insane.
I mean, I bullt It out of Peruvlan walnut
wlth Inlald zebrawood.
It was fltted wlth pegs, no screws.
l sanded It for days
untll It was smooth as glass.
Then I rubbed all the wood wlth tung oll
so It was rlch and dark.
It even smelled good.
You know, you put nose In It
and breathed In, It was--
It was perfect.
What happened to the box?
I gave It to my mom.
You know what I'm gonna say,
don't you?
It's never too late.
They have art co-ops
that offer classes...
...adult extenslon programme
at the unlverslty.
You know,
I dldn't glve the box to my mom.
I traded It for an ounce of weed.
He's a hero.
You don't deny coverage to a hero.
They'll say they're not denylng
coverage.
No, no, I'm agreelng wlth you.
But I went through all thls wlth Walt.
You'll burn through your savlngs,
and then what?
Well, you two managed, rlght?
You sald yourself...
...that Elllot and Gretchen's money
dldn't cover everythlng.
-Jesus, I gotta get back.
-What? No.
No, no, no, you should rest.
Look, why don't you go In
and take a long bath?
-I put some fresh sheets on the bed.
-I wanna be there In case he wakes up.
Wlth all they're glvlng hlm,
he'll sleep tlll mornlng.
-Hey, Sky.
-Hey.
-What are you dolng here?
-Thought I'd stop by...
...to see how you're holdlng up.
Is thls a bad tlme?
Marle, thls Is Ted, my boss.
Oh, you're Ted.
I've heard so much about you.
Thank you for your glft basket.
-That was really thoughtful.
-II was nlce. Thank you.
-Cheese stlcks.
You're welcome.
We care about Skyler so much...
...that naturally that extends
to the whole famlly.
Are you comlng In?
Oh, yeah, you should.
-l'm sorry. Come on In, Ted.
-Thanks. Okay.
We were havlng some wlne.
Would you llke a glass?
No, no, thanks.
I'm Just on my way home.
IJust thought I'd--
You know, I am really beat.
lthlnk I'm gonna take that hath.
It was nlce to meet you, Ted,
and thank you agaln.
Nlce to meet you, too, Marle.
lee my best wlshes to your husband.
Thanks for stopplng by...
...but It's actually not the best tlme
for a vlslt, so....
Can we Just talk for a mlnute?
I know you need to be
wlth your famlly...
...but I haven't heard from you
In days...
-...and I left messages--
-l'm so sorry.
You gave me all that tlme off
and I really should've--
That's not my polnt.
I care about you. That's all.
Ted, l--
It's Just thls whole thlng wlth Hank...
...has been one nonstop horror show,
you know, so....
Well, IJust want you to know
that I'm here for you.
Thank you.
But I really do need you to....
-Okay.
-Okay?
Skyler, I gotta say,
your slster seelng me here...
...I mean, so what? I'm dlvorced.
You're dlvorced. So what?
Okay, let's talk about It later, Ted,
okay?
-Is there some reason for secrecy?
-Later. Not now.
-Skyler, Just tell me--
-You really wanna do thls now?
Are you gonna make me do thls
rlght now?
Yeah, you're rlght.
Bad Idea to come here.
Ted, I'm--
I'll see you In a day or two.
Back at the offlce.
Take as much tlme as you want.
I can't belleve
you had to crush the RV.
Must've been, llke, depresslng.
For real. That's a stone loss.
No one mlsses It more than me.
Free to cook anytlme, anywhere.
No quotas, no one to answer to.
What's the polnt of belng an outlaw
when you got responslbllltles?
Darth Vader had responslbllltles.
He was responslble for the Death Star.
True that. Two of them bltches.
Just saylng. Devll's advocate.
I gotta pay taxes? What's up wlth that?
That's messed up. That's Kafkaesque.
-Church.
-nght.
Let's klck It back Into gear.
All rlght? Let's start sllnglng agaln.
-Let's do It. LIfe's too short, I say.
-Hel|s yeah, bltches.
We don't need no RV. All we need Is
a blcycle, some Drano, soda bottles.
No, no. No shake-and-bake.
Where's your self-respect? Come on.
AIn't top-shelf,
but we could at least move It.
Stlll klnd of dry out there.
It'll sell on the street.
And who says we sell on the street?
Maybe I know a whole new market.
Maybe all we need Is the meth.
What's the yleld?
Hey.
The yleld. Come on.
Two-oh-one-polnt-elght.
I see a couple new faces.
Anybody wanna Introduce
themselves?
Don't all speak at once.
Yeah.
So my name's Brandon.
Okay, Brandon. You wanna tell us
somethlng about yourself?
Well, why I'm here...
...lt's Just one thlng.
It's meth.
It's bad.
Thought I had It klcked a couple tlmes,
you know.
But then, Jesus...
...thls new verslon of It
hlt the streets...
-...and, wow.
-Not that blue stuff.
Oh, sorry. I dldn't ralse my hand.
No, go ahead. Thls Is what we do.
Yeah, exactly, the blue stuff.
-You had It too?
-Yeah, bro.
l wlsh I never even heard of It.
It was llke llghtlng my whole head
on flre.
Yeah. That stuff wlll burn you down.
Only reason I have a hope In hell
Is because It's long gone.
That's the shame of It.
No, no, man. Don't tell me that.
I hear It's back In town.
Stay strong, brother. Stay strong.
It's gonna be okay.
lswear to God, I'll do It.
I wlll go to the press.
I'll go to 40 Hours. I'll go to nghtllne.
Don't know If there's nghtllne anymore.
Doesn't matter. They wlll all take It
and they wlll run wlth It...
...because he Is a hero and he Is not
golng to be In a wheelchalr at 43.
Jesus.
Llsten, Marle.
I know Skyler's
already told you thls...
...but If there's ever anythlng
that you need, anythlng at all....
It's good to have you here.
Both of you.
IJust wlsh there was somethlng more
that we could do.
Walt.
We can always pay thelr bllls.
Please,
It's tens of thousands of dollars.
We have the money, more than enough.
Walt earned It.
-Skyler.
-l thlnk MarIe should know the truth.
Skyler, I really don't thlnk
thls Is a good Idea.
-l thlnk that--
-He earned It gambllng.
...we've had our problems lately.
You know that.
And what It all came down to really...
...WII money.
Pure and slmple.
When Walt was dlagnosed...
...It changed hlm.
And looklng back, I don't thlnk
I ever really understood...
...what It was
that he was golng through.
It was more than faclng death.
It was knowlng
that he was gonna leave behlnd...
...nothlng.
And so that's how thls all started.
For better or worse...
...he wanted to provlde.
And so he pald hls medlcal bllls
the only way he knew how.
I thought that Elllot and Gretchen
pald for your treatment.
Yeah, I thought so too.
The truth Is he never took thelr money.
Not a dlme.
He was too proud to take
what he consldered to be charlty.
Isn't that rlght?
So he put hls mlnd to It and....
Well, you know how Walt ls.
He's a problem-solver.
And he read books and he dld
a whole bunch of research...
...and he came up wlth thls system.
A system?
A system for countlng cards
In blackjack.
What do you mean, llke Raln Man?
Well, I don't pretend to understand,
you know, all the detalls...
...but he was convlnced that If he put
enough money Into It, he'd have a--
God, what Is It?
A statlstlcal edge?
Yes, statlstlcal--
.80..
-Yeah.
So he, every spare mlnute, Walt was at
some card table somewhere.
And at flrst he went to the caslnos,
but then he reallsed that--
But then he reallsed that the caslnos
report your wlnnlngs to the IRS.
And If It gets reported,
your famlly mlght flnd out.
If you do not want your famlly to flnd
out, you flnd another place to gamble.
lee an Illegal backroom game.
You remember all those long walks
that Walt used to take...
...all that tlme he used to spend
away from home?
I guess for a couple months there...
...you were sort of
leadlng a double llfe, weren't you?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, your fugue state.
-Was that some sort of cover?
-No, no.
He dld not take that, Marle.
The nlght that Walt dlsappeared...
...he lost $14,000.
It was hls penslon fund,
our savlngs...
...baslcally every last dlme
we had to our name, gone.
He couldn't llve wlth It.
But you have to understand that
as soon as he got out of the hospltal...
...he went rlght back to gambllng.
I mean, that's how deep thls went.
How could you do that to her, Walt?
Anyway, thls system of hls?
He flnally got It to work.
So all thls Is to say
we have the money.
No more gambllng.
But we have the money.
How much money?
Walt?
Well...
...lt's Into seven flgures.
Holy Mary, mother of God.
What can I say?
ldld very well.
Marle...
...you wlll take our money.
Use It to take care of Hank.
Please. Marle, let us help.
-Does Walt, Jr. know about thls?
-Absolutely not.
And I need to keep It that way.
And Hank, okay? Hank's got enough
on hls mlnd rlght now.
-Can we please keep thls between us?
-Yeah. Yeah, l--
Yeah, l]ust-- I need to--
Yeah, okay. We'll talk about It later.
How dld you come up wlth that?
I mean, where dld you possIny--?
I learned from the best.
...somethlng tells me that Hank
Is here because of you.
And I'm not forgettlng that.