Thlnk you'll be okay
waltlng here by yourself?
Yoah, whatovor.
Slr, If you'd Ilka to Imoko, you nud
to be another 20 foot from the door.
So roll me furthor, bltch.
What's comlng?
Mala, Caucaslan. Early 40s.
Multlpla gunshot wounds.
BP Is 70. Seven-zero ovar palp.
Pulso 14o. Ono-four-zoro.
Woak and thready at the brachlal.
No broath sounds on the rlght sldo,
belly ls rlgld.
Appears pale and dlaphoretlc.
How many entry wounds?
Four. Shoulder and hlp,
through and through.
nght lung ln lower left quadrant,
no vlslble exlt wounds.
Let's get hlm 2 grams of oxygen.
-What's hls haemoglobln?
-Seven-polnt-three.
Need two large-bore IVs,
slx unlts O-neg.
Type and cross for slx more unlts,
chest x-ray and KUB.
Notlfy the 0R, we are on the way.
0R 1 Is clear. Let's put hlm In there.
Yo, Jesse, sorry I'm late, man.
Damn, brother, look at you.
That's messed up.
How are you l'eellng? You okay?
Actually...
...l'm great.
I don't understand.
I thought thlngs
were golng pretty well.
I thought we were klnd ol' slmpatlco.
You know?
We were becomlng a real team.
Not-- Not so much, no.
ls thls about the temperature settlng?
I can assure you that wlll not happen--
No, It's blgger than that, Gale.
It's much more than that.
Could you elaborate?
Well, yes, of course I could...
...but I don't thlnk elther of us...
...would necessarlly benel'lt
from a prolonged....
Yeah, so....
Yeah.
I set up the entlre lab.
You sald you llked the conl'lguratlon.
And I do.
For the most part.
Look, you're a l'lne chemlst, really,
wlth a promlslng l'uture.
It's Just that l--
That we Just have dlfl'erent rhythms,
Gale.
You see-- It's--
It's as If I'm classlcal...
...but you are more Jazz.
-Jazz.
-Jazz. Yes.
And God knows
there Is nothlng wrong wlth Jazz.
It's slmply that l requlre....
-CIasslcal.
-Exactly.
0h, shlt.
Man, thls Is the bomb.
What's up, partner?
-I can't belleve thls.
-My replacement?
Oh, Jesus.
-Nlce to meet you.
-What's up?
Man. We should've dltched that RV
months ago.
It's all, llke, shlny up In here.
I'm sorry, I must be mlsslng somethlng.
I don't mean-- I don't mean to be--
-Thls--
-No.
So I guess thls ls....
Oh, dear mother of God.
Thls Is for the best.
Two hundred pounds a week. Got It?
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Mr. Whlte.
Okay, there's a lot to show you.
Some new technlques to learn.
-What, now?
-Yes, now.
We've only got a couple days
before our next batch ls due.
And I need to get you up to speed.
nght on. I'm Just saylng....
How's the cell servlce down here?
It's nonexlstent.
We're shlelded.
There's a hard llne l'or emergencles.
Come on.
So you haven't talked
to anybody today...
...other than, you know,
Captaln Nerd there.
Why?
Your brother-ln-law.
What about hlm?
-What's the story?
-He was unresponslve.
You gettlng exposure
on those wounds?
-Two unlts of normal sallne.
-Blvalve mass.
Breath sounds bllaterally.
Femur's llke a wet bag of gravel.
Other one's not much better.
Get those boots oft.
See It you get a pulse.
Get blood-pressure cup or an ABI?
Where's that blood?
Dr. Bordlng to Cardlology.
-Slr, can I help you?
-Yeah, l--
-lt's all rlght. He's l'amlly.
-Thank you.
Marle. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, honey.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what to say.
-How Is he?
-I don't know.
They won't really tell us anythlng.
He's stlll ln surgery.
They shot hlm l'our tlmes.
0h, Chrlst.
-Where's Holly?
-I got a sltter.
-Hey, how are you, huh?
-F|ne.
Yeah?
Sure?
I'm l'lne. IJust need some fresh alr.
Okay.
-Here. Let me get the door.
-I got lt. I'm l'lne.
Walt. Walt, thls ls ASAc Merkert.
Hank's brother-ln-law, Walt.
-Hello.
-l'm very sorry.
Thank you.
Can you tell us anythlng
or any detalls?
nght now, all we know
Is two men ambushed Hank.
They dldn't have any ID on them.
Probably Mexlcan natlonals.
Thelr tattoos lndlcated an aI'I'Illatlon
wlth the drug cartel.
Why dld they attack Hank?
We're not sure yet.
It could be In relatlon to a lnvestlgatlon
Hank was worklng...
...or It could be a message
to the DEA In general.
They had an axe.
The cartels tend to be dramatlc.
Jesus.
-Where are they? I mean, dld they--?
-Hank got both of them.
He kllled one outrlght, the other one's
upstalrs In crltlcal condltlon.
Your brother-ln-law's one tough
son of a bltch to take them both out...
...conslderlng
he dldn't even have hls gun.
He dldn't have hls gun?
Why dldn't Hank have hls gun?
Marle, the assault charge.
I had to suspend Hank
pendlng the lnvestlgatlon.
That means
I had to take away hls weapon.
You had to take It.
-lt's standard procedure. No one--
-Okay. All rlght, llsten.
It you all llstened to hlm from the start
and let hlm arrest that degenerate...
...he wouldn't have taken thlngs
Into hls own hands.
And he would've had a gun
and could've del'ended hlmsell'.
-Marle, let's Just--
-No. Just--
It's thelr I'ault.
He dldn't have a gun.
Honey, thls Isn't helplng you.
You.
What klnd of partner are you?
You were supposed to back hlm up,
and where were you?
Where were you?
Texas.
And you.
You're supposed
to protect your agents...
...lnstead ol' taklng thelr guns...
...not supportlng them,
not backlng them up.
-Marle. Marle.
-When they--
Honey, let's Just go and slt down,
okay?
I'm not dolng anythlng untll these two
get the hell out of here. I mean It.
-Sorry--
-Go.
You are not welcome here.
-The DEA Is not welcome here.
-Okay, honey.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go slt down.
It's not Just them.
It's you, Walt.
Thls Plnkman
that Hank was looklng I'or...
...Hank would have never
even heard hls name...
...ll' you hadn't bought marIJuana
I'rom hlm.
-Marle--
-Do you ever thlnk about that, Walt?
Do you?
Do you thlnk about everythlng
that you have put hlm through?
Marle, stop.
You're upset, and you're looklng
for someone to blame...
...and It's understandable,
but don't blame Walt.
It's not hls I'ault.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-Sweetheart....
-No. No. Don't--
-lt's okay.
-lt's Hank.
It's all rlght.
All rlght, you're done.
Okay, next.
Yeah.
Yo, yo, yo.
Jesse Plnkman In the house.
Oh, my dear God.
Walter Whlte
to the nearest courtesy phone.
Walter Whlte,
please pIck up a courtesy phone.
Yo, we worklng sometlme thls year?
What the hell are you thlnklng?
Why are you calllng me here?
-How am I to get a hold of you?
-You aren't.
It's been a whole day.
How long Is thls ngevIng process?
Just put a clock on It for me.
All I 'm saylng
Is we have a schedule, rlght?
My I'amlly
comes before your schedule.
Dude, It's not my schedule.
-We have responslbllltles here.
-l'll get there when I get there.
You know what? Whatever.
I'll Just cook on my own.
-You wlll do no such thlng.
-Why not?
Well, for starters...
you aren't the least blt famIlIar
wlth any of the equlpment.
There's gotta be some sort of manual,
rlght?
-And I can read.
-Jesse, touch nothlng.
Stop treatlng me
llke I'm llke your asslstant.
I'm not your bltch to order around.
We're partners. Remember?
I need you to slt patlently and walt,
lwlll be there as soon as I can.
Thank you very much
for your klnd words.
-We really do appreclate that.
-What, Is your wll'e there?
Yes. Yes, she Is.
She would be happy to know
you asked about her.
Please do keep us In your thoughts.
Hey, tell your douche bag
brother-ln-law...
...to head towards the llght.
So I'm thlnklng maybe we should go
get everybody some breakfast.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Do you know who that was?
You know,
these eggs are really not too bad.
-Look at that.
-Look at what?
At what? Thls. These spots.
Thls lork ls absolutely I'llthy.
Tell me you see thls.
You've got good eyes. Look at that.
Marle, those are Just water spots.
That's I'lne.
Those are not 'water spots.'
That's dlrt.
Thls sllverware's
obvlously not been cleaned.
It's covered In germs
from someone else's mouth.
God knows what.
Serlously, Aunt Marle,
It's water spots.
Ours at home aren't any better.
Yours at home are Irrelevant.
We're In a hospltal.
They need to be a hlgher standard.
They have a responslblllty.
Well, I'm not actually sure...
...II the caleterla necessarlly qualll'les
as belng part of the hospltal.
It's In the same bulldlng.
It's all under the same roof.
Do you thlnk that slck people...
...aren't eatlng
wlth thls bacterla-Inl'ested sllverware?
My God, how are you supposed
to survlve thls death trap?
Marle....
l survlved.
I had my lobectomy at thls hospltal.
Remember that?
Remember how scared we all were?
l dldn't wanna act llke It,
but I was terrllled.
All that week, all I could thlnk ol'...
...was how they were actually
golng to cut me open...
...and take out a part of me...
...that was wlth me my entlre llle.
I couldn't get that Image
out of my head.
l thlnk the scarlest part
was when they took me Into pre-op.
Lylng there,
waltlng for them to anesthetlse you.
Knowlng that you may never
wake up agaln.
Actually what I really remember
about that day...
...ls drlvlng to the hospltal.
Skyler, you remember me
wantlng to drlve that day?
Yeah.
Anyway, there we are.
We're drlvlng up Central...
...and we hlt every green llght.
I mean,
every slngle llght that we hlt...green.
It's Just-- When does that happen?
Just llke, bang, bang,
green the entlre way.
And the whole tlme,
all I could thlnk about was:
'Why today? Why?
Why can't I Just spend...
...a few extra mlnutes In the car
wlth my I'amlly?'
I never wanted to be stuck In trafï¬c
so bad In my llle.
At least I was wlth my lamlly.
I had that.
Anyway, I survlved thls place.
And I'm not half the man
your husband ls.
Yes?
What the hell Is golng on up there?
l was gonna ask you
the same questlon.
You know about my men?
I heard that they attacked a DEA agent.
Why would they do that?
What's the matter?
Spanlsh not good enough anymore?
l dldn't order thls, and my men
would never do thls on thelr own.
Someone gave the go-ahead.
Are you accuslng me?
I'm Just saylng
they wouldn't act on thelr own.
I am not In the hablt
of plcklng my own pocket.
I assume that the next shlpment
wlll be delayed.
-Any thoughts on when It mlght arrlve?
-A week, a month.
There's too much locus on the border.
We lay low for the tlme belng.
We lay low,
and then we get the real story...
...lrom my man who survlved.
Your man Is In custody.
God bless Amerlcal
He's Innocent untll proven gullty.
Correct?
I'll get hlm the best lawyer...
...and then we'll learn the truth.
Well, keep me apprlsed.
Any tlme you got that close proxlmlty
to the splne...
...there's always gonna be cause
for concern...
...but as I say,
It's really too soon to tell.
He's out of surgery, at least, whlch Is--
-Out of surgery, on way to recovery.
-All rlght. And where's that?
Unfortunately, you can't see hlm yet.
We're gonna have to walt
for hlm to stablllze.
How long wlll that take?
I can't really say. It could be hours.
But we'll let you know
Just as soon as you can see hlm.
Thank you.
Maybe we should get you home
for a couple hours?
Get some rest?
I'm not golng anywhere.
Me nelther.
Well, Is anyone else
dylng to brush thelr teeth...
...or Is It Just me?
What If I ran over to the house
and plcked up a few thlngs?
Marle? I could swlng by your place.
That would be great. Thanks, Walt.
Okay.
Walt. Walt.
We Just heard he came through.
Yeah, well, It's, you know,
guardedly good news.
-Thank God. I'll take It.
-Yeah.
HOV. guys,
thls ls Hank's brother-ln-law, Walt.
-Good to meet you. HI.
-Hey.
-We were Just swapplng Hank storles.
-That could go on all day.
God knows,
there's a mllllon of them.
-Meanwhlle....
-M|serable plece of shlt.
Guy who shot hlm, one that's left,
he's up there.
Got the palnklllers golng on,
restlng comfortably.
Your tax dollars at work.
Gotta see what Hank dld
to that bastard.
Wanna see?
Come on, let me show you.
You comfortable, you plece of shlt?
-You got hlm?
-Come on.
-All rlght.
-Easy now, easy.
Come here.
0h, shlt.
Oh, sheesh.
One for you and two for--
Yeah.
Flnally. About damn tlme.
Why Isn't there anythlng cooklng?
Walter Whlte
to the nearest courtesy phone.
-Operator.
-Thls ls Walter Whlte.
I'll connect you.
Yo, we got problems, bIg ones.
Reverend, so nlce of you to call.
Agaln.
Turn your phone on already.
You know,
I wlll defInItely look Into that.
I'll tell you what. Why don't I Just
call you rlght back on my cell phone?
Okay?
I told you to walt. I don't know
how many more ways I could say It.
Yeah, dIck, I was waltlng...
...and then that creepy, quIet guy
showed up.
-Gus came by?
-Not hlm, man.
Apparently
I'm not worthy of meetlng hlm.
The other one.
The one I'm quallfled to speak to.
He started asklng questlons too.
LIke why haven't we cooked anythlng.
All rlght, we have a quota.
It's due tomorrow.
Do you serlously not care or what?
Because that guy,
he's got, llke, the dead eyes.
Let me ask you somethlng.
Do you remember when we were
out In the desert wlth Tuco?
Oh, you mean when he put
a machlne gun to my head?
Yeah, lthlnk that does rlng a tlny bell.
Why?
No. He kept-- He kept saylng...
...that someone was comlng up
from Mexlco to get us.
Do you remember?
Now, who was that?
What the hell has thls got to do wlth--?
Look, I don't know. It was....
nght, Jesse? It was--
It was hls couslns.
Yeah, couslns.
Whatever, man. Why?
Any news?
Okay, well, I dldn't know
whose toothbrushes were whose...
...so I Just stopped by the drugstore.
Thank God for travel slzes, rlght?
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, lthlnk I'm gonna
go wash my face.
I'm golng crazy.
-Do you wanna come?
-Yeah.
Nurse FranklIn,
please page the operator.
Nurse FranklIn, page the operator.
I got candy bars.
ls thls what you were asklng for?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
Yeah, I sklmmed through It.
-Looks lnterestlng.
-Yeah.
Uncle Hank gave It to me.
Well, what's It about?
Pablo Escobar,
thls blg drug guy In the '80s.
Yeah. Yeah.
I remember seelng hlm on the news.
Well, It's more about the guys
who Investlgated hlm...
...and trled to brlng hlm down.
Some of them were DEA, you know?
Uncle Hank sald
that they were worth learnlng about...
...that everybody knows
who Pablo Escobar ls...
...but nobody knows about the guys
that brought hlm down.
I guess I never thought about It.
He sald that good guys never get Ink
llke the bad guys do.
So he gave It to me.
Flgured I'd read It.
I need to--
-l'll be rlght back, okay?
-Okay.
No, I assure you.
We are hard at work. Absolutely.
So I can expect deIIvery by tomorrow
as scheduled.
Well--
Unfortunately....
Unfortunately...
...we're not golng to be able
to keep our schedule thls week.
But not for lack of trylng.
Is there somethlng I should know?
Well, to be completely honest
wlth you...
...Gale really screwed us up.
I mean, not on purpose, of course,
but he Just-- He set us way back.
And we've been playlng catch-up
ever slnce.
And I've had to be out
runnlng errands...
...and trylng to keep us on target.
Some of the equlpment
wasn't callbrated correctly--
Well, It's Just all very technlcal
and borlng.
But rest assured that--
That we wlll do whatever It takes.
It has my total attentIon.
We'll cook through weekend
If necessary.
We wlll have 400 pounds for you
by next week.
l have your word on that?
You do. You have my word on that.
Thank you for the update.
Yeah. nght.
Any news?
No, I'm Just wanderlng.
-How's everybody dolng?
-Well, as well as can be expected.
It's thls not knowlng...
...that's the hardest part, I thlnk.
Anythlng new on these guys?
Who they are? What they wanted?
No, nothlng yet, but we'll get It.
Steve....
Do you thlnk
there could maybe be others?
Buddy, nobody's gettlng to Hank.
That was thelr one shot
and they blew It.
No way.
Jesus.
I'd love to walk In there and shoot
that bastard rlght In the head.
Me too.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah?
Great. We'll be rlght down.
Food's here.
Hey, you llke Pollos Hermanos?
-You guys comlng?
-Yeah.
-On occaslon, yeah.
-Owner's a blg booster for the DEA.
He heard what happened. He's gonna
feed every cop In the bulldlng.
-That's wonderful.
-Yeah.
And, apparently,
he's brlnglng It by personally.
-I don't even know what to say.
-That's an Incredlble....
-Good, huh?
-Dellclous.
That's so generous of you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you.
Guys, dld you hear that?
Mr. Frlng ls offerlng
a 10,000-dollar reward...
...on any lnformatlon about the case.
Well, that's.... That's wonderful.
Wow, thank you, Mr. Frlng.
You're very welcome.
Men llke your husband...
...are thln blue llne
between us and these anlmals.
I only wlsh I could do more.
Well, we do appreclate your support.
Thls reward could turn the tlde here.
It'll really help.
Agaln,
I can't express how sorry I am.
As It happens,
I actually met Agent Schrader.
-Really?
-Our fund run, couple of months ago.
Mr. Frlng was one of our sponsors.
I talked for a few mlnutes
wlth your husband.
As a matter of fact,
Mr. Whlte, your name came up.
Really?
Yeah, there happened to be
a collectlon Jar out for you...
...and we spoke brlefly
about your health concerns.
I hope that there's been good news.
Thlngs have Improved, yes.
That's wonderful to hear.
It was clear to me
how deeply he cares for you.
Well, I have taken up
enough of your tlme.
Thank you agaln very much.
It was a great pleasure to meet you.
-Thank you.
-Yes, thank you.
-Let me walk you out.
-Oh, no, It's not necessary.
You know, I dldn't say thank you.
I'll walk hlm out. Be rlght back.
Good to see you.
En]oylng the chlcken?
-Good. Good-- Hey.
-Excuse me.
My pleasure. My pleasure, yeah.
-Thank you.
It's good chlcken, huh? Yeah. Good.
-Mr. Frlng.
-Mr. Whlte.
-I Just wanted to thank you agaln.
-lt's my pleasure.
May l--? May I speak wlth you?
Just a moment.
You knew.
You knew my brother-In-law
was wlth the DEA.
l Investlgate everyone
wlth whom I do buslness.
What careful man wouldn't?
He Is not a problem for us,
for our buslness.
Your belng here Is--
ls thls some sort of message?
I'm supportlng my communlty.
l hlde In plaln slght, same as you.
-Are we done?
-No, llsten, l--
Thls attack on my brother-ln-law,
I don't understand It.
I don't know what It means.
Please,
If you have some knowledge...
...that you could share wlth me....
I fear for my famlly.
I'm sure they'll be flne.
I am told the assassln that survlved
ls gravely Injured.
It's doubtful he'll llve.
Now thank me and shake my hand.
-Thank you. Thank you agaln.
-You're qulte welcome, Mr. Whlte.
Dld you hear that?
-We're golng up?
-Come on.
What's golng on?
What's happenlng?
Startlng chest compresslons.
One, two, three, four.
-One, two, three--
-Deflb?
Patlent Is In asystole.
Contlnulng chest compresslons.
One, two, three, four.
-G|ve me a lltre of sallne.
-I can't get a pulse.
One, two, three, four.
-Stlll nothlng.
-All rlght, stopplng compresslons.
-Tlme?
-E|ght forty-three.
Tlme of death, 20:43.
Burn In hell, you plece of shlt.
Yes? Juan?
I assume you heard the news.
Your man dled. I heard.
-lt's unfortunate.
-Yeah, unfortunate.
And meanwhlle, l have Federales
surroundlng my house.
You know what I thlnk, Gustavo?
lthlnk you're behlnd all thls.
-How would It serve me?
-That's the part I'm trylng to flgure out.
Go off on your own, maybe.
Would you actually thlnk
that would work?
Juan, you sound IIke
you're under a lot of stress.
You should call me back when
you're seelng thlngs more clearly.
One DEA gets shot,
all of Washlngton starts barklng.
D.F. suddenly has to put
on a blg show...
...andI wInd up wlth Federales
In my rosebushes.
But just for a thIe.
Appearances, polltlcs.
Are you stlll there, Gustavo?
Yes.
I'm here.
I'll weather thls. I always do.
My brother's a pollce chlef.
I got connectlons.
They'll get me through.
And when I get proof...
...and the others flnd out
what you've done...
...maybe we come pay you a vlslt.
Maybe we can--
Skyler. Skyler. Marle. Marle.
Oh, how Is he?
Tell me somethlng good.
lthlnk he's stable enough now
for you to go see hlm brlefly.
I'm sorry,
I'm afrald It's Immedlately famlly only.
-We're all famlly.
-I understand.
But we have a certaln protocol here
that we need--
We're all famlly.