You can do thll.
You have reached Walter White.
Please state your name...
...number, and the reason for your on".
Thank you.
Thlrd try.
Watt, If you're there, please plck up.
[really wanted to do this together
but I can hear him getting up.
It's not like I can keep him
from seeing the thing.
So, I'm sorry, but I've waited
as long as possible and |....
I guess I'm gonna have to go ahead
wlthout you.
Thanks, Mom.
Of course,
I thought you mlght sleep through It.
So since it's almost, oh, noon...
...I think your first big birthday
decision is breakfast or lunch?
Oh, could you do me a favour?
I forgot to get the paper.
Can you grab It for me?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
Surprlse.
It's from me and your dad.
It's pretty sllck, huh?
Yeah. Thanks, Mom. lt's.... It's great.
I really did a lot of research...
...and, I don't know,
thls car Just really stood out to me.
It's got a ton of great features,
power everything, solid engine.
It's really roomy so you can,
you know, carpool with all your friends.
And, of course,
It Is safe because I'm stlll your mother.
And it has a CD player...
...so you can llsten to tunes
whlle crulslng around.
So you know what? Breakfast can wait.
You wanna take it for a spin?
Maybe later. I'm kind of starving.
Yeah, okay. Well, let's....
Let's get those pancakes going.
Saul, he's here.
Bad idea. This is a bad idea.
Saul?
Mr. Beneke. Saul Goodman.
Thank you for coming down.
-Hey.
-Yeah, hl.
Have a seat, please.
I don't understand why I'm here.
-Something to do with my creditors?
-Creditors? No.
l'll cut right to the chase, Mr. Beneke.
l have some bad news.
Nothing but lately.
Your Great-aunt Birgit passed away.
I'm sorry, who?
Apparently she passed away
in Diekirch, Luxembourg.
And this was-- Wow, eight years ago.
IJust assumed you two were close,
glven that....
Well, maybe this is good news.
Birgit left behind a sizeable estate...
...of which you, Mr. Beneke,
are the primary beneficiary.
What?
She had no immediate relatives
so the estate's just been sitting...
...while the folks over in the EU
searched for a living heir.
Well, I don't know of any relatlves
In Luxembourg.
Definitely no one
who would name me in their will.
Well....
Well, here we go. She left no will.
So that's probably why it took so long.
They traced the Inherltance
to your father.
But having passed-- My condolences.
--you are the next in line...
...to the tune of $621,552.33.
And when does Don Eladio arrive?
Let's see how the cook goes first.
Who's the chemist?
ls thls a Joke?
He's asking if you're the chemist.
I'm one of them.
Okay, we've all met.
Let's get to work.
Where's the phenylacetic acid?
Please show him the phenylacetic acid.
We synthesize it ourselves.
All the ingredients are here.
They synthesize their own.
What?
I don't do that.
What's the problem?
Look, I get my phenylacetic acid
from the barrel with the bee on it.
That's howl know how to do it.
Mr. Pinkman was under the impression
that the phenylacetic acid...
...would already be syntheslzed
upon hls arrlval.
Any sophomore chemistry
student can make it.
What klnd of amateur
have you brought us?
-What's he saylng?
-We're worklng It out.
Thls ls rldlculous.
I'm not letting some infant...
...who can't even syntheslze
phenylacetlc acld...
...teach me my business.
Tell this asshole if he wants to learn
how to make my product...
...he's gotta do It my way.
The rlght way.
So you understand
what 'asshole' means.
Now, go get me my phenylacetic acid,
asshole.
How long is it gonna take
to get him what he needs?
I don't know. I have no Idea.
Several hours, at least.
I can wait. Gives us time to talk
about the state of this lab.
Don't you have standards?
I mean, this place is disgusting.
All right, we're gonna scour every vat,
every tank, every cook surface.
We clean up every possible source
of contamination. And then we cook.
Who do you think you are?
I'm the guy your boss brought here
to show you how it's done.
And If thls Is how you run your lab,
no wonder.
You're lucky he hasn't fired your ass.
Now, if you don't want that to happen...
...I suggest you stop whining
like a little bitch, and do what I say.
Clean up!
...number, and the reason for your call.
Thank you.
Dad, you there?
I'm outside. Are you okay?
I know you're home, your car is here.
You missed my party which feels like
something's gotta be really wrong.
l.... I'm gonna have to call 911.
ldon't know what else to do.
Dad?
Come in, if you're coming in.
What happened to you?
What happened?
I got Into a flght.
What do you mean, a flght?
lee--? What flght?
Are you gonna talk to me here?
What are you doing?
-l'm calllng Mom.
-Don't do that.
Look, I....
I appreciate that you're concerned,
but I'm fine.
Just do not call your mother.
Why not?
If you tell your mother, I just--
I will never, never hear the end of it.
Can we just keep this between us?
Would you do that for me?
Just.... Just keep it to yourself.
I don't understand.
How'd you get Into a flght?
And with who?
I made a mistake.
It's my own fault.
-I had It comlng.
-Dad...
...It's okay.
It's all my fault.
l]ust....
I'm sorry.
Come here.
Come on. Dad, it's okay.
No. Hey, hey, no.
-lt's okay. Come on, please. It's okay.
-No.
Look at me. Look at me.
It's okay. It Is. Come on.
Come on.
lt's-- It's okay.
Hey.
How was your birthday?
Good. Get some rest.
Okay.
The new car...
...did you drive it here?
Yeah.
That's good.
You llke It?
Sure. I do.
It drlves great.
That's good, Jesse.
Yes.
-Yes.
-Well done.
The flrst of many.
Yeah? What's that mean?
You're staylng.
You belong to the cartel now.
You can't come to my work like this.
You're too recognisable.
Your face is plastered on every
bus bench within a five-mile radius.
Celebrities have to get their cars
washed just like everybody else.
I wouldn't have come
If It wasn't Important.
-0kay?
-What Is It?
Well, I went ahead and met
with your Mr. Beneke. Right?
Which, I will say again,
loudly and for the record, bad idea.
Yes, but It Is better than prlson,
correct?
Marginally. Which is why I disbursed
the funds as you requested.
All rlght, good.
Yeah. I can't belleve
he actually bought It.
Great-aunt Birgit. What?
But you called it. People see zeroes
dance before their eyes...
-...it's like highway hypnosis.
-So, what's the problem?
Let's just say, you and I don't
wear the same rose-coloured glasses...
...where Johnny Fabulous
Is concerned.
So I kept an eye on his bank accounts,
and pulled his credit report.
If you would, note the time on that.
Three fifty-four p.m. yesterday.
-Three hours after leaving my office.
-He bought a Mercedes SL550.
He's actually leaslng It,
but he put 4500 down.
He's gonna pay 1830 a month.
Fully loaded.
He even got the heated steering wheel.
But that's upwards of 6300
that won't be going to the IRS.
I just thought you might like to know,
loath as I am to say, I told you so.
Where is he now?
Hey.
How you dolng?
How are you?
I'm fine, but your mother
is going to be worried sick.
I called her last night.
Oh, God.
I told her
I was spendlng the nlght at Louls'.
It's cool. So....
How are you?
I'm flne, son. I....
Well, I....
I took these painkillers
that I had leftover from my surgery...
...and I made the brilliant decision...
...to wash them down
wlth a couple of beers.
Not my most sterllng moment,
I admlt.
But I'm flne.
I wish I could take back last night.
It was your birthday.
-Thls shouldn't be on your mlnd.
-lt's okay.
No, It's not okay.
I'm your father,
and I don't want last nlght to be....
I mean, you really...
...can't think of me like....
lee what?
I don't understand.
My father died when I was 6.
-You knew that, rlght?
-Yeah.
He had Huntington's disease. It's....
It destroys portions of the brain...
...affects muscle control...
...leads to dementla,
It's just a nasty dlsease.
It's genetlc.
Terrlfled my mother
that l mlght have It...
...so they ran tests on me
when I was a kid, but I came up clean.
My father fell very ill when I was...
...four or 5.
He spent a lot of time in the hospital.
My....
My mother would tell me
so many stories about my father.
She would talk about hlm
all the tlme.
I knew about his personality...
...how he treated people...
...I even knew how
he llked hls steaks cooked.
Medlum rare.
Just llke you.
I knew things about my father.
I had a lot of information.
It's because people
would tell me these thlngs.
They would paint this picture...
...of my father for me.
And I always pretended
that was who I saw too.
Who I remembered. But it was a lie.
In truth, I only have one real...
...actual memory of my father.
It must have been
rlght before he dled.
My mother would take me
to the hospital to visit him.
And I remember the smell
in there, the chemicals.
It was as if they used up...
...every single cleaning product
they could find in a 50-mile radius.
Like they didn't want you
smelling the sick people.
There was thls stench
of Lysol and bleach.
I mean, you could just feel It
coatlng your lungs.
Anyway, there lying on the bed...
...Is my father.
He's all twisted up.
And my mom...
...she puts me on her lap.
She's sitting on the bed next to him
so I can get a good look at him.
But really, he just scares me.
And he's looking right at me...
...but I can't even be sure
that he knows who I am.
And your grandmother is talking...
...trylng to be cheerful,
you know, as she does...
...but the only thlng
I could remember...
...ls hlm breathlng.
Thls....
Thls rattllng sound.
Like if you were shaking
an empty spray paint can.
Like there was nothing in him.
Anyway...
...that is the only real memory
that I have of my father.
I don't want you to think of me
the way I was last night.
I don't want that to be the memory
you have of me when I'm gone.
Remembering you that way...
...wouldn't be so bad.
The bad way to remember you
would be the way....
The way you've been
thls whole last year.
At least last night you were....
You were real, you know?
-Bye.
Somewhere you should be?
Well, baslcally
It was a temporary hlatus.
But you give us two weeks, we will
be up and running 100 percent.
All right, you talk to your people
and get back to me, okay?
-Hl.
-Yeah, thanks, Tanya.
Okay. You bet.
Say hl to the klds for me.
-Hey.
-Hl.
Nice surprise. What's up?
Just thought I'd swing by,
see how things are going.
Well, thlngs are....
Thlngs took a turn. It's klnd of crazy.
Oh, yeah?
The universe is telling me something.
I got some good news.
Some very good news...
...and I'm gettlng the buslness
golng agaln.
I figure we haven't been down long...
...so we should be able to get most
of our old contracts back. Sit.
Oh, thank you. That's--
Gosh, that's....
That's wow.
How is that even possible?
Well, I got a very unexpected
cash lnfuslon.
I guess someone's
looklng out for me.
Is that yours, outside?
Yeah, well, you know...
...I can't be driving a piece of crap.
You got to present
that successful Image.
nght. So the IRS stuff.
That's resolved?
Yeah, It's In progress.
So you pald them?
Well, not yet. But I will.
When?
Well, it's not that simple.
Here's the thing:
I never had proper legal counsel.
So I was thlnklng...
...I should hire someone good who can
maybe hammer out a better deal.
There wlll never
be a better deal, Ted.
The deal Is you pay
your back taxes...
...you pay your penalty
and you don't go to prlson.
That's a good deal. So....
Let's keep our priorities straight.
Well, my prlorlty
Is gettlng my buslness back.
And putting my employees back on the
payroll so they can pay the mortgages.
Right. But I think
your employees would agree...
...that you need to get
your financial situation in control...
...before you can help them.
Boy, the IRS
got you on commlsslon?
I'm just saylng that,
though I really understand...
...the temptatlon
to restart the buslness...
...maybe the universe is telling you...
...that you need to pay what you owe.
Skyler...
...thls Is my money.
Why are we having this conversation?
You're no longer a part of my life.
A decision you made, by the way.
So I don't understand
why you're hectoring me about this.
-Ted, thls affects both of us.
-No It doesn't.
I'm telling you to drop this.
You need to use that money
to pay your blll.
By the end of this month.
Which you promised
the IRS in writing that you would do.
It Is that slmple.
Okay.
Okay, duly noted.
What does that mean?
Does that mean yes? Because
I really need a yes here, Ted.
All rlght, Skyler,
I'll tell you what It means. It means...
...in the most respectful way possible,
there's the door.
And I'm inviting you to, you know....
And thank you for your concern,
but I'm done talking about this.
From whom exactly do you think
you got that 600,000, Ted?
Great-aunt Birgit?
That was you?
Yeah.
What is this shit?
I don't get a vote?
I'm supposed to just
stay down here forever?
l promlse you thls:
Elther we're all golng home
or none of us are.
Now settle down.
On your feet.
Gustavo.
I'm so happy...
...you finally came to your senses.
May I present the cook.
This is your new employer.
You address him as Don Eladio.
It's a term of respect.
Hello, young man.
He doesn't speak
a word of Spanlsh, does he?
And he's no chemist...
...I'll tell you that.
I don't care if he's a pig farmer.
He cooks better meth than you do...
...wlth all your fancy
college degrees.
And this one will have
plenty of time to learn Spanish.
What's in there?
A glft?
Gustavo, you're so generous.
It's a token of respect.
In honour of our renewed friendship.
Let's see what's in here.
Zaflro Ahejol
Look at thls.
Even the bottle is a work of art.
It's perfectlonl
Perhaps...
...It's too good to share.
What do you think, Gustavo?
It's yours to do with as you choose.
...to drlnk ItI
Careful.
That's beautiful stuff.
If you splll a drop...
...l'll cut off your hand.
Come on, hurry up.
Gustavo.
Welcome to Mexico.
Now you say:
This one's an addict.
To work, he must be sober.
None for you!
Brlng the glrlsI
No. No, no, I don't....
Gustavo.
Cheer up, man.
Gustavo...
...I'm not angry.
I had to spank you.
But what choice did I have?
Look, once every 20 years...
...you forget your place.
There's no place for emotion in this.
You of all people should understand.
Business is business.
If you'll excuse me.
-Where are you golng?
-To use your bathroom.
If I may.
Show Gustavo the pisser.
And make sure he doesn't get lost.
Hurry up.
Make yourself useful. Find a gun.
Don Eladio is dead!
His capos are dead!
You have no one left to fight for!
F|ll your pockets...
...and leave In peaceI
Or flght me...
I hope to hell that works.
Take hlm.
Keys.
Okay. Okay.
Hey. Hey, you still with us?
Kid, get us out of here, kid.
Come on.