You're not thinking about
going to work today, are you?
Thought I would. That inhaler really
seems to be doing the trick.
-What?
-Ju:t take the rest of the weak.
Please. You've earned it.
Don't push It.
Besides, I want you well
for the weekend.
Mom wants to party.
It's Just a little get-together,
that's all.
Sunday afternoon, maybe?
Nothing too big.
Just family and a few friends.
We've got a lot to celebrate.
Don't you think?
Oh, thank you.
...what are you supposed
to do today?
-Nothlng.
-Excellent.
Brownie points for taking a nap.
Can you meet?
I thought maybe you
might have, you know...
Signed-- Signed off.
l was even checking the obits.
So where does it stand?
Coughing up blood,
giving speeches, you know, like:
"I deserve this. I'm an asshole."
What's the upshot?
The upshot.
The upshot Is that
l have radlatlon pneumonltls.
Actually, It's not
as bad as It sounds.
It's a fairly common occurrence,
easlly treated.
In fact...
...the news is all good.
What do you mean, good?
You mean, like, "good" good?
What, you mean, like,
remlsslon good?
Remission. Not to imply l'm cured.
I still have cancer.
But there's been a significant
reduction in the tumours.
How slgnlflcant?
Eighty percent.
Dude. No way.
Now, I'm not out of the woods yet,
not by any stretch...
...but "options" is the word
they keep bandying about.
That's awesome. Serious?
That's-- That's great, man.
I mean, my aunt, she never--
I mean, you know, at your stage...
...I didn't think that could happen.
Yeah.
Mr. White, you kicked its ass, yo!
No. You must be so psyched.
Of course. I am.
Okay, now we....
I mean, what do we...?
Oh, hey, I almost forgot.
So how do you want to...
...you know, proceed...
...in light of this kick-ass news?
We'll take our time
and stay cautlous.
Sell off what we have.
And then....
Well, then I guess...
-Batter up.
-Everyone?
Hey, you guys.
I would like to make a toast...
-...with my non-alcoholic beverage.
-Somebody kill the music.
I know one party
can't begin to repay...
...all your support
and your many, many kindnesses.
But then again...
...Hank does make
one mean margarlta.
We really do want to thank you.
These last few months have been...
...wow, a challenging time,
to put It mlldly.
But I have to say
Walt's come through it like a champ.
-All right.
-Honey, I'm so proud of you.
We all are.
Okay, I'm gonna stop
with the sappy stuff. I am.
But it's true. It really is.
And for the first time
In a long time...
...we are so excited about the future.
Okay, anyway...
...I want to also
express my gratitude...
...to two very special people
who couldn't be here today.
But they send their regrets
and their warm wishes.
Gretchen and Elliott Schwartz...
...for those of you
who don't know them, are....
Well, they're heroes.
They are incredibly generous friends
who made the amazing offer...
...to pay for Walt's treatment.
And they did.
...to Gretchen and Elliott.
-To Gretchen and Elliot.
-Cheers.
Hey, how about the man of the hour?
Come on.
-Speech.
-Yes.
-Yeah, Dad.
Come on, Walt. Speech.
Well, It's....
It's kind of funny.
When I got my diagnosis, cancer...
...I said to myself, you know:
'Why me?'
And then...
...the other day,
when I got the good news...
...I said the same thing.
Anyway.
Thank you for coming.
And enjoy.
-All right, cheers.
-Yeah.
Cheers.
lnsplratlonal.
Tell you what. I gotta give
those bastards points for originality.
I'll tell you that much.
A little mercury swltch,
9-volt battery...
...five or six ounces of C-4,
that's how those cartel boys party.
Yeah, but why a turtle?
Oh, that's the best part. It was a....
It was a.... What the hell's the word
I'm looking for?
Not a metaphor, not an analogy,
It's a....
Walt, what's the word
I'm looking for?
Anyway...
...Tortuga. Okay?
That was the name of our snitch.
Bean-speak for tortoise. Okay?
Tortoise, turtle, what have you.
I never knew the difference myself.
Hey, top me off there,
will you, buddy?
Anyway.
Poetlc.
I guess, yeah. Poetic. It was poetic.
That's the word.
I guess that's the word.
Better not let your mom see.
Oh, yeah, lthlnk I see a hair.
Maybe two.
-There's no worm in this, right?
-No, that would be mescal.
Talk about your hangovers, okay?
l was down in Glynco, Georgia.
I was back east, doing some training.
Had this flrearm Instructor
who was....
He was a good old boy, you know?
Hey. There you go. Thanks.
I mean, this guy could put them away
like he had two livers, okay?
Like a fish, okay? Like a drunk fish.
We were drinking mescal stupid.
But-- Hey, hey.
Wait, what you doing there?
What does it look like I'm doing?
The kld's 16.
What are you going for,
Father of the Year?
What are you looking at him for?
We're celebrating. Come on.
That's all right.
Jesus.
Listen, I'd take a pass on that one
if I were you, okay?
Think we've been bogarting
this puppy long enough.
Hey.
Bring the bottle back.
Sorry, buddy. No can do.
It's my son. My bottle. My house.
-lt's all right.
-What are you waiting for?
Bring It back.
Why don't we just call it a day?
All right, pal?
-We good?
-The bottle.
What's going on?
Jesus.
Here, sweetie. Okay. Okay.
Oh, my God.
Okay. Okay.
There you go. Okay. That's it.
Just get it out. That's okay.
This Is your brain.
This is your brain on drugs.
You weren't supposed to wake up.
Ever or...?
No, l was just thinking
that I'd bring it, you know, in.
You want me to go back to bed?
No, I guess that'd be kind of--
Need some help?
No, I got It.
Just have a seat.
Is there any coffee?
Yeah, shit. One second.
Well, at least let me do that.
No, I don't want you to have
to do anything, you know?
All right. Here.
You take the good one.
lt's huevos rancheros.
-I can tell.
-Yeah?
-Fork.
-Oh, yeah.
There you go.
So, what are you up to today?
Working?
-Whatever that means.
-No.
I'm all yours.
Really?
Hey, this is Skyler.
Please leave me a message. Thanks.
I just wanted to say that....
We'll talk tonlght...
...but I wanted to say that...
...l'm not exactly sure
who that was yesterday...
...but It wasn't me.
And I'm sorry.
Love you.
Oh, boy.
ljust wanted to say that...
No.
We'll talk tonlght,
but I wanted to say that...
Hey there.
-Wow, who brought the churros?
-That would be me.
If I leave them at home, I'll just
wind up eating them all myself, so....
They're actually-- They're leftovers.
We had a little get-together for Walt.
It wasn't his birthday, was it?
Actually...
...Walt's got....
He's been battling cancer.
-Skyler--
-And last week we got good news.
-l'm so sorry.
-But we're really optlmIstIc.
Great.
-Great. Good news Is great.
-Yeah.
Yeah, It Is. It really ls.
Well...
...feel free to bring these any time.
Yeah.
Got some real beauts.
You cannot beat
the thermal efficiency of the ca.
Yeah?
Then again, what about tankless?
Sure. We got them.
The good ones will
really run up your price though.
Set you back about 1200.
It's not an Issue.
You want installation, right?
-No. I'm gonna do it myself.
-That's what I like to hear.
And who's this?
This guy can surf without a board?
That's Hover Man.
He can surf, skate, glide...
...whatever, because he's always got
a 6-inch cushion of air under his feet.
That's cool. Great lines.
And this guy?
What's hls superpower?
That's Kanga-man.
Kanga-man?
Half-man, half-kangaroo?
-And who's this In his pouch?
-H|s sldeklck, Joey.
He rIdes around In his pouch
and, you know...
...flghts crlme.
So that makes Kanga-man a she.
You know that, right?
Only female kangaroos
have pouches.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
But, you know, it's definitely a dude.
He's a product of experimentation.
He's kind of hot, I guess.
Nlce haunches.
-And this Is?
-lt's Backwardo.
Walt, no. I actually--
I changed It to Rewlndo.
Anyways, he goes backwards.
He can make everything
go In reverse.
Time and stuff? Like time travelling?
No, he just walks backwards.
He walks backwards?
Is that a superpower?
What good Is that?
No, I mean, he does It,
like, really fast.
Okay, look, say someone's
coming at him with a knife, right?
I mean, it's helpful. Then he can just
zip backwards away from them.
Okay.
Yo, I was a kid...
...when I drew all these.
It was like four years ago.
-They all look like you.
-What?
lt's you in all of these.
I wonder what a shrink would say
if he saw them.
Oh, shut up.
Like you never wanted
a superpower.
-Is that your door or mine?
-I don't know.
It sounds like mine.
-I gotta go.
-Where?
Hey, where?
Hey, hold up. Where are you...?
Jane.
-Hey, Dad.
-There you are.
HI, honey.
I saw your car, so I was
pretty sure you were home.
Yeah, sorry. I was working.
I had my headphones on.
Finally realised that
I wasn't the drum track?
-Exactly.
-Well, lwas In the neighbourhood.
Was wondering if you wanted
to grab some lunch.
Sure. Yeah.
Hey, this your dad?
-Yes.
-Hello.
This is the new tenant.
-Donald.
-Jesse.
I'm sorry. Did you need something?
-No.
-Dad, why don't you come In?
It was nice seeing you.
-It was nice to meet you.
-You too.
Hey, Dad.
-Hey, son. Are you home early?
-No.
Oh, man.
It was a good day?
Now it is. Finally, hot water.
No more toxic waste.
Yes. Yes, Indeed.
Top of the line, on demand,
unlimited supply.
-Sweet.
-Yeah.
-Hey, want to take her for a spin?
-Oh, yeah.
LIsten, why don't you
go to the kitchen sink?
Let me know when you're ready,
and I'll give you a holler.
Okay.
Pllot In.
lgnltlon. Blngo.
Okay.
-Ready.
-All right. Let her rIp.
Hundred and seventeen
thousand BTUs.
-Oh, yeah?
-Oh, yeah.
BuIIt-In corroslon-reslstant
draught reducer...
...safety thermocouple
with the leot burner.
Sounds really good, Dad.
And the energy savings. I mean....
Oh, careful, careful, careful.
There's probably some adjustments
I need to make. You okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-Okay.
-...about yesterday--
-l'm sorry about the pool.
No, no, no, that was not your fault.
Not at all.
See, your....
Your old man embarrassed himself...
...and I'm not very proud
of my behaviour.
l have to say I feel very foolish.
You and Uncle Hank,
you seemed pissed off.
No. No. We're flne.
Everything's flne.
I called him this morning
and made my apologies.
But, son, I owe you
an apology most of all.
I should have used
better judgement all around.
Havlng you drink In the first place,
It was not right...
...and for that I'm very sorry.
But I kept up, right?
You and Uncle Hank. I drank three.
l have some tools to put away.
Hey.
Yo.
You want to catch a movie later?
-What?
-What was that all about?
What?
Before. With your dad.
It wasn't about anything.
Oh, okay, so I totally
just mlsread your total dIs?
If anything, I was doing you a favour.
A favour?
Yeah, I told you. He's a hard-ass.
-He seemed cool to me.
-Yeah, well.
-So, what's the deal?
-There's no deal.
l was helping you out, okay?
Protectlng you.
-How's that?
-I mean...
...l'm letting you smoke In here
and everything.
I bought a filter.
And I figured
the less he knows, the better.
You acted like
you didn't even know me.
So?
-So?
-You think I'm gonna be all like:
'Dad, meet the stoner guy
who lives next door.
And by the way,
I'm sleeping with hlm'?
That's all you think you're doing?
-Why do you even care about my dad?
-I don't.
Good. Then I don't know
why we're talking about it.
Us. All right? I'm talking about us.
-Us.
-Yeah.
You and me.
Who's you and me?
I'm out of here.
Oh, boy.
Dad?
Dad? Hello?
What? Oh, hey.
-What are you doing?
-We've got rot.
-Rot?
-Yeah. Here.
I'll show you. Here.
Take a look at that.
See that? Yeah.
Ever seen anything like It?
-lt's wood.
-lt's wood...
...that contains fruiting bodies.
Frulty what?
Fungus. And it is on a rampage.
I don't really see anything.
Yeah, well, it's there. You just have
to know where to look. Here.
Then you cut it all out.
You just cut it out and start fresh.
Well, better get to it.
Is the whole house
gonna collapse or something?
Not If I can help It.
Hey. You bucking for a promotion?
-Go home already.
-I will. I will.
Hey, can ljust ask...
-...the Keller account?
-The Keller account?
lt's listed as a current asset
on this balance sheet...
...but the invoice was never presented
to accounts receivable, so....
Oh, God.
One of these days I'm gonna just
sort through all the Dad stuff.
He had so many "Don't worry about it,
pay me Friday" relationships...
...with these little companies.
We'll figure it out tomorrow. Or not.
nght.
Seriously, you're not gonna
make me lock you in, are you?
Sky?
Skyler?
Jesus.
No, I'm fine.
It's hormones. Honestly.
It happens all the tIme.
I'll see you tomorrow.
What's wrong?
I guess It just...
...doesn't feel any different.
The good news?
I mean, nothing's really changed.
It's just postponed.
There was supposed to be a light
at the end of the tunnel.
But lately, it just feels like....
More tunnel.
I'm sorry.
I just feel so damn ungrateful.
I don't know.
For me, it was the flu.
-What?
-My dad rallled at the end.
I mean, It wasn't the full-on
good news Walt got...
...dlfferent circumstances,
but we were happy...
...we were over the moon.
And right then, I got sick.
Flu.
Knocked me on my ass for days.
Couldn't get out of bed,
I couldn't move.
-Great tlmlng, huh?
-Yeah.
And I wasn't even putting two
and two together. I was just thinking:
'Why now?'
Being that rock.
You know...
...belng that rock
takes everything you got.
Yeah.
--causlng the houslng prlces
to trend.
Foreclosures are belng fuelled
by a splke In....
The economy is rapidly deteriorating
and unemployment is climbing.
With Americans losing money over
rising inflation and tight spending...
the houslng market
ls unllkely to rebound...
...speIIlng more paln
for the economy.
Yeah.
Are you going to work today?
Skyler, there's rot.
All right. We'll take care of that
tomorrow. Okay, good night.
-Good night, Ted.
-Good night.
Oh, damn.
-CIumsy.
-I got It.
No, no, Ted.
You don't have to do that.
Get organised. Storage containers
to meet every need...
...big or small, on Aisle 3.
Stashlng your stuff
has never been so easy.
Get a thlcker, fuller lawn
In less than slx weeks.
Why can't the grass
always be greener on your side?
Go to Aisle 10 to go green.
Get a manager
on Checkout 4, please.
Manager to Checkout 4.
Pest problems? No problem.
Your extermlnatlon destlnatlon
ls Alsle 6.
You're buying the wrong matches.
-What?
-Those matches.
They're the wrong kind.
Red phosphorous Is found
In the striker strlps...
...not the matches themselves.
You need to get the big 200-count box
of individual matchbooks.
More striker strips. You understand?
Those only have the one.
And don't buy everything
In one place.
Do It pIecemeal.
Different items, different stores.
Attracts less attention.
Are you following me here?
You've been putting off
refinishing that deck long enough.
We have everything you need
to do the job right.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
-Next.
-H|. Here you go.
-You didn't buy my stuff?
-No, I didn't.
We don't have time for this.
Hey, there he is. That's the guy.
Stay out of my territory.