KDK-12, come In.
-KDK-12.
Hey, Bobby,
need you to look In on Mrs. Peykelewa.
-She all rlght?
-Her daughter called from Callfornla.
She hasn't heard from her In a thIe,
kInd of worrIed.
Wlll do.
Mlu Peyketewa, hello.
Mlu Peyketewa.
KDK-12 here.
Janet, Jesus, we got a homlclde.
-Come agaln?
-M|ss Peyketewa, she's dead.
-I need some backup out here.
-Okay. On lhelr way.
Whoever's In there,
show yourself rlght now!
Hold It rlght there.
Let me see your hands.
All rlght, down.
On your knees.
You understand me?
Do you speak Engllsh?
l sald, down. On your knees.
Damn It, get down.
On your knees.
Do It.
On your knees or I'll tlrel
-Yeah?
-I found the papers.
nght where you left them,
In the crlh.
Yeah, well....
You know best, rlght?
Anythlng else?
Do you have any thought...
...about how we're golng
to approach thls wlth Walter Jr.?
Well, he's stIll my son.
-I mean, he wlll remaIn--
-0t course.
My polnt helng...
...the dlvorce.
Well, I....
lthlnk he gets It, don't you?
lthlnk he saw It comlng.
He sees your unhapplness and--
My unhapplness?
My completely out-of-the-clear...
...blue-sky unhapplness?
Really?
Look, as you sald, tor the best.
Yeah.
Okay.
Last thlng and then I'll let you go.
In the chlld support worksheet,
you lIst medlcal, dental...
...chlld care, transportatlon, houslng,
educatlon, tood, clothlng.
That's rlght, all of It.
Walt.
-No.
-Skyler, you wanted me out...
...l'm out,
but I wlll provlde for my tamlly.
Not wlth that money.
You'd be maklng us accessorles
after the fact.
How do you thlnk we've been paylng
our bllls these last slx months?
l have to go.
Yep, I was rlght.
Three unlts avallable,
exact same floor plan.
I can call over, get you In
to see any of the others.
No, no, thls one's tlne.
I'll take It.
Now, unfortunately,
thls one Is the model, so--
Yeah, I llke It.
l llke everythlng about It.
I'll take It as-Is.
Name one thlng In thls world
that Is not negotlable.
-You have to clean the fryer.
-Yes, slr.
We try to clean them every nlght...
...but make sure It's off
before you open the Intake valve.
Good. Now, I suggest that you add thls
to your Monday malntenance schedule.
Yes, slr. Now, select freezlng mode...
...clock button off, press and hold
auto-control untll It beeps.
Maln valve on, maln swltch on.
lee the compressor tlme
for the needle to enter the green.
You're for real?
-Th|s Is all you?
-All me.
Helsenberg who? That's what I say.
My man Jesse can cook.
Check It, yo.
It aIn't cloudy or dlrty or nothlng.
-Just the rlght shade of blue.
-Good shade.
Check out that crystal slze.
If that bltch was any blgger...
-...lt would be a Jolly Rancher.
-Be my guest.
You sure?
I feel kInd of dlcklsh
wlth you belng In rehab and all.
No. I can watch, yo.
-I can cook and I can watch.
-Go for It.
l trled It last week.
I'm stlll comlng down.
Go easy.
Okay.
Rlverdance.
Hey, hey, stop marklng up my floor,
dumb-ass. Come on.
Bow before me.
I am Lord of the Dance.
Shlt.
I gotta try that agaln.
Yeah, no, lthlnk you're good.
That Is awesome, Jesse.
I feel llke somebody took my braln out
and bolled It In, llke, bolllng hot--
It's the bomb, man, serlously.
lee anthrax.
...you ready to talk some buslness?
You mean thls Is not, llke,
Just recreatlonal?
...what you're thlnklng.
Trust me,
It's not gonna be llke It was.
All rlght, never gonna be llke It was.
-How's that?
-We sell It safe.
All rlght? We sell It smart.
We don't get greedy, llke before.
I don't know, man.
Combo and all.
stlll...
...man's gotta make hls llvlng.
If It's llke Jesse says
and we're not greedy....
...I guess I can see It.
Had a good thlng golng
before we started pushlng our luck.
-If It can go back to belng llke that--
-Hey, It wlll be.
step one, we bulld Inventory.
Badger, go see Clovls.
Get the RV In shape, tune-up,
oll change, brake llghts, and whatnot.
Cops always pull you over
for brake llghts. Not us.
Cautlous.
-R|ght on.
-You got It.
You know that buzzer thlng?
Leave the key In the Ignltlon, It buzzes?
Just have hlm put In
one of those too.
Sklnny, you're In charge of supplles.
I'll get you a llst.
mm on.
-Yeah.
-Al| rlght.
-...we good?
-Yeah.
Good?
-Al| rlght.
-Let's do thls thlng.
Brandon Mayhew.
I know you.
Small world, Albuquerque.
Wanna talk about It?
Why? It's not llke I get a vote.
You know, lronlcally...
...l thlnk you're gonna see
much more of me from now on.
Sure.
Well, Just as much of me at least.
I'm taklng you to the school,
to and from, every day.
What, I don't get a vote In thls
elther?
I gotta stop golng wlth Louls
Just because you're feellng gullty?
I do feel gullty.
I am the man that I am, son...
...and there's plenty
that I would change about that, but....
Here we are,
and thls Is Just what It Is.
You know what? Call me crazy...
...but I'm actually feellng very good
about the future.
Mornlng.
I'm wonderlng If we should
maybe call the pollce or somethlng.
Why?
They're dolng nothlng wrong.
Okay, let's put thls on Table 33,
okay?
Hello there.
Mr. Whlte, I presume?
Oh, yes. HI.
Sorry. I'll be rlght down.
-H|. Gale Boettlcher.
-Hl.
You're my new lab asslstant,
I take If.
Yes, I am.
I suppose you'll wanna hear
my quallflcatlons.
l have my resume here for you.
l recelved my bachelor's degree
from UNM.
My master's
from the Unlverslty of Colorado.
Organlc chemlstry
wlth a speclallty In....
It's all rlght there.
'X-ray crystallography.‘
Really?
I could talk about that for hours.
I would love to.
But flrst, I'm curlous about thls.
That's a llttle pet project of mlne.
See, In my oplnlon,
It's all about the qulnlc acId level.
You want Just north of 4800 mIllIgrams
per lltre...
...but If you over-boll to get there,
you'll leach your tannlns.
Bltterness, yuck.
So I pull a mIld vacuum.
That way, I can keep the temperature
no hlgher than 92 c and....
Judge for yourself.
Oh, my God.
My God, that Is the best coffee
I've ever tasted.
Sumatran beans...
...and I also have to glve credlt
to the grlnd...
-...but thank you, Mr. Whlte.
-Walt.
Please, call me Walt.
Why the hell are we maklng meth?
Hey.
Tell me...
...wlth the phenylacetlc acId
solutlon...
...you sald 150 drops per mlnute
for the flrst 1o mlnutes...
...and then 90 for the remalnder.
Why Is that?
Well, my thlnklng Is,
by taperlng the phenyl...
...you get an olller aqueous layer,
and hence--
Better benzene extractlon.
Exactly.
But actually, I prefer ether.
Oh, I'll have It for tomorrow.
Gale, I'm wonderlng how you--
Ended up here.
Well, actually, I'm stlll wonderlng
how I ended up here, but, yes.
I mean, I can't lmaglne
we strlke each other as crImlnals.
Well, there's crlme
and then there's crlme...
I'm deflnltely a llbertarlan.
Consentlng adults want
what they want...
...and If I'm not supplylng If,
they wlll get It somewhere else.
Wlth me, they're gettlng exactly
what they pay for.
No added toxlns or adulterants.
Yeah, I was dolng It
the way you are supposed to...
...pursulng my doctorate at Colorado,
NSF research grant.
l was on my way,
Jumplng through hoops...
...klsslng the proper behlnds...
...attendlng to all the non-chemlstry
that one flnds oneself occupled by.
You know that world.
That Is not what I slgned on for.
I love the lab.
Because It's all stlll maglc.
You know?
Chemlstry?
...once you lose that...
It Is.
It Is maglc.
It stlll ls.
And all the whlle, I kept thlnklng
about that great old Whltman poem:
'When I Heard
the Learn'd Astronomer.‘
I don't know It.
Anyway....
Well, can you reclte It?
Pathetlcally enough, I could.
All rlght, well....
No, no, come on. Come on.
Yeah?
When I heard the learn'd astronomer
When the proofs, the ﬁgures
Were ranged In columns before me
When I was shown the charts
And the dlagrams
To add, dlvlde, and measure them
When I, sIttIng,
Heard the astronomer
Where he lectured wlth much applause
In the lecture-room
How soon, unaccountable
I became tIred and slck
Tlll rIsIng and glIdIng out
I wander'd off by myself
In the mystlcal molst nIght-alr
And from tlme to tlme
Look'd up In perfect sIlence
At the stars
Yes.
I am a nerd.
-Bravo.
-Thank you.
Come on, Plnkman.
You llttle rat bastard.
Get off your lazy ass
and go break the law.
-Hey, baby.
-Are you ever comlng home?
Marle, I'm worklng.
DId you flnd It? The RV?
No. Worklng on It, so....
Why can't you Just arrest hlm,
make hlm tell you?
It's not slmple.
There's a thlng called the Constltutlon.
Constltutlon, blah, blah, blah.
Thls kld, Iswear to God,
I wlsh I just could....
Thls Is that Plnkman character?
That's the one.
Posltlve the llttle bastard's
got an RV.
IJust don't know where he keeps It.
Untll he actually leads me to It
or does somethlng...
...l'm stuck here, Marle, so sorry.
Well, not to brlng up
anclent hlstory...
...but I, for one, can thlnk of someone
who mlght know somethlng.
Posslbly.
It's worth a shot.
Yeah?
Who?
-Hel|o.
-Oh, hey, buddy.
Hey, how you dolng?
Oh, hey, Hank. What's up?
Llsten, I hate to bother you.
-I just had a qulck questlon.
-Shoot.
I only ask thls because I'm at a,
you know, dead end here, potentlally.
I'm worklng a case and--
You know that I would never put you on
the spot or make you uncomfortable.
Hank, you could Just cut
to the chase.
Back when we lost you
and l was trylng to track you down...
through your student,
Jesse Plnkman.
Now, you know that I know
that once upon a tlme...
...he may have dealt you
a llttle weed.
-Hank--
-Just a llttle.
And I so do not care about that.
As far as I'm concerned,
you never Inhaled.
lee you sald, cut to the chase.
Do you remember
If thls Plnkman kId ever had an RV?
You know, a recreatlonal vehlcle...
...you know, llke a WInnebago-type
deal, brown and belge?
Why?
Long story, but I'm personally of
the oplnlon he's moved on from weed...
...and graduated to selllng
crystal meth, uslng It as a rolllng lab.
Walt?
Yo.
What, Mr. Whlte?
How's my favourlte genlus?
ls thls a secure llne?
ls thls a secure--?
Yes, what's wlth the--?
Hey, hello to you too.
Llsten, we've got a problem,
a DEA problem.
-l'm llstenlng.
-My brother-In-law...
...he knows about the RV.
What RV?
Our RV...
...the one whlch contalns a meth lab,
whlch Is covered wlth my flngerprlnts.
What does 'knows about' mean?
Does he have It? Has he searched It?
No, he knows It exlsts
and he's trylng to flnd It.
He has llnked It to Jesse. It's a matter
of tlme before he tracks It down.
So get rId of Itl
What are you dolng sIttIng there?
Better yet, have Plnkman get rld of It.
nght? You don't go near It.
My brother-ln-law,
he Is survellllng Jesse's house.
So he mlght have tapped the phones
or bugged hls house.
Jesus. Plan A, then.
Go. Get to It before the feds do.
And do what exactly?
I mean, what--?
The thlng Is the slze of a--
It's RV-slze.
lmean, where do I go
to make an RV dlsappear?
I'm not DavId Copperfleld.
What do I look llke,
the RV dlsposal people?
-D|d you not plan for thls contlngency?
-No.
Well, next tlme, plan for It,
would you?
The Starshlp Enterprlse
had a self-destruct button.
Okay. Shut up.
I'm Just saylng,
you're good wlth tools and all.
Why don't you Invent
a water-powered car, you know?
You dId that,
you would be rolllng In It.
Socket wrench.
The blg one.
What? You scared of the Arabs?
You out of your mlnds?
Why Is thls In the open?
-Who the hell are you?
-He's Helsenberg.
-ls thls drlvable?
-Yeah. I was changlng the o".
Flnlsh It. We'll wlpe It clean,
take If out to the desert.
Come on, help me.
Hold up. What's thls about?
The DEA,
the Drug Enforcement Admlnlstratlon.
You've heard of them, rlght?
I know you have.
They know all about thls RV
and they're trylng to flnd It rlght now.
I want thls off my property now.
No, no, we have got
to destroy the evldence.
-We've gotta rlg thls thlng to burn.
-Not here. Get It out of here.
Now, llsten to me.
I need your help, okay?
If I go down, we all go down.
Do you understand?
All rlght, Just--
I know a way. I know a guy that'll
wlpe thls off the planet, no questlons.
Call hlm.
Hey, what about Jesse?
What about hlm?
Hey, It's me.
Wanna hear somethlng welrd?
Now, llsten to me.
You get that address.
Now, Badger, I don't care how.
You flnd out where he's taklng It.
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me. Are you leavlng?
Excuse me, gentlemen, these booths
are for paylng customers only.
Cynthla, It's okay. I'll handle thls.
What can I do for you?
You know.
Sunset.
Nlnety-slx, 97, 98, 99, 100.
Beyond recovery, rlght?
-Beyond recovery means--
-I got It. Beyond recovery.
-Obllterated, no evldence.
-Hey, don't worry.
When we're through wlth It,
It's gonna be about yay blg.
Then we flatbed It over to Long Beach,
shlp It across the Paclflc.
Chlnese turn If Into patlo furnlture...
...so mlnd at ease.
Llsten, can you do me a favour?
I'm obvlously gonna need a rlde.
-Could you call a cab?
-You got It. Pleasure dolng buslness.
Thank you. I'll be rlght behlnd you.
IJust need to....
-The hell you thlnk you're dolng?
-Me?
Thls Is mlne Just as much as yours.
You don't get to Just--
-0h, God.
-What?
What?
He's here.
Who's here?
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
You led hlm rlght to us.
Shlt.
Mr. Plnkman,
you wanna add reslstlng arrest?
We'll add If. No skln off my ass.
Last chance to do It the easy way.
Got a warrant?
Who are you, huh? Who are you
and what do you know about thls RV?
Well, I'm the owner of thls lot...
...whlch means you're trespasslng
on prlvate property.
As far as the RV goes,
seems to me It's locked...
...whlch means you're trylng to break
and enter, so agaln, you got a warrant?
Well, I don't need one
If I've got probable cause, counsellor.
Probable cause usually relates
to vehlcles, Is my understandlng.
You know, trafflc stops and whatnot.
See these round rubber thlngs?
Those are wheels.
Thls Is a vehlcle.
Thls Is a domlclle, a resldence...
...protected by the Fourth Amendment
from unlawful search and selzure.
-Why don't you Just go out--?
-D|d you see thls drlve?
How do you know It runs?
DId you actually wltness
any wrongdolng?
It seems to me
you're Just out here flshlng.
Don't see that holdlng up
In a court of law.
Oh, yeah?
Look at these.
What do those look llke to you?
They sure look llke bullet holes to me.
There was a flrearm dlscharged
lnslde of thls domlclle.
There's a Judge or two out there
who'd see that as probable cause.
Call the Albuquerque pollce....
How could you have known they were
there before you took off the tape?
What?
How could you have known they were
there before you took off the tape?
Say It. Say It.
--DEA operatlon, there's 20 guys
rushlng In here llke the wrath of God.
How could you have known they were
there before you took off the tape?
That's rlght.
Probable cause
needs to be readlly apparent.
There's somebody In there.
'PrIvate domlclle
and I won't be harassed.‘
I'll glve you three seconds
to get your ass out here. One, two--
Thls Is my own prlvate domlclle
and l wlll not be harassed.
Bltch.
Flne. You want your warrant?
I'll have my guys brlng It and dellver It
on a llttle satln plllow. How's that?
l walted thls long.
I'll walt a llttle longer.
Hey, Vlcky.
Yeah, Schrader.
Get me Merkert, wlll you?
You know, I say--
I say we Just ram hlm.
All rlght?
I mean, we.... We....
We start her up
and Just ram the shlt out of hls truck.
We make our escape. nght?
Yeah, he'd shoot me In the head.
So, what do we do, man, huh?
What do we--? What?
Please tell me you got somethlng.
Yeah, I got somethlng.
It's me.
We need your help.
Yeah.
ls thls Mr. Henry R. Schrader?
Yeah. Who's thls?
Slr, thls Is Offlcer Elalne Tanner
wlth the Albuquerque pollce.
Is your wlfe Marle Schrader?
Yes, why?
I'm sorry to Inform you your wlfe's
been In an automoblle accldent.
She's belng alrllfted
to Los Ranchos Medlcal Center...
...and should be arrlvlng there
shortly.
-How Is she? What's her condltlon?
-I don't have the current Informatlon.
But I thlnk you mlght wanna get there
as soon as posslble.
You're gonna have to
start paylng me more.
-Mar|e?
-I'm just checklng In.
I'd love to have some Idea
of whether I should cook dlnner or not.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Why?
Hank?
What's up?
I told you before.
You wlll not klll Walter Whlte.
Not untll my buslness
wlth hlm has concluded.
We've walted long enough.
We won't walt any longer.
You'll have to.
The declslon...
...Is not yours to make.
Explaln to me, why thls man Whlte?
He betrayed your cousln Tuco, yes.
But he's not the one
who murdered hlm.
Was there not another man...
...who pulled the trlgger?
A DEA agent.
Bolsa says the DEA Is off-llmlts.
North of the border Is my terrltory.
My say.
As a show of respect...
...I say yes.
The agent's name Is...
...Hank Schrader.
May hls death satlsfy you.