We Interrupt scheduled programmlng
lo brlng you this breaking news.
Good afternoon.
In the last several mlnutes...
...KOB has recelved
dozens of reports...
...of what appears to he a crashed
alrcraft, posslhty two alrcraft...
...on Alhuquerque's east slde.
As of yet detalts are scarce...
...hut callers descrlhe wltnesslng
an exploslon overhead...
...followed by falllng dehrls.
Vlslhle now--
--Crash lnvestlgators wlth the
Natlonal Transportatlon Safety Board...
...are expected on slte
as early as thls evenlng.
But ofllclals warn that wlth a dehrls ﬁeld
of thls magnltude, the lnvestlgatlon--
Ofllclals are now saylng
that the Boelng 737...
...was helng re-routed,
or vectored, through the alrspace...
...whlch ls standard procedure
accordlng to a spokesman for the FAA.
The elght-seat Klng Alr 350
was a charter ﬂlght...
...operatlng out of St. George, Utah,
bound for Amarlllo, Texas.
It sounded llke hall,
llke heavy hallstones.
It was just hump-hump-hump,
all over the nelghhourhood....
--lndlcatlng that the ﬁnal death toll
now stands at 167.
--One hundred and slxty-seven.
Thls mld-alr colllslon
has left many wonderlng...
...how such an accldent could take place
In a system wlth so many safeguards.
--That the colllslon
whlch brought down Fllght 515...
...was caused
by lmproper alr trafflc control.
We have the bombshell conﬂrmatlon
out of Oklahoma Clty...
...as the FAA conﬂrmed...
...lt was lndeed a lone
alr trafflc controller's fateful mlstake...
...whlch brought about the crash.
--ls Donald Margolls,
a 19-year veteran...
...of the FAA 's Alr Route Trafflc
Control Center In Albuquerque....
--Margolls recently returned to work
after a flve-week absence...
...whlch was due to, quote,
"a personal loss ".
Whlle It's now known that Margolls
had recently lost a daughter to a--
--Drug overdose a month before.
Hls troubled daughter Jane Margolls,
aged 26...
...apparently had a long hlstory
of substance abuse.
Frlends of the famlly say...
...the death of hls only chlld
hlt Margolls partlcularly hard.
Comlng as It dld
llttle more than a month before...
...many are questlonlng
the tlmlng of hls return to work...
...and are wonderlng
how much blame truly lles...
...wlth those
who let thls grlevlng father--
I usually open wlth
'So sorry you're here.‘
Where would you llke to begln?
l reallyjust need thls qulck and easy,
you know?
As qulck as somethlng llke thls
can be. So....
Okay. Is that mutual?
Does your husband go along wlth that?
Does he know?
Well, I mean, he certalnly knows
we're separated, so....
Has he moved out?
We're In the process
of movlng hlm out.
Yeah. Today, hopefully.
And In the meantlme,
my son and my daughter...
...and l are staylng wlth my slster.
-So you've moved out?
-Well, yes, Just temporarlly.
Only so he could
get hls thlngs and....
That was supposed to happen last week,
but then came the crash and....
Oh, God, you weren't one of the--?
nght, yeah.
nght beneath the tllght path.
And we had debrls land In our yard,
and all over our nelghbourhood, so....
-Terr|ble.
-Yeah. Apparently, even...
...you know, parts of bodles.
So I certalnly couldn't
brlng myself to....
-So awful.
-I know.
Anyway, I was certalnly not ready
to move back. But It's tlme.
And I'm sure we're drlvlng
my slster and her husband up a wall.
Well, you deflnltely wanna malntaln
resldency In your actual home.
It Just puts you In a better posltlon
In regards to custody.
Two chlldren, you sald?
Yes. Holly here, and then I have a son
In hlgh school, Walter Jr.
-They need to stay wlth me.
-Okay.
-How long have you been marrled?
-8|xteen years.
And It's not an apartment,
It's a house that you llve In?
Do you own outrlght,
do you have a mortgage...?
Yes, there's deflnltely a mortgage.
We have maybe 15 years on It.
What about other debts or assets?
Do you feel
you have a good understandlng...
...of you and your husband's
flnanclal sltuatlon?
-Is your husband employed?
-Here's the thlng.
I'm really not looklng
for any sort of loopholes...
-...or I don't know, Just--
-No, no loopholes.
IJust lntend that every one of my cllents
get a full and honest accountlng...
...of what It Is they owe
and what It Is they own.
To that end,
I say let's leave no stone unturned.
You'd be amazed what I've seen
partners hlde from one another.
Walt?
Hey, buddy?
Hey, Walt?
-Hey.
-There you are.
Llsten, I.... You know, well....
lt's....
It's tlme.
The shlttlest week slnce 9l11, okay?
Bar none.
Thls Is It.
Hands down, we're llvlng It.
I speak wlth authorlty...
...because we had some shltty weeks
the past few months.
But thls here? I mean...
...call freaklng Gulnness Book
of World Records, call freaklng....
Am I talklng too much?
I am, rlght? I am, I know.
But thls sltuatlon between you and....
You know, I don't know.
I'm not asklng, by the way.
It's none of my buslness.
I do not wanna get
In the mlddle of you two.
I'm Just saylng, llsten, okay?
You beat a llttle tactlcal retreat...
...you regroup, and then:
You know, absence makes the....
Yeah.
I'm pulllng for you, man.
I'm pulllng for you.
-No heavy llftlng. I got It.
-No, It's okay.
I got It.
Jesus. What do you got In there,
clnder blocks?
Half a mllllon In cash.
That's the splrlt.
I got It, I got It.
Who's here for self-Improvement?
Come on, glve me a show of hands.
Who among you Is here hoplng they
can actlvely Improve who they are?
All rlght. See, that's your flrst mlstake.
You should be here
to learn self-acceptance.
Hey, honey,
you want another waffle?
l stlll got the Iron out.
I could cut up some bananas.
HI, you've reached Walt, Skyler, Flynn
and Holly. Please leave us a message.
Hey. Hello, everybody.
Good mornlng.
I was just checklng In...
...and thought I'd pass along
the current contact Informatlon.
You certalnly
can always reach me on my cell...
...l've always got that on me,
but In terms of a malllng address...
...l'm here at the Beachcomber...
...and you know what,
It's actually very nlce, very pleasant.
Not as hIgh-end as the Oakwood,
but not as corporate--
-Oh, hey, would you please Just--?
-Hey, Dad, It's me.
No, I'm not okay.
I don't know what's golng on.
Nobody's telllng me Jackshlt
around here.
-Hey, Flynn.
-Whatever.
I don't even care anymore.
Can you Just glve me
a rlde to school?
-l'll take you to school.
-Yeah. No, I'm ready now.
Flynn, I'm taklng you to school.
All rlght, I'm here. See you soon.
Okay.
May I have your attentlon, please?
As all of you know, last week
our clty suffered a terrlble tragedy.
One that none of us wIll ever forget.
Whlch Is why today we're golng to
take a llttle tlme out of our schedule...
...to gather In the gym and talk.
IJust flnd It, you know,
really, really hard to concentrate.
Because of all the horrors, you know,
we percelved.
It Just really
gets lnslde your braln and....
In college, they have thls thlng
where If your roommate kllls hlmself...
...llke, If you come home and flnd hlm
hanglng In the closet or whatever...
...lt's baslcally an automatlc A
for you.
And IJust thlnk
that that klnd of compasslon Is....
-ls somethlng to--
-Okay. Thank you, Barry.
Who wants to go next?
No Judgments, guys. Just feellngs.
You can say anythlng and everythlng
that's on your mlnd. Anyone?
There you go, honey.
IJust keep asklng myself....
Honey, could you please stand up?
Thank you.
IJust keep asklng myself,
'Why dld thls happen?‘
I mean, If there's a God and all...
...why does he allow all those
Innocent people to dle for no reason?
Anyhow, I haven't
really been sleeplng much.
Does anyone else have that?
IJust keep hearlng that sound.
That boom.
It Just plays over and over In my head
llke It won't ever stop.
Thank you, sweetheart.
-Is there anyone else?
-Over here.
My nelghbour, he heard the crash...
...and he ran outslde,
and he found, llke, thls seat.
lee an alrllne seat.
lee what you have on a alrllner?
Well, anyway, the seat was standlng
perfectly uprlght In hls front yard...
...rlght next to hls Sea-Doos,
because, llke, he has Sea-Doos.
But there was stlll a palr of legs
buckled Into them.
Jesus H. Chrlst.
-You okay?
-Yeah, sorry. I'm....
l was Just moved.
Maybe we should hear
from the faculty.
Certalnly thls tragedy
dldn't only affect our students.
Mr. Whlte,
would you llke to say somethlng?
And by the way, welcome back.
It's so good to have you back.
I guess what I would-- Sorry, sorry.
I guess what I would wanna say ls...
...to look on the brlght slde.
Flrst of all,
nobody on the ground was kllled.
And that...
I mean, an lncldent llke thls,
over a populated urban centre?
That rlght there, that's Just gotta be
some mlnor mlracle. So....
Plus, nelther plane was full.
You know, the 737 was, what, maybe
two-thlrds full, I belleve? nght, yes?
Or maybe even three-quarters full?
Well, at any rate,
what you're left wlth casualty-wlse...
...Is Just the 50th-worst aIr dlsaster.
Actually, tled for 50th.
There are, In truth...
...53 crashes throughout hlstory...
...that are Just as bad or worse.
Tenerlfe.
Has anybody...?
Anybody hear of Tenerlfe? No?
In 1977, two fully loaded 747s...
...crashed Into each other on Tenerlfe.
Does anybody know how blg
a 747 Is?
I mean, It's way blgger than a 737,
and we're talklng about two of them.
Nearly 600 people dled on Tenerlfe.
But do any of you even remember It
at all? Any of you? I doubt It.
You know why?
It's because people move on.
They Just move on.
And we wlll too. We wlll move on,
and we wlll get past thls.
Because that Is what human belngs do,
we survlve, and....
We survlve and we overcome. Yeah.
We survlve. We survlve and--
-Okay?
-Thank you.
Hey, how's your Aunt Marle dolng?
Flne. I guess.
You make sure you say hello to her
for me, wlll you?
Why don't you Just come Inslde?
It's your house.
-How's what?
-Tr|cks. It's an expresslon.
How are you?
Why you gotta treat hlm llke thls?
Why you gotta be llke thls?
-Why can't you Just talk even?
-Hey, hey, hey. Cool down, okay?
Out of the mouths of babes, huh?
You know, try not to hold It
agalnst hlm.
You know, I mean, the poor kld,
he's probably Just dylng of curloslty.
You know, and I guess
It would be natural for hlm to wonder.
He's probably wonderlng, 'What Is If
that could have gone so wrong...
-Mar|e. Marle.
-...that my mother would leave--?'
I can't help you get through thls...
...you know, If you won't tell me
what It Is that Walt dld?
Well, you know what, I don't remember
asklng you, all rlght?
So If you wanna be supportlve,
you could be supportlve wlthout prylng.
-That would be really great...
-'Pry|ng.'
-...and so helpful.
-Well, prylng's a strong word.
It's that volce lnslde your head.
It's that sneaky, rat-bastard,
24I7 volce.
You know what I'm talklng about.
That volce that tells you
you're not good enough.
Not good enough for what?
Not good enough to be what...
...presldent of the Unlted States?
Well, okay,
so maybe you're not that good.
But now...
...are you good enough to deserve
your share of baslc human happlness?
Are you good enough to be okay
wlth who and what you are?
I say yes.
But It doesn't matter what I say.
It's your volce, whlch means
you're the one that hears It.
Whlch means you're the only one
that can flght It, rlght?
Jesse, we never hear from you.
What's golng on? You can tell me
I'm full of shlt. It's okay, I don't mlnd.
Just come on. Let us In on It.
So, llke, what makes you the expert?
I don't thlnk I ever sald l was that.
Yeah, but you're the one
slttlng here, rlght?
Telllng us 'thus' and 'so,‘ 'be happy,‘
'forglve yourself,‘ blah, blah, blah.
Have you ever really hurt anybody?
I don't Just mean dlsappolnted
your mother or whatever...
...but dld you ever really
hurt someone?
l kllled my daughter.
It was July 18th,
whlch Is my blrthday.
July 1am, 1992.
l was hlgh on cocalne
and l was drunk.
Cocalne wasn't an Issue. I had bought
myself two grams as a blrthday present.
I had plenty left.
But I was out of vodka.
And thls Is In Portsmouth, Vlrglnla...
...they have these ABc stores...
...whlch close at 5 p.m.,
and rlght then It was llke 4:42.
So I'm argulng wlth my wlfe.
'Come on. Go to the A30 for me,
It's my blrthday.
Come on.
They're not gonna sell It to me.‘
And she's saylng 'No, no.'
So I'm plssed. And the clock Is tlcklng,
so I Jump In my truck.
She's my 6-year-old daughter.
She's playlng
at the end of the drlveway.
How do you not hate yourself?
l dld hate myself for a long tlme.
But It dldn't stop me
from drlnklng and gettlng hlgh.
It Just made If that much worse.
Self-hatred, gullt,
It accompllshes nothlng.
It Just stands In the way.
Stands In the way of what?
True change.
Skyler.
ls thls a good tlme to talk?
Yeah. Come In. Please.
Skyler.
Do you wanna start?
Okay.
Why are you dolng thls?
Why are you even thlnklng thls way?
-Is It to punlsh me?
-I am not punlshlng you, Walt.
Thls Is punltlve, Is what thls ls.
We are happlly marrled.
I am happlly marrled. I am happy.
We're Just...
I love you, Skyler.
And I would do anythlng for you.
Would you even conslder...?
I mean, JesusI
You come In here and you wave
these papers In my face...
...when there's a whole other,
entlre slde to thls thlng.
There's your slde and there's my slde,
and you haven't heard my slde yet.
You haven't heard any of It at all.
You're a drug dealer.
No. What--? How...? What?
Yeah.
How else could you posslbly
make that klnd of money?
Marljuana. That Plnkman kld.
No?
Oh, my God, Walt.
Cocalne?
It's methamphetamlne.
But I'm a manufacturer,
I'm not a dealer...
...per se.
It doesn't mean.... No, Skyler!
-Llsten to me. Skyler, l|sten--
-No, no!
There are a lot of angles to thls, okay?
It's compllcated, all rlght?
So please, let's-- Please, let's Just
slt back down and talk It through.
I'm gonna make you a deal, Walt.
I won't tell Hank and I won't tell
your chlldren or anybody else.
Nobody wlll hear It from me.
But only If you grant me thls dlvorce
and stay out of our llves.
-No, Skyler--
-I mean It.
Now let me the hell out of here
before I throw up.
Bye, Jesse.
Yeah.
thtle frlctlon
In the marrlage rlght now.
Strlctly temporary. We're Just...
We're Just taklng a llttle break.
That's you, over there.
Llsten, money.
Saul has got It for you,
so as soon as you're feellng better--
I'm better.
-What, the rehab? It helped?
-Yeah. I'm done uslng.
That's excellent. That's....
That's very good, Jesse.
Boy, very good.
You know,
In splte of how bad thlngs got...
...lt really could be looked at
llke a wake-up call for both of us.
I mean, you know, Just to get our llves
back together agaln...
...and on the stralght and narrow.
You been followlng
thls alrplane crash?
Yeah.
You know It was Jane's dad who
accldentally crashed them together...
...because he was so torn up?
Okay, look, let me stop you
rlght there, all rlght?
You are not responslble for thls.
Not In any way, shape or form,
all rlght?
Now, I am very up-to-date on thls thlng,
probably far more than you are...
...and there are many factors
at play there.
Yeah?
For Instance, there's some sort of
colllslon radar on the Jet...
...that may not have been worklng.
That's publlc record.
You can look that up.
And the whole system
Is run on 1960s technology.
No, really, I blame the government.
You elther run from thlngs
or you face them, Mr. Whlte.
-What exactly does that mean?
-I learned It In rehab.
It's all about acceptlng
who you really are.
I accept who I am.
And who are you?
I'm the bad guy.
Here's some napklns for you.
Enjoy.
-Is the food to your satlsfactlon?
-Very much.
It's good to see you agaln.
-May I?
-Please.
l have an offer that l thlnk
wlll be of Interest to you.
I actually am not here to....
I'm here because I owe you
the courtesy and respect...
...to tell you thls personally.
It has nothlng to do
wlth you personally.
l flnd you
extraordlnarlly professlonal...
...and l appreclate
the way you do buslness.
I'm Just maklng a change In my llfe,
Is what It Is.
And I'm....
I'm at somethlng of a crossroads...
...and It's brought me
to a reallzatlon.
I am not a crlmlnal.
No offence to any people who are...
...but thls Is not me.
I'd llke you to hear my offer,
notwlthstandlng.
It won't change my mlnd, I'm sorry.
Three mllllon dollars
for three months of your tlme.
Three months, then out.
Three mllllon?
May I take thls as a 'yes'?
l have money. I have more money
than I know how to spend.
What I don't have Is my famlly.
The answer Is stlll no.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
That's It!
Dld you feel It?
TexasI
I've made thls trlp three tlmes...
...and every tlme
there's three blg bumps...
...and that's how you know!
We are offlclally In Texas!
Thls tlme I got a Job waltlng for me.
I got a cousln who's got a body shop.
Yo, that's for me, homes!
They call me 'Ollve OII' because
I palnt them sllck.
I do pearlescent, colour-shlft,
you name It.
l palnted cars for some of...
...the blggest gangsters In Mlchoacan.
Wow, those are beautlful boots!
Not much good for worklng, but....
Hey, what's on the toes there?
thtle sllver....
What the hell's golng on In there?