Joule?
Jun!
Show yourulf rlght now!
I'll be In touch.
Okay. Hay, Huell.
Lllten, I want you to swung by
the hlgh school on your way to Saul'l.
I can't bollove he would
go altar my son, but...
-You got It.
-And Kuby': at the car wash, rlght?
Parked rlght across the strut.
All'a qulet. No Plnkman.
Okay. Juat tlnd hlm.
Please leave a message.
Jesse, llsten.
I mean, obvlously,
you've changed your mlnd here...
...and so thank you for that.
And I know you're angry.
I wanna l'lx thls, okay?
Whatever It takes, all rlght?
We'll talk, and we wlll l'lx thls.
Untll then, Just....
Just sleep It oft, okay?
And then call me.
Be safe.
How's It comlng?
I replaced the doorjamb
and the strlker plate.
-Swltch thls out, we'll be good to go.
-Good.
Do you want separate keys
for the dlfl'erent locks...
-...or do you want one worklng both?
-No, no, no. No re-key.
Same exact keys as before.
Usually wlth a break-In,
people llke to get new keys.
No, same keys, same locks.
The old keys
have to work here, okay?
-0kay.
-All rlght.
Oh, no, no. Hey, guys, guys, guys.
-Cut that. Yeah, thls....
-That area's stlll pretty bad.
nght. We'll have to go over thls
a lot more.
We've made three passes already.
lee I say, gasollne's trlcky.
No, no, no. The smell has got
to be gone completely.
My wll'e ls comlng home,
and I can't have any odour, any staln...
...any slgn that anythlng
happened here.
Understand?
l-- I know. Thls ls short notlce,
and I really appreclate lt.
Slr, we'd love to take
more of your money...
...but you've got gas soaked
through to your subtloor.
Untll you pull thls up
and get new carpet, new paddlng...
...thls Is as good as It gets.
Is that gasollne?
-Ask Dad.
-Hey. Over here.
-What happened?
-What happened Is that...
...I should sue someone.
That's what happened.
So I'm on my way to the drugstore,
and l have to stop to get some gas...
...and there Is thls
total pump mall'unctlon.
You know what?
She shouldn't be In thls room.
I mean, thls ls supposedly green,
but you know how It Is.
You can close the wlndows
In the nursery...
...because It's really
only out here.
Thls Is as good as It gets.
...pump mall'unctlon?
Yeah. I'm standlng there l'llllng up
llke I've done a thousand tlmes...
...and I hear a chunk.
You know, the pump's nozzle.
The metal thlng.
The thlng you squeeze?
I hear a chunk.
So, I suppose, In my nalvete
...I took to understand that gas Is
no longer comlng out of the nozzle...
...so I pull out the hose to put It back
and whooshl
Yeah, I am suddenly
soaked ln gasollne.
I mean, on my arms
and my legs and my groln.
So now I am In a panlc.
l race home, I run lnslde the house...
...and I'm strlpplng off
my clothes as last as I can.
IJump In the shower.
It's not untll
after I get out of the shower...
...that l reallse
my gas-covered clothes...
...have been soaklng
In the llvlng room rug thls entlre tlme.
I mean, lt's-- It's--
The whole thlng Is Just so stupld.
I could have rlnsed off at the statlon.
Halfway home, I started to reallse...
...walt a mlnute, there's a water hose
rlght there next to the alr pump.
You know, for tyres.
Anyway, so that was my day.
How was yours?
-Dad?
-Yeah.
Please, can you Just tell the truth?
Tell-- What do you mean?
You l'alnted, dldn't you?
Because you're slck agaln?
You were pumplng gas,
and the fumes...
...they made you pass out agaln.
Just-- Just admlt lt.
No, the-- No.
It was the pump.
All rlght, l....
Maybe I dld get a llttle
swlmmy at one polnt...
...but I dld not l'alnt. Okay?
I'm l'lne, and that's the truth.
However, In the best Interest
of all of our contlnued good health...
...I don't thlnk we can stay here.
-I mean, not untll we get new carpet.
-Yeah.
Uncle Hank and Aunt Marle,
they got plenty of space.
Hey, what about a hotel?
A hotel. That could be sweet.
A good one.
l llke the way you're thlnklng. Yes.
Could be a llttle l'amlly vacatlon.
Mlght be fun. What do you say?
Why don't you put
some clothes together.
Yeah. All rlght.
I'm sorry. It's not my l'lnest hour.
-Okay.
Thlnk thls'll leave a scar?
I never should have let
my doJo membershlp run out.
Jesus. Jesse dld that?
Yeah, but you gotta understand,
deep down he loves me.
So where Is he?
-Stlll looklng.
-Where have you looked?
Hls place, hls l'olk's place,
thls Brock kld's place.
Crack shacks at Slesta Hllls,
the lndlgo, the Crystal Palace...
...go-kart Jolnt on Copper Ave...
...AA meetlng off the 40.
Hls buddles,
Beaver and what's-hls-name?
Badger and Sklnny Pete.
Yeah, no, he's not wlth them.
They could be coverlng l'or hlm.
l posed as a metre reader. I put a bug
on the tall kld's mom's place.
For three hours stralght, all he talked
about was somethlng called Babylon 5.
I checked wlth my gal at A.P.D.
Plnkman's not In thelr system...
-...so the cops don't have hlm.
-Yet.
Maybe he changed hls mlnd
about leavlng...
...called your guy back.
Somebody mlsses thelr l'lrst chance
wlth my guy, there's no second.
Well, keep looklng.
What then?
What do you mean?
I mean, Plnkman's llke a bad penny.
Sooner or later, he'll turn up.
I'm wonderlng what you wanna do
when he does.
Jesse ls upset about the boy.
IJust need to explaln to hlm
why that had to happen.
Okay, but say, you know,
Just for the sake of argument...
...the kld's not In the mood
for a nuanced dlscusslon...
...ol' the vlrtues ol' chlld polsonlng.
Hls plans are runnlng more towards
stabblng you to death...
...wlth a polnted stlck.
In that scenarlo, then what?
You have a suggestlon?
We were wonderlng ll' maybe thls Isn't
an Old Yeller type sltuatlon.
Old Yeller?
Yeah, Old Yeller was the best,
most loyal dog there ever was.
I mean, everybody loved that mutt...
...but one day he showed up rabld...
...and llttle Tlmmy,
for Old Yeller's own sake...
...had to....
Oh, you-- You saw the movle.
You're full of colourful metaphors,
aren't you, Saul?
Bellze, Old Yeller....
Just brlmmlng wlth advlce.
Do not I'loat that Idea agaln.
Flnd hlm.
Sorry. Sorry.
Room key wouldn't
let me Into the Ice room...
...so I had to go down
to the front desk.
But here we are.
Checked In on Junlor.
Pay-per-vlew and room servlce.
He's In heaven.
Hey, I thought you
were gonna take a bath.
How's Saul dolng?
Saul? Goodman?
-No Idea.
-No?
You were Just out talklng to hlm
In the parklng lot.
I'm sorry. Were you spylng on me?
Yes.
And I feel Just awl'ul about It too.
You know, I played along...
...wlth your pump mall'unctlon
bullshlt...
...because Junlor
was standlng rlght there...
...but now I would llke to know
what's golng on.
Flrst of all, It's no blg deal.
Comlng here Is Just me
belng overly cautlous.
Jesse Plnkman, you know?
He came over to our house
that tlme l'or dlnner, remember?
Well, he.... He got upset over thls....
Somethlng he thlnks l dld.
I dld do It.
But I dld It for very good reasons.
And It's Just-- It's compllcated.
Walt, are you...?
Are you telllng me that he trled to...
...burn our house down?
That was...
...probably, for a brlel' moment,
hls Intentlon...
...but, obvlously, he changed hls mlnd.
And how does that work?
Hlm--? Hlm changlng hls mlnd?
Look....
You've got to understand
that wlth Jesse...
...there are emotlonal Issues,
personal Issues, some drug abuse.
But he has always been more
of a danger to hlmsell' than anyone else.
He has a tendency
to fly off the handle, that's all.
So he has never hurt anybody?
I can't belleve
you got her down so fast.
...what's your course of actlon here?
Saul's guy, Kuby, tracks hlm down,
whlch shouldn't take long...
I'm gonna talk to hlm.
Make hlm see reason.
Talk to hlm?
Make hlm see reason?
So I'm clear...
...these are Just euphemlsms...
...you're uslng here, rlght?
What?
Wh--? What does that mean?
My God.
I knew thls was golng to happen.
I knew It. I told you that someday...
...someone was golng to come
to our door and try to hurt us.
And now here we are.
Jesse dldn't go there to hurt anyone.
He poured gasollne
all over our house, Walt.
He trled to set our house on I'lre.
He changed hls mlnd.
He dldn't do It, dld he?
What II' he changes It back?
Walt, you need...
...to deal wlth thls.
How much have you had to drlnk?
Not nearly enough.
I don't know how we got off...
...on whatever It Is
we're talklng about here...
...but, clearly, I haven't explalned
the sltuatlon well enough...
...because thls Is a blg overreactlon.
We all need to Just take a deep breath
and calm down...
...because Jesse Isn't Just some....
Some-- Some rabld dog.
-Thls Is a person.
-A person that Is a threat to us.
I mean, my God, where we are now
wlth Hank and Marle...
...and that awful tape we made.
After everythlng we've done...
...you can't Just talk to thls person.
You're saylng...
...that I Just....
What--? What exactly are you saylng?
We've come thls I'ar.
For us.
What's one more?
Jessel
Stop what you're dolng
and turn and lace mel
You wanna--?
You wanna know what he dld?
You wanna hear about It?
Jesse, put out the llghter.
He polsoned a llttle kld.
An 8-year-old boy.
Just because, you know--
Just as a move!
Walt's a bastard. Secret's out.
We'll talk about It.
But I need you to put out
the llghter, okay?
Look, Jesse....
Jesse, I don't wanna klll you.
And you don't wanna be kllled.
So put It out.
He can't keep gettlng away wlth Itl
He won't.
You really wanna burn hlm down?
Let's do It together.
You were I'ollowlng me?
Yeah. Slnce Goodman's.
Where we golng now?
DEA. Downtown.
What, I'm, llke, arrested?
Yeah, you know how thls works.
Be a good wltness for me...
...lt'll go better for you.
Yeah, slttlng around MDC...
...waltlng to be a wltness
agalnst Mr. Whlte.
lt's....
It's gonna go great for me.
...you're angry.
I can't sleep. I'm not eatlng.
Last nlght, l was onllne l'or slx hours
looklng up untraceable polsons.
Thls close I'amlly I'rlend...
...had been keeplng a secret
from you and Hank...
...and somehow thls person's secret
became known...
...and now you're sad and hurt
and angry.
l'm--? I'm In the ballpark?
To be thls wrong about someone.
Thls oft.
We all lead double llves
to some extent, don't we?
-We all have our secrets.
-Yeah. Not llke thls.
Not llke hlm.
Marle, lthlnk It's tlme you I'llled me In
on some more detalls here.
Who and what are we talklng about?
l sald I can't do that.
It'd be bad for Hank.
Our I'rlend made that clear
In hls llttle movle.
Those klds...
...under hls rool'. That baby.
I'm slck Just thlnklng about It.
How could I have not seen thls?
II' I weren't belng such a...
...Idlotlc-- Stupld ldlot, I could've--
We could have....
Blackjack wlnnlngs.
Nothlng susplclous about that at all.
Tell me about thls movle.
Dave, can we slmply...
...Just locus on my I'eellngs here?
The detalls don't really matter, do they?
There's nothlng to be done, okay?
He screwed us and he won.
Can we Just...?
Can we talk about
somethlng else, please?
Yes?
How's work?
Last week, you were upset
about the new parklng rules.
Marle?
Saxltoxln.
Derlved I'rom shelll'lsh.
Produces a I'laccld paralysls
that leaves the vlctlm consclous...
...through a progresslon of symptoms.
Death occurs from resplratory I'allure.
Marle...
...you're not ready to I'lll me In here...
...that's I'lne.
But I want you to llsten.
There Is no problem,
no matter how dll'l'lcult...
...or palnl'ul or seemlngly unsolvable...
...that vlolence won't make worse.
Don't worry. I wouldn't hurt anybody.
l]ust....
It Just feels good to thlnk about It.
-Hey, babe.
-What's the story here?
Oh, well, somethlng's come up.
I thought you mlght wanna
get out of the house for a day or two.
You thought I'd pack up
and move out of my own house.
Why? What's golng on?
Look, I don't wanna get Into It now.
But you know that thlng wlth Walt,
there's....
There's been a development.
-What happened? Are you In danger?
-No, no, no, not at all.
Just-- It's a I'luld sltuatlon.
lthlnk It mlght go a llttle smoother
If you're not here.
So I....
It's gonna be great, you know?
I booked you a spa package
at La Posada.
-You can do that rlver-stones thlng.
-Hank, what the hell ls golng on?
Hank?
We have a guest.
He was a llttle keyed up.
Gave hlm a couple sleeplng pllls.
Okay. Okay, so llsten.
l brlng that kld In,
put hlm In the system...
...Walt's gonna I'lnd out
I'lve mlnutes later. You know?
My last 10 wltnesses
dled In Jall, remember?
And I can't use a DEA sale house
wlthout wrltlng hlm up.
I can't rlsk a motel.
I know It sounds crazy,
but thls Is the best place.
For now. Just a day or two, tops--
Okay, Just answer me
thls one questlon:
ls thls bad for Walt?
Yeah. Very.
Good. I'm staylng.
I'll heat up lasagne.
Phone's rlnglng.
You have one new message.
Jesse, llsten.
lmean, obvlously,
you've changed your mlnd here...
...and so thank you for that.
And I know you're angry.
I wanna ﬂx thls, okay?
Whatever It takes, all rlght?
We'll talk, and we wlll ﬂx thls.
Untll then, just...
Just sleep It off, okay?
And then call me.
Be safe.
Hey.
What are you stlll dolng up?
Couldn't sleep.
You and me both. Here. Have a seat.
-Everythlng okay?
-Oh, yeah.
Just buslness stufl'.
Golng over some optlons.
You guys stlll thlnk
you mlght buy another car wash?
Yeah. Well, maybe.
See how It goes.
How It goes now that--
Now that you're--
You're slck agaln, rlght?
No. That's not what I mean.
Hey. Told you not to worry, remember?
How--? How can I not worry?
Come on.
You thlnk I came all thls way...
...Just to let somethlng as sllly
as lung cancer take me down?
Not a chance.
I'm not golng anywhere.
Should've brought our sults, huh?
It's okay.
It's all rlght.
I'll be up In a mlnute.
Okay.
-See you In the mornlng.
-Okay.
Would you llke some coffee?
Mornlng.
You want some coffee?
No. The lady....
lthlnk your wlfe....
You take cream and sugar?
Thanks.
Thls ls probably gonna take a whlle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-l'll run some errands.
-Okay.
All rlght.
You remember Agent Gomez?
-How you feellng? Your head clear?
-Yeah.
Thls-- Thls can't be what you mean
by burnlng hlm to the ground, rlght?
I got storles
that'll make your toes curl...
...but, you know, It's Just 'my word
agalnst hls word' klnd of stuff.
So, you know, I don't really
have any, llke, proof or anythlng.
Gomey, can you grab the curtalns
over there?
There's a glare thlng happenlng here.
You know he's retlred, rlght? He's....
He's not even In the buslness
anymore.
So you're never gonna catch hlm
wlth a camcorder.
We're gonna catch hlm.
We gotta do thls flrst, okay? Come on.
Just tell us everythlng you remember.
Any buslness deallngs,
any personal deallngs...
...any crlmlnal actlvlty
you were a wltness or a party to.
Anythlng and everythlng.
Just tell us your story, okay?
Start from the beglnnlng.
When dld you flrst meet Walter Whlte?
nght. Okay....
l flrst met Mr. Whlte--
Walter Whlte.
--|n Junlor year chemlstry.
He was my teacher.
You belleve hlm?
Yeah. I do, unfortunately.
And I hate to admlt It,
but I thlnk the kld ls rlght.
There Is no physlcal evldence,
not that I heard.
Yeah, well, no weapons,
no bodles, no worklng lab.
Just the word
of one nut-Job meth-head...
...agalnst
Mr. Rogers-Has-a-Lung-Tumour.
So do we take a run
at Lydla Rodarte-Ouayle?
Vamonos Pest?
Follow up wlth the Drew Sharp kllllng?
Where do we start?
I say we start wlth thls.
Jesse...
...I'm gonna be at Clvlc Plaza
tomorrow at noon.
lhope you'll glve me the chance
to explaln myself...
...and talk through everythlng
once and for all.
I'll be alone and unarmed.
So If you wanna come and shoot me
In the head, that's up to you.
Elther way...
...I'm In your hands.
Go and talk to that asshole?
You can't be serlous.
Go and llsten.
He wants to explaln hlmself.
We put a wlre on you
and let hlm explaln.
So your plan Is to do hls plan?
You serlously thlnk that thls--?
Thls whole
'once and for all In the plaza' thlng...
...ls so he can talk to me?
Why not?
l-- l-- I can't belleve you two.
The dude wanted me out of town
before I came to burn hls house down...
...and now I'm more of a threat to hlm.
And he's got a zero-tolerance pollcy
on threats, you know?
If I go to thls plaza,
I'm a dead man, Is why not.
Hey, Walt's ruthless.
He'll do Just about anythlng
to protect hls Interests.
I agree. Except when It comes to you.
He cares about you.
Can't you see?
Oh, yeah. You mean when he's not
rlpplng me off or calllng me an ldlot...
...or polsonlng people
that I care about?
Yeah, no, Mr. Whlte's gay for me.
Everyone knows that.
No, I mean It.
Based on everythlng you told us.
He pald for your rehab...
...ran over those two drug dealers
wlth hls car.
Sounds llke he saved your llfe.
Made you a 50-50 partner.
He dldn't need to do that.
Yeah, he sort of dld.
I'm the only one near as good as hlm.
I don't know. The way you tell It...
...sounds llke he's manlpulatlng you
to stlck around.
lee he doesn't wanna lose you.
All those numbers he runs on you...
...over and over,
helplng you flnd the rlcln clgarette.
Look how far he'll go to show you--
To convlnce you
that he's not such a bad guy.
-That's what thls Is.
-What If It's about...
...kllllng me, you know?
You know, gettlng me out In the open...
...hlre some-- Some clock-tower guy...
...or have me slt on a polsoned needle
or somethlng, you know?
Nothlng's gonna happen to you.
The plaza's one of the most wlde-open
publlc places In all of Albuquerque.
It's the mlddle of the day.
And Agent Gomez and l wlll
be rlght there wlth you.
Look, you two guys
are Just guys, okay?
Mr. Whlte, he's the devll.
You know, he Is.
He Is smarter than you...
...he ls luckler than you.
Whatever-- Whatever you thlnk
ls supposed to happen...
...I'm telllng you,
the exact reverse opposlte of that...
...ls gonna happen, okay?
Jesse, Jesse,
we're not bralnstormlng here.
Thls Is not asklng.
Unless you know another way to get the
man or you wanna take your chances...
...wlth the banger boys over In MDC,
then thls Is It.
Thls ls what's happenlng.
-I gotta plss. Can I plss?
-Yeah. Down to the left.
You got another SD card?
-What?
-What If the kld's rlght?
What If It's a trap?
The kld?
Oh, you mean the Junkle murderer...
...that's drlbbllng all over
my guest bathroom floor?
Well, then, he's rlght.
Plnkman gets kllled...
...and we get It all on tape.
Remember, you're hurt, angry,
but you're here for answers, okay?
But don't.... Don't push the questlons.
Okay?
Let's not get hlm susplclous, all rlght?
You let hlm do the talklng, rlght?
Just relax. That's what matters most.
Don't cross your arms,
If you can help It.
Pancho Vllla, Salma Hayek.
Pancho VIIIa, Salma Hayek.
You gettlng that?
-Loud and clear, Idlota.
-How's It looklng, Gomey?
He's just slttlng there.
Are we dolng thls, or what?
Ready to klck some ass, partner?
All rlght. Tlme to go.
Okay.
Hey, Hank, you got eyes on thls?
What's wlth the kld?
He's Just standlng there.
What the hell Is he dolng?
He's on the move now.
He's taklng off. I thlnk he's runnlng.
Oh, no, no, no, kld. Come on.
You got hlm? He's at the pay phone.
Who the hell Is he calllng?
Oh, no, no, no. Come on, kld.
No. Come on.
Hello?
Nlce try, asshole.
Jesse, where are you?
IJust wanna talk.
No. I'm not dolng what you want
anymore. Okay, asshole?
Thls Is just a heads-up
to let you know I'm comlng for you.
See, I declded that burnlng down
your house Is nothlng.
Next tlme, I'm gonna get you
where you really llve.
Jesse, llsten.
Jesse? Jesse?
-Daddyl Daddyl
-Heyl
Get In.
Son of a bltchl Stupld, hlgh llttle--
What the hell was that all about?
What were you thlnklng?
-Thlnk|ng there's another way.
-What?
To get hlm. There's another way.
A better way.
Hey.
It's Walt.
I'm okay.
Todd...
...l thlnk l mlght have another Job
for your uncle.