Hay, Mr. Whlta. It's me.
I know you're probably
roal busy wlth rotlroment...
...but I got aoma new: I thlnk
you should maybe know about.
Mo and Doclan had aoma
dlﬂ'erencoa of oplnlon...
...and It got a llttla...
...meaay.
It's all atralghtonod out now...
...but Just a heads-up, there's been
a klnd of change In management.
Anyway,
Just thought you should know.
Feel free to glve me a call
It you want the detalla...
...but, you know, It's cool,
so whatever.
Okay, then. Thanka. Bye.
nght, so there lam,
I'm on top of the traln...
...pumplng the water In, he'a watchlng
to make sure we out In...
...exactly what he'd calculated.
We gotta be real preclae because
water and methylene welgh dll'l'erent...
...and he ﬁgured It all out to,
llke, mlllllltre.
I'm up there wlth my hoae...
...we're golng as last as we can.
We only got a few mlnutea.
At the croaalng, we got thla guy
who's amooth-talklng the englneer.
And It's all Just golng great...
...untll thla other dude show: up
In thla monater truck...
...ao we're pretty much acrewed,
because he can Just puah...
...the entlre dump truck off the tracks,
whlch, you know, la what he does.
Walt. What's your guy dolng?
-You can't atop hlm?
-Yeah, but what's he gonna say?
'Thanka anyway, alr, but my l'rlenda
are atlll ateallng cargo back there.'
So I'm looklng all around,
because I know we're not done...
...but the gallon:
are slowly tlcklng away.
And l'lnally Mr. Whlte
tell: me to cut lt.
So I l'llng the hole, I'm grabblng the cap,
I'm acrewlng In the bolts.
Juat, llke, buatlng all, you know?
And then I feel the traln atart movlng
and I'm--
-You're....
-l'm on top.
-Dld you plea your pants?
-Yeah, rlght?
So the thlng atarta apeedlng up,
so I Jump off the movlng traln.
lee, total atuntman atul'l'.
lt'a llke Hooper. You ever see Hooper?
0h, hey, man, Burt Reynolds.
Good movle.
He Jumped out of a hellcopter,
not a traln.
Whatever, man. It's a good movle.
Thla guy Jeaae, he'a underneath,
and the traln Juat drlvea rlght over hlm.
And lucklly he'a thla aklnny llttle guy.
Damn. That's a tlght operatlon.
It was perfect.
No one even knew they got robbed,
Juat llke we planned.
Mr. Whlte told me It was, llke,
the blggeat traln helat ever...
...llke, potentlal money-wlae.
So that's how that happened.
Can I get you anythlng elae?
Nope. Thanka, darllng.
I'm ready for the cheque.
You l'eellng good about cooklng?
Yeah.
You'll be able to run your own lab?
-Do It up rlght?
-Yeah. For sure. I got thla.
All rlght.
Let's make some money, then.
I gotta hlt the head.
Ever been on a plane
and l'lnd youraell'...
...looklng down at the armreat
next to you...
...looklng at the llttle plug
where the aahtray used to go?
I look at that and I say, 'What the hell
happened to thla country?‘
Nanny atate.
I see a kld wlth a blcycle helmet on...
...I wanna amack the ahlt out of hlm,
llke, l'or hla own good.
Mr. Plnkman.
How are you today?
Not so good, huh?
Of course, I mlght be able
to help you out.
I wanna talk to you about
your partner, Helaenberg.
See, I know he's my brother-ln-law,
Walt.
Oh, yeah. That's the look.
Lucky for you,
I'm more Interested In hlm.
So I got an offer.
It you help me out here...
...tell me all about you and hlm
and your llttle meth bualneaa...
...maybe I talk to my l'rlenda
at the A.P.D...
...and make all thla go away.
I know he's the maatermlnd here.
Plua...
...l'm thlnklng,
based on your recent actlvltlea...
...that maybe there's a llttle trouble
In paradlae?
Maybe you guys aren't
gettlng along so good?
I'm rlght, aren't I?
Eat me.
Sure that's how you want to play thla?
Why don't you try and beat It
out of me?
That's your thlng, rlght?
He really dld a number on you,
dldn't he?
I don't know...
...but happy people
usually don't go around...
...throwlng mllllona of dollar: away.
I don't thlnk...
...Walt'a gonna be pattlng you
on the back for that.
But maybe that's the polnt.
But, you see, I get that.
My own brother-ln-law...
...lylng to me for over a year.
Ualng me.
Maybe you understand that Ieellng.
Help me out here, Jeaae...
...and we can put hlm away.
I know you want that.
lthlnk you wanna talk.
Not to you.
Agent Schrader,
beat any good auapecta lately?
Tall and taller, aak hlm
about hla hlatory wlth my cllent.
He knocked the poor kld unconacloua
laat tlme they were alone.
So, what'll It be, a clvll rlghta lawault
the alze of Montana?
Becauae I'll obllge you.
So long, Rocky. Keep your left up.
Detectlvea, I'm lnvltlng you to leave.
I'm gonna try to remaln calm...
...but wlll you do me a favour
and tell me what la up wlth you?
My guys are buatlng thelr aaaea...
...trylng to hlde Walt'a money
from the feds...
...and you're toaalng your:
out a wlndow?
And I have to hear about your llttle act
of phllanthropy on the news?
Dld you hlt your head
or aomethlng?
Why dldn't you call me
the second you got arrested?
What dld you say to Schrader?
Nothlng. Jeaua. Juat chlll out.
Chlll out? No.
No, I don't chlll out rlght now...
...becauae thlnga have gone nuclear.
l lmaglne Schrader ahared
wlth you hla recent dlacovery.
Okay, well, then you get
my complete lack of chlll.
Just use the money that I gave you.
Stop-- Saul. Stop talklng. I don't care.
Juat-- Just make It happen.
Work your maglc.
And call me when he's out.
Hey, Dad, I'm home.
Oh, okay. I'll be rlght out.
Hey, you golng to work today?
You were out late last nlght.
|-- Well, I....
Yeah, I guess IJuat lost track of tlme.
I'm gonna head out, okay?
-Where you golng?
-Aunt Marle Juat called.
She wants me to help her
wlth some computer thlng...
...and asked me to stay for dlnner.
That cool?
-I guess that--
-Cool. All rlght, see you later.
Walt, aon?
-Junlor. Hang on a second.
-Yeah?
-0h, good. Come on back lnalde.
-What happened?
0h, thla? Nothlng.
No, I'm Ilne. lt'a Ilne.
Really. I do wanna talk to you, though.
Okay. Are you okay?
Yeah. Here. Slt down a second.
IJuat don't wanna keep thlnga
from you, okay?
I mean, you deserve to know
what's happenlng.
Yesterday, I passed out.
Brlel'ly. Very, very brleI'ly.
And I dld thll.
Why dld you pass out?
Well, my latest acana...
...ahow a llttle shadow on my lung.
But my doctor put me rlght on
a new round of chemo...
...whlch la why I've been so tlred lately.
But l was puahlng myself too hard.
I know It.
IJuat don't want you to worry.
I learned my lesson.
Well, what's the...?
What now?
What now la that we go on,
llke alwaya. nght?
Hey, don't worry about thla, okay?
I know that's hard,
but I beat thla once.
There's no reason to thlnk
I won't agaln.
And my doctor says I'm dolng great.
I'm reapondlng really well
to the treatment.
And I'm....
I'm Ieellng very--
Very good about thla, all rlght?
And what would really help me out...
...la II we all atayed poaltlve.
Can we do that?
Yeah?
Okay.
So why don't you go
and help your Aunt Marle...
-...and we'll talk about thla later.
-No. No. No way.
I'm ataylng. I'm not leavlng.
-Flynn la not wlth you, la he?
-No.
No. Why would he be?
How'd It go?
That bad, huh?
How bad are we talklng, Hank?
l dldn't tell them.
Why not?
-lt'a Just not tlme yet.
-No, It's paat tlme.
Way paat tlme. We talked about thla.
You've got to tell them now.
It's gonna be worse...
...II they Ilnd out that
you've kept thla from them.
Look, It's Just I've got some thlnga
I gotta chase down.
What? What thlnga?
-Leada, you know.
-What leada? What? Somethlng new?
I'm not keeplng anythlng
from anybody, Marle, okay? Jeaua.
Don't tell me how to do my Job.
Walt.
Are you sure about thla?
It's the only way.
Okay.
I'm ready.
My name la Walter Hartwell Whlte.
l llve at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane...
...Albuquerque, New Mexlco, 87104.
Thla la my conl'eaalon.
They're here.
Thank you for comlng.
Okay, I'll start.
-Skyler and In
-Welcome to Gardullo'a.
My name la Trent.
I'll be taklng care of you.
Can I start anybody oft
wlth aome beveragea?
Margarlta? How about some
of our tablealde guacamole?
lthlnk we're Ilne.
We need some tlme wlth the menu.
No worrlea.
Be rlght back wlth some water.
So you here to confess?
There'a nothlng to confess.
We're here to talk about Walter, Jr.
Flynn and Holly should be llvlng
wlth ua. End of story.
And whlle we respect your oplnlon...
...we thlnk that your concern
la mlaplaced.
Skyler and I feel,
due to Marle'a attempt...
-...to lure hlm to your house--
-I wasn't trylng to lure hlm.
Regardless of what you mlght call It...
...Skyler and I would llke to ask you...
...to please leave
our chlldren out of thla.
Junlor has been through
a lot already thla year.
You are Juat....
Thla Inveatlgatlon, Hank...
...do you reallae
what thla wlll do to hlm?
Hearlng theae thlnga?
He'a gonna hear It when l klck In
your front door and arrest you.
II that day ever comes, so be It.
You have no evldence
to support your clalma.
Why tear thla Iamlly apart?
So how about that guacamole?
We make It rlght here at the table.
I'll Juat glve you guy:
a few more mlnutea.
How can you alt there
and llaten to thla?
All we want la Ior thoae klda
to be aal'e.
You're puttlng them In danger,
keeplng them under the aame root--
They are aal'e, Marle.
You youraell' aent them
out of the houae.
And I brought them back.
Look, whatever you thlnk he dld...
...thla la not an ongolng altuatlon.
-Skyler.
-No.
They need to underatand.
lt'a In the paat.
lt'a over.
There la nothlng to go after here.
-There'a nothlng to accompllah.
-How can we belleve anythlng you aay?
There'a no telllng
where the llea begln and end.
That afl'alr oI' youra,
dld that even happen?
Pleaae. Look, JunlorJuat found out
that my cancer la back.
He'a already Iaclng the Idea
of llvlng wlthout hla Iather.
To put thla on top of that?
lt'a Juat not rlght.
l awear to God, you atart
throwlng the word 'rlght' at me--
-What I mean--
-Waa It rlght to run a drug emplre?
There la no drug emplre.
Lylng to your aon,
to all of ua, la that rlght?
What do I have to do
to make you belleve me?
Why don't you klll youraell', Walt?
-What?
-Juat klll youraell'.
Thla whole thlng dlea wlth you.
That'a what you're aaylng here?
la that Hank ahould Juat let It go
and walt for you to dle.
Well, maybe you ahould Juat
go ahead and dle, then.
-That la not a aolutlon.
-No, It'a not a aolutlon.
-He'a not gettlng off that eaay.
-Jeaua, Hank.
And the aame goea for you
It you atlck wlth hlm.
Both of you thlnk you're Juat gonna
walk away from thla thlng?
Never gonna happen.
-That la not what we're aaylng.
-Enough wlth the bullahlt.
You're not gonna negotlate
your way out of thla thlng.
There'a only one aolutlon: Step up,
be a man and admlt what you've done.
That'a It. There la no other optlon.
Let'a go.
My name Ia Walter Hartwell Whlte.
I llve at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane...
...Albuquerque, New Mexlco, 87104.
Thla Ia my confeaalon.
If you're watchlng thla tape...
...l'm probably dead...
...murdered by my brother-In-Iaw,
Hank Schrader.
Hank has been bulldlng
a meth emplre...
...for over a year now
and ualng me as hla chemlat.
Shortly after my 50th blrthday...
...he aaked that I use
my chemlatry knowledge...
to cook methamphetamlne,
whlch he would then aell...
...ualng connectlona that he made
through hla career wlth the DEA.
I was astounded.
I.... I always thought Hank
was a very moral man...
...and! was partlcularly
vulnerable at the tlme...
...somethlng he knew
and took advantage of.
I was reellng
from a cancer dlagnosls...
...that was polsed
to bankrupt my famIIy.
Hank took me on a rIde-along
and showed me just how much money...
...even a small meth operatlon
could make.
And! was weak.
I dldn't want my famIIy
to go Into ﬂnancIaI ruln...
...so I agreed.
Hank had a partner, a buslnessman
named Gustavo Frlng.
Hank sold me Into servltude
to thla man...
...and when I trled to qult,
Frlng threatened my famIIy.
I dldn't know where to turn.
Eventually, Hank and Frlng
had a faIIIng out...
...and thlngs escalated.
Frlng was able to arrange...
...I guess--
I guess you call It a hlt on Hank.
It faIIed,
but Hank was serlously Injured...
...and I wound up
paylng hla medIcaI bIIIs...
...whlch amounted
to a llttle over $177, 000.
Upon recovery,
Hank was bent on revenge.
Worklng wlth a man
named Hector Salamanca...
...he plotted to M" Frlng.
The bomb that he used
was buIIt by me.
He gave me no optlon In that.
I have often contemplated suIcIde...
...but I'm a coward.
I wanted to go to the poIIce...
...but I was frlghtened.
Hank had rlsen to become the head
of the Albuquerque DEA.
To keep me In "M,
he took my chlldren.
For three months he kept them.
My wlfe had no Idea
of my crImInaI actIvItIes...
...was horrlﬂed to learn
what I had done.
I was In hell.
I hated myself for what
I had brought upon my famlly.
Recently, I trled once agaln to qult...
...and In response, he gave me thla.
I can't take thla anymore.
I llve In fear every day
that Hank wlll klll me...
...or worse, hurt my famlly.
All I could thlnk to do
was to make thla vldeo...
...and hope that the world
wlll flnally see thla man...
...for what he really ls.
Who do you thlnk he's shown thls to?
No one. It's a threat.
It's what he wlll do II I don't back off.
lthlnk you should show thls to Ramey.
Just get ahead of It.
That vldeo Is a bunch of lles, Hank.
Anybody who knows you wlll know.
A hundred and seventy-seven
thousand dollars?
Hell Is he talklng about?
Marle?
They told me It was gambllng money.
What was gambllng money?
Oh, Jesus Chrlst, Marle.
-Oh, God, no.
-How was I supposed to know?
How was I to know
where It came from?
Why were they paylng for my bllls?
What about my Insurance?
Insurance wouldn't have covered
the treatment you needed, and l....
-I wanted the best for you.
-Why dldn't you tell me?
Because I knew that
you would refuse It...
...and wlthout It, you may never
have been able to walk agaln.
Oh, Chrlst, Marle.
You kllled me here.
I mean, It's the-- It's the last nall.
That's the last nall In the cofﬁn.
What do we do?
II I were you, I'd be more nervous.
Jesus.
It's always the desert.
I already checked It.
It's clean.
I wouldn't have drlven It here It It wasn't.
Get one of these, by the way.
Reads radlo slgnals. Much easler.
What does he know?
I mean, he knows you're Helsenberg.
But I Ilgure not much else...
...otherwlse, you know,
you'd be locked up.
What dld he say exactly?
He wants me to Inform on you
for hlm.
Tell hlm everythlng we dld.
Anythlng else?
I don't thlnk he's told
the rest of the DEA.
Why do you say that?
Just hlm belng there all by hlmsell'...
...and, plus,
he was actlng klnd oI' shady.
Seemed llke he dldn't
want the other cops...
...hearlng what he had to say.
Are we gonna talk about the raln oI' caca
the kld brought down upon us?
Want to hazard a guess
what hls llttle charlty drlve cost you?
Why don't you go take a walk, Saul?
Jesse, wlll you let me help you?
I don't llke to see you hurtlng llke thls.
Maybe It's tlme tor a change.
What klnd of change?
I don't know.
I don't know, maybe....
Maybe It's tlme for you to Just...
...leave all of thls behlnd.
Just get out of town.
Don't look back.
He speclallzes In glvlng people
new Identltles.
He would move you someplace
far away...
...and set you up
wlth a whole new llI'e.
Yeah, I know,
sounds a llttle extreme.
But maybe It's exactly
what you need.
You know, I really thlnk
that would be good for you.
A clean slate.
All rlght, Just thlnk about It.
You get a Job, somethlng legltlmate,
somethlng you llke.
Meet a glrl, start a Iamlly, even.
Hell, you're stlll so damn young.
And what's here for you now anyway?
ltell you, II I could, I'd trade places.
A whole lll'etlme ahead of you...
...wlth a chance to hlt
the reset button.
In a few years...
...thls mlght all feel llke nothlng more
than a bad dream.
Would you Just, for once...
...stop worklng me?
What are you talklng about?
Can you Just stop worklng me for, llke,
10 seconds stralght?
Stop Jerklng me around?
Jesse, I am not worklng you.
Yes. Yes, you are.
All rlght, Just drop the whole
concerned-dad thlng...
...and tell me the truth.
I mean, you're actlng llke...
...me leavlng town Is all about me...
...and turnlng over a new leaf,
but It's really-- It's really about you.
I mean, you need me gone...
...because your dlckhead brother-In-law
ls never gonna let up.
Just say so.
Just ask me for a favour.
Just tell me you don't glve a shlt
about me...
...and It's elther thls....
It's elther thls or you'll klll me
the same way you kllled Mlke.
I mean, Isn't that
what thls Is all about?
Us meetlng way the hell out here.
In case I say no.
Come on.
Just tell me you need thls.
Your change.
If you'll hand thls
to your car wash prol'esslonal...
...and have an A-1 day.
Skyler?
Skyler, I've got my chemo
In about 45 mlnutes.
Can you take over the reglster for me?
Skyler?
It worked...
...and we're Ilne.
Okay?
We're Ilne.
So Palmer and Castanares...
...are slttlng on that Jerkoﬂ'
Saul Goodman's oI'I'Ice...
-...keep|ng an eye on Jesse Plnkman.
-Yeah, I put them on It.
You wanna explaln that to me?
Yeah. nght.
Why the hell should I know anythlng?
They're Just my guys, after all.
You gotta tell me what's golng on.
Plnkman ls A.P.D.'s problem, not ours.
You got a hlstory wlth thls kld.
II he catches wlnd
that you're tralllng hlm...
...and thls explodes, he could sue.
Look, II I can't explaln thls to Ramey,
I gotta pull my guys.
Flne. Take them off.
l sald, take them off.
What else you want?
I'm golng out for a whlle.
You have that 3:88.
Wlll you be back?
You know what, It's gonna have
to be another day. Reschedule It.
Last chance. You sure there's nobody
you wanna say bye to?
Nobody at all?
Thls Is It. Once I make the call,
there's no take-backs.
I need a new dust Illter...
...for my Hoover Max Extract
Pressure Pro, model 68.
Can you help me wlth that?
Yeah, plckup.
He's hot. Not 'hot' hot,
Just a llttle hot.
Currently out on ball.
Yeah, he knows the rules.
One hour. Okay, he'll be there.
And done.
Okay, thls guy's I'ee Is 125.
Your benel'actor...
...asked me to send you out
wlth somethlng extra.
Get you started, you know?
Keep you slttlng pretty...
...untll you get Into the groove
of your new llI'e.
Provlded, of course, you don't
toss It out the wlndow on the way.
Serlously, thls Is the last of It...
...so you mlght wanna thlnk
about maklng a budget.
Hey, what are you dolng?
You can't Ilre up a doob In here.
Put that out.
I mean It. Put It out.
Look, Mr. Natural, I'm not
gonna let you sabotage thls thlng.
Thls guy Is not gonna take you
It you show up hlgh...
...so stop screwlng around,
or It's both our asses.
nght. Well, that's a start.
Now, glve wlth the dope.
Chrlst.
Some people are Immune
to good advlce.
I'm gonna get a bag for thls cash.
Don't even thlnk
about llghtlng up agaln.
Francesca, we got any bags?
For money. Money-slzed bags.
Huell wlll drop you
at the plckup spot...
...then he's gonna get
the hell out of there.
You got that?
Guy won't plck up the kld
If he's got company.
You got a phone?
Cops took It.
All rlght,
In case somethlng goes wrong...
...guy doesn't show, whatever,
you glve me a call.
Serlously? Hello Kltty?
Serlously, It's free.
We got a beggars-choosers sltuatlon
here, so stop bustlng my balls.
Corner of Juan Tabo and Osuna.
You, you're gonna slt and walt.
Thls guy's punctual wlth a capltal P.
Okay? So don't move.
Don't get up and get an Ice cream.
Just stay put llke a good boy.
He'll plck you up, you pay hlm.
He'll take your ID,
he'll glve you a new one.
Goodbye, Jesse Plnkman.
Hello, Mr. Credlt to Soclety.
So do I get to plck where I go?
Well, It's your llI'e.
l lmaglne you get a say.
Want a suggestlon?
How about Florlda?
You get a tan,
meet the Swedlsh blklnl team...
...you know,
swlm wlth the dolphlns.
What about Alaska?
Alaska. Okay, well,
that's a dlfl'erent vlbe.
I never Ilgured you
for a moose lover...
-...but whatever floats your boat.
-Alaska.
Alaska's good.
Anywhere you can get
a fresh start ls gonna be good.
You ready?
Yeah.
Take care, Jesse.
All rlght.
Hey, man, you can't go In there!
He a no-show? Why dldn't you call?
Why dldn't you--?
StopI
Code redI
-HuellI
-NoI HeyI
-HeyI
-Get In hereI
Back off!
You, stay where you are.
What? I don't know what happened here.
What dld I do?
You stole It off me.
You and hlm, you took It
out of my pocket, dldn't you?
Calm down. Yes.
Okay. I had Huell llIt your dope.
I told you I couldn't rlsk
the guy not taklng you.
NoI Before. The clgarette.
You stole the clgarette.
-What?
-The rlcln clgaretteI
You had hlm steal It off of me!
And all for that asshole Mr. WhlteI
He polsoned BrockI
He polsoned Brock, and you--
You helped hlmI
-Okay, Jesse, calm down.
-Say It agalnI
Tell me one more tlme
to calm down! Come on!
I'm sorry. Yes. Okay.
I had Huell llIt your clgarette,
but Walt made me.
He told me he was helplng you,
he was savlng you.
I never would've agreed to It
If I'd known what he was gonna do.
Jesse, you gotta belleve me.
I dldn't want any of thlsI
Get off me!
What do I pay you for?
Hey, It's me. We got a blg problem.
--elghteen, 19 and 28.
Actually, you gave me a 5, not a 1.
Oh, l-- l dld. l'm-- I'm so sorry.
Here you go.
Thank you for your honesty.
Oh, and please glve thls
to your car wash prol'esslonal.
Have an A-1 day.
-Hey.
-Hl.
-What's golng on?
-Not much.
-Yeah? Nothlng?
-Nope. Thlngs are Ilne.
-Good.
-Why?
Oh, no reason.
You know what I found the other day...
...latchlng.
lt's-- It's catchlng every tlme
that l stock that darn thlng.
So I thought I'd check It out.
Great.
Thank you.
Exact change.
I llke that. Thank you very much.
Okay.
And...
...please glve thls
to your car-care prol'esslonal...
-...and have an A-1 day. Thank you.
-Thank you.
IJust remembered
they gave me a prescrlptlon...
...to go plck up, so....
I forgot.
I'm gonna go head on over
to the drugstore, okay?
-Yeah, okay.
-All rlght.