WAITRESS:
Here you go.
What happened then?
It's my blrthday.
Yoah? Wall, happy blrthday.
Blrthday mull are iron at Denny's.
All you gotta show I: a valld ID.
I'm good. Thanks.
Really? Fru meal.
Pros I: good.
Even II' I was, Ilka, rlch,
I'ru |s always good.
MAN: Thank you.
Mm-hm.
Okay.
Now Hampshlro.
You're a long way from homo.
How long a drlvo Is that?
About 30 hours,
It all you stop for Is gas.
Wow. You hoadod
to Calll'ornla?
No. Hora.
Okay.
So, what's here?
You know,
I was In Boston once.
Boston and a llttle town
called Swampscott,
whlch ls rlght outslde
of Boston.
That's klnd of near
New Hampshlre, rlght?
Uh...
Yeah. More or less.
Yeah, I was maybe 6,
so I don't really remember It.
I want to say I llked lt.
They got thls really blg aquarlum.
Yeah. Great sclence museum there.
My name's Lucy.
I'll be your server.
[noon OPENS]
I got your word thls won't
wlnd up crosslng the border?
It's never leavlng town.
Is there a manual?
lnstructlon manual?
I pulled somethlng
off the Internet.
It's In there.
Well,
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
Happy blrthday,
Mr. Lambert.
[OAR ALARM HONKING]
[J'J'J']
Jesus, Walt, the news here.
Gus Frlng ls dead.
He was blown up
along wlth some person
from some Mexlcan cartel,
and the DEA has no ldea
what to make of It.
Do you know about thls?
Walt?
Walt, I need you to--
WALT [OVER PHONE]:
It's over. We're safe.
Was thls you?
What happened?
[J'J'J']
Oh, God.
[noon OPENS]
WALT JR.:
Dad.
Hey.
Serlous-- You don't have the TV on?
Serlously?
No, sorry, I...
You dldn't tell hlm about Mr. Frlng?
Um, he knows.
Welcome home.
Jesus, Dad,
It's all they're talklng about.
They haven't sald It on TV yet,
but Uncle Hank says he was
thls major, major drug dealer.
I mean, llke, holy shlt.
Your uncle ls saI'e, rlght?
How do they know that?
Uncle Hank was
after thls guy all along.
He dldn't tell us, but he was.
He even took me
to hls restaurant one tlme,
Just, llke, totally toylng
wlth the guy,
Just llke, 'I got my eye on you.'
lee that.
They I'lgure Mr. Frlng was the one
who put the hlt out on Uncle Hank.
Just somebody got to hlm I'lrst.
Wow.
Yeah, wow.
Aunt Marle's stlll pretty I'reaked.
She dldn't want us to leave,
but Mom I'lgured It was tlme.
Ah.
There's stlll some agents over there,
but they I'lgure It's over.
Hm.
lee, when thls hlts the news,
Uncle Hank ls gonna be a hero.
Yeah.
I mean, even more so than before.
Serlously.
See-- See II' It's on TV.
Yeah, yeah, I want to.
Just glve me
a couple mlnutes, huh?
MAN [ON TV]:
--around the 24-yard-llne.
They break huddle--
[HOLLY CRIESJ
HI, sweet pea.
Oh, Daddy mlssed you so much.
Yes, he dld.
l mlssed you too.
Well, don't you thlnk
I rate a 'hello,' at least?
Hello to you too.
So are you gonna talk to me here?
Are you gonna...
You gonna show some klnd oI'...
I don't know, some klnd oI' mlld relleI'
that I'm allve?
I am relleved, Walt.
And scared.
Scared of what?
You.
[HOLLY BABBLING]
Hey.
Oh, shlt.
[J'J'J']
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
GOMEZ:
Jesus, Just say It already.
Tell me 'I told you so.'
Get It out of your system
before you need, llke,
dlalysls or somethlng.
It's exactly llke Boettlcher's drawlngs.
Where were the two bodles?
Over by
the I'relght elevator.
Over there.
No Idea who they were?
No, not much left.
Apparently the teeth
do thls popcorn thlng
when they get too hot,
so they tell me.
Whoever torched It dld It up rlght.
Frlng, you magnlI'lcent bastard.
What do you I'lgure that was?
I don't know,
some klnd of lab equlpment?
Maybe a camera?
[CLUCKING]
Come on. Come on, you, be nlce.
Be nlce.
Come on. Hey. Hey!
You be nlce. Just be nlce.
Let Wendell In there.
II' Wendell doesn't eat, nobody eats.
Yeah.
[MAN SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[COUGHS]
It's Gustavo.
[J'J'J']
[HORN HONKING]
Son of a bltch.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold up! Hold up!
Get out of my way, kld.
Walt a mlnute, all rlght? Let hlm talk.
I am done llstenlng to thls asshole talk.
Now get out of my way.
He's got somethlng
you need to hear, all rlght?
What'd you do, Jesse?
Do you even know?
Do you even know
what you've done?
Yeah, he saved hls own llI'e--
One more word.
It you klll hlm, you're gonna
have to klll me. Come on.
Oh, Jesse.
Jesus.
What Is It wlth you guys?
Honest to God.
May I?
Look, whatever dlfl'erences
you and l have, they'll keep.
nght now we've got
blgger I'lsh to try.
Blgger I'lsh.
The vldeo cameras.
Gus kept cameras on us
at the lab,
at the laundry,
God only knows where else.
And of course,
when I say 'us,'
I'm lncludlng you.
Mlke, II' he taped all that shlt,
us cooklng, you plcklng up.
II' Gus had a record of that
and the pollce get to It
before we do...
You son of a bltch.
Mlke, It's all on tape somewhere,
or a hard drlve.
Where?
Where dld he keep It?
He had a laptop ln hls oI'I'Ice.
Kept It In the back of the restaurant.
It all I'ed stralght to there.
What?
Keys, scumbag.
It's the unlversal symbol for keys.
[J'J'J']
MIKE:
Meter I'raud.
And yes, yes, It's a blg deal.
Guy rlgs hls meter so he's paylng
2 cents less for I'lrst-class postage.
I'm here to tell you that the USPS
takes that very serlously.
It's money out of your pocket,
lt's money out of my pocket.
l was hoplng-- Now, look, sarge.
Do you thlnk we could
work together on thls thlng?
You folks have It over there?
Could you tell me that, at least?
Yeah.
Well, thanks for your help.
Inspector Clark--
Inspector Dave Clark,
llke the Dave Clark Flve?
Oh. Before your tlme.
Well, you feel free to call me
day or nlght at thls number.
Yes, slr. No, you as well.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
We're boned.
[CELL PHONE CRACKS]
Well...
You know how they say
'lt's been a pleasure'?
It hasn't.
Are you gonna tell us
about the laptop?
Where you golng?
I'm gettlng the hell out of Dodge, kld.
And so should you.
It's Just a matter of tlme.
Mlke, where Is the laptop?
What the hell dll'l'erence does It make?
They got lt. End of story.
[SCOFFS]
A.P.D., Northwest Area Command
on Second.
They tagged lt, they I'lled lt,
It's In the system, and they locked It
In thelr evldence room.
All rlght.
So descrlbe the bulldlng.
Heh. Descrlbe the...
How about I descrlbe Fort Knox?
And what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna put on your black leotard
and go dangllng on a clothesllne?
It's a bulldlng full of cops.
What else do you need to know?
And why In the hell
am I talklng to you?
Mlke, we gotta do somethlng.
I am dolng somethlng.
He's good wlth thls stuI'I', okay?
Just glve hlm a chance.
Now, you look.
That laptop mlght as well
be on the moon.
They bulld these evldence rooms
llke bank vaults because, guess what,
lunatlcs llke you
wanna break Into them.
But unllke a bank vault, thls Is a place
that Is guarded 24 hours a day
by the pollce.
There's no way you're gettlng It
out of there.
Who sald that
we have to get It out of there?
We Just need to destroy what's on It.
Oh, so now you wanna
blow up a pollce statlon?
I don't belleve l sald that, no.
Nurslng home full of old folks
Just whet your appetlte.
Now you wanna klll
a bunch of cops.
I never sald anythlng
about kllllng anybody.
I am, however, conslderlng
the posslblllty of a devlce.
A devlce.
Yes, a small devlce.
Say thls devlce gets I'lled
Into evldence.
Now It Is lnslde that room.
What about a magnet?
You wanna commlt
a whole other crlme Just to
get thls bomb Into evldence.
Who sald 'bomb'? l sald 'a devlce.'
What about a magnet?
An lncendlary devlce.
One qulck I'lre Is all It would take.
You don't thlnk
they have I'lre suppresslon?
I'm not talklng sprlnklers.
I'm talklng about halon.
Because halon doesn't
destroy evldence.
A magnet, though, maybe llke--
A bomb then. We plant a bomb outslde.
Oh, actually I knew a crew
out of Fort Worth
that trled to blow up
an evldence room from outslde.
About all they dld was
take out a couple of hedges.
You are probably talklng about
2 feet of relnI'orced concrete.
Or what about a magnet?
What magnet?
What about It?
You know, Just:
[IMITATES WHOOSHING]
Pm.
WALT:
So, what do you thlnk?
OLD JOE:
Expenslve.
Leavlng aslde englneerlng,
rlgglng some klnd of
alternate power source,
my prlmary stlcklng polnt ls
I actually need the thlng.
As you gentlemen can see,
It's paylng the bllls.
But I mean It's I'easlble, doable?
Hey, we're llvlng In a tlme
oI' strlng theorles and God partlcles.
Feaslble, doable?
Yeah, sure, why not?
Expenslve.
JESSE:
What would you put It In?
What about that?
Does It run?
OLD JOE:
We can get It runnlng.
What's the box made of?
Plywood and alumlnlum,
Just what you need.
All rlght,
so you wanna talk money?
Step Into my ofï¬ce.
WALT:
Hey, llsten, um...
I don't actually have
any money rlght now.
My wlI'e.
There's an IRS lssue.
Anyway, I'd appreclate It It you could
spot me my share. I'll pay you back.
Yeah. Whatever.
nght.
You comlng?
It you have any bralns,
you'll take that money you saved
and you'll sklp town.
Today. nght now.
You don't thlnk thls can work?
Is that a serlous questlon?
Mlke, thls Is a three-man Job.
The only way I know It won't work
for sure Is II' we don't have you.
[CRANE WHIRRING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come In.
Get In. Close the door.
What dld we say
about you comlng here?
Yeah, speaklng oI' thlngs
that tend to rlle you up,
the pollce, they may call.
Let me back up a llttle.
Can I slt down?
I'm gonna slt down.
Okay, why are the pollce
gonna call?
May call you.
Dlstant, outslde posslblllty.
But on the off chance,
I want you thlnklng one thought:
Hogan's Heroes.
Sergeant Schultz.
You remember Sergeant Schultz?
'I know nothlng. I see nothlng.'
You remember how he--?
I want you llke that.
Okay, Saul, why are the pollce--?
There was an lncldent wlth Beneke--
Oh, God.
And It's--
Oh, Jesus.
What lncldent?
An act of God.
There's no rlght.
There's no wrong.
I mean, It Just--
That's the best phrase.
It I'lts, but we got a problem.
Ted's dead.
Sorry?
Ted ls dead?
He Just woke up.
OLD JOE:
nght-o, that should do her.
All rlght, watches oft.
Necklaces, earrlngs, rlngs, bracelets.
Gold. These are nonI'errous.
Better hope.
What about that stuff you young guys
wear on the end of your prlcks?
Speak now or I'orever slng soprano.
What's up wlth that, by the way?
Why would anybody wanna
put a metal rlng through
the end of thelr prlck?
What are you
looklng at me for?
All rlght, guns, knlves,
tools, keys, plates In your head,
uh, artlI'lclal hlps.
Check your pockets for me
one more tlme, please.
Oh, credlt cards.
You want that plastlc worklng
come Mlller tlme.
You know, I can foresee
a lot of posslble outcomes
to thls thlng,
and not a slngle one of them
Involves Mlller tlme.
P.M.A.
Posltlve mental attltude.
Okay, I thlnk we're good to go.
All rlght, where do you
want me wlth thls?
Start 40 feet out.
That's more than
the length of the room.
Who's dolng the honours?
Me.
Fllp that swltch, turns It on.
Twlst thls here.
That's your power control.
All rlght.
Everybody ready?
WALT: Yeah.
Okay.
Flre In the hole!
WALT:
All rlght, you ready?
Flngers crossed It don't yank
the drlve shaft through the floor.
Anythlng?
Nope. It's stlll worklng.
All rlght, start walklng
I'orward slowly.
JESSE:
Whoa. Whoa, whoa. Walt, walt, walt.
Yeah. That dld lt.
Yes.
Whoa.
Yeah, bltchI
MagnetsI OhI
How many batterles ls thls?
That there's 21, wlred ln serles,
so 21 tlmes 12.
Two hundred I'ltty-two volts.
Can you add 21 more,
wlred In parallel?
Up the amperage?
Everythlng goes I'lylng
In that evldence room,
It's gonna make
one hell of a nolse,
and there goes
your element of surprlse.
Won't matter.
Slxty seconds, we'll be gone.
SKYLER:
Um, excuse me.
HI. Who are you looklng I'or?
Ted Beneke. I'm a I'rlend oI' hls.
But II' It's not a good tlme, I could--
No, no, no, thls ls I'lne.
I'm Just I'lnlshlng up. Come on In.
[EKG BEEPING]
[GASPS]
Hey, Ted.
[cnvmc]
NURSE:
I tell you, he's been a real champ.
Hls colour's better
and hls blood pressure's up.
We are gonna have you
eatlng solld food In a day or two,
I bet you money.
That's wonderl'ul.
All rlght,
I'm Just down the hall.
Ted.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Ted, IJust...
I don't even know--
Skyler.
I haven't sald anythlng...
to anyone.
I told them It was an accldent.
ltrlpped...
and tell. That Is all they know.
Just...
l've-- I've got chlldren.
Famlly.
I swear to you.
Please.
IJust...
wlll never breathe...
one word of thls.
[J'J'J']
[ENGINE STARTS]
WALT:
It should be about a quarter
of the way down on the left.
We'll do a loop and come around
the other slde. Turn here.
nght up there.
That's the wall.
JESSE:
What the hell ls thls?
There's some blg-ass
hump In the way.
WALT:
So? Just drlve over It.
JESSE: Ah. All rlght.
Come on, you can do It.
Take It easy. Take It easy.
You got lt.
WALT:
Cut lt.
It's, llke, 8 feet away.
ls thls cool? Huh?
ls thls close enough?
It'll work.
[MAGNET THUMPS]
[TRUCK CREAKING]
[ALARM WAILING]
Mr. Whlte, let's go.
Hold on.
Let's Just go!
Hang on.
Mr. Whlte, let's get out of here.
WALT:
Just one mlnute.
[snuurmc]
Turn It ofI'I Turn It off.
I wlll.
JacocksI Jacocks, you okay?
OutsldeI OutsldeI
[JESSE YELLS]
Yeah, bltchI
Shut up.
Oh. Yeah.
And what exactly
are you celebratlng?
You left the truck behlnd.
WALT:
So what?
MIKE:
'So what'?
So, what If they flnd prlnts?
And what If they trace It back
to the wrecklng yard?
They won't.
There's no prlnts,
I made sure of that.
There's no paperwork on the truck,
the magnet or the batterles.
Untraceable salvage, all of It.
I made sure of that too.
Well, you got all the answers.
So you tell me, Answer Man,
dld all that even work Just now?
Yes. It worked.
And I'm supposed to take that
on falth?
Yeah? And why?
How do we know?
Because I say so.
OFFICER:
07-66-26432.
Gutlerrez, Alvln B.
Rooflng hammer.
Undamaged. Bag stlll sealed.
11-58-73321.
Frlng, Gustavo.
Samsung laptop computer.
Damaged. Glass screen
ls broken and In pleces.
Bag stlll sealed.
11-58-73317.
Frlng, Gustavo.
Framed photograph of two men.
The glass ls broken
and photo has sllpped
out of Its frame.
Bag appears to be sllghtly punctured
by broken glass.
Huh. Check It out.
That's not on the manlfest.
SAUL:
All rlght, so flrst off,
I'm not a marrlage counsellor.
Nor do I take sldes ln thls thlng.
And, not taklng sldes, mlnd you,
but you dld put her In charge
of your money,
whlch l advlsed agalnst,
If you'll recall,
all of whlch Is not to be construed
as an 'I told you so.'
I'm Just walklng you through
my mental process, so to speak.
So she comes to me wlth a problem.
That she's been
cooklng Beneke's books,
he's ln Dutch wlth the IRS,
and once they audlt,
lt's Rlo de Caca for the both of them.
To whlch I say, 'Hey, let's Involve Walt
ln thls dlscusslon.'
To whlch she says,
'No, let's cut Beneke a cheque
so's he can pay off the IRS.'
Agaln, not taklng sldes,
but she really was trylng to protect you.
A llttle feedback here mlght be nlce.
'Let's Involve Walt ln thls dlscusslon.'
Yeah, that's what I told her.
She sald no.
And you dldn't argue the polnt.
You dldn't thlnk to contact me.
You were a tad preoccupled
at the tlme, If you'll recall.
Okay.
So you took It upon yourself
to glve away $622,000
of my money
to a man who had been
sleeplng wlth my wlfe.
She's my cllent,
same as you.
Does thls arrangement
get a llttle trlcky at tlmes?
Absolutely.
But I try my best, you know,
ethlcally, In my duty--
Ethlcally?
I'm sorry. I must be hearlng thlngs.
Dld you actually Just use
the word 'ethlcally' In a sentence?
You're not Clarence Darrow, Saul.
You're a two-blt bus-bench lawyer.
And you work for me.
Yeah, well, Clarence Darrow
never had a cllent llke you ask hlm
for somethlng
llke thls.
Okay? Yeah, I put my ass
on the llne for you.
Huell too. Huh?
He's got flngers llke hot dogs.
He could've easlly busted thls In two
and kllled everyone In the offlce.
But do I complaln?
No. Beg, borrow or steal,
I'm your huckleberry.
I go the extra mlle.
Only you never told me
that kld would wlnd up In the hospltal.
You know--
Take that thlng
and get the hell out of here.
You and me, we're done.
What are you--?
Come on. Hey.
Hey.
We're done
when I say we're done.
SKYLER:
Yes, you are. Yes.
Hey.
I heard what happened to Ted.
He's not gonna talk.
Yeah.
l forglve you.
[J'J'J']