So clgarattu and gas II $79.70.
Crap.
Thara': an ATM rlght outllde.
Yaah, I don't hava a card.
Well, you can wrlta a parsonal cheque
wlth ID.
Klnd of In batman bank: rlght now.
You thlnk I could Just
coma back latar?
I'm totally good for It.
I'd coma back, I awaar.
If It wara ma, I'd ha totally,
you know, 'No problam.‘
But my dad I:
thla glnormoua hard-an.
Ha was In Fallujah for a yaar.
And ha alwaya chacka tha racalpta.
l maan, Ilka, alwaya.
I gotta call hlm. I'm sorry.
Walt, walt, walt.
Mayba wa could...
...trada.
Evar try It?
l maan, l amoka pot a lot aomatlmaa.
l party.
But....
-But that atul’t'a raally addlctlva, rlght?
-Not raally.
It's Just a madla thlng. You know?
What's It Ilka?
lt'a awaaoma.
Evarythlng'a maxlmum lntaraatlng.
You gat thaaa raally cold
and sharp-Ilka actlon daggar l'aallnga.
lt'a awaaoma.
Coma on. What do you say?
Hava a nlca day.
So how doaa It l'aal?
Doaa It hurt?
Yaah, lt'a tlght.
-Yaah, but la It palnl'ul?
-lt'a hard to braatha.
Wall, you naad your braathlng.
Although lat'a not loaa alght
of tha l'act...
...that you wara tha vlctlm
of a tarrlbla accldant, Antonlo...
...ao aoma dlacoml'ort la
to ba axpactad.
Lat'a go wlth that ona.
A caahlar'a chaqua, por favor.
Oh, and apraad tha word.
I'm bulldlng a claaa-actlon, l'llght 515.
Vlctlma' l'amlllaa would ha graat.
I'll taka anyona on tha ground
who aufl'arad amotlonally.
Anxlaty, alaaplaaanaaa.
You gat tha plctura.
Troubla?
Tad Banaka? You cannot be aarloua.
-That guy I: a joke.
-You know what? You called my bluff.
What does that even mean?
You dared ma to tall the pollca
and! couldn't do It, so you wln.
If you want to stay In thls house, ﬁne,
but we are not marrlad anymore.
I told you that
I was done cooklng math, Skyler.
-I promlsed you that.
-So what?
You know what?
At least I dIdn't run off to go--
Jesusl I mean, everythlng that I dId,
I dId for thls famIIy.
-Just keep teIIIng yourself that.
-What Is that supposed to mean?
You don't lIke It, then leave.
-And take your drug money wlth you.
-That's what you want.
-Jasus.
-Garbaga dlsposal.
You thInk thls wIll get me
to move out?
You can screw Ted. You can screw
the butcher, the maIlman.
-God, Walt.
-Whoever you want.
Screw them all.
I'm not golng anywhere.
Sult yourself.
ls thls a good or bad thlng?
Sult myself.
You want me to salt myself?
I'll suIt myself to hIs facel
It's a bad thlng.
Waltar Whlta to sea Tad Banaka.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Banaka's on a conference call.
Okay. I wlll walt.
It could be a whlla.
l have all the tlma In the world.
Okay.
-Hara we go. Okay.
-Excusa ma.
-Mr. Banaka's not avallabla.
-Tad? Come on.
Slr, excuse me.
Tad, I can see you.
I can see you standlng rlght there
In your offlca.
Open the door. Come on, let's talk.
IJust want to talk. That's all.
Come on, let's be men about thls.
Okay? How about that?
Hay, Walt. I'm klnd of In the mlddla
of somathlng now.
Oh, yes, you are.
So open the door.
You'ra damn rlght.
You'ra rlght In the mlddla.
Just open the door
and let's talk about It, okay?
Open the door, Tad, rlght now.
You don't want to be a man about It?
Plan B. How do you Ilka that? Plan B.
We have a sltuatlon.
Walt. Walt. Walt.
What are you dolng?
I'm talklng wlth Tad.
Next tlma, you'll open the door.
-FraazaI Come on.
-Oh, damn lt.
No, I'm Just here to talk.
-I Just want to talk to hlm.
-Outslda. Let's go.
God. Can IJust talk?
IJust want to talk to hlm.
-Calm down.
-l'm Just-- Okay, all rlght.
All rlght, all rlght, all rlght.
I'm calm. I'm calm.
Asshola.
What do you want?
Hey! Hey, come on.
What the hall ls wrong wlth you?
You act Ilka you're the flrst guy
thls happened to.
I caught my second wlfa scrawlng
my stapdad, okay?
It's a cruel world, Walt. Grow up.
-I Just wanted to talk to hlm.
-Yaah, well, now I'm talklng to you.
Consldar thls an lntarvantlon.
You could have been arrested
back there. You understand.
Spaaklng as your lawyer,
I'm always looklng I'or blllabla hours.
But spaaklng as
your buslnass assoclata...
...l'm strongly advlslng
that you get your shlt togathar.
Just cool It wlth thls Banaka guy,
at least for now. Okay?
Let's talk shop, because
lthlnk thls Is a great opportunlty...
...to channel some of that nagatlva
anargy Into somathlng posltlva.
-How dld you know?
-Sorry?
About Skylar.
About where to flnd me Just now.
How dld you know?
That's Just my matlculousnass.
Don't bog down In datall, Walt.
-Tha lasson here should ba--
-Dld you bug my house?
Yeah, but I dldn't know It was
your house, dld I?
You'd moved out.
Basldas, you baslcally told me to.
-I told you to?
-You strongly hlntad that I should.
You were worrlad your wlfa mlght say
somathlng to tha pollca.
What? No, no, that's not true.
When the hall dld I say that?
Let's not get lost In the who,
what and whans.
Tha polnt ls wa dld our dua dlllganca
and she dldn't talk.
She kept qulat.
She stood by you, Walt...
...whlch, If you ask me,
Is the lronlcal sllvar llnlng hara.
I mean, on the one hand...
...sura, sha snuck off the rasarvatlon
to get some dlrty, damp and deep.
On the other hand--
Off ma.
You'ra I'lradI
-You'ra donaI
-GoodI
'Oh, boohoo,
I won't cook math anymora.'
You're a crybaby. Who needs you?
I'm unplugglng tha wabslta,
so no more money laundarlng.
How do you Ilka that?
I want those bugs
out of my house today.
I want them out now!
You Just bought a $300 sult, psychoI
Great, drlllad rlght Into the stucco.
A llttla blt of putty, you'll be flna.
Just make sure
you get all of those thlngs.
A, thasa thlngs cost $800 aplaca.
B, you're not that lntarastlng.
So yeah, I'll get all of them, Waltar.
Graat llna of work, by the way.
Raal upstandlng flald.
Yeah, well...
...I enjoy It.
You'ra free to leave now. Anytlma.
You know, Waltar...
...somatlmas It doesn't hurt
to have someone watchlng your back.
Mr. Whlta?
What's up?
I can't bagln to understand
what you're golng through, Walt...
...wlth all of your health concerns
and the stresses you've been under.
But stlll, as educators...
...thara ara cartaln rasponslbllltlas
we need to ba maatlng hara...
...to the school
and to the students themselves.
Of course.
ls thls a whaatan tarrlar?
Norfolk.
Norfolk?
That's surprlslng.
Walt, could you come back over here
and have a seat, plaasa?
Sura.
You've been absent a lot racantly.
And when you are here at school, there
have been some bahavloural quastlons.
And frankly I'm concerned.
Thank you.
Are you faallng okay?
Do you thlnk maybe
I should call Skylar?
Lat's Just keep thls....
What"?
HayI
Walt, what's wrong wlth you?
You know, look, you're the one
always talklng about D.c., okay?
Thls ls how you get there.
You answer the ball.
You pay your dues.
Basldas, you know,
It's a blg deal to get plckad I'or thls.
El Paso's Ilka the Super Bowl.
I could get klllad crosslng the street,
okay?
Whatever. You know, I want to go.
What about last tlma?
Schradar.
Hay, sharlff. Yaah.
Blua, huh?
Yeah, yeah. Thlng ls--
Thlng ls I'm supposed to ba gattlng
on a plane rlght now.
The stuff thls guy had was blua.
You sure about that?
Yaah.
Yeah, I want to talk to hlm.
Taxl.
-Hl.
-Man, I'm sorry.
I needed to talk to you,
but you weren't at your apartment.
No, I moved back home.
That's good, rlght?
Yaah.
-Yo, dld you Just get flrad?
-No.
lndaflnlta. Yaah.
So, what's up?
Should we go somewhere?
No, thls ls flna.
So I want an Intro to your guy.
What guy?
Your guy. Your dlstrlbutlon guy.
The guy Saul hookad you up wlth.
No, no, no. Come on, Jassa.
-I thought about It and I want to.
-God.
It's the one thlng I'm good at.
No, that Is Just not true.
You'ra good at a lot of thlngs, son.
lea what?
What about your sobrlaty?
ltold you, I'm not uslng.
Evan
IJust want back Into the buslnass.
Well, I don't. I'm sorry.
I know, and that's cool.
I'm not asklng you to cook.
What's thls?
In the and, IJust want wlth
two reflux condansars.
l dldn't want to lose track
of my pH levels.
But I dld avarythlng else
Just Ilka you taught me.
Supar caraful In my amounts...
...and watched the numbers
every step of the way.
So, what do you thlnk?
It's good, rlght?
What In the hall ls thls?
-What?
Thls. Thls. Thls Is my product.
Thls Is my formula. Thls ls mlna.
It's our product,
but yeah, I was gonna cut you In.
Oh, you were gonna cut me In?
No, no, no. I cut you In.
What the hall Is your problem?
All I'm asklng Is for you to set a meat.
-Absolutaly not.
-Why?
Because I am not gonna land my name
to an lnfarlor product.
I mean, look at the dlamatars hara.
What dld you use for raductlon?
Don't tell me. Platlnum dloxlda, rlght?
No. Marcury-alumlnlum amalgam.
Tha dloxlda's too hard to keep wat.
All rlght, well,
you must'va done It wrong, then.
Your colour Is all cloudy, so you were
struggllng wlth dlstlllatlon too.
Now, thls Is very shoddy work,
Plnkman.
I'm actually ambarrassad for you.
What?
No way. I gave out samples
and everyone sald It was the bomb.
Oh, they sald It was the bomb.
And who were they, I wonder?
A bunch of math haads?
-Yaah.
-Thay should know, rlght?
-Yaah, wall, sorry.
-I can't help you.
-Flna, ass-wad.
-l'll contact the guy mysalf.
-Oh, yeah? Well, good luck.
Because my guy Is a pro
and he doesn't daal wlth Junklas.
-You know what? Eat ma.
-Anytlma, losar.
Hey, hey, hey!
Walt. HayI
I can't ballava It's only 4:00.
Thls day Is dragglng.
Okay.
l wlsh I could stay.
So stay.
What's stopplng you?
What, Ilka avarythlng, you mean?
How about my lunatlc husband
rafuslng to leave the house?
So move In hara.
And then my son hatlng me
even more.
That'll pass.
lwant through that wlth tha glrls.
Thay adapt.
And now everyone at work thlnks
I'm an avll laddar-cllmblng whora.
They're all flrad,
affactlva lmmadlataly.
What else?
Oh, aren't you the answer man?
Whara dld lt--?
Whara dld It go wrong, axactly,
wlth you and Walt?
I mean, I always saw hlm as klnd of...
...mlld-mannarad.
Somathlng, I don't know,
change when he got slck or...?
I don't know what changad, Tad.
And IJust don't feel really comfortable
talklng about It.
Sorry.
Just asklng out of salt-lntarast.
Gotta make sure
I don't make the same mlstaka.
Just let me see If
I'm followlng you here, Russall.
You got thls stuff from some guy
at Gasparza's...
...who was waarlng tan pants...
...and who you're 00 percent sure
had a moustacha.
That's It, rlght?
That's your braln
worklng at maxlmum capaclty?
Evarythlng all rlght In there?
Mal. Tha duda's name was Mal.
Well, there you go. See?
You sarvad an actual aarthly functlon.
I can't ballava I remembered that.
Mal who?
Does he have a last name?
Yaah, Mal.
Walt.
Was It Mal...
...or Mark?
It was daflnltaly an M nama.
Oh, man, I'm loslng lt.
Walt, walt.
Yaah.
It's gone.
-It was an M nama though.
-Yaah.
I remember tha...sound.
All rlght, wall,
we'll go wlth tha...sound.
-Thanks a lot. Appraclata lt.
-Yaah.
Ha daflnltaly had tan pants.
Ramlnd me to get a vasectomy.
Okay, lt's after 9,
so thls bar that Glrl Gaorga Is at...
...probably wall-to-wall dlrtbags
by now.
Let's go have a llttla looky-loo,
sea If we can't flnd thls M-namad clown.
What? It's a lead.
-Laad to what?
-To Halsanbarg.
I told you It was only a matter of tlma
bafora thls guy bootad up agaln.
Here we go, my frland.
Don't hate me because I'm baautlful,
Gomay.
Just apologlsa and buy me a bear.
Man, you'ra raachlng.
Thls stuff could be a knockoff
or left over from an older cook.
How do you know Halsanbarg's
gaarlng up agaln?
How do I know?
I don't get It.
Thls Is the reason why
you're blowlng off the task force?
Chase down taanars?
I'm gattlng tlrad
of all the sacond-guasslng.
If you're not sufflclantly stlmulatad
by thls lnvastlgatlon...
...do us both a favour
and ask for a transfer.
What Is up wlth you lately?
Startlng bar flghts,
turnlng down El Paso...
...and now thls bullshlt?
Do you need to talk to someone
or what?
Talk to someone?
Talk to who?
I'm not trylng to step on your toes,
bro. Okay?
I'm Just worrlad about you.
That's all.
Appraclata that, bro.
Now take your hand off my shoulder.
Yeah, yeah, the one that was on TV.
Dld any llttla placa
fall on your property?
I'm not looklng for an antlra wlng here,
Mr. Llnkas.
It could be a nut or a bolt.
It could be a bag of peanuts...
...Just so long as It caused you
paln and suffarlng.
Oh, no, no, no. Closed.
Calllng you back.
You had your chance.
I told you to get hlm cooklng agaln.
You blaw It off and now It's too late.
The guy's gona mass manlac on us!
All I wanted was to show you two
your potantlal.
And what do I get In return?
A bone contuslon.
You wanna sea the scar?
l wlsh you two had--
HI, thara.
-How In the hall dld you get Walt to--?
-I made It.
You know the guy
who knows the guy, rlght?
Well, good news ls...
...for a staga-thraa cancer,
the guy's dolng wall physlcally.
Mantally, the guy's a dlsastar.
Ha's gone off the ralls
ovar thls thlng wlth hls wlfa.
My oplnlon, he's not comlng back.
Not on hls own.
Your frlands were at hls placa agaln,
by the way.
Thay draw somathlng on the street
outslda hls housa.
-Tha scytha.
-Anlmals.
-Doas the lawyer know?
-Should he?
If you want thls guy to produce agaln,
why not Just tell hlm?
You stand batwaan hlm
and an axe In the head.
I don't ballava fear
to be an affactlva motlvator.
I want lnvastmant.
For now, I'm slmply Interested
In tlma frama.
Ha wlll llva for the foreseeable future,
yas?
Forasaaabla. Couple years at least,
barrlng acts of God and man wlth axas.
From the lawyer,
I'm supposed to let you know...
...tha Plnkman kld ls looklng to sell.
-I don't work wlth Junklas.
-That's what I thought you'd say.
Probably for the best.
What I hear,
he and Walter ara splltsvllla.
Raally?
That's what Goodman says.
Cats and dogs.
Do the deal.
You have one unheard message.
Agent Schrader, you need to be callIng
me back ASAP.
I've got Texas breathlng down my neck
and I'm not about--
No, I haven't saa Matt slnca my dad
flrad hlm, Ilka, a whlla ago.
Where can I flnd hlm, you thlnk?
-No Idea. Haven't seen hlm.
-I know. You sald that a few tlmas.
Yaah, because I haven't seen hlm.
I don't know what else to say.
-What's your name, darllng?
-Cara.
Whara dld thls come from, Cara?
I don't know.
What Is It? Drugs?
Look, I'm Just gonna come rlght out
and say It.
You're a bad llar, Cara.
Don't get me wrong.
Not the worst I've ever seen.
Onca had a guy try to axplaln the dope
balloon up hls butt on bad Thal food.
Stlll, you're not a very good llar.
-I honestly don't know--
-Stop.
You look Ilka a good kld.
I'm not here to get you In troubla.
But you need to tell me
where thls came from rlght nowI
I never do stuff Ilka thls.
I swear to God.
l trlad It and I hated It,
so I Just gava It to Matt.
-Okay, and who gave It to you?
-Soma guy.
He came In a couple days ago
and wanted to trade It for gas.
Some guy? What's hls nama?
Okay, what--? What dld he look Ilka?
I don't know.
He looked pretty normal.
You know, whlta.
lthlnk hls halr was llghtlsh brown.
He had really blue eyes.
They were really, really blua.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, draamy.
Okay, what else?
Plarclngs, Jawallary, dlstlnctlva
artlclas of clothlng. Come on.
Come on.
Llstan to ma.
It's real Important that l flnd the person
that had these drugs.
So If you can remember
anythlng alsa....
Come on, thlnk.
Come on, now. Come on.
He drove an RV.
Okay, good, good.
What can you remember?
What klnd of RV?
What colour?
Dld you spot a llcansa plata?
I don't know the klnds
and l dldn't sea the llcansa.
But the colour was,
I thlnk, whlta, brownlsh colour.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm not halplng you...
...but, please, don't tell my dad.
Cara.
Please, tell me that
that camera works.
Damn It.
Thasa eggs are good, Mom.
Thanks.
Hey, you know what's walrd?
Dad's wabslta.
It's been three days
slnca the last donatlon.
Yeah, well, people lose lntarast.
So how long are you off for?
A few weeks.
I'll play It by ear.
I probably pushad It, you know,
golng back to work too soon.
Thlnk I can get a rlda today?
Louls has a doctor's appolntmant.
Yaah.
Hay, so, Dad can babyslt now, rlght?
You won't have to take Holly
to work every day.
Somatlma, mayba.
Yaah, we'll see.
What's up?
lthlnk you'll sarlously anJoy, yo.
Walt. No, no. No way.
Hey! Hey!
Hay. What the hall? Thls ls only half.
That's rlght. It's your half.
Yo, where's the other half, bltch?
I mean, the whole thlng was crazy.
Poor bastard. I felt sorry for hlm.
lthlnk he actually thought
we were the cable guys, you know.
Anyway, sorry about
those mlssad calls, chlaf.
I'm changlng provldars.
It won't happen agaln.
Are you golng to El Paso, Hank?
Hall, yas.
Wlth polnty boots and balls on.
Got thls braak In the Halsanbarg casa.
The blue math, you mean?
The taanth?
Yeah, well,
that taanth got thlngs rolllng.
l tracad It to a gas statlon ln Clbola.
That's where I got these.
Tha statlon's closad-clrcult was down--
Surprlsa, surprlsa.
--but I was able to pull some of these
snapshots off an ATM sacurlty camara.
We always thought these guys
mlght ba camper-cooklng.
Flrst off, your typlcal Class c
motor home...
...ls gonna grunt at least 5000 pounds
of lntarlor flxturas.
Appllancas, furnltura, bullt-lns,
5000 pounds at least, okay?
See how hlgh
that suspanslon's rldlng?
No way, no how, thls thlng's carrylng
that klnd of walght.
Thls thlng has been cleared out and
strlppad down to Its tlght-and-curllas.
For what? Blood bank?
Maybe a bookmoblla?
There's no clear vlaw of the plates.
Yeah, well, you can only get
so lucky, rlght?
But there's no front plate. Talls me
It's llkaly Naw Maxlco raglstratlon.
I check wlth DMV.
There are only 29 of these early-'00s
Boundars raglstarad In the state.
-Only 29?
-Yaah.
So I gotta go, you know,
knock on some doors.
They need you In El Paso, Hank.
You bet. I'm Just gonna wrap up
thls Halsanbarg thlng flrst.
-You'ra rafuslng tha asslgnmant.
-l'm not. I'll go.
It's Just I need some more tlma.
You're not haarlng ma,
Agant Schradar.
You'ra out of tlma.
Are you golng to El Paso now,
tonlght?
It's a slmpla yes or no.
No. I can't.
But that's only because
I'm really close to somathlng blg hara.
Better get to It, then.
Thls ls KECA 400,
Albuquerque's news radIo.
KECA news tIme, 10:13.
Our top story thls hour,
Donald Margolls...
...the aIr-traffIc controller crItIcIsed
for hls role In the recent aIr dIsaster...
...In whlch 107 persons dIed...
...was rushed to an area hospltal
early thls mornlng...
...apparently the vlctlm of
a self-Inﬂlcted gunshot wound.
PolIce won't say whether or not--
Your half.
Okay, okay.