[EASTERLING & GILDERSLEEVE'S
'GOOD AND LONELY'
PLAYING OVER RADIO
Gotta lay, whon you flrst brought
har In, I had my doubts.
But your l|ttle darllng':
got nlne llvu.
Rear-whul assembly took
the brunt of the Impact. So, uh...
Yoah.
cv shaft, boots, Jolnts, axlo...
Roplacod all of It.
No way around It.
I wont attarmarkot
on most of the parts here.
You want me to swap In factory parts,
that's "no.
But uslng attormarket's the only way
wo'll kup It under Blue Book
and on the Insurance company's
dlme, okay?
Nothlng beats l'ree.
Uh, swapped out your alr l'llter,
topped off your l'lulds.
Dldn't have to replace
the wlndshleld thls tlme.
I know, rlght?
Oh, and l notlced you had
some sort of gunky bulldup
In the front end here.
Flrst, I had no ldea
what I was looklng at.
Then I remembered
you had me replace
that front fender a few months back
when you ran over that deer.
We went at It wlth the steam hose,
cleaned It up for you.
Hardest part was the palnt.
Fern green.
lnterestlng tlnt.
Anythlng else?
That's It. Zero balance,
llke l sald.
Slgn here,
you're good to go.
People llke to Joke,
but I really, really llke thls car.
She's sturdy as all hell.
I'm bettlng you get
another 200,000 mlles out of her.
[PIER BRANOH'S
'MY GOOD THING'S GONE'
PLAYING OVER RADIO]
Hey, Benny.
What would you glve me for It?
What's the Blue Book, you mean?
No.
I mean, what wlll
you pay me for thls car?
Well, I'm not really looklng for...
A hundred dollars?
Flfty?
Insurance company Just shelled out
1900 for the parts alone.
Then It's a bargaln.
You glve me 50 bucks,
and she's all yours.
You sure about thls?
Sure as shootlng.
I'll check the reglster.
WALT JR.:
Dad?
Fltty bucks? Are you crazy?
[KNIFE PARTY'S 'BONFIRE'
PLAYING]
[ENGINE REVS]
J' Bonflre J'
[TYRES SOREEOH]
[ENGINES REWING]
J' Bonflre J'
J' Bonflre J'J'
[PEOPLE SPEAKING IN GERMAN
OVER PHONE]
Gotta be klddlng me.
MAN [OVER INTERCOM]: Lydla?
[LYDIA SPEAKING IN GERMAN]
[PEOPLE CONTINUE SPEAKING
IN GERMAN OVER PHONE]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
0h, Chrlst.
[VIBRATING CONTINUES]
I'm at work rlght now.
MIKE:
Yeah, lknow.
ThIs Is a heads-up. You got vIsItors.
Vlsltors? What...? You mean today?
I mean 30 seconds.
Come In.
Ms. Rodarte-Quayle?
Agent Hank Schrader,
Agent Steve Gomez, DEA.
We met brlel'ly In Albuquerque.
Uh, yes, we dld.
What can I do for you?
There. The I'oreman.
Navy pants, powder-blue shlrt.
HANK:
Hey, buddy.
[SPEAKING INDISTINOTLY]
[PEOPLE SPEAKING IN GERMAN
OVER PHONE]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
MIKE: Yeah?
They got Ron.
Okay.
Not okay, Mlke.
Not okay. The...
The look he Just gave me was
the very antlthesls oI' 'okay,' okay?
Breathe, LydIa.
No one's talklng to the poIIce.
IJust had llke 14 DEA agents
barge Into my ofï¬ce,
screamlng and yelllng at me
and they were swarmlng
all over the warehouse, okay?
The warehouse.
Besldes, Ron was my guy. Remember?
I don't have a guy anymore.
Ron I'lxed securlty, pulled the barrels,
drove the truck.
You can't expect me to do that stuff.
I mean, let's be reallstlc.
Mlke, thls Is crazy.
I'll send a new guy.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
[HOLLY COOING]
WALT JR.:
You're crazy.
My car almost has 500 horsepower.
It would totally smoke--
WALT: Horsepower Isn't everythlng.
Don't you know that?
You have to factor In drag
and torque and suspenslon
and welght ol' the car.
One more factor
that you're not thlnklng about:
The experlence ol' the drlver.
I totally got you there.
Please. Please. You drlve llke a geezer.
I got you.
Really?
I drlve llke a gee--
Tell me, can a geezer do donuts?
I don't thlnk so.
And, yes, I dld.
Serlously?
Yes, serlously.
And It you show me
Just a modlcum of respect,
maybe I'll teach you.
Yeah? Yes?
No. No, I won't. I take that back.
Yes. Yes. No. You're saylng yes.
Just a Joke. I'm Just...
No! No, no.
That was klddlng.
We dldn't shake on It. No.
Yes. Yes.
We are now.
That doesn't count!
WALT:
I know you don't approve.
But mlne,
we'll call a blrthday present
to myself.
And Junlor's...
People wlll Just chalk that up
as me belng a softy.
And besldes,
l dldn't actually buy
elther one.
They're both leases.
So It all flts our story.
Okay?
Oh.
[DRAWER OPENS THEN CLOSES]
We can afford It now.
You're back at It?
Well, yeah.
We have to make up
that 600,000 we lost.
What do you thlnk
about boardlng school?
Boardlng school?
For who? For Junlor?
Yeah. There's thls place
In northern Arlzona
and It's supposed to be
one of the top 10 In the country.
He's a year away from college.
Why on earth would we do that?
I... I don't know. IJust...
Just thlnklng about the klds.
Hmm. Holly too?
Where are we sendlng
our 0-month-old?
Peace Corps?
No. IJust...
A new envlronment
mlght be good for them.
What does that mean?
What's wrong wlth thelr envlronment?
Skyler.
Nothlng.
Hey.
Llsten, I know these last few weeks
have been rough.
The threat to Hank
and thls whole thlng wlth Beneke.
But there's absolutely nothlng
for you to be afrald of anymore,
okay?
I mean, clear salllng from here on out.
I promlse.
You know, I want us to try and start
looklng forward to thlngs agaln.
Speaklng of whlch, my blrthday. Hm?
I don't know--
I don't know what you have planned,
and wlth everythlng
that's been golng on lately
I'd understand It you haven't
even glven It a thought.
But I thlnk
For all of us.
You know, a blrthday party.
What do you thlnk? Hm?
Yeah?
Okay.
And maybe, If I may be so bold,
chocolate cake wlth chocolate lclng?
Hm?
Llfe Is good, Skyler.
WALT: Mmm. Thank you.
Hey, Mom, you forgot somethlng.
Hm?
Dad's bacon.
That's okay.
I can do It.
No. Mom has to.
[HOLLY COOING]
Well, It Is sort of a tradltlon.
Watch thls, Holly.
Watch what she does
wlth bacon.
Watch. Watch thls.
What Is she dolng?
That's a pretty small '1.'
Klnd of Is.
Just a llttle.
WALT:
Ah, now you're talklng.
No. No.
WALT: Good move.
WALT JR.: No.
No, no, no. It's good.
Very good. Famlly teamwork.
Maklng sacrlflces.
Very Important.
WALT JR.: Happy blrthday, Dad.
WALT: Thank you, buddy.
You want some?
HANK:
Guy's some plece of work, Isn't he?
Slx feet under and half a face,
he's stlll screwlng wlth us.
So, what's next?
I don't know.
Thls Madrlgal thlng seems hlnky,
though, you know?
We got Burgermelster Melsterburger
over here In Germany,
and 5000 mlles away,
you got thls guy.
There's gotta be someone
In the mlddle, you know?
Someone we're mlsslng.
What about that
Lydla what's-her-name?
Lady Banjo Eyes
at the warehouse?
In thls world? No way.
Too uptlght. Too together.
Maybe.
She was wearlng mlsmatched shoes.
How together can she be?
Gentlemen, how goes It wlth Frlng?
You know, Just worklng through
the grlef.
How soon before
you submlt a flnal?
Well, we've been klcklng around
some Ideas.
Had you asked
a couple of weeks ago,
I'd have sald
thls was a mop-up Job, but...
But?
HANK:
None of Frlng's crew Is talklng to us.
I mean, not a peep,
no matter how hard we squeeze.
Makes It llkely there's somebody
keeplng them In llne.
Our money Is on thls guy,
Mlchael Ehrmantraut.
He's Frlng's head
of 'corporate securlty.'
He's a deflnlte hard case.
HANK: Now, we're gonna stay on hlm.
We're puttlng together
a survelllance team
as we speak. Okay?
The other thlng ls...
Thls may be unrelated,
but the blue meth Is maklng
a blt of a comeback. Tell hlm, Gomey.
Yeah. Some small amounts
on the street-slde pulls.
Lab's telllng us It's the same stuff.
I mean, It could be
old Inventory leaklng out,
or It could be somebody's rebootlng,
uslng Frlng's former cooks
to set up a new operatlon.
I thought we had Frlng's cooks.
The unsubs In the lab flre.
Thought maybe one of them
was your Helsenberg.
Yeah. Maybe. I don't know.
lee l sald,
there's stlll a lot of questlons.
Agent Gomez,
could you glve us a moment?
Yeah.
Hank, I gotta say,
your work here has been stellar.
Really flrst-rate.
Thank you, slr.
So much so that I'm wonderlng
If It's tlme you made a change.
You know I have to
get back to El Paso.
Thls offlce needs an ASAc,
and I'm thlnklng we should be
promotlng from wlthln.
If you were to put In
an appllcatlon,
and I recommend that you do,
you wlll get the Job.
l have no doubt thls D.O. would be
well served wlth you at the helm.
Wow. That's, uh...
I'm not sure what to say.
It's a blg step up.
It's not wlthout Its headaches.
The polltlcs may take
some gettlng used to.
so you'd need to reasslgn
all your day-to-days, Frlng Included.
Much as I hate loslng
a good fleld man,
that's the Job,
and you need to be okay wlth It.
What do you say, Hank?
You want It?
Well, conslderlng my wlfe
would murder me If I sald 'no'...
Yeah. I want It.
Congratulatlons.
Thank you.
Can you flnlsh up for me?
It's... It's my blrthday.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
I probably have a blrthday party
waltlng for me, you know, so...
Yeah. Cool. Yeah, no problem.
Hey, happy blrthday.
Thanks. Thanks.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV]
WALT JR.: Hey, Dad.
Hey.
Where's your mom?
Kltchen.
WALT:
Hey.
SKYLER:
Oh, hey.
WALT:
So, what's the plan?
SKYLER:
Um, Hank and Marle are on thelr way.
Roast chlcken
and potatoes for dlnner,
rocky road for dessert,
and chocolate cake,
as requested.
[MICROWAVE BEEPS
THEN WHIRRS]
What's up?
Me?
Nothlng.
Thought you'd be more Jazzed
about the new Job.
No. What...? No. I am.
Baby, I'm so proud of you.
Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Sorry, sorry.
I belleve you. Just don't klll us here.
Marle, you've been moplng around
the last few days.
Marle?
What's up?
Marle, come on.
I'm sorry. l--
I made a promlse to someone.
To who?
Who?
Your brother-ln-law.
Are you gonna glve me a hlnt at least?
It Involves Infldellty. That's all I'll say.
Oh, shlt. I knew It.
Knew what? What dld you...?
What dld you know?
Well, I mean, I dldn't know It, but I've
been, you know, saylng It forever.
Walt's second cell phone,
you know?
Sorry, babe, but I was
way ahead of you on thls one.
Way ahead of me.
Well, It wasn't Walt.
Skyler?
No way.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Hey.
Hey! There she ls.
HeyI HII
HeyI
HANK: Hey, buddy.
Hey, pal.
Welcome. Welcome. Come on In.
MARIE:
Happy blrthday. HI.
I'm In the centre lane
golng about 60.
I had no cholce but to Just
tear butt out of there.
Just 'bwaaaI' So sweet.
nghway patrol's
gonna be sweet on It too.
Gonna get thelr tlcket quota
In a month.
You'll help me out, rlght, Uncle Hank,
now that you run the DEA?
Oh, yeah. For my spolled-brat,
car-wash-mllllonalre nephew?
Sure. I'll make sure you get
a cell wlth a vlew.
All rlght.
Well, I'm out of here.
Okay.
Happy blrthday.
Thank you, buddy.
Congratulatlons agaln,
Uncle Hank.
Thanks.
I'll see y'all later.
HANK: All rlght.
Bye. Be safe.
HANK: Have fun.
Drlve safely, okay?
WALT JR.: I do.
HANK: Slow down.
WALT JR.: Never.
A hell of a couple
cars there, Walt.
Honey, for my next blrthday,
I'm gonna take a page here from Walt
and buy myself
a Jet plane.
HANK:
Ah. Maybe I overdld It a llttle.
But wlth these new lease rates...
I mean, they're mlghty attractlve.
Yeah.
Great dlnner, Skyler.
Those were some bad-ass
whlpped potatoes, I'll tell you.
You have to tell me
how you get all the lumps out.
How do you do that?
A potato rlcer.
A rlcer? You don't hand-mash?
HANK: Well, uh...
Boy, It has...
It has been qulte a year, huh?
Do you know that
It's almost exactly a year ago
that I got my dlagnosls?
Jesus. Yeah, rlght?
Yeah.
It seems llke longer, doesn't It?
Yeah. No. It's, uh...
One year ago tomorrow.
The day after my 50th.
Honestly never thought
I'd make It thls far.
Wlth the cancer and surgery
and Hank belng shot...
It Just...
So many dark days.
Well...
There's Marle's talklng plllow.
Remember that?
It was effectlve.
Boy, I dld not want
to get any treatment.
lthlnk l was too scared
or too angry or...
I don't know. IJust wanted to qult.
But you guys...
You got me through It somehow.
Kept me golng.
And that happened agaln
and agaln and agaln.
I mean, there were tlmes
when l was sure I was done for.
But then someone or somethlng
would come through for me.
God. And Skyler, I can't--
Honey, remember
that flrst week of chemotherapy?
That nlght on the bathroom floor?
What you sald to me?
It was rough golng at flrst.
[J'J'J']
But Skyler...
She was rlght there,
of course,
puttlng wet washcloths
on my forehead.
And she's slnglng to me.
And thls would go on and on,
day after day.
And I remember I was lylng
on the floor of the bathroom
because the tlle felt
nlce and cool, you know?
And my head
was In Skyler's lap
and l was Just asklng her
If thls could all be over.
It was too hard. It was...
IJust wanted It stopped.
Skyler, Isn't that freezlng?
HANK:
Whoa. Hey-o. Pool party.
MARIE:
What are you dolng, Skyler?
What Is she dolng? Walt?
HANK:
Hey, Sky, maybe
It's tlme to get out now.
What do you thlnk?
Skyler, Hank asked you
a questlon.
You need to get out...
SkylerI
She's gonna come up, rlght?
She has to.
SkylerI
[WATER SPLASHES]
LYDIA:
Oh, my God.
Wha...? Okay.
Okay. It's gotta be...
Okay.
Come on!
How am I supposed to--?
[CAMERA POWERS DOWN]
Hey.
Walt.
Walt, walt. Who are you?
I'm the-- I'm the guy.
So where's the...?
Who sent you?
Who sent me?
Who do you thlnk?
No. I'm asklng you.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
And thls Mlke person...
What's hls last name?
Lady, IJust got off a plane
from New Mexlco
and I got a 900-mlle drlve back.
That's 14 hours If I don't stop.
So the sooner we do thls,
the sooner It's done.
Uh... Ehrmantraut.
Okay? Satlsfled?
LYDIA:
Sorry, but I'm not gonna
apologlse for belng careful.
Wlth all that's been happenlng,
for all I knew,
you were one
of those undercover people.
So, yeah,
I'll take paranold any day
over gettlng gang-raped
by prlson guards.
JESSE:
Uh-huh. No doubt.
So where's the--?
LYDIA:
Up there. Number 22356.
That's the one I erased from
the Inventory, so It has to be that one.
Can you reach It?
Yeah, wlth, llke, a forkllft.
You got one?
Walt, walt, waItI StopI
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What?
Please tell me
that's not what I thlnk It Is.
Has anythlng llke thls
ever happened before?
No. No, of course not.
No, no. IJust...
She and l have been
havlng some Issues.
Yeah, yeah. I mlght've heard
a llttle blt about that.
I mean, hey, look,
Marle dldn't go Into detall.
She Just, you know, sald that,
you know, you guys were
havlng some Issues.
So, what's the next move?
Mlght be good to have her talk
to someone.
Oh... I agree.
Yeah.
I'm gonna get on that flrst thlng.
There's Marle's guy, Dave.
She seems really happy wlth hlm.
Not that Marle's an advertlsement
for advanced mental health
or anythlng.
You know...
IJust had no Idea
she was taklng It thls hard.
Some blrthday, huh?
[noon CLOSES]
She's gonna try
and get some sleep.
Okay.
What was that?
I don't know.
I mean, was she trylng...?
No, not In a swlmmlng pool. No.
Wlth all of us there?
No, I don't thlnk so.
But we both, um,
thlnk that
she should talk to someone.
I'm gonna get you Dave's number.
Okay.
Llsten, Walt, I...
I can't help but sense
that there may be some Issues
between you and Skyler.
None of our buslness, of course.
And, Hank,
I don't know If you've
plcked up on any of the--
He knows. He knows I know.
These thlngs happen In a marrlage,
but It Isn't unflxable.
lthlnk what would be great Is It
you two had some space
to work through thls stuff.
And keep an open mlnd here.
What If we took the klds
for a whlle?
Took the klds?
Absolutely.
We'll look after them for
a day or two, or however long,
and leave you and Skyler
to look after each other.
That's very generous of you,
Marle,
but I... IJust don't see
how that's a solutlon.
And, I mean--
Besldes, Junlor and Holly,
that's a lot of work.
No, It Isn't.
Junlor's Independent
and my nlece Is only the easlest,
most dellclous baby
that was ever born.
It'll be fun, rlght?
Yeah. Yeah. No, yeah. Yeah.
Absolutely. Yeah.
It's a good Idea.
Well, lthlnk
It's a great Idea.
Just the thlng
for both of you.
Marle, thls Idea...
Was It yours?
Actually, It was Skyler's.
Uh-huh.
MARIE:
She really needs thls, Walt.
Yep.
WALT:
I gave Marle bottles.
They'll stop and plck up dlapers
along the way.
I spoke wlth Junlor on the phone,
and after much dlscusslon,
he agreed to swlng by tomorrow,
plck up some clothes. And so volla,
the klds are out of thls envlronment.
What a colncldence.
I know you're awake.
What was that about?
Can you explaln It?
I don't want the chlldren
here anymore.
It Isn't safe.
Skyler, we have talked
about thls repeatedly.
It has never been more safe.
'Never been'?
A couple weeks ago,
a man was comlng to thls house
to klll us,
to murder your entlre famlly.
You were In the crawlspace,
screamlng.
And I dealt wlth hlm. It's over.
It Is not.
You're rlght back
In the meth buslness agaln.
Thls Is dlfferent.
Now I'm runnlng thlngs.
So walt. Now that you're In charge,
It's what? It's gonna be
smooth salllng from here on out?
I don't see why not.
I keep the work at work, Skyler,
and nothlng wlll ever
Impact you or the klds.
You don't know that.
You can't make that promlse, Walt.
I can promlse you
that Gus Frlng Is dead.
And he was the threat.
He was the danger.
I thought you were the danger.
Is that what your pool stunt
was about?
Trylng to protect
my chlldren from me?
Not Just you.
There's blood on my hands too.
What blood? Beneke?
He's In the hospltal
because of me.
No.
Because of what I dld.
Skyler, you can't beat yourself up
over thls thlng.
Please. You dldn't set out
to hurt anybody.
You made a mlstake,
and thlngs got out of control,
but you dld what you had to
to protect your famlly. I'm sorry.
That doesn't make you a bad person,
It makes you a human belng.
Stop It, Walt. Just stop.
I don't need to hear any
of your bullshlt ratlonales.
I'm In It now.
I'm compromlsed. But I won't--
lwlll not have my chlldren
llvlng In a house
where deallng drugs
and hurtlng people
and kllllng people
Is shrugged off as 'shlt happens.'
We're back at It? Flne.
But the klds stay away,
and that's that.
'That's that'? That's what?
I got them out of thls house.
To a sleepover
at thelr aunt and uncle's?
They spend a day or two,
Junlor stays up late watchlng movles,
and then what happens?
We'll see.
No, I'll tell you what happens.
They come home to thls house,
to thelr parents who love them.
No. l wlll not let
our buslness endanger them.
How many tlmes
do I have to say
that they are not In--?
I sald no.
I swear to God,
I won't have them back here.
What are you gonna do to stop It?
Whatever It takes.
Everythlng In my power.
lee what? I mean, speclflcally.
What Is your next move?
My next move Is
maybe I hurt myself.
Make It clear we need more tlme.
Let Hank and Marle see
we're stlll struggllng.
No, more llke
you're stlll struggllng.
So maybe next tlme,
l have you commltted.
Put you In some lnpatlent faclllty
whlle I take care of the klds myself.
Is that what you want?
So then maybe I show up
wlth brulses on my neck,
glve myself a black eye,
say that you beat me
when you found out about my lover.
So you want to Involve Ted?
Oh, well, that'll be fun,
brlnglng the pollce
up to speed on all of that.
But not as much fun as
telllng your 16-year-old son
that hls father Is a wlfe-beater.
Also not a very good plan.
What else you got?
I could send Junlor away to school.
Oh. Now here's the conversatlon:
'So, honey, I know you've only got
one year left In hlgh school,
but I would love It
If you'd drop everythlng,
leave all your frlends behlnd,
and go to boardlng school In Arlzona.'
You have any other Ideas?
Because I'm not hearlng
a solutlon to your problem.
How are you golng to save our klds
from thls terrlble envlronment?
I don't...
What are you gonna do?
Run off to France? You gonna
close the curtalns, change the locks?
Thls Is a Joke.
Come on, Skyler.
You wanna take me on?
You wanna take away my chlldren?
What's the plan?
I don't know!
Thls Is the best
I could come up wlth, okay?
lwlll count every mlnute
that the klds are away from here,
away from you, as a vlctory.
But you're rlght.
It's a bad plan.
I don't have any
of your maglc, Walt.
I don't know what to do.
I'm a coward.
l-- I can't go to the pollce.
I can't stop launderlng your money.
I can't keep you out of thls house.
I can't even keep you out of my bed.
All I can do Is walt.
That's It.
That's the only good optlon.
Hold on, blde my tlme,
and walt.
Walt for what?
What are you waltlng for?
For the cancer to come back.
[J'J'J']
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
Yeah?
Okay. Okay.
Just relax. I'm comlng.
JESSE:
Look at that. You tell me
what that looks llke.
If the DEA's tracklng her barrels,
there goes our precursor connectlon.
That's done.
And I'm telllng you, these days,
chances of gettlng a new
methylamlne hookup Is rare, man.
It's llke Blgfoot. lee unlcorn-rare.
Kld, It's Just...
You're glvlng me heartburn here.
GPS on the bottom
of the barrel.
Why dldn't they put It lnslde
where nobody would see It?
Look, It's lnslde, It gets wet.
They made these thlngs
to put under cars.
It can get wet.
Huh. Even by cop standards,
thls Is sloppy.
And the other barrels,
they have trackers
on the outslde too?
I don't know. Probably.
You dldn't check
any of the other barrels?
No. But that's the only one
we could've taken, accordlng to her.
Once we spotted It, she freaked out,
I put the barrel back, and we F.O.'d.
Let me ask you somethlng.
The person who spotted thls,
was It you or was It her?
Lydla. She saw It flrst.
Okay.
Walt, walt, walt. What?
Lydla planted thls thlng,
not the cops.
She's thlnklng If she makes It look
llke her Inventory's belng watched
that we'll leave her alone
and take our buslness elsewhere.
And she's rlght.
We wlll be taklng our buslness
elsewhere,
rlght after I leave her alone
In a dltch.
But walt, hey, If the DEA's
not tracklng her stuff,
that's a good thlng, rlght?
I mean, all we gotta do Is tell her
to cut the crap
and keep the methylamlne comlng.
You don't know thls woman
llke I do.
I had a chance to deal wlth thls before,
and I gave her a pass.
That's what I get for belng sexlst.
Now, If you'll excuse me...
Mlke, you can't Just--
Look, that's our precursor.
We need her.
Kld, If we have to ramp down
for a whlle, so be It.
It beats worklng wlth a lunatlc
who's gonna get us arrested or kllled.
Look, she dldn't seem
crazy to me, you know?
She Just seemed, llke, uptlght.
And now you're belng sexlst.
Trust me, thls woman deserves to dle
as much as any man I've ever met.
WaltI
Just walt.
What If thls really was the cops,
you know?
And what If you're wrong about her?
I'm not wrong.
But what If you are?
Jesse, your mlsglvlngs
have been duly noted.
Now move away from me.
No. Thls Is a votlng thlng.
I don't thlnk so.
I vote It's a votlng thlng.
Mr. Whlte, welgh In here, would you?
What do you thlnk?
Mr. Whlte?
The methylamlne keeps flowlng,
no matter what.
We are not ramplng down.
We're Just gettlng started.
Nothlng stops thls traln.
Nothlng.
Hey, yo, Mr. Whlte.
Hold up.
Hey, IJust wanted to say
I llked your Idea.
You know, It's pretty, uh...
lthlnk It's the way to go.
Oh, hey.
You sald It was
your blrthday, so...
I left the recelpt In the box
In case you wanna exchange It.
Anyway, hey, happy blrthday.
I stopped by Hank and Marle's.
Junlor Is stlll asklng,
'What Is golng on?'
Nonstop, very Inslstently.
But everythlng's okay.
They're watchlng Ratatoullle.
It's very sweet.
How are you?
There's gonna be some more
money comlng In soon.
Is that okay?
Flne.
You comlng to bed?
I wanna show you
somethlng.
See that watch?
It was a blrthday present.
The person who gave me
thls present
wanted me dead too.
Not that long ago,
he polnted a gun
rlght between my eyes, rlght here,
and he threatened to klll me.
He changed hls mlnd
about me, Skyler,
and so wlll you.
[WATCH TICKING]
[TICKING CONTINUES]
[J'J'J']