CATELYN: Are you
sure about this?
No.
It's dangerous.
Ifwe take Tywin's castle from him,
the lords of Westeros
will realise he's not invincible.
Take his home, take his gold, take his power.
Why are you telling me?
You begged me not to send Theon
to negotiate with his father,
and I ignored your advice.
Now Winterfell is burnt to the ground,
the North is overrun
with ironborn, and Bran and Rickon are gone.
So, Casterly Rock...
I'm asking your advice.
We have enough men?
If Walder Frey cooperates.
lf reinforcements arrive from King's
Landing before we take the castle,
we'll be caught between
Tywin's army and the sea.
We'll lose the war and die the way Father died.
Orworse.
Show them how it feels to lose what they love.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(SOLDIERS URGING HORSES)
WALDER: My honoured guests,
be welcome within my walls and at my table.
I extend to you my hospitality
and protection in the light ofthe Seven.
We thank you for your hospitality, my lord.
l have come to make my apologies, my
lord, and to beg your forgiveness.
Don't beg my forgiveness, Your Grace.
It wasn't me you spurned. It was my girls.
One ofthem was supposed to be queen.
Now none ofthem are.
This is Arwyn, my daughter.
My daughter Walda, my daughter Derwa,
my daughterWaldra.
My eldest granddaughters Ginia and Neila.
Serra and Sarra, granddaughters, twins.
You could have had either.
Could have had both, for all I care.
My granddaughter Marianne.
My granddaughter Freya.
My granddaughter...
Wertha.
Waldra.
Waldina.
l'm Merry.
Fine.
And here's my youngest daughter Shirei,
though she hasn't bled yet.
Clearly you don't have
the patience for all that.
My ladies.
All men should
keep theirword, kings most of all.
lwas pledged to
marry one of you and I broke that vow.
The fault is not with you.
Any man would be lucky
to have any one of you.
ldid what I did
not to slight you, but because I loved another.
I know these words cannot set right
the wrong I have done to you and your house.
I beg your forgiveness
and pledge to do all I can to make
amends so the Freys ofthe Crossing
and the Starks ofWinterfell
may once again be friends.
WALDER: Very good.
There she is.
Come closer. Let me have a look at you.
Still can't see you.
Old eyes.
Love.
That's what the Starks ofWinterfell call it, eh?
(LAUGHS)
Very honourable. I call it a pretty face.
Mmm.
Very pretty.
Prettier than this lot, that's for sure.
Very shapely as well.
Oh, you try to hide her underthat dress.
lfyou wanted to hide her,
you shouldn't have
brought her here in the first place.
I can always see
what's going on beneath a dress.
Been at this a long time.
I bet when you take that dress off,
everything stays right where it is.
Doesn't drop an inch.
Your king says he betrayed me for love.
I say he betrayed
me for firm tits and a tight fit.
And I can respect that.
When I was your age, I'd have broken 50 oaths
to get into that without a second thought.
Well, I've enough room in the hall foryou lot.
We'll set up tents outside
with food and ale for the rest of your men.
Thank you, my lord.
Well, let's get ready.
The wine will flow red
and the music will play loud
and we'll put this mess behind us.
(METALLIC CLANGING)
Where?
There.
There. It's a back gate.
My men use it
when they visit Yunkai's bed slaves.
Your men, but not you?
DAARIO: l have no interest in slaves.
A man cannot make love to property.
This is where we enter
the city. Very few guards. They know me.
They let me inside...
We're not gonna
sneak an army through a back gate.
DAARIO: I kill the guards.
I take your two best men
and lead them
through the back streets, which I know well,
and open the front gates.
Then comes the army.
Once the walls are breached,
the city will fall in hours.
Or perhaps you'll lead Grey
Worm and me to the slaughter,
cutting the head off our army.
The masters onunkai will pay you your fee
and you won't have to split it three ways
'cause you've already
slaughtered your partners.
You have a very suspicious mind.
In my experience,
only dishonest people think this way.
(SIGHS) You command the Unsullied.
-What do you think?
-(DAENERYS SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
You are a leader now.
Do you trust him?
(IN VALYRIAN)
ltrust him.
You leave tonight.
Very good. We'll prepare.
Ser Jorah.
You can use an extra sword.
You're the Queensguard,
Ser Barristan. Your place is by the Queen.
lfwe are truly her loyal servants,
we'll do whatever needs to be done,
no matter the cost, no matter our pride.
(WIND HOWLING)
SAMWELL: We're west of Castle Black,
but the Nightfort's closest to us.
It was the first castle on the Wall.
The Watch abandoned it
during the reign of King Jaehaerys l.
Too big. Impossible to maintain.
Other than Castle Black itself,
the Nightfort's the perfect castle for us.
It's got a secret sally port,
the Black Gate, as old as the Wall itself.
No one's used it in centuries, most likely.
It leads through
the Wall right down into the Nightfort,
if one knows how to find it,
which, itjust so happens, (CHUCKLES) I do.
How do you know all that?
| read about it in a very old book.
You know all that
from staring at marks on paper?
Yes.
You're like a wizard.
(GURGLES)
Our father used to tell us
that no wildling ever looked
upon the Wall and lived.
Here we are.
Alive.
(DONKEY BRAYING)
Remember what happens to children who run.
I'm your father and I'll do the talking.
The roads have gone right to hell.
Cracked three spokes this morning.
Need a hand?
Need about eight hands.
Oh!
Got to get this
salt pork to the Twins in time for the wedding.
Manythanks.
(GROANS)
Don't! Don't kill him.
Dead rats don't squeak.
You're so dangerous, aren't you?
Saying scary things to little girls.
Killing little
boys and old people. A real hard man you are.
More than anyone you know.
You're wrong.
I know a killer.
-A real killer.
-That so?
You'd be like a kitten
to him. He'd kill you with his little finger.
That him?
-No.
-Good.
(GRUNTS) Don't kill him.
Please.
Please don't.
You're very kind. Someday it'll get you killed.
(MAN GROANlNG)
(GRUNTS)
Where are we?
The Gift, lthink.
Brandon the Builder gave all this land
south ofthe Wall to the Night's Watch
for their sustenance and support.
Maester Luwin taught me that.
Doesn't seem to be supporting
anyone at the moment.
It's good land, and there's no war up here.
Why leave?
Wildlings.
Sorry.
But they come over
the Wall and raid, steal, carry off women.
Old Nan said they turn your skull into a cup
and make you drink your own blood from it.
That's what Old Nan said.
There's a storm coming.
I don't see any.
(THUNDER RUMBLlNG)
It's as good a place to shelter as any.
We can drink some blood while we wait.
I don't need much.
(CAWING)
(PANTlNG) Only one old man
and eight good horses.
What's one old man doing with eight horses?
He breeds them for the Watch.
How's he keep folks from stealing them?
The Watch protects him.
ORELL: Not today, they don't.
He's selling horses,
he's got some gold in there.
TORMUND: And proper steel.
ORELL: Let's carve him up.
We just take the horses and go.
The old man's no threat.
I keep telling you.
He's an old man.
A spear through the heart's a better way to die
than coughing up your
last with no one but your horses to hear.
The Watch might send
a few men looking for a horse thief.
They'll send a lot more
to hunt down murderers.
I hope so.
Killing crows in their castle is tough.
Killing them out
here in the open, that's what we do.
Spread out. Surround the hut and move in.
(PANTlNG)
(GRUNTS)
(SNUFFLES)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Ygritte!
TORMUND: Clear the barn!
No one's going to believe
you're a hog farmer ifyou eat them all.
Best part ofthe animal.
Don't worry. They're still there.
I know they're still there.
You check every five minutes
like you're afraid they're gonna move.
I'm not afraid.
Of course you are.
You're almost there
and you're afraid you won't make it.
The closer you get, the worse the fear gets.
No point in trying to hide behind that face.
I know fear when | see it.
Seen it a lot.
I knew fear when I saw it in you.
You're afraid of fire.
When Beric's sword went up in flames,
you looked like a scared little girl.
And I know why, too.
I heard what your brother did to you.
Pressed your face to
the fire like you're a nice juicy mutton chop.
That give you some ideas?
Might do.
Go ahead, then. You might get away.
Might even make it there on your own.
They're just over the river.
The closest you've been to family
since llyn Payne snipped your daddy's neck.
Someday I'll put a sword through
your eye and out the back of your skull.
(THUNDER RUMBLlNG)
How are we going to get past the Wall?
My uncle said it's 700 feet high.
(THUNDER RUMBLlNG)
How did you get past it?
Got in a boat and rowed past the Bay of Seals.
It would take us two months
to get to the Bay of Seals.
Some climb straight up the ice.
Even Hodor's not strong enough to
climb the Wall with me on his back.
HODOR: Hodor.
Nineteen castles guard the Wall.
Only three are still manned.
-(THUNDER RUMBLES)
-Hodor!
One ofthose abandoned
fortresses will give us a way through.
My uncle said the gates were sealed with ice
and stone when the castles were deserted.
Well, we'll have to open them up again.
-(HORSE NEIGHING)
-OLD MAN: Whoa, whoa, whoa!
MEERA: There's a rider out there.
-Just one?
-(THUNDER RUMBLES)
-MEERA: There's more.
-Hodor!
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(WHIMPERING)
It's just thunder, sweet giant.
Hodor.
OLD MAN: lyield.
-I yield.
-Wild|ings.
(MEN SHOUTlNG)
Where's Shaggydog and Summer?
Hunting.
-(THUNDER RUMBLlNG)
-Hodor!
-Shh. Quiet, Hodor.
Make him shut up. lfthey hear us...
Hush, Hodor. No... No more Hodoring.
Hodor! (GRUNTS)
-Hodor!
-Hodor, calm down.
-You need to keep quiet.
-They're gonna hear us.
BRANDON: Hodor, be quiet.
-Hodor!
-Hodor, calm down.
Hodor! Hodor!
Hodor, be quiet!
What did you do?
Nothing.
I don't know.
(HORSE GROANlNG)
What's that?
That's a horse dying.
(EXHALES)
MAN 1: Bring them over here.
MAN 2: That was
the last ofthem. The rest are dead.
ORELL: I heard shouting up there.
Thunder.
lknowthe difference
between shouting and thunder.
Maybe it's ghosts. (LAUGHS)
(RAVEN CAWlNG)
That won't help you, grandpa.
Where you riding?
Doesn't matter now, does it?
No, it doesn't matter now.
Cut his throat,
or he'll tell the crows we're here.
You understand.
Let me stand at least.
Let me go with a bit of dignity.
(GRUNTS)
Make the crow kill him.
You're one of us now. Prove it.
JOJEN: The wolves are out there.
I can't do it by choice.
I don't know how.
It happens in my dreams.
You're a warg, Bran. It's in your blood.
I can't.
Youjustdid, with him.
A wolf is nothing compared to that.
(WHIMPERS)
(THUNDER RUMBLlNG)
She looks sharp.
(PRAYlNG lNDlSTlNCTLY)
Do it.
I told you. He's still one ofthem.
Go on, boy.
Go on!
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
He's a crow. He'll always be a crow.
And here's his crow wife guarding him.
He'll stab us in the back first chance he gets.
-Kill him.
-(GRUNTS)
(JON YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTlNG)
(SCREAMS)
(YGRlTTE YELLlNG)
He's one ofthem.
No!
Do you hear me? Ahh!
(YGRlTTE PANTlNG)
You're not gonna die for one ofthem.
Do it.
They'll find us ifyou don't.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SNARLS)
(GRUNTlNG)
(SCREAMS)
(YELLS)
(BONES CRUNCHING)
(GROANlNG)
You were right the whole time.
-(STABB|NG)
-(GASPS)
(CAWlNG)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTlNG)
(URGES HORSE)
(PANTlNG)
DAARIO: When you hear
a songbird's whistle, you come.
(GUARD SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Daario Naharis.
(DAARIO WHISTLES)
DAARIO: That one was quick.
-There may be others.
-I doubt it.
The Yunkish prefer
to let their slaves do their fighting for them.
(SOLDIERS SHOUTlNG)
(ALL GRUNTlNG)
(GROANlNG)
JORAH: That's what you call a few guards?
(SIGHS)
(ALL SHOUTlNG)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTlNG)
Come on! What do you got, huh?
(ALL CHEERING)
(SIGHS)
Lord Edmure,
I hope I'm not a disappointment to you.
(HUFFS)
You're a delight to me, my lady.
You may now cloak
the bride and bring her underyour protection.
In the sight ofthe Seven,
I hereby seal these two souls,
binding them as one for eternity.
Look upon each other and say the words.
-Father, Smith...
-...Warrior, Mother...
-...Maiden, Crone, Stranger.
-I am hers...
-I am his...
-...and she is mine...
-...and he is mine...
BOTH: ...from this day
until the end of my days.
MEERA: Is that safe?
OSHA: They're long gone.
BRANDON: You were right.
I can get inside
Summer's mind whenever I want.
Of course you can.
North ofthe Wall there are wildlings
who can control all sorts of animals.
But you did a lot more than that.
You got inside Hodor's mind.
They can't do that north ofthe Wall?
No one can do that. Anywhere.
When I was looking through Summer's eyes,
-I saw Jon.
-Where?
He was with the wildlings.
Theytried to kill him, but he got away.
OSHA: He'll be heading back
to Castle Black, then.
That's where we should go.
For all we know,
Castle Black's already under attack.
If this many wildlings got through...
I already told you.
I'm not going north ofthe Wall.
Everything Jojen told me is true.
You saw what I did to Hodor.
l have to find the three-eyed raven.
Listen to me, little lord.
Don't worry.
I'm not asking you to come with me.
It won't be safe for Rickon.
Me? I'm coming with you.
No.
You and Osha and Shaggydog
head for the Last Hearth.
The Umbers are our bannermen.
They'll protect you.
I'm coming with you.
I'm your brother. I have to protect you.
Right now l have to protect you.
Robb's at war and I'm going beyond the Wall.
If something happens to us,
you're the heir to Winterfell.
Would you know how to find the Last Hearth?
You Southerners
build your big castles and you never move.
You're easy to find.
We're not Southerners.
And I don't want to leave you.
OSHA: Shh!
Come here, little soldier.
You and me,
we're gonna have some adventures.
You don't have to do any ofthis.
(SOBBING)
Your family took me in
and was good to me without cause.
(OSHA SHUSHING)
We'll be fine, you and me.
The Umbers are great warriors. Even I
heard about them growing up.
They'll teach you how to swing a sword.
I know how to swing a sword.
You're leaving now?
It's the middle ofthe night.
I learned to walk in darkness.
Say your good-byes, little man.
Keep this one safe.
He means the world to me.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
We've been waiting a long time.
Haven't we?
Well, I don't know, you tell me.
How long does it take to sack a city?
lt wasjust as you said.
They did not believe until it was too late.
Their slave soldiers
threw down their spears and surrendered.
And Daario Naharis?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
The city is yours, my queen.
(PLAYING LIVELY MUSIC)
(GUESTS CHATTERING)
They're good, aren't they?
They ought to be because they cost enough.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING)
Look at the crowd there.
(CATELYN LAUGHING)
He complained about this marriage
the entire ride from Riverrun,
and now look at him.
BLACKFlSH: The Gods love to reward a fool.
-(CHUCKLES) Uncle.
-What?
He's my nephew. I love him.
And he's a damned fool.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Don't you drink, Lord Bolton?
Never do, my lady. Dulls the senses.
BLACKFlSH: That's the point.
Didn't you marry one ofthese Frey girls?
Aye. Lord Walder
let me choose any of his granddaughters
and promised me
the girl's weight in silver as a dowry.
Sol have a fat young bride.
(LAUGHING)
I hope she makes you very happy.
Well, she's made me very rich.
Pardon, my lord,
my lady. I need to find atree to piss on.
My mother's alone
with Roose Bolton. I should rescue her.
Your mother is less in need of rescue
than any woman I've ever met.
Be kind. She's finally starting to like you.
And I like her.
But if she had herway,
I would be back in Volantis
playing my harp
and you would be sitting over there,
eating blackberries out of Roslin Frey's hand.
Perhaps I've made a terrible mistake.
(GASPS)
Striking your king is an act oftreason.
No, don't.
Don't insult them.
Your Grace.
(KNOCKING ON TABLES)
(MUSIC STOPS)
The septon has prayed his prayers,
some words were said,
and Lord Edmure
has wrapped my daughter in a cloak.
But they are not yet man and wife.
A sword needs a sheath.
(ALL LAUGHING)
And a wedding needs a bedding.
(ALL CHEERING)
What does my sire say?
ALL: (CHANTING) To bed! To bed! To bed!
lfyou think
the time is right, Lord Walder, by all means,
let us bed them.
(ALL CHEERING)
(BAND PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
ALL: (CHANTING) To bed! To bed! To bed!
MAN: Go on.
(MEN LAUGHING)
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
Ho-ho!
Careful now, ladies.
Once you set that monster free,
there's no caging him again. (LAUGHS)
ALL: (CHANTING) To bed! To bed! To bed!
Poorgirl.
Every bride suffers the same.
I'm sure you endured yours with grace.
Oh, Ned forbade it.
He said it wouldn't be right
if he broke a man's jaw on our wedding night.
(CHUCKLES)
That is a very strange custom.
I suppose it does
seem strange from a foreigner's perspective.
It seems normal to you?
lt's atradition.
Without the bedding ceremony,
there's no real proof
the lord and lady
consummated their marriage.
No, but there
are other ways of providing proof.
Boy or girl?
I don't know.
But if it's a boy,
I know what we should name him.
Oh, do you?
It seems to me the father
should have some say in his son's naming.
Eddard.
Don't you want to
teach little Ned Stark how to ride horses?
I do.
(MUSIC STOPS)
(BAND PLAYING THE RAINS OF CASTAMERE)
(GREY WIND WHINING)
(WHIMPERING)
MAN: Go on, line 'em up!
(THE RAINS OF CASTAMERE
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(MEN LAUGHING)
HOUND: Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where are you going?
Got salt pork for the feast.
The feast is over.
HOUND: Doesn't sound like it's over.
If I tell you it's over, it's over.
Turn this cart around
and get the hell out of here.
HOUND: Got pig's feet, too.
Are you soft in the head?
Turn this cart around.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Your Grace.
lfeel I've been remiss in my duties.
I've given you meat and wine and music,
but I haven't shown you
the hospitality you deserve.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
My king has married
and I owe my new queen a wedding gift.
(GASPS)
Robb!
(GROANlNG)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(ALL GROANlNG)
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(GROANS)
Ohh!
-(MEN SHOUTlNG)
-Ahh!
Ahh!
(STARK SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(NEIGHING)
MAN 1: (LAUGHING)
You ready to head home to Winterfell, eh?
(MEN LAUGHING)
MAN 2: Feast overyet, is it?
Aye, it's over.
(GROANlNG)
(STARK SOLDIERS GROANlNG)
(GREY WIND WHINING)
(BANGING)
(GREY WIND GROWLING)
Aim!
(GROWLING)
(GREY WIND YOWLS)
(GROANS)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTlNG)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
It's too late.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTlNG)
(STRAINING)
The King in the North arises.
-(GRUNTS)
-(WALDER CHUCKLES)
Lord Walder!
Lord Walder, enough!
Let it end!
Please. He is my son.
My first son.
Let him go,
and I swear that we will forget this.
I swear it by the Old Gods and New.
We will take no vengeance.
You already swore me
one oath right here in my castle.
You swore by all the Gods
your son would marry my daughter!
CATELYN: Take me
for a hostage, but let Robb go.
Robb, get up. Get up and walk out.
Please!
And why would I let him do that?
On my honour as a Tully,
on my honour as a Stark,
let him go, or I will cut yourwife's throat.
I'll find another.
Mother.
The Lannisters send their regards.
-(STABB|NG)
-(GROANS)
(WAILING)
(THUDS)