We shouldn't be out here alone.
Why not?
If your father...
He'|| never know we're gone.
But if he finds out...
You don't need to be afraid of my father.
GIRL 1: Are you sure?
GIRL 2: Yes.
We shouldn't go in.
Of course we should.
-(AN|MAL SCREECHES)
-(SCREAMS)
Get out! Get out!
-Let's go.
-No.
Listen to your friend.
They said that you were terrifying,
with cat's teeth and three eyes.
You're not terrifying.
You're boring.
You don't know what I am.
I know you're a witch
and you can see the future.
Tell me mine.
Everyone wants to know their future
until they know their future.
This is my father's |and. My |and.
Tell me my future,
or I'll have yourtwo boring eyes
gouged out of your head.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Your blood.
Give me ataste.
(GASPS)
Three questions you get.
You won't like the answers.
I've been promised to the prince.
When will we marry?
You will neverwed the prince.
You will wed the king.
But I will be queen?
Oh, yes.
You'll be queen.
For a time.
Then comes another,
younger,
more beautiful,
to cast you down and take all you hold dear.
Will the king and l have children?
No. The king will have 20 children,
and you will have three.
That doesn't make sense.
Gold will be their crowns.
Gold their shrouds.
(LAUGHING)
GIRL 1: Come on, we have to go.
We have to go! Cersei.
MAN: Bearers, put it down.
(BELL TOLLING)
Bearers, up.
Away.
SEPTON: Your Grace, we are honoured
by your presence.
The mourners are waiting.
They will keep waiting.
I want a moment alone with him.
But, Your Grace,
many ofthese lords and ladies
have travelled day and night
to be here from all seven kingdoms.
CERSEI: They will wait.
(DOOR OPENS)
He never wanted you to be a Kingsguard,
but here you are, protecting his dead body.
What he built, it's ours.
He built it for us. He meant it for us.
-They're going to try to take it away. All of it.
-They?
All ofthem out there. Our enemies.
They're waiting in line
to make sure he's really dead.
And as soon as they see
the stones on his eyes,
they'll set to work on tearing us apart.
They have nothing to do with it.
The man who murdered our father,
he tore us apart.
He's the enemy.
I've been telling you for years.
You've been defending him foryears.
This is exactly what they want.
And now our father is dead,
and that little monster
is out there somewhere drawing breath.
Did you set him free?
Tyrion may be a monster,
but at least he killed our father on purpose.
You killed him by mistake.
With stupidity.
You're a man of action, aren't you?
When it occurs to you to do something,
you do it.
Never mind the consequences.
Take a look.
Look at the consequences.
Here they are.
He loved you more than anyone in this world.
(S EA WAVES CRASHING)
(SEAGULLS SQUAWKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTING)
(WOOD CREAKS)
(STRAINING)
Apologies.
I still don't see why I had to stay
in this fucking crate once we set sail.
I saved your life.
lfthey catch you, they catch me.
I cannot say | feel overly guilty
about leaving you in that fucking crate.
Do you know what it's like to stuff your shit
through one ofthose air holes?
No, | only know what it's like
to pick up your shit and throw it overboard.
Pentos?
The home of my colleague,
lllyrio Mopatis, a merchant.
He and I met many years ago
through mutual friends.
A group of people who saw Robert Baratheon
forthe disaster he was.
We tried to do what was best for the realm
by supporting a Targaryen restoration.
And thus began the chain of mistakes
that has led us both here.
Things have gotten worse, not better.
Westeros needs to be saved from itself.
Mmm.
Much better.
My lord?
I don't think I am any more.
A lord.
Are you a lord ifyou kill your father?
I don't imagine they revoke your nobility
for killing awhore.
It must happen all the time.
You already drank yourself
across the Narrow Sea.
In a box. Why stop now?
Because we are talking
about the future of our country.
The future is shit.
Just like the past.
(MEN GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(WOMAN MOANlNG LOUDLY)
(SPEAKING VALYRlAN)
You want the same?
Same as always?
You...
you don't have to.
Habit.
(SHUSHING GENTLY)
(HUMMING)
(CHOKING)
DAENERYS: The Sons ofthe Harpy?
BARRISTAN: Yes, Your Grace.
They left it on the body.
They've never killed before.
It was only a matter oftime, Your Grace.
Conquerors always meet with resistance.
I didn't conquerthem. Their own people did.
(SPEAKING VALYRlAN)
They do not see us as people, Your Grace.
Then they will have to learn to see
things differently, Mossador.
He did not risk his life
fighting for his freedom
so cowards in masks could take it away.
And I did not take up residence
in this pyramid
so I could watch the city below
decline into chaos.
What was the name ofthe man you lost?
White Rat, Your Grace.
lwant him buried with honour, publically,
in the Temple ofthe Graces.
The Sons ofthe Harpy will hear that message.
Make them very angry.
Angry snakes lash out.
Makes chopping offtheir heads
that much easier.
Find the men who did this
and bring them to me.
Your Grace.
(SPEAKING VALYRlAN)
I wanted to speak with you.
Why do you come?
White Rat, the Unsullied who...
l have heard they found his body in a brothel.
l have heard that more than one Unsullied
has been known to visit Meereen's brothels.
May I ask you why?
Why would an Unsullied go to a brothel?
I do not know.
I must go.
(GRUNTING)
(METAL CLANGING)
-Get your shield up.
-|t's too heavy.
If it wasn't heavy, it wouldn't stop a sword.
Now get it up.
Come. Try it again.
Drive at me. Keep your shield up,
or I'll ring your head like a bell.
Shouldn't you be training, too?
Well, I'm hardly a new recruit.
How many brothers can say that
they've killed a White Walker and a Thenn?
I might be the first in history.
-JON: Shield up.
-ALLISER: These men need a firm hand.
Always have.
They're poachers and thieves.
Not soldiers.
That one hates me.
SAMWELL: If Ser Alliser is chosen
as the new Lord Commander...
-He hates the wildlings.
-(BABY CRYING)
All the wildlings.
-Don't let them send us away.
-|t's not a sure thing.
Ser Denys Mallister has commanded
the Shadow Tower for 20 years,
and people say he's a good man.
He's running against Ser Alliser...
Sam, don't let them send us away.
ltold you.
Wherever you go, I go, too.
You can't leave. They'll execute you.
Good, good, pivot. Don't forget to pivot.
Shield up.
The king wants a word.
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(WIND HOWLING)
You're not cold, my lady?
Never.
The Lord's fire lives within me, Jon Snow.
Feel.
Are you a virgin?
No.
Good.
Your Grace.
The bastard ofWinterfell.
You know who rules at Winterfell now?
Roose Bolton.
Hmm. The traitorwho plunged a dagger
in Robb Stark's heart.
Don't you want to avenge him?
I want a great many things, Your Grace.
But I'm a sworn brother
ofthe Night's Watch now.
I've been talking to your sworn brothers.
-Many ofthem love you.
-They're good men.
DAVOS: Many don't.
You were seen taking the body
ofawildling girl north ofthe Wall.
VVhy?
It's where she belonged.
Some ofthe Night's Watch feel you have
too much affection for the wildlings.
They were born on the wrong side ofthe Wall.
That doesn't make them monsters.
STANNIS: No matter.
I shall take back the North
from the thieves who stole it.
Tywin Lannister is dead.
He can't protect them now.
I shall mount Roose Bolton's head on a spike.
But if I'm to take Winterfell, I need more men.
The men ofthe Night's Watch
are sworn to play no part...
I'm not talking about the damn Night's Watch.
I'm talking about the wildlings.
Your Grace,
you want the wildlings
to march in your army?
lfthey swear to follow me, I'll pardon them.
We'll take Winterfell.
Once the North is won,
I'll declare them citizens ofthe realm.
I'll give them land to live on.
It's a fair offer. More than fair.
I'll offer them their lives and their freedom
if Mance kneels before me
and swears his loyalty.
I don't think that's likely.
STANNIS: You admire him, don't you?
I respect him.
He likes you.
-Convince him to bend the knee, or he burns.
-Your Grace.
How much time do I have?
STANNIS: Nightfall.
The sun drops fast this time of year.
Hurry, Jon Snow.
MAN: Shield up.
-(ROB|N WHIMPERING)
-MAN: Attack, my lord!
-MAN: Attack!
-(ROB|N GROANING)
MAN: Don't cross your feet.
My sons had swords in their hands
from the time they could walk. This one...
LITTLEFINGER: Lord Arryn
will never be a great warrior.
ROYCE: Great warrior?
He swings a sword like a girl with palsy.
My lord.
MAN: Sword up, my lord!
LITTLEFINGER: Some boys
develop more slowly.
He's still young.
ROYCE: He's 13.
Boys go to war at 13.
-He has other gifts.
-Does he?
The gift of a great name.
Sometimes that's all one needs.
(G ROANS LOUDLY)
Good-bye, Lord Royce,
and thank you for all you've done for me.
l have done nothing more
than my duty, my lady.
l have no doubt that on my return,
Robin's skills will have
improved immeasurably.
He'll be safe here.
As for his skills,
I make no promises.
Will we head north at some point?
He said Sansa had a brother at Castle Black.
We're a few days' ride from the King's Road.
-But that will take us...
-Us?
The only reason you're here
is because Jaime Lannister
told me you weren't safe in the capital.
You're hundreds of miles
from King's Landing.
No one knows what you look like.
No one cares. You're safe.
-But I'm your squire.
-Do you even know what a squire is?
An attendant to a knight.
I'm not a knight.
That means you're not a squire.
Well, where would I go?
I don't care. I'm not your mother.
You swore to find the Stark girls.
I found Arya. She didn't want my protection.
-Sansa still might.
-Will you shut your mouth?
I didn't ask for your advice.
I don't want anyone following me.
I'm not a leader.
All I everwanted
was to fight for a lord I believed in.
The good lords are dead,
and the rest are monsters.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
You told Lord Royce
we were going to the Fingers.
Idid.
-But we're heading west.
-We are.
If he wanted to betray us,
he already would have.
Lord Royce might be as honourable
as he thinks he is,
but he's not alone in that castle.
Do you trust all those knights and ladies,
stable boys and serving girls?
No, do you trust the carriage driver
or the knights escorting us?
No. (CHUCKLES)
But I paythem well,
and they've seen what happens
to men who disappoint me.
So where are we going?
To a land where you trust everyone?
To a land so far from here,
even Cersei Lannister
can't get her hands on you.
It was such a deep, deep shock to us all.
Your fatherwas a...
A force to be reckoned with. He truly was.
I wouldn't presume to claim
to have known him as such, but...
Butjust being in his presence was enough
to make it so clear
just how formidable
a person you were dealing with.
What a force to be reckoned with.
Thank you so much for your kind words.
Deepest condolences, Your Grace.
This tragedy... l nevertrusted Varys.
I often warned...
Your Grace.
Cousin Lancel. I hardly recognised you.
My deepest sympathies.
I apologise for my son's appearance.
Uncle, that's quite all right.
They call themselves Sparrows.
Bloody fanatics.
Religion has its place, of course,
but at a certain point...
They never would have come
to the capital when Tywin was alive.
I'm sure he'll grow out of it, whatever it is.
-Excuse me.
-Of course.
Your wounds from the Blackwater
seem to have healed.
It wasn't my wounds that needed healing.
What can I do foryou?
You can forgive me.
What could you possibly have done
to warrant my forgiveness?
I led you into the darkness.
I doubt you've ever led anyone anywhere.
l tempted you into our...
unnatural relations.
And, of course, there was the king,
his boar hunt.
His wine.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm a different person now.
I've found peace in the light ofthe Seven.
You can, too.
They watch over all of us,
ready to dole out mercy
orjustice.
Theirworld is at hand.
lwill pray foryour father's soul.
(LAUGHS)
The day Tywin Lannister's soul
needs your help...
-OLYVAR: It looks like Dorne.
-LORAS: It doesn't.
(OLYVAR LAUGHS)
It does.
That's the Sunspear bit, right there.
And that's where the mountains are.
And over here is...
Stonespear?
Sandstone.
Yes.
Yes, Sandstone.
Just there.
Fine.
It's Dorne.
We should go there.
I think we would have a lovely time,
judging by my experience.
That would be wonderful.
Dorne, Highgarden.
Anywhere but here.
We're late for dinner as it is.
You're very respectful.
I'm very hungry.
What's your name?
Olyvar, my lady.
I'm afraid my brother
is keeping the king waiting, Olyvar.
My lady.
Perhaps you might consider
being a bit more discreet?
VVhy?
They all know about me anyway.
Everybody knows everything about everyone.
What's the point in trying to
keep a secret in a place like this?
In any event,
you shouldn't keep your intended waiting.
My intended? Please.
Tywin's dead.
That means no one
can force Cersei to marry me.
-Lucky you.
-Un|ucky you.
You think I want that woman
married to my brother?
If she doesn't marry me,
she doesn't go to Highgarden.
Which means she stays in King's Landing.
Which means you're trapped here
with Cersei Lannister as your mother by law.
Perhaps.
Perhaps?
Eunuch, the spider, the Master ofWhisperers.
Imp, halfman.
There are faster ways to kill yourself.
Not for a coward.
You are manythings, my friend,
but not a coward.
You nevertold me why
you set me free.
Your brother asked me to.
Could have said no.
Refuse the Kingslayer?
A dangerous proposition.
Not as dangerous as releasing me.
You risked your life,
your position, everything.
Why? You're not family.
You owe me nothing.
I didn't do it for you.
I did it forthe Seven Kingdoms.
A drunken dwarf will never be
the saviour ofthe Seven Kingdoms.
I don't believe in saviours.
I believe men oftalent
have a part to play in the war to come.
You're going to have to find another soldier.
I'm done with Westeros,
and Westeros is done with me.
You have many admirable qualities,
self-pity is not one ofthem.
Any fool with a bit of luck
can find himself born into power.
But earning it for yourself, that takes work.
I'm not well-suited for work.
lthinkyou are.
You have your father's instincts for politics,
and you have compassion.
Compassion? Yes.
I killed my loverwith my bare hands.
I shot my own father with a crossbow.
I never said you were perfect.
What is it you want exactly?
Peace.
Prosperity.
A land where the powerful
do not prey on the powerless.
Where the castles are made of gingerbread,
and the moats are filled with blackberry wine.
The powerful have always
preyed on the powerless.
That's how they became powerful
in the first place.
Perhaps.
And perhaps we've grown so used to horror,
we assume there's no other way.
lfyou sat on the Iron Throne,
would you spread misery
throughout the land?
I will never sit on the Iron Throne.
No, you won't.
But you could help another climb those steps
and take that seat.
The Seven Kingdoms
need someone stronger than Tommen,
but gentler than Stannis.
A monarch who can intimidate
the high lords and inspire the people.
A ruler loved by millions with a powerful army
and the right family name.
Good luck finding him.
Who said anything about "him"?
You have a choice, my friend.
You can stay here at lllyrio's palace
and drink yourselfto death,
oryou can ride with me to Meereen,
meet Daenerys Targaryen,
and decide ifthe world is worth fighting for.
Can I drink myselfto death
on the road to Meereen?
When did the Unsullied
start patrolling the streets of Meereen?
Looks like your friends
haven't been behaving themselves.
Our mission to Yunkai
was a resounding success.
The Wise Masters onunkai
have agreed to cede power
to a council of elders made up of both
the freed men and the former slaveholders.
All matters of consequence
will be brought to you for review.
Good.
They did ask for some concessions.
Concessions?
Politics is the art of compromise, Your Grace.
I'm not a politician. I'm a queen.
HIZDAHR: Forgive me. You're right, of course.
Still, it's easier to rule happy subjects
than angry ones.
DAENERYS:
I don't expect the Wise Masters to be happy.
Slavery made them rich.
I ended slavery.
They do not ask for the return of slavery.
They ask for the reopening
ofthe fighting pits.
DAENERYS: The fighting pits?
Where slaves fought slaves to the death?
In the new world that you've brought to us,
free men would fight free men.
The pit fighters you liberated
plead for this opportunity.
Bring some here and ask them yourself.
No fighting pits.
Opening them would
show the people onunkai and Meereen
that you respect theirtraditions.
I do not respect
the tradition of human cockfighting.
lfyou...
How many times must I say no
before you understand?
Whatever he wants from me,
he's not going to get it.
If he really believes
I'm going to reopen the fighting pits...
DAARIO: You should reopen the fighting pits.
What?
My mother was a whore.
ltold you that.
She liked to drink pear brandy.
The older she got,
the less she made selling her body,
the more she wanted to drink.
So one day when l was 12,
she sold me to a slaver
she fucked the night before.
I'm sorry.
Why? I was a bad child.
I wasn't big, but I was quick
and I loved to fight.
So they sold me to a man in Tolos
who trained fighters for the pits.
I had my first match when l was 16.
You were sold into slavery,
forced to fight to the death
for the amusement ofthe masters,
-and you're defending the fighting pits?
-(LAUGHS)
I'm only here because ofthose pits.
I learned to fight like a Dothraki screamer,
a Norvoshi priest, aWesterosi knight.
Soon I was famous.
Ten thousand men and women screamed
my name when I stepped into the pit.
I made so much money for my master,
he set me free when he died.
ljoined the Second Sons,
and then I met you.
You're the queen.
Everyone's too afraid of you to speak truth.
Everyone but me.
You've made thousands of enemies
all across the world.
As soon as they see weakness,
they'll attack.
Show your strength here, now.
That's why I have the Unsullied
patrolling the streets.
(SCOFFS)
Anyone with a chest full of gold
can buy an army of Unsullied.
You're not the Mother of Unsullied.
You're the Mother of Dragons.
I don't want another child's bones
dropped at my feet.
No one's seen Drogon in weeks.
For all I know,
he's flown halfway across the world.
I can't control them any more.
A dragon queen with no dragons
is not a queen.
(CHAINS RATTLING)
DAENERYS: Viserion?
Rhaegal?
(ROARING)
Easy. Easy.
Easy.
(SCREECHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
So here we are.
Here we are.
When we first met,
you were my prisoner.
And now, for our last meeting...
This doesn't have to be our last meeting.
No, but it will be.
You know what Stannis wants?
He wants me to bend the knee.
And he wants the free folk to fight for him.
I'll give him this much, he's bold.
Shouldn't a king be bold?
Oh, aye.
I respect him.
If he gets what he wants,
I expect he'll be a better ruler
than the fools sitting on the Iron Throne
the last hundred years.
But I'll never serve him.
You told me you weren't here to conquer.
You told me your people have bled enough.
That's right.
I don't want them
bleeding for Stannis Baratheon either.
You spent your life convincing 90 clans
to come together for the first time in history.
Thenns and Hornfoots,
the ice-river clans, even the giants.
A life's work uniting them.
You didn't do it for power.
You didn't do it for glory.
You brought them together to save them
because none ofthem will survive the winter,
not ifthey're north ofthe Wall.
Isn't their survival
more important than your pride?
Pride?
Fuck my pride.
This isn't about that.
Then bend the knee and save your people.
They followed me because they respected me.
Because they believed in me.
The moment I kneel for a southern king,
that's all gone.
And how many tens ofthousands
are out there right now?
How many women?
How many children?
And you won't go out
and rescue them because why?
You're afraid of looking afraid.
Oh, lam afraid.
No shame in that.
How will they do it?
Beheading?
Hanging?
They'll burn you alive.
Bad way to go.
I'll be honest with you.
I don't want to die.
And burned to death?
I don't want people to remember me like that,
scorched and screaming.
But it's betterthan
betraying everything I believe.
And what happens to your people?
You preserve your dignity and die standing,
and they'll sing songs about you.
You'd rather burn than kneel.
The great hero.
Until winter comes,
and the White Walkers come for us all,
and there's no one left to sing.
You're a good lad.
Truly you are.
But ifyou can't understand
why I won't enlist my people
in a foreigner's war,
there's no point explaining.
(JON KNOCKING ON DOOR)
I think you're making a terrible mistake.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
The freedom to make my own mistakes
was all I ever wanted.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Mance Rayder, you have been
called the King-beyond-the-Wall.
Westeros only has one king.
Bend the knee,
I promise you mercy.
Kneel and live.
This was my home for many years.
lwish you good fortune in the wars to come.
We all must choose.
Man orwoman, young or old,
lord or peasant, our choices are the same.
We choose light, or we choose darkness.
We choose good, or we choose evil.
We choose the true god or the false.
Free folk,
there is only one true king,
and his name is Stannis.
Here stands your king of lies.
Behold the fate ofthose
who choose the darkness.
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS LOUDLY)