(Bells chiming, birds singing)
(Horse whinnies)
(Men shouting)
(Ned) Does Ser Hugh have
any family in the capital?
No.
I stood vigil
for him myself last night.
He had no one else.
He'd never worn this armour before.
Bad luck for him -
going against the Mountain.
Who determines the draw”
All the knights draw straws, Lord Stark.
Aye.
But who holds the straws?
You've done good work. Sisters.
Life is strange.
Not so many years ago
we fought as enemies at the Trident.
I'm glad we never met
on the ﬁeld, Ser Barrislan.
As is my wife. I don‘t think
the widovfs life would suit her.
(Chuckles) You're too modest.
I've seen you cut down
a dozen great knights.
My father once told me
you were the best he'd ever seen.
I never knew the man to be wrong
about matters of combat.
He was a ﬁne man, your father.
What the Mad King
did to him was a terrible crime.
And that lad -
he was a squire
until a few months ago.
How could he afford a new suit of armour?
Perhaps Lord Arryn
left him some money?
- I hear the king wants to joust today.
- Yes, that will never happen.
(Chuckles) Robert tends
to do what he wants.
If the king got what
he wanted all the time,
It's made too small, Your Grace.
It won't go.
Your mother was
a dumb whore with a fat arse.
Did you know that?
Look at this idiotl
One ball and no brains.
He can't even put
a man's armour on him properly.
- You're too fat for your armour.
- Fat?
Fat, is it?
Is that how you speak to your king?
(Laughing)
Oh, it's funny, is it?
- No, Your Grace.
- No?
You don't like the Hand's joke?
You're torturing the poor boy.
You heard the Hand.
The king's too fat for his armour.
Go ﬁnd the breastplate
stretcher - nowl
- (Laughs)
- "The breastplate stretcher"?
How long before he ﬁgures it out?
- Maybe you should have one invented.
- All ﬁght, all right.
You watch me out there.
I still know how to point a lance.
You've no business jousting.
Leave that for the young men.
Why, because I'm king?
Piss on that. I want to hit someny
- And who's going to hit you back?
- Anybody who can.
- And the last man in his saddle...
- Will be you.
There's not a man in the Seven Kingdoms
would risk hurting you.
Are you telling me
those cowards would let me win?
Aye.
- Drink
- I'm not thirsty.
Drink Your king commands it.
Gods,
too fat for my armour.
Your squire -
a Lannister boy?
Mm. A bloody idiot,
but Cersei insisted.
l have Jon Arryn to thank for her.
"Cersei Lannister will make
a good match," he told me.
"You'll need her father on your side."
I thought being king
meant I could do whatever I wanted.
Enough of this.
Let's go watch 'em r'ide.
At least I can smell
someone else's blood.
- Robert.
- What?
Oh. (Laughs)
An inspiring sight for the people, eh?
Come, bow before your kingl
Bow, you shitsl
(Ned chuckles)
(Cheering)
- Where's Arya?
- At her dancing lessons.
The Knight of the Flowers.
Thank you, Ser Loras.
(Horse neighs)
(Crowd jeering)
(Horse grunting and neighing)
Don't let Ser Gregor hurt him.
- Hey.
- I can't watch.
A hundred gold dragons on the Mountain.
- I'll take that bet.
- Now what will I buy with 100 gold dragons?
A dozen barrels of Domish wine?
Or a girl from
the pleasure houses of Lys?
- Or you could even buy a ﬁiend.
- He's going to die.
Ser Loras r'ides well.
(Neighing)
(Fanfare)
- (Gasm)
- (Laughs)
Such a shame, Littleﬁnger.
It would have been so nice
for you to have a ﬁiend.
And tell me, Lord Renly,
when will you be having your ﬁiend?
(Neighs)
Loras knew his mare was in heat.
Quite crafty, really.
Ser Loras would never do that.
- There's no honour in tricks.
- No honour and quite a bit of gold.
- (Helmet clanks)
- Swordl
(Horse neighs)
- (Gasm)
- (Neighs)
- (CFOWd gasps)
- (Grunts)
Leave him bel
(Growls)
Stop this madness
in the name of your kingl
(Robert) Let him gol
I owe you my life, ser.
I'm no ser.
(Cheering)
(Grunting)
Remove his hood.
J' On that eve, the captive lmp
J' Downwards from his horse did limp
J' No more would he preen and primp
J' In garb of red and gold I
(T yrion) This isn't the Kingsroad.
- You said we were riding for Winterfell.
- I did... Often and loudly.
Very wise.
They'll be out in droves,
looking for me in the wrong place.
Word's probably gotten
to my father by now.
He'll be offering a handsome reward.
Everyone knows
a Lannister always pays his debts.
Would you be so good as to untie me?
- And why would I do that?
- Why not?
Am I going to run?
The hill tribes would kill me for my boots.
Unless a shadowcat ate me ﬁrst.
Shadowcats and hill tribes
are the least of your concerns.
Ah, the eastern road.
We're going to the Vale.
You're taking me to your sister's
to answer for my imagined crimes.
Tell me, Lady Stark.
when was the last time you saw your sister?
- Five years ago.
- She's changed.
She was always a bit touched, but now...
You might as well kill me here.
- I am not a murderer, Lannister.
- Neither am I.
I had nothing to do
with the attempt on your son's life.
- The dagger found...
- What sort of imbecile
arms an assassin with his own blade?
- Should I gag him?
- Why?
Am I starting to make sense?
- (T huds, grunts)
- (Catelyn) Rodrikl
(Roaring)
My lady, this way.
Untie me.
If I die, what's the point?
(Neighs)
Ahl
(Man roars)
(Breathing heavily)
- Rodrik?
- I'll be ﬁne, my lady.
There's no need to bloody yourself.
Your ﬁrst?
You need a woman.
Nothing like a woman after a ﬁght.
I'm willing if she is.
(Laughing)
(Bran) The Iron Islands.
Sigil - a kraken.
Words - 'We do not sow."
- Lords?
- The Greyjoys.
Famed for their skills at archery,
navigation and lovemaking.
(Laughs)
And failed rebellions.
Sigil - a stag,
a crowned stag now that Robert's king.
- Good.
- Words - "Ours is the fury."
- Lords - the Baratheons.
- Mm-hm.
The Westerlands.
- Sigil - a lion.
- Mmm.
- Words - "A Lannister always pays his debts."
- No.
A common saying,
but not their ofﬁcial motto.
- (Arrow thunks)
- Lords - the Lannisters.
- We're still on their words.
- I don't know them.
You do know them. Think
"Unbowed, unbent, unbroken."
- That's House Martell.
- "Righteous in wrath."
- House Homwood.
- "Family, duty, honour."
Those are Tully words -
your mother's.
- Are we playing a game?
- Family, duty, honour...
- Is that the right order?
- You know it is.
Family comes ﬁrst?
Your mother had to leave Winterfell
to protect the family.
How can she protect the family
if she's not with her family?
Your mother sat by your bed
for three weeks while you slept.
And then she leftl
When you were born, I was the one
who pulled you from your mother.
I placed you in her arms.
From that moment
until the moment she dies,
she will love you.
Absolutely.
(Sighs) I still can't tell you,
- but she will be home soon.
- Do you know where she is now
- (Arrow thunks)
- Today?
- No, I don't.
- Then how can you promise me
she'll be home soon?
Sometimes I worry
you're too smart for your own good.
I'll never shoot another arrow.
And where is that written?
- You need legs to work a bow.
- Hmm.
If the saddle Lord Tyr'ion
designed actually works,
you could learn
to shoot a bow from horseback
Really?
Dothraki boys learn
when they're four years old.
Why shouldn't you?
(Grunting)
(Moans)
Shh, keep it down.
You're not supposed to be
inside the castle walls.
I thought you were supposed to be
an important person around here.
Important enough for the likes of you.
You're not the only nobleman
in my life, you know.
Who, the Imp?
I'd call him half a nobleman.
Jealous?
Why should I be jealous?
Anyone with a few coppers
in his pocket can own you for the night.
What's a dwarf like down below?
I've always wondered.
- Might surprise you.
- Hmm?
He's good with his ﬁngers too.
And his tongue.
Generous tipper.
I guess gold is cheap for a Lannister.
You are jealous.
I'm a Greyjoy.
We've been lords
of the Iron Islands for 300 years.
There's not a family in Westeros
that can look down on us,
not even the Lannisters.
And what about the Starks?
I've been Lord Starks ward
since I was eight years old.
A ward -
that's a nice word for it.
Your father rebelled
against King Robert and if he does it again...
My father fought
for the freedom of his people.
What did your father do?
Fucked a cook and whelped a whore.
You're a very serious boy.
- I'm not a boy.
- Oh, yes, you are.
A serious boy
with a serious cock
I don't want to pay for it.
Then get yourself a wife.
- (Arya) Come on.
- (Meows)
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
(Meows)
How is your son, my lord?
He'll never walk again.
But his mind is sound?
So they say.
A blessing, then.
I suffered an early mutilation myself.
Some doors close forever...
others open
in most unexpected places.
May I?
If the wrong ears heard
what I'm about to tell you,
off comes my head.
And who would mourn poor Varys then?
North or South,
they sing no songs for spiders.
But there are things you must know.
You are the King's Hand
and the king is a fool -
your ﬁiend, I know, but a fool -
and doomed unless you save him.
I've been in the capital a month.
Why have you waited so long
to tell me this?
I didn't trust you.
So why do you trust me now
The queen is not the only one
who has been watching you closely.
There are few men of honour
in the capital.
You are one of them.
I would like to believe I am another,
strange as that may seem.
What sort of doom does the king face?
The same sort as Jon Arryn.
The tears of lys, they call it.
A rare and costly thing,
as clear and tasteless as water.
It leaves no trace.
Who gave it to him?
Some dear ﬁiend, no doubt.
But which one?
There were many.
Lord Arryn was a kind and trusting man.
(Sighs) There was one boy.
All he was he owed to Jon Arryn.
The squire, Ser Hugh?
Pity, what happened to him,
just when his life seemed to be
going so nicely.
If Ser Hugh poisoned him...
who paid Ser Hugh?
- Someone who could afford it.
- Jon was a man of peace.
He was Hand for 17 years -
17 good years.
Why kill him?
He started asking questions.
(Meows)
(Man) He's found
one bastard already.
He has the book
- The rest will come.
- (Lock clicks)
(Man #2) And when he knows the truth,
what will he do?
(Man #1) The gods alone know.
The fools tried to kill his son.
What's worse -
they botched it.
The wolf and the lion
will be at each other's throats.
- We will be at war soon, my ﬁiend.
- (Man #2) What good is war nom
We're not ready.
If one Hand can die,
why not a smond?
(Man #1) This Hand is not the other.
(Man #2) We need time.
Khal Drogo will not make his move
until his son is born.
- You know what these savages are.
- "Delay," you say.
"Move fast," I reply.
This is no longer
a game for two players.
(Man #2) It never was.
The ﬁrst to arrive
and the last to leave.
I admire your industry.
You do move quietly.
We all have our qualities.
You look a bit lonely today.
You should pay a visit
to my brothel this evening.
- First boy is on the house.
- I think you're mistaking
- business with pleasure.
- Am I?
All those birds that whisper in your ear -
such pretty little things.
Trust me,
we awommodate all inclinations.
Oh, I'm sure. Lord Redwyne
likes his boys very young, I hear.
I'm a purveyor of beauty and discretion -
both equally important.
Though I suppose beauty
is a subjective quality, no?
Is it true that Ser Marlon of Tumblestone
prefers amputees?
All desires are valid
to a man with a full purse.
And I heard the most awful rumour
about a certain lord
with a taste for fresh cadavers.
Must be enormously difﬁcult
to awommodate that inclination.
The logistics alone...
to ﬁnd beautiful corpses
before they rot.
Strictly speaking, such a thing would not be
in awordance with the king's laws.
Strictly speaking.
Tell me. Does someone somewhere
keep your balls in a little box?
I've often wondered.
Do you know,
I have no idea where they are.
- And we had been so close.
- (Chuckles)
But enough about me.
How have you been
since we last saw each other?
Since you last saw me
or since I last saw you?
Now the last time I saw you,
you were talking to the Hand of the King.
-Sawmewithyourowneyes?
-Eyeslown.
Council business.
We all have so much
to discuss with Ned Stark
Everyone's well aware of
your enduring fondness for Lord Starks wife.
If the Lannisters were behind the attempt
on the Stark boy's life
and it was discovered that you helped
the Starks come to that conclusion...
to think a simple word to the queen...
- One shudders at the thought.
- Ooh.
But you know something?
I do believe that I have seen you
even more mently
than you have seen me.
- Have you?
- Yes.
Earlier today, I distinctly mall
seeing you talking
to Lord Stark in his chambers.
Was that you under the bed?
And not long after that
when I saw you escorting a certain
foreign dignitary...
Council business?
Of course, you would have ﬁiends
from across the Narrow Sea.
You're from there yourself, after all.
We're ﬁiends, aren't we, Lord Varys?
I'd like to think we are.
So you can imagine my burden,
wondering ifthe king
might question my ﬁiend's sympathies.
To stand at a crossroads
where turning left means loyalty to a ﬁiend,
turning right loyalty to the realm...
- Oh, please.
- To ﬁnd myself in a position
- where a simple word to the king...
- (Door opens)
What are you two conspiring about?
Well, whatever it is,
you'd best hurry up.
- My brother is coming.
- To a small council meeting?
Disturbing news from far away.
Hadn't you heard?
(Birds cawing, waves breaking)
Off with you. No begging.
I'm not a beggar.
I live here.
D'you want a smack on your ear
to help you with your hearing?
I want to see my father.
I want to fuck the queen,
for all the good it does me.
You want your father, boy?
He's lying on the ﬂoor of some tavern,
getting pissed on by his ﬁiends.
My father is Hand of the Kingl
I'm not a boy.
I'm Arya Stark of Winterfell.
And if you lay a hand on me, my father
will have both your heads on spikes.
Now are you going to let me by
or do I need to smack you
on the ear to help with your hearing?
You know I had half my guard
out searching for you?
- You promised me this would stop.
- They said they were going to kill you.
- Who did?
- I didn't see them,
- but I think one was fat.
- Oh, Arya. (Sighs)
I'm not lyingl
They said you found the bastard
and the wolves are ﬁghting
the lions and the savage...
Something about the savage.
- Where did you hear this?
- In the dungeons,
- near the dragon skulls.
- What were you doing in the dungeons?
Chasing a cat.
(Knock. door opens)
Pardon, my lord.
There's a night's watchman here
begging a word. Says it's urgent.
- Your name, ﬁiend?
- Yoren, if it please.
- This must be your son. He has the look
- I'm a girll
Did Benjen send you?
No one sent me, my lord.
I'm here to ﬁnd men for the Wall,
see ifthere's any scum in the dungeons
that might be ﬁt for service.
- Oh, we'll ﬁnd recruits for you.
- Thank you, my lord.
But that's not why I disturb you now.
Your brother Benjen,
his blood runs black -
makes him as much
my brother as yours.
It's for his sake I rode here so hard
I damn near killed my horse.
There are others riding too.
The whole city will know by tomorrow.
Know what?
Best said in private, my lord.
Go on. We'll talk more later.
Jory, take her safely to her room.
Come along, my lady.
You heard your father.
- How many guards does my father have?
- Here in King's Landing? Fifty.
You wouldn't let anyone
kill him, would you?
No fear on that count, little lady.
- Well?
- It's about your wife, my lord.
She's taken the Imp.
(Neighs)
You're far from home, Lady Stark.
- To whom do I speak?
- Ser Vardis Egan, knight of the Vale.
- ls Lady Arryn expecting your visit?
- There was no time to send word.
May I ask. my lady,
why he is with you?
That's why there was no time.
- He is my prisoner.
- He doesn't look like a prisoner.
My sister will decide what he looks like.
Yes, my lady.
She will at that.
The Eyrie.
They say it's impregnable.
Give me ten good men
and some climbing spikes,
I'll impregnate the bitch.
(T yrion) I like you.
Lord Stark. your presence
has been requested
in the small council chamber.
A meeting has been called.
I need to see the king ﬁrst - alone.
The king is at
the small council meeting, my lord.
He has summoned you.
- Is it about my wife?
- No, my lord.
I believe it concerns Daenerys Targaryen.
- The whore is pregnant.
- You're speaking of murdering a child.
I warned you this would happen,
back in the North.
I warned you, but you didn't care to hear.
Well, hear it now.
I want 'em dead,
mother and child both.
And that fool Viserys as well.
Is that plain enough for you?
I want them both dead.
You will dishonour yourself
forever if you do this.
Honour?l
I've got seven kingdoms to rulel
One king, seven kingdoms.
Do you think honour keeps them in line?
Do you think it's honour
that's keeping the peace?
- It's fear - fear and blood.
- Then we're no better than the Mad King.
- Careful, Ned. Careful now.
- You want to assassinate a girl
because the spider heard a rumour?
No rumour, my lord.
The princess is with child.
- Based on whose information?
- Ser Jorah Morrnont.
He is serving as advisor
to the Targaryens.
Morrnont?
You bring us the whispers
of a traitor half a world away
and call it fact?
Jorah Morrnont's a slaver,
not a traitor.
Small difference, I know,
to an honourable man.
He broke the law,
betrayed his family, ﬁed our land.
We commit murder
on the word of this man?
(Robert) And if he's right?
If she has a son?
A Targaryen at the head
of a Dothraki army -
- what then?
- The Narrow Sea still lies between us.
I'll fear the Dothraki the day they teach
their horses to run on water.
Do nothing?
That's your wise advice?
Do nothing till our enemies
are on our shores?
You're my council.
Counsell
Speak sense to this honourable fool.
I understand your misgivings, my lord.
Truly, I do.
It is a terrible thing
we must consider, a vile thing.
Yet we who presume to rule
must sometimes do vile things
for the good of the realm.
Should the gods
grant Daenerys a son,
- the realm will bleed.
- I bear this girl no ill will,
but should the Dothraki invade,
how many innocents will die?
How many towns will burn?
Is it not wiser, kinder even,
that she should die now
so that tens of thousands might live?
We should have had them
both killed years ago.
When you ﬁnd yourself
in bed with an ugly woman,
best close your eyes,
get it over with.
Cut her throat.
Be done with it.
I followed you into war -
twice,
without doubts,
without swond thoughts.
But I will not follow you now.
The Robert I grew up with
didn't tremble at the shadow
of an unborn child.
She dies.
I will have no part in it.
You're the King's Hand, Lord Stark.
You'll do as I command
or I'll ﬁnd me a Hand who will.
And good luck to him.
- I thought you were a better man.
- Out. Out, damn you.
I'm done with you.
Go, run back to Winterfelll
I'll have your head on a spikel
(Robert) I'll put it there myself, you fooll
You think you're too good for this?
Too proud and honourable?
This is a warl
I'll go ahead with my daughters.
Get them ready. Do it yourself.
- Don't ask anyone for help.
- Right away, my lord.
Lord Baelish is here for you.
His Grace went on about you
at some length
- What can I do for you?
- When do you return to Winterfell?
- Why? What do you care?
- If you're still here come nighthll,
I'll take you to see the last person
Jon Arryn spoke with before falling ill.
If that sort of thing still interests you.
I don't have the time.
It won't take more than an hour.
But as you please.
Round up all the men we have
and station them outside the girls' chambers.
- Who are your best two swords?
- Heward and Wyl.
Find them and meet me at the stables.
You bring him here without permission?
You pollute my home with his presence?
(Sucking sounds)
Your aunt has done a bad thing,
Robin, a very bad thing.
You remember her, don't you?
Isn't he beautiful?
And strong too. Jon knew it.
His last words were
"The seed is strong."
He wanted everyone to know
what a good, strong boy
his son would grow up to be.
Look at him,
the lord of all the Vale.
Lysa,
you wrote me about the Lannisters,
- warning me...
- To stay away from theml
Not to bring one herel
Mummy...
- is that the bad man?
- It is.
(Chuckles)
He's little.
(Lysa) He's Tyr'ion the Imp,
of House Lannister.
He killed your father.
He murdered the Hand of the Kingl
Oh, did I kill him too?
- I've been a very busy man.
- You will watch your tonguel
These men are knights of the Vale.
Every one of them loved Jon Arryn.
Every one of them would die for me.
If any harm comes to me,
my brother Jaime will see that they do.
You can't hurt us.
No one can hurt us here. Tell him, Mummyl
- Tell himl
- Shh-shh-shh-shh-shh, my sweet boy.
He's just trying to ﬁighten us.
Lannisters are all liars.
No one will hurt my baby.
Mummy...
I want to see the bad man ﬁy.
- Perhaps you will, my little love.
- This man is my prisoner.
I will not have him harmed.
Ser Vardis,
my sister's guest is weary.
Take him down below
so he can rest.
Introduce him to Mord.
You go sleep, dwarf man. (Chuckles)
Sleep good, little dwarf manl
(Laughs)
(Slams, lock clunks)
(Wind whistling)
Lord Starks lucky he still has a head.
Robert will rant for a few days,
but he won't do anything.
- He adores the man.
- You're jealous.
- Are you sure this won't hurt?
- Only if I slip.
(Scraping)
- And you'd prefer me like this?
- Mm-hm.
If you want hairless,
maybe you should ﬁnd a little boy.
I want you.
My brother thinks that anyone
who hasn't been to war isn't a man.
He treats me as if I'm a spoilt child.
Oh, and you're not?
Loras Tyrell,
the Knight of the Flowers?
How many wars have you fought in?
Oh, and how much did your father spend
on that armour of yours?
Hold still.
All I ever hear from Robert and Stannis
is how I'm not tough enough,
how I squirm at the sight of blood.
You did vomit when that boy's eye
was knocked out in the melee.
His eye was dangling
out of the damn socketl
He shouldn't have entered the melee
if he didn't know how to ﬁght.
Easy for you to say.
Not everyone is such a gifted swordsman.
(Groans) It's not a gift.
No one gave it to me.
I'mgood bwauselworkatit-
every day of my life
since I could hold a stick
I could work at ﬁghting all day, every day,
I'd still never be as good as you.
Yes, well, I guess we'll never know.
(Sighs)
- Everywhere?
- Everywhere.
So how did it end up?
- The Targaryen girl will die?
- It needs to be done, unpleasant as it is.
Robert's rather tasteless about it.
Every time he talks about killing her,
I swear the table rises six inches.
It's a shame he can't muster
the same enthusiasm for his wife.
He does have a deep,
abiding lust for her money.
You have to give it
to the Lannisters - they may be
the most pompous, ponderous cunts
the gods ever suffered to walk the world,
but they do have
outrageous amounts of money.
- I have an outrageous amount of money.
- Not as much as the Lannisters.
(Laughs) But a lot more than you.
Robert's threatening
to take me hunting with him.
Last time we were out there
for two weeks.
Tramping through the trees
in the rain, day after day,
all so he can stick his spear
into something's ﬁesh.
Oh. But Robert loves his killing.
- And he's the king.
- Hmm.
- How did that ever happen?
- Because he loves his killing.
Andheusedtobegoodatit.
Do you know who should be king?
- Be serious.
- I am.
My father could be your bank
I've never fought in a war before,
- but I'd ﬁght for you.
- I'm fourth in line.
And where's Robert
in the line of royal suwession?
Joffrey is a monster.
Tommen is eight.
- Stannis?
- Stannis has the personality of a lobster.
He's still my older brother.
- (Gasps) What are you doing?l
- Look at it.
- You cut me.
- It's just blood. We've all got it in us.
Sometimes a little spills.
If you bmome king,
you're going to see a lot of this.
You need to get used to it.
Go on. Look
People love you.
They love to serve you
because you're kind to them.
They want to be near you.
You're willing to do
what needs to be done,
but you don't gloat over it.
You don't love killing.
Where is it written that power
is the sole province of the worst?
That thrones are only made
for the hated and the feared?
You would be a wonderful king.
(Kissing and sucking sounds)
(Door creaks)
I'm sorry your marriage
to Ned Stark didn't work out.
You seemed so good together.
I'm glad I could do something
to make you happy.
Without a Hand,
everything will fall to pimes.
I suppose this is where you tell me
to give the job to your brother Jaime.
No.
He's not serious enough.
I'll say this for Ned Stark -
he's serious enough.
(Robert) Hmm.
Was it really worth it?
Losing him this way?
I don't know.
But I do know this -
ifthe Targaryen girl convinces
her horselord husband to invade
and the Dothraki horde
crosses the Narrow Sea...
we won't be able to stop them.
The Dothraki don't sail.
Every child knows that.
They don't have discipline.
They don't have armour.
- They don't have siege weapons.
- It's a neat little trick you do -
you move your lips
and your father's voice comes out.
(Chuckles softly) Is my father wrong?
Let's say Viserys Targaryen lands
with 40,000 Dothraki screamers at his back
We hole up in our castles.
Awisemove-
only a fool would meet
the Dothraki in an open ﬁeld.
They leave us in our castles.
They go from town to town,
looting and burning,
killing every man
who can't hide behind a stone wall,
stealing all our crops and livestock.
enslaving all our women and children.
How long do the people
of the Seven Kingdoms stand behind
their absentee king,
their cowardly king
hiding behind high walls?
When do the people decide
that Viserys Targaryen
is the rightful monarch after all?
We still outnumber them.
Which is the bigger number -
ﬁve or one?
Five.
Five...
One.
One army - a real army
united behind one leader
with one purpose.
Our purpose died with the Mad King.
Now we've got as many armies
as there are men
with gold in their purse.
And everybody wants
something different.
Your father wants to own the world.
Ned Stark wants to run away
and bury his head in the snow.
What do you want?
We haven't had
a real ﬁght in nine years.
Backstabbing doesn't prepare you
for a ﬁght.
And that's all the realm is now -
backstabbing and scheming
and arse-licking
and money-grubbing.
Sometimes I don't know
what holds it together.
- Our marriage.
- (Laughs)
Ah, so here we sit,
17 years later,
holding it all together.
Don't you get tired?
Every day.
How long can hate
hold a thing together?
Well, 17 years is quite a long time.
Yes, it is.
What was she like?
You've never asked
about her, not once.
Why not?
At ﬁrst, just saying her name
even in private
felt like I was breathing life
back into her.
I thought if I didn't talk about her,
she'd just fade away for you.
When I realised
that wasn't going to happen,
I refused to ask out ofspite.
I didn't want to give you the satishction
of thinking I cared enough to ask
And eventually it became clear
that my spite didn't mean anything to you.
As far as I could tell,
you actually enjoyed it.
What harm could Lyanna Starks ghost
do to either of us
that we haven't done to each other
a hundred times over?
You want to know the horrible truth?
I can't even remember
what she looked like.
I only know she was
the one thing I ever wanted.
Someone took her away from me,
and seven kingdoms
couldn't ﬁll the hole she left behind.
I felt something
for you once, you know
I know.
Even after we lost our ﬁrst boy.
For quite a while, actually.
Was it ever possible for us?
Was there ever a time, ever a moment?
No.
Does that make you feel better or worse?
It doesn't make me feel anything.
(Door opens, closes)
She looks like him,
don't she, my lord?
She has his nose,
his black hair.
Aye.
Tell him when you see him, my lord.
If it please you,
tell him how beautiful she is.
- I will.
- And tell him I've been with no one else.
I swear it, my lord,
by the old gods and new.
I don't want no jewels or nothing,
just him.
The king was always good to me.
When Jon Arryn came to visit you,
- what did he want?
- He wasn't that sort of man, my lord.
He just wanted to know
ifthe child was happy,
healthy.
Looks healthy enough to me.
The girl shall want for nothing.
Brothels make a much better
investment than ships,
I've found.
Whores rarely sink
What do you know
of King Robert's bastards?
Well, he has more than you, for a start.
- (Ned) How many?
- Does it matter?
If you fuck enough women,
some of them will give you presents.
And Jon Arryn
tracked them all down. Why?
He was the King's Hand.
Perhaps Robert wanted them looked after.
He was overcome with fatherly love.
Come.
- Joryl
- My lord.
Such a small pack of wolves.
Stay back. ser.
This is the Hand of the King.
Was the Hand of the King.
Now I'm not sure what he is -
lord of somewhere very far away.
What's the meaning of this, Lannister?
Get back inside where it's safe.
I'm looking for my brother.
You remember my brother,
don't you, Lord Stark?
Blond hair,
sharp tongue, short man.
- I remember him well.
- It seems he had some trouble on the road.
You wouldn't know
what happened to him, would you?
He was taken at my command
to answer for his crimes.
- (Littleﬁnger) My Iordsl
- (Horse neighs)
I'll bring the City Watch.
Come, Stark.
I'd rather you die sword in hand.
- If you threaten my lord again...
- Threaten?
As in, "I'm going to open your lord
"from balls to brains
and see what Starks are made of'?
You kill me,
your brother's a dead man.
You're right.
Take him alive. Kill his men.
(Roars)
Yahl
My brother, Lord Stark -
we want him back
(Horse neighs)