(FIRE CRACKLING)
(THE RAINS OF CASTAMERE PLAYING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
-Magnificent.
-Mmm-hmm.
Looks fresh-forged.
It is.
No one's made a Valyrian steel sword
since the Doom of Valyria.
There are three living smiths
who know how to rework Valyrian stee|.
The finest ofthem was in Volantis.
Came here to King's Landing at my invitation.
Where did you get this much Valyrian steel?
From someone who no longer had need of it.
You've wanted one in the family
for a long time.
-And now we have two.
-Two?
The original weapon was absurdly large.
Plenty of steel for two swords.
Well, thank you. It's glorious.
(GRUNTS)
You'll have to train your left hand.
Any decent swordsman
knows how to use both hands.
You'll never be as good.
No.
But as long as I'm better than everyone else,
it doesn't matter.
You can't serve in the Kingsguard
with one hand.
Where's that written? I can and I will.
The Kingsguard oath is for life.
The war is over. The King is safe.
The King is never safe.
How many people in this city alone
would love to see his head on a pike?
Other knights protected the King
while you were a prisoner.
They will continue to do so
when you go home.
Home?
You'll return to Casterly Rock
and rule in my stead.
You are the Lord of Casterly Rock.
lam the King's Hand. My place is here.
I don't expect to see the Rock again
before I die.
You know what they call me?
Kingslayer. Oathbreaker. Man without honour.
Now you want me to
break another sacred vow.
You won't be breaking anything.
There is a precedent
to relieve a Kingsguard of his duties.
The King will exercise that prerogative.
No.
No?
-I don't believe I asked you a question.
-There's my answer.
lfyou think your bloody honour
comes before your...
My bloody honour is beyond repair,
but my answer is still no.
I don't want Casterly Rock, a wife, children.
What do you want?
Supper would be nice.
For 40 years I've tried to teach you.
lfyou haven't learned by now, you neverwill.
Go.
lf serving as a glorified bodyguard
is the sum of your ambition, go serve.
I suppose you want the sword back.
Keep it.
A one-handed man with no family
needs all the help he can get.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(GOATS BLEATING)
How many Dornishmen
does it take to fuck a goat?
Please don't.
BRONN: Seems to me the smart place to
meet travellers is in a tavern.
That way, one party is late,
the other party can drink some ale inside.
This is the Prince of Dorne we're waiting for,
not one of your sellsword friends.
If he's so damned important,
how come they sent you to meet him?
There's bad blood between the Martells
of Dome and the Lannisters of Casterly Rock.
Has been for years.
And just in case the Martells of Dorne
are looking to spill some Lannister blood,
-it may as well be yours, eh?
-No need for cynicism.
I happen to be an accomplished diplomat.
Oh.
Ah, here we are.
(CLAPPING)
TYRION: Can you read the sigils?
Yellow balls?
Wild lemons on a purple field,
House Dalt of Lemonwood.
A vulture grasping a baby in its talons,
House of Blackmont.
A crowned skull,
the Manwoodys of Kingsgrave.
Boy knows his Dornish houses.
I need a sigil.
And House Martell,
a red sun pierced by a spear?
I don't see it, my lord.
Well met, my lords. His Grace King Joffrey
welcomes you in his name.
My lord father, the King's Hand,
sends his greetings as well.
lam Tyrion Lannister of Casterly Rock,
Master of Coin.
Forgive me.
I don't see Prince Doran in your company.
The prince's health
forces him to remain at Sunspear.
He sends his brother, Prince Oberyn,
to attend the royal wedding.
The King will be delighted
to enjoy the company of a warrior
as renowned as Prince Oberyn.
Will he?
Where is Prince Oberyn?
Arrived before dawn.
Not a man for welcome parties.
Very well. My lords,
these fine men from the City Watch
will escort you to your quarters
in the Red Keep.
You must be weary after such a long journey.
Some accomplished diplomacy that was.
Now where?
We must find Prince Oberyn before
he kills somebody, or several somebodies.
How do you plan on finding
a single Dornishman in a citythis big?
You're famous for fucking half of Westeros.
You just arrived at the capital
after two weeks of bad road.
Where would you go?
I'd probably go to sleep, but I'm getting old.
Look at this one.
Beautiful.
But pale.
We like them pale in the capital.
Shows they don't work the fields.
Do | frighten you?
You like?
Timid bores me.
Hmm.
You're a bit of mischief, aren't you?
I think she likes you. (CHUCKLES)
She has good taste.
You're not timid, are you?
(LAUGHS) Not timid.
Do you like women?
When they look like her, my lord.
This one will do nicely.
OLYVER: Very good, my lady.
Oh, I'm not a lady.
A term of courtesy in this establishment.
A lie anywhere.
Why not use the right words?
I'm a bastard.
She is a whore. And you're what?
A procurer.
Any ofthe others?
(SIGHING) The two girls can leave.
-(OLYVER SNAPS FINGERS)
-You stay.
I'm afraid I'm not on offer, my lord.
Everyone who works for Littlefinger
is on offer.
Take off your clothes. We'll be here a while.
-My lord.
-I am a prince, boy.
(WOMAN MOANS)
Have you ever been with a prince?
Can't say l have.
-|'m wildly expensive.
-(SCOFFS)
Take off your clothes.
Which way do you like it?
-(GASPS)
-My way.
MAN: (SINGING)
And so he spoke, and so he spoke
That Lord of Castamere
But nowthe rains...
Oberyn.
Weep o'er his hall...
Oberyn, don't.
With no one there to hear
Yes now the rains weep o'er his hall
And not a soul to hear
You lost, friend?
Forgive me for staring.
I don't see many Lannisters where I'm from.
I don't see many Dornishmen in the capital.
We don't like the smell.
(LAUGHS)
-Come with me, lover.
-Gods, look at this one.
Sirs, ifyou follow me,
I'll arrange for a private room.
Why are you wasting a woman like this
on a Dornishman?
Bring him a shaved goat
and a bottle of olive oil.
(LAUGHS)
OBERYN: Hmm.
Do you know why all the world
hates a Lannister?
You think your gold
and your lions and your gold lions
make you better than everyone.
May | tell you a secret?
You're not a golden lion.
You're just a pink little man
who is far too slow on the draw.
(SCREAMING)
Longsword is a bad option in close quarters.
When I pull my blade,
your friend starts bleeding.
Quite a lot, I'm afraid.
So many veins in the wrist.
(GROANING)
He'll live ifyou get him help straightaway.
So, decisions.
(CONTINUES GROANING)
Prince Oberyn, forgive the intrusion.
We heard there might be...
(MAN SCREAMS)
...trouble.
Apologies, my love.
(DOOR CLOSES)
I'm here to welcome you to the capital.
Ellaria Sand, my paramour.
The King's own Uncle lmp.
Tyrion, son of Tywin Lannister.
lfthere's anything I can do
to make your stay at King's Landing...
What are you? His hired killer?
It started that way, aye. Now I'm a knight.
How did that come to pass?
Killed the right people.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
We'll need a few more girls. Girls, yes?
You don't partake?
Oh, I partook. Now I'm married.
Prince Oberyn, aword in private?
Seems I visited the Lannister brothel
by mistake.
-Oh, they take all kinds.
-Even Dornishmen.
TYRION: The King is very grateful
that you travelled all this way for his wedding.
Let us speak truth here. Joffrey is insulted.
lam only the second son.
Well, speaking as a fellow second son,
l have grown rather used
to being the family insult.
(OBERYN CHUCKLES)
Why did you come to King's Landing?
l was invited to the royal wedding.
I thought we were speaking truth.
The last time l was in the capital
was many years ago.
Another wedding.
My sister Elia and Rhaegar Targaryen,
the Last Dragon.
My sister loved him. She bore his children.
Swaddled them, rocked them,
fed them at her own breast.
Elia wouldn't let the wet nurse touch them.
And beautiful, noble Rhaegar Targaryen
left her for another woman.
That started awar,
and the war ended right here,
when your father's army took the city.
I wasn't actually present.
They butchered those children.
My nephew and niece.
Carved them up
and wrapped them in Lannister cloaks.
And my sister,
you know what they did to her?
I'm asking you a question.
-|'ve heard rumours.
-Hmm.
So have I.
The one I keep hearing
is that Gregor Clegane the Mountain
raped Elia and split her in half
with his great sword.
I wasn't there. I don't know what happened.
lfthe Mountain killed my sister,
your father gave the order.
Tell your father I'm here.
And tell him the Lannisters
aren't the only ones who pay their debts.
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
(GROWLS)
(SCREECHING)
-(GROWLS)
-(CHUCKLES)
-(SCREECHES)
-(SHUSH|NG)
(SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
(SHUSHING)
-(ROARS)
-(GASPS)
(SCREECHES)
They're dragons, Khaleesi.
They can never be tamed.
Not even bytheir mother.
Ser Barristan.
Your Grace.
Where's Daario Naharis?
Where's Grey Worm?
Gambling, Your Grace.
Gambling?
CROWD: Mhysa. Mhysa.
How long have they been at it?
Since midnight, Your Grace.
SerWorm is strongerthan he looks.
But I can see his arms beginning to shake.
What's the prize
to winning this stupid contest?
The honour of riding by your side
on the road to Meereen.
as neither ofthem
kept me waiting this morning.
You two will ride in the rear guard
and protect the livestock.
The last man holding his sword
can find a new queen to fight for.
(DAARIO GROANING)
(BOTH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
You likethis girl?
Must be frustrating.
You are not a smart man, Daario Naharis.
I'd rather have no brains
and two balls.
You need to eat something.
Pigeon pie.
No, thank you.
Lemon cakes?
You love lemon cakes.
Tell her she needs to eat.
My lady, you do need to eat.
I don't want to eat.
lfl could have a moment alone with my wife.
She needs to eat.
TYRION: I can't let you starve.
I swore to protect you.
My lady,
lam your husband. Let me help you.
How can you help me?
I don't know, but I can try.
I lie awake all night staring at the canopy,
thinking about how they died.
I could get you essence of nightshade
to help you sleep.
How they sewed his direwolf's head
onto his body?
And my mother.
They cut her throat to the bone
and threw her body in the river.
What happened to your family
was aterrible crime.
I didn't know your brother.
He seemed like a good man,
but I didn't know him.
Your mother, I admired her.
She wanted to have me executed,
but I admired her.
She was a strong woman.
And she was fierce
when it came to protecting her children.
Sansa.
Your mother would want you to carry on.
You know it's true.
Will you pardon me, my lord?
I'd like to visit the godswood.
Of course. Prayer can be helpful, I hear.
I don't pray any more.
It's the only place I can go
where people don't talk to me.
SHAE: My lion.
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Come here.
How many times have I told you?
You can't visit me here.
I know. We have come to a dangerous place.
Have you forgotten me?
Do you know how long it's been?
Of course I haven't forgotten.
I want you.
Don't you want me?
Things are a bit tense right now.
What things?
My nephew the King wants to murder me.
My wife hates me
because my father murdered her family.
Oberyn Martell wants to murder
everyone whose last name is Lannister.
You need to relax.
Don't you want to relax?
-What's wrong?
-I told you.
-|t's not a good time.
-|t's never a good time.
-You have your child bride now.
-Shae.
Do you love her?
Love her? I barely know her. She's a child.
She despises me.
That's not an answer.
I don't love her.
You tried to ship me away.
Ship you away?
Give me diamonds and make me disappear.
What are you talking about?
lfyou want me to leave, just say it.
-Say it!
-Shh.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You want me to stay?
(GROANS)
Awork of art.
The craftsmanship is excellent.
You like it so much, you're welcome
to chop off your own hand and take it.
You're such an ingrate.
I spent days with the goldsmith
getting the details just right.
Days?
Better part of an afternoon.
There, how does that feel?
Uh...
A hook would be more practical.
Elegant, lthink.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
CERSEI: Thank you foryour help
with the other matter.
-QYBURN: The symptoms have abated?
-Gone completely.
lam in your debt, Maester beurn.
Not a maester, Your Grace,
but happy to help whenever I can.
(DOOR OPENS)
-Odd little man.
-|'ve grown fond of him.
(DOOR CLOSES)
He's quite talented.
-What symptoms?
-(CHUCKLES)
Symptoms that are not your concern.
You let him touch you?
You jealous?
I'm surprised.
You never let Pycelle near you.
(LAUGHS) You think I'd let that old lecher
put his hands on me?
He smells like a dead cat.
I'm not sure I've ever smelled a dead cat.
Well, they smell like Pycelle.
You drink more than you used to.
-Yes.
-Why?
Hmm. Let's see.
You started a brawl in the streets with
Ned Stark and disappeared from the capital.
My husband died in a tragic hunting accident.
It must have been traumatic for you.
My only daughter was shipped offto Dorne.
We suffered through a siege.
A rather short siege.
That I didn't expect to survive.
And now I'm marrying my eldest son
to a wicked little bitch from Highgarden,
while I'm supposed to marry her brother,
a renowned pillow-biter. So...
Father disowned me today.
He can't disown you. You're all he's got.
-You're forgetting Tyrion.
-(SCOFFS)
You don't really plan on staying
in the Kingsguard, do you?
Staying in the Kingsguard means
I live right here in the Red Keep with you.
-Not now.
-I want...
Not now? When? I've been back for weeks.
-Something's changed.
-Everything's changed.
You come back after all this time
with no apologies and one hand
and expect everything to be the same?
What do you want me to apologise for?
For leaving me.
You think I wanted to be taken prisoner?
Don't know what you wanted.
You weren't here.
You left me alone.
Every day l was a prisoner,
l plotted my escape.
Every day.
l murdered people
so I could be here with you.
-You tooktoo long.
-|...
-What are you saying?
-You tooktoo long.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
-Come in.
-JA|ME: Go away.
Forgive me, Your Grace.
You told me to come at once
ifthere was anything important.
(BLOWING)
You plan on killing all the crows yourself?
Do you plan on sitting here,
scratching your balls till winter?
We wait for Mance's orders.
You sent a man over the Wall at the full moon.
If he's not back yet, he's not coming back.
And what is it you want?
March on Castle Black with just this lot?
Your pretty crow said
athousand men are nesting there.
He's a liar.
He is?
Shouldn't it be "he was"?
You said you put three arrows in him.
Idid.
I've seen you slip a shaft
through a rabbit's eye at 200 yards.
lfthat boy's still walking,
it's 'cause you let him go.
(WHISTLING)
Thenns.
I fucking hate Thenns.
Mance sent you?
-(GRUNTS)
-How did you find us?
(CAWS)
You came from the south, not the north.
Took a detour.
Got some supper
from a village down that way.
Why does the meat down here
taste so much better
than it does on our side ofthe Wall?
Help yourself.
(CHUCKLES)
Maybe everything's just better fed down here.
Fat and lazy.
Easier for us. (CHUCKLES)
You didn't see us coming?
Lost your warg?
And that baby crow you had with you,
lost him, too?
l'll answerto Mance.
lwon't answerto you.
She yours?
I'm not anybody's.
Too scrawny.
Not like those crows at Castle Black.
Think ofthem stuck in their larders,
stuffing their faces
with ham and blood sausage
and stew, getting nice and fat and marbled.
I know we've had our differences, Tormund,
but just one time before you die,
you really ought to try crow.
MAN: Draw.
Loose.
JON: Last time I saw him,
he was in the courtyard at Winterfell.
He said, "Next time | see you,
you'll be all in black."
l was jealous of Robb my whole life.
(GROANS)
The way my father looked at him,
I wanted that.
He was better than me at everything.
Fighting and hunting
and riding
and girls.
Gods, the girls loved him.
lwanted to hate him, but I never could.
Sometimes I want to hate you.
You're better than me at everything.
Except reading.
They're, um...
They're ready foryou.
He's wanted to hang me for a while.
Now's his chance.
No one's going to hang you.
You've done nothing wrong.
I've done plenty wrong.
So you admit you murdered Qhorin Halfhand?
-JON: I didn't murder him.
-No?
You put your sword
through a brother ofthe Night's Watch.
What do you call that?
He wanted me to kill him.
A bastard son of a traitor.
What would you expect?
The Halfhand believed our only chance to
stop Mance was to get a man inside his army.
Don't talk about the Halfhand
as ifyou knew him. He was my brother.
Then you'd know he'd do anything
to defend the Wall.
The free folk would have boiled him alive,
but letting me kill him...
JANOS: The free folk? Listen to him.
He even talks like a wildling now.
Aye, | talk like awildling.
late with the wildlings.
I climbed the Wall with the wildlings. l...
I laid with awildling girl.
You admit to breaking your vows, then?
I do.
The law is the law.
The boy must die.
lfwe beheaded every ranger
who lay with a girl,
the Wall would be manned by headless men.
There's a difference between
sneaking offto the Mole's Town brothel
and sleeping with the enemy.
While we sit here
debating which rules I broke,
Mance Rayder marches on the Wall
with an army of 100,000.
Impossible.
You can't get 50 wildlings together
before they start killing each other.
100,000.
He's united the Thenns, the Hornfoots,
the ice-river clans.
He has giants fighting for him.
(LAUGHS) Giants?
Have you ever been beyond the Wall, ser?
l commanded the City Watch
of King's Landing, boy.
And now you're here.
You must not have been
very good at yourjob.
How dare you?
There's a band of wildlings south ofthe Wall
already, led by Tormund Giantsbane.
I killed theirwarg and three others.
They shot me full of arrows.
Their orders are to attack Castle Black from
the south when Mance hits it from the north.
The signal for the attack will be a bonfire.
Mance said it would be the greatest fire
the North has ever seen.
That's the truth.
All the truth.
Do you intend to execute me,
or am | free to go?
None of us are free.
We are men ofthe Night's Watch.
But we won't be taking your head today,
Jon Snow.
Go on.
lam acting commander here, MaesterAemon.
Yes, you are.
And I don't trust the bastard.
He told the truth.
And you always know
when a man's telling a lie?
How did you acquire this magical power?
I grew up in King's Landing.
OLENNA: No.
You're a queen, not an ox.
Your grandfather gave me a necklace
just like this one for my 51st nameday.
The wedding is in a fortnight, Grandmother.
You can't say no to everything.
Nonsense. My little dears,
go and speak
to the jewellers of King's Landing.
Tell them who you are, who sent you.
The one who brings me the best necklace
will get to keep the next best.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
The Margaery Tyrell who walks into the Sept
a fortnight from now
will inspire athousand songs.
How sad it will be
if she's wearing rubbish like that.
Perhaps I should just let Joffrey
choose it for me.
End up with a string of dead sparrow heads
around my neck.
You watch that. Even here, with me.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
My word.
My lady.
Please pardon me for interrupting.
My name is Brienne of Tarth.
We know who you are.
We've heard all about you.
But hearing is one thing.
Aren't you just marvellous!
Absolutely singular.
I hear you knocked my grandson into the dirt,
like the silly little boy he is.
My lady, I know this is a very busy time
for you, but ifl could just have a moment.
You dare not refuse.
A shadow?
With the face of Stannis Baratheon.
I swear to you by all the gods it was Stannis.
He plunged his sword through Renly's heart
and disappeared.
One day, I will avenge our king.
Joffrey is our king now.
-I meant no offence.
-And you've given none.
All the Kingsguard will be on duty.
Ser Boros will be stationed here.
Ser Preston will be stationed here,
beside the primary entertainment.
-Your Grace?
-Huh?
One guard at the thing. Go on.
Ser Meryn will guard
Lady Margaery and Tommen.
I've always guarded the King himself,
my lord. Ever since your absence.
And I thank you for it, Ser Meryn.
All very good. I don't expect any trouble.
The people love their King.
They know who keeps them fed.
Margaery Tyrell, I've heard.
By my leave.
They know I saved the city. I won the war.
The war's not won. Not while Stannis lives.
I broke Stannis on the Blackwater.
Pity you weren't there to help, Uncle.
My apologies, Your Grace. l was rather busy.
Busy getting captured.
So this is the famous Book of Brothers?
All the great deeds
of all the great Kingsguard.
Ser Arthur Dayne. The Sword ofthe Morning.
(CHUCKLES)
Led the attack
on the Kingswood Brotherhood.
Defeated the Smiling Knight in single combat.
Ser Duncan the Tall.
(LAUGHS)
Four pages.
-He must have been quite a man.
-So they say.
Ser Jaime Lannister.
Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
Someone forgot to write down
all your great deeds.
-There's still time.
-Is there?
For a 40-year-old knight with one hand?
How can you protect me with that?
I use my left hand now, Your Grace.
Makes for more of a contest.
(SCOFFS)
DAENERYS: Have you ever been to Meereen?
Several times, Your Grace,
with Master Kraznys.
And?
They say a thousand slaves died
building the Great Pyramid of Meereen.
And now an army of former slaves
is marching to her gates.
You think the Great Masters are worried?
lfthey're smart, Your Grace.
You were told to ride at the back ofthe train.
Yes, My Queen.
But I need to speak to you
about something important.
A matter of strategy.
Your Grace.
All right, what is this matter of strategy?
A dusk rose.
Would you like to walk at the back ofthe train
instead of riding?
And this one's called lady's lace.
Would you like to walk without shoes?
You have to know a land to rule it.
lts plants, its rivers, its roads, its people.
Dusk rose tea eases fever.
Everyone in Meereen knows that.
Especiallythe slaves
who have to make the tea.
lfyou want them to follow you,
you have to become a part oftheir world.
Strategy.
Harpy's Gold.
No tea from this one.
Beautiful but poisonous.
You are a gambler, aren't you?
Your Grace.
(SOLDIER SHOUTS IN VALYRIAN)
There's one on every mile marker
between here and Meereen.
How many miles are there?
163, Your Grace.
BARRISTAN: I'll tell our men to ride ahead
and burythem.
You don't need to see this.
You will do no such thing.
I will see each and every one oftheir faces.
Remove her collar before you bury her.
BRIENNE: There she is.
JAIME: Yes.
-And?
-You made a promise.
To return the Stark girls to their mother,
who is now dead.
To keep them safe.
Arya Stark hasn't been seen
since her father was killed.
Where do you think she is?
My money's on dead.
There's a certain safety in death,
wouldn't you say?
And Sansa Stark is now Sansa Lannister.
Bit ofa complication.
A complication
does not release you from a vow.
What do you want me to do?
Kidnap my sister-in-law? And take her where?
Where would she be safer than here?
Look me in the eye and tell me that
you think she'll be safe in King's Landing.
Are you sure we're not related?
Ever since I've returned,
every Lannister I've seen
has been a miserable pain in my ass.
Maybe you're a Lannister, too.
You've got the hair for it, if not the looks.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(FOOTSTEPS STOP)
(GASPS)
-(GASPS)
-(STAMMER|NG) It's all right.
-You're drunk.
-Yes.
l have good reason to be.
Once I was a knight. Now I'm only a fool.
Don't you know me?
Ser Dontos. The King's nameday celebration.
I'm sorry. I should have remembered.
I can't accept your apology.
I may be a fool,
but I'm a living fool, thanks to you.
Anyone would have done the same.
But only you did.
I can never repay you. You gave me my life.
But this is worth more than my life.
lt belonged to my mother,
and her mother before her.
House Hollard was strong once.
House on the rise.
That's all that's left ofthose days,
thanks to a few sad, fat drunks like me.
I can't take it.
It's very kind of you, but I can't.
I don't have anything else left.
That's all.
Take it. Wear it.
Let my name
have one more moment in the sun
before it disappears from the world.
I'll wear it with pride, Ser Dontos.
Yeah.
(FLIES BUZZING)
ARYA: When am I
going to get a horse of my own?
HOUND: The little lady wants a pony.
The little lady wants away from your stench.
Horses aren't easy to come by.
Even ifthey were, you think
I'm gonna put you on your own horse?
Watch the only thing of value
I've got in the world ride away?
Why don't you have any money?
Didn't you steal anything from Joffrey
before you left?
No.
You're not very smart, are you?
I'm not athief.
You're fine with murdering little boys,
but thieving is beneath you?
A man's got to have a code.
You think I'm gonna escape?
Where would I go?
I'd be dead by nightfall without you.
My family's gone. I've got no one.
You've got an aunt in the Vale.
Your rich Aunt Lysa.
After I sell you to her,
maybe she'll have enough left over
to buy you that pony you want so much.
ARYA: I'm hungry. You're hungry.
Five horses, five men.
More than I feel like killing
on an empty stomach.
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
lknow him.
The small one. His name is Polliver.
He captured us and took us to Harrenhal.
(BOTH URINATING)
He killed Lommy.
What the fuck's a Lommy?
He was my friend.
Polliver stole my sword
and put it right through his neck.
He's still got it.
HOUND: Got what?
My sword Needle.
Needle?
Of course you named your sword.
Lots of people name their swords.
Lots of cunts.
(FOOTSTEPS RETREATING)
What are you... Get back...
My brother gave me that sword.
-Get back here.
-He killed my friend.
I don't care if he ate your friend.
We're not going in there.
-(MEN LAUGHING)
-MAN: Come on, give it up.
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
-MAN: Come here.
-(WH|MPER|NG CONTINUES)
-Let's have a feel, eh?
-Leave it.
-(WOMAN WHIMPERS)
-MAN: Come here.
INNKEEPER: Please, she's a good girl.
Shut your mouth and pour us more ale,
and we may not take her with us
when we're done with her.
I know you.
You're the Hound.
Pour our new friend some ale.
What brings you so far north?
Just keeping the King's peace.
No need. The war's over.
So I've heard.
Stannis defeated at the Blackwater.
Robb Stark killed at the Twins.
And where am | for all of it?
Stuck with your brother.
-Meaning no offence.
-None taken.
He's good, the Mountain is.
Best at what he does.
But torture, torture.
You spend enough time
putting the hammer to people,
you start to feel like a carpenter
making chairs.
Drains the fun right out of it.
And what's life without a little fun?
(POLLIVER CHUCKLES)
But I don't need to tell you that, eh?
She's all right. I've had better.
(LAUGHS)
You know what?
You should come with us.
His kind, they've always got
something hidden away somewhere.
Gold, silver, more daughters.
Always something
ifyou know how to make them talk.
And there's plenty of him
between here and King's Landing.
You could do well for yourself.
We certainly have been.
-|'m not going to King's Landing.
-Think about it.
We could do whatever we like,
whereverwe go.
These are the King's colours.
No one's standing in his way now.
Which means no one's standing in ours.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Fuckthe King.
(LAUGHING STOPS)
When I heard that Joffrey's dog had tucked
tail and run from the Battle ofthe Blackwater,
I didn't believe it.
-But here you are.
-Here I am.
Bring me one ofthose chickens.
-You got money to pay for it?
-You paid for it?
(LAUGHS) No.
But we're the King's men.
So, you got money?
Not a penny.
I'll still take that chicken.
Tell you what.
We'll trade you.
One of our little chickens for one of yours.
Give us a go at your friend.
Lowell there likes them a bit broken in.
(MEN CHUCKLE)
You're atalker.
Listening makes me thirsty.
(SiGHS)
And hungry.
Think I'll take two chickens.
You don't understand the situation.
I understand that if any more words
come pouring out your cunt mouth,
I'm gonna have to eat every fucking chicken
in this room.
You lived your life forthe King.
You're gonna die for some chickens?
Someone is.
(HOUND GRUNTS)
(MAN SHOUTING)
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
Something wrong with your leg, boy?
(STAMMERING) What do you mean?
Can you walk? I've got to carry you?
Carry me?
Fine little blade.
Maybe I'll pick my teeth with it.
(GASPS)
(GURGLiNG)