(Gate rumbling, chains rattling)
(Horse snorbs)
(Rumbling, chain rattling)
(Wind whistling)
- Easy, boy.
- (Grunts)
(Horse whinnies)
(Man) What do you expect?
They're savages.
One lot steals a goat from another lot,
before you know it
they're ripping each other to pimes.
I've never seen wildlings do a thing like this.
I never seen a thing like this,
not ever in my life.
- (Horse snorts)
- How close did you get?
- Close as any man would.
- We should head back to the Wall.
Do the dead frighten you?
Our orders were to track the wildlings.
We tracked them.
They won‘t trouble us no more.
You don‘t think he'll ask us how they died?
Get back on your horse.
(Sighs, mutters)
Whatever did it to them
could do it to us.
They even killed the children.
It's a good thing we're not children.
You want to run away south,
run away.
Of course,
they will behead you as a deserter.
If I don't catch you ﬁrst.
Get back on your horse.
I won't say it again.
(Shrill animal coll)
Your dead men seem
to have moved comp.
They were here.
See where they went.
(Echoing creature cries)
What is it?
It's...
(Cracking, creaking)
(Distant scream)
(Horses neighing)
(Galloping hooves)
(Snarling)
(Chi‘ttering)
(Coughing)
(Panting)
(Laboured breathing)
(Snarling)
(GBSPS)
(Crackling)
(Chi‘ttering)
(Galloping hooves)
(stamps)
Go on, Father's watching.
And your mother.
Fine work. as always.
Well done.
Thank you.
I love the detail that you've managed
to get in these comers.
Quite beautiful.
The stitching...
Oh, no, no, no. This stitch is very...
(Arrows impacting, men laughing)
- It's beautiful.
- Thank you.
(Arrow impacting)
- (Sighs)
- (Laughing)
And which one of you
was a marksman at ten?
Keep practicing, Bran.
Go on.
Don't think too much, Bran.
Relax your bow arm.
(Men laughing)
- Quick Branl
- Faster.
Lord Starkl
My lady.
A guardsman just rode in from the hills.
They've captured a deserter
from the Night's Watch.
Get the lads to saddle their horses.
Do you have to?
He swore an oath, Cat.
Law is law, my lady.
Tell Bran he's coming too.
Ned.
Ten is too young
to see such things.
He won't be a boy forever.
And winter is coming.
Good lad, go run back and get the rest.
White walkers.
I saw the white walkers.
The white walkers, I saw them.
(Exhales)
I know I broke my oath.
And I know I'm a deserter.
I should have gone back to the Wall
and warned them, but...
lsawwhatlsaw.
I saw the white walkers.
People need to know.
If you can get word to my family...
tell them I'm no coward.
Tell them I'm sorry.
(Whispers) Forgive me, Lord.
In the name of Robert
of the House Baratheon,
- the ﬁrst of his name...
- Don't look away.
- ..King of the Andals and the First Men...
- Father will know if you do.
..Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and protector of the realm,
l, Eddard of the House Stark.
Lord of Winterfell
and Warden of the North,
sentence you to die.
You did well.
You understand why I did it?
Jon said he was a deserter.
But do you understand
why I had to kill him?
"Our way is the old way"?
The man who passes the sentence
should swing the sword.
Is it true he saw the white walkers?
The white walkers have been gone
for thousands of years.
So he was lying?
A madman sees what he sees.
What is it?
Mountain lion?
There are no mountain lions
in these woods.
(Pup whines)
It's a freak
It's a direwolf.
Tough old beast.
There are no direwolves
south of the Wall.
Now there are ﬁve.
You want to hold it?
(Pup whimpers)
(Bran) Where will they go?
Their mother's dead.
They don't belong down here.
Better a quick death.
They won't last without their mother.
- Right. Give it here.
- Nol
- (Whimpers)
- Put away your blade.
- I take orders from your father, not you.
- Please, Fatherl
I'm sorry, Bran.
Lord Stark?
One for each of the Stark children.
- (Pup cries)
- The direwolf is the sigil of your house.
They were meant to have them.
You will train them yourselves.
You will feed them yourselves.
And ifthey die, you will bury them yourselves.
What about you?
I'm not a Stark.
Get on.
(Whimpering)
What is it?
The runt of the litter.
That one's yours, Snow.
(Bells tolling)
As your brother,
I feel it's my duty to warn you...
you worry too much.
- It's starting to show.
- And you never worry about anything.
When we were seven and you jumped off
the cliffs at Casterly Rock.
100-foot drop into the water...
you were never afraid.
There was nothing to be afraid of
until you told Father.
(Mimics) 'We're Lannisters.
Lannisters don't act like fools."
- What if Jon Arryn told someone?
- But who would he tell?
My husband.
If he told the king, both our heads would be
skewered on the city gates by now.
Whatever Jon Arryn knew or didn't know,
it died with him.
And Robert will choose
a new Hand of the King,
someone to do his job while he's off
flicking boars and hunting whores.
Or is it the other way around?
And life will go on.
You should be the Hand of the King.
That's an honour I can do without.
Their days are too long,
their lives are too short.
(Thunder rumbles)
(OEWS)
(Birds chirping)
All these years,
and I still feel like an outsider
when I come here.
You have ﬁve northern children.
You're not an outsider.
I wonder ifthe old gods agree.
It's your gods with all the rules.
I am so sorry, my love.
- Tell me.
- There was a raven from King's Landing.
Jon Arryn is dead.
A fever took him.
I know he was like a father to you.
- Your sister, the boy?
- They both have their health,
gods be good.
The raven brought more news.
The king rides for Winterfell...
with the queen and all the rest of them.
If he's coming this far north...
there's only one thing he's after.
You can always say no, Ned.
(Catelyn) We'll need plenty of candles
for Lord Tyrion's chamber.
- I'm told he reads all night.
- I'm told he drinks all night.
How much could he possibly drink?
A man of his...
stature?
We've brought up eight barrels of ale
from the cellar.
Perhaps we'll ﬁnd out.
In any case, candles.
Why is your mother so dead set on us
getting pretty for the king?
It's for the queen, I bet.
I hear she's a sleek bit of mink
I hear the prince is a right royal prick
Think of all those southem girls he gets to stab
with his right royal prick
Go on, Tommy, shear him good.
He's never met a girl he likes better
than his own hair.
(Laughter)
- (PUP YBPS)
- Gods, but they grow fast.
Brandonl
I saw the king.
He's got hundreds of people.
But he's coming right now, down our road.
I want you to promise me,
no more climbing.
I promise.
- Do you know what?
- What?
You always look at your feet
before you lie.
(Chuckles)
Run and ﬁnd your father.
Tell him the king is close.
Where's Arya?
Sansa, where's your sister?
- HEY. he! he! he!-
- Oh.
What are you doing with that on?
- Go on.
- (Groans)
(AWE) Movel
(Neighs)
Your Grace.
You've got fat.
(Laughter)
- Catl
- Your Grace.
Nine years... Why haven't I seen you?
Where the hell have you been?
Guarding the North for you, Your Grace.
Winterfell is yours.
- Where's the lmp?
- Will you shut up?
(Robert) Who have we here?
You must be Robb.
My, you're a pretty one.
Your name is?
Arya.
Oh, show us your muscles.
(Chuckles) You'll be a soldier.
(Arya) That's Jaime Lannister,
the queen's twin brother.
(Sansa) Would you please shut up?
My queen.
Take me to your crypt.
I want to pay my respects.
We've been riding for a month, my love.
Surely the dead can wait.
Ned.
Where's the lmp?
(Queen) Where is our brother?
Go and ﬁnd the little beast.
Tell me about Jon Arryn.
One minute he was ﬁne and then...
burned right through him,
whatever it was.
I loved that man.
We both did.
(Robert) He never had to teach you much,
but me? You remember me at 16?
- (Chuckles)
- All I wanted to do
was crack skulls and fuck girls.
- He showed me what was what.
- Aye.
Don't look at me like that.
It's not his fault I didn't listen.
(Both laugh)
(Sighs)
I need you, Ned,
down at King's Landing, not up here
where you're no damn use to anybody.
Lord Eddard Stark...
I would name you the Hand of the King.
I'm not worthy of the honour.
I'm not trying to honour you.
I'm trying to get you to run my kingdom
while I eat, drink and whore my way
to an early grave.
Damn it, Ned, stand up.
You helped me win the Iron Throne,
now help me keep the damn thing.
We were meant to rule together.
If your sister had lived,
we'd have been bound by blood.
Well, it's not too late.
l have a son,
you have a daughter.
We'll join our houses.
(Woman moaning)
(Sighs)
(Cup falls)
It is true what they say
about the northern girls.
(Giggles)
Did you hear the king's in Winterfell?
I did hear something about that.
And the queen and her twin brother.
They say that he is the most handsome man
in the Seven Kingdoms.
And the other brother?
- The queen has two brothers?
- There's the pretty one...
and there's the clever one.
I hear they call him the lmp.
I hear he hates that nickname.
Oh? I hear he's more than earned it.
I hear he's a drunken little lecher,
prone to all manner of perversions.
Clever girl.
We've been expecting you, Lord Tyrion.
Have you?
- Already?
- Ohl
- The gods gave me one blessing.
- (Laughs)
(Door opens)
- Don't get up.
- My lord.
Should I explain to you the meaning of
a closed door in a whorehouse, brother?
You have much to teach me, no doubt,
but our sister craves your attention.
She has odd cravings, our sister.
A family trait.
Now, the Starks are feasting us at sundown.
- Don't leave me alone with these people.
- I'm sorry, I've begun the feast a bit early.
And this is the ﬁrst of many courses.
I thought you might say that.
But since we're short on time...
Come on, girls.
(Giaalina)
See you at sundown.
(T yrion) Close the doorl
Did you have to bury her
in a place like this?
She should be on a hill somewhere
with the sun and the clouds above her.
She was my sister.
This is where she belongs.
She belonged with me.
In my dreams,
I kill him every night.
It's done, Your Grace.
The Targaryens are gone.
(Gull crying)
(Man) Daenerysl
Daenerys.
There's our bride-to-be.
Look a gift from lllyrio.
Touch it.
Go on, feel the fabric.
Isn't he a gracious host?
We've been his guests for over a year
and he's never asked us for anything.
lllyrio's no fool.
He knows I won't forget my ﬁiends
when I come into my throne.
You still slouch.
Let them see.
You have a woman's body now.
(Sighs)
I need you to be perfect today.
Can you do that for me?
You don't want to wake the dragon, do you?
No.
When they write the history
of my reign, sweet sister,
they will say it began today.
It's too hot, my lady.
(Gulls crying)
Where is he?
The Dothraki are not known
for their punctuality.
(lllyrio) Athchomar chomaloaan, Khal vezhven.
May I present my honoured guests?
Viserys of House Targaryen,
the third of his name,
the rightful King of the Andals
and the First Men,
and his sister,
Daenerys of House Targaryen.
(Speaking Dothraki)
Do you see how long his hair is?
When Dothraki are defeated in combat
they cut off their braid
so the whole world can see their shame.
Khal Drogo has never been defeated.
He's a savage, of course,
but he's one of the ﬁnest killers alive.
And you will be his queen.
Come forward, my dear.
Where is he going?
- The ceremony is over.
- But he... But he didn't say anything.
Did he like her?
Trust me, Your Grace,
if he didn't like her, we'd know.
(lllyrio) It won't be long now.
Soon you will cross the narrow sea
and take back your father's throne.
The people drink secret toasts
to your health.
They cry out for their true king.
When will they be married?
Soon.
The Dothraki never stay still for long.
Is it true they lie with their horses?
I wouldn't ask Khal Drogo.
Do you take me for a fool?
I take you for a king.
Kings lack the caution
of common men.
My apologies if I've given offence.
I know how to play a man like Drogo.
I give him a queen
and he gives me an army.
I don't want to be his queen.
I want to go home.
Sodol.
I want us both to go home,
but they took it from us.
So tell me, sweet sister,
how do we go home?
I don't know.
We go home with an army.
With Khal Drogo's army.
I would let his whole tribe fuck you,
all 40,000 men and their horses too,
if that's what it took.
(Kisses)
Do you think Joffrey will like me?
What if he thinks I'm ugly?
Then he is the stupidest prince that ever lived.
He's so handsome.
When would we be married?
Soon? Or do we have to wait?
Hush now.
Your father hasn't even said yes.
Why would he say no?
He'd be the swond most powerful man
in the kingdoms.
He'd have to leave home.
He'd have to leave me.
And so would you.
You left your home to come here.
And I'd be queen someday.
Please make Father say yesl
- Sansa...
- Please, pleasel
It's the only thing I ever wanted.
(Music playing, people chattering)
(Laughter)
Fill that upl
Boys, Rodrik come on.
Come onl
Come here, you little beautyl
(Robert laughing)
Is he dead yet?
Uncle Benjen.
(Laughs)
You got bigger.
Rode all day.
Didn't want to leave you alone
with the Lannisters.
Why aren't you at the feast?
Lady Stark thought it might
insult the royal family
to seat a bastard in their midst.
Well, you're always
welcome on the Wall.
No bastard was ever
refused a seat there.
So take me with you
when you go back
- Jon...
- Father will let me if you ask him.
I know he will.
The Wall isn't going anywhere.
I'm ready to swear your oath.
You don't understand
what you'd be giving up.
We have no families.
- None of us will ever father sons.
- I don't care about that.
You might, if you knew what it meant.
(Sighs) I'd better get inside,
rescue your father from his guests.
We'll talk later.
(T yrion) Your uncle's in the Night's Watch.
What are you doing back there?
Preparing for a night with your family.
I've always wanted to see the Wall.
You're Tyr'ion Lannister,
the queen's brother?
My greatest awomplishment.
And you, you're Ned Starks bastard,
aren't you?
Did I offend you? Sorry.
You are the bastard, though.
Lord Eddard Stark is my father.
And Lady Stark is not your mother,
making you...the bastard.
Let me give you some advice, bastard.
Never forget what you are.
The rest of the world will not.
Wear it like armour...
and it can never be used to hurt you.
What the hell do you know
about being a bastard?
All dwarves are bastards
in their father's eyes.
(Music playing, chattering)
(Laughter)
You at a feast...
it's like a bear in a trap.
The boy | beheaded...
- did you know him?
- Of course I did. Just a lad.
But he was tough, Ned,
a true ranger.
(Scoﬁs)
He was talking madness.
Said the walkers slaughtered his ﬁiends.
The two he was with are still missing.
Hmph. A wildling ambush.
Maybe.
Direwolves south of the Wall,
talk of the walkers,
and my brother might be
the next Hand of the King.
Winter is coming.
(They chuckle)
- Uncle Benjen.
- Robb boy.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
(Laughter)
Is this your ﬁrst time
in the North, Your Grace?
Yes. Lovely country.
I'm sure it's very grim
after King's Landing.
I remember how scared I was when
Ned brought me up here for the ﬁrst time.
Hello, little dove.
But you are a beauty.
- How old are you?
- Thirteen, Your Grace.
You're tall. Still growing?
I think so, Your Grace.
And have you bled yet?
No, Your Grace.
Your dress, did you make it?
Such talent.
You must make something for me.
I hear we might share
a grandchild someday.
I hear the same.
Your daughter will do well in the capital.
Such a beauty shouldn't stay
hidden up here forever.
- Your pardon.
- I hear we might be neighbours soon.
- I hope it's true.
- Yes, the king has honoured me with his offer.
I'm sure we'll have a tournament to celebrate
your new title, if you accept.
It would be good
to have you on the ﬁeld.
The competition has bmome a bit stale.
- I don't ﬁght in tournaments.
- No?
Getting a little old for it?
(Chuckles)
I don't ﬁght in tournaments
bwause when I ﬁght a man for real,
I don't want him to know what I can do.
Well said.
- (Laughing)
- Aryal
It's not funnyl
She always does this.
This was my favourite dress
and she ruined it
She always does it
and it's not funnyl
(Robb) Time for bed.
(Arya groans)
(Ned) I'm a Northman.
I belong here with you, not down south
in that rats' nest they call a capital.
I won't let him take you.
The king takes what he wants.
(Snorts) That's why he's king.
I'll say, "Listen, fat man."
(He laughs)
"You are not taking
my husband anywhere.
"He belongs to me now."
How did he get so fat?
He only stops eating
when it's time for a drink (Chuckles)
(Knocking)
(Man) It's Maester Luwin, my lord.
Send him in.
Pardon, my lord, my lady.
A rider in the night...
from your sister.
- Stay.
- This was sent from the Eyrie.
(Door closes)
What's she doing at the Eyrie?
She hasn't been back there
since her wedding.
(Ned) What news?
(Catelyn) She's ﬂed the capital.
She says Jon Arryn was murdered.
By the Lannisters.
She says the king is in danger.
She's fresh widowed, Oat.
She doesn't know what she's saying.
Lysa's head would be on a spike right now
ifthe wrong people had found that letter.
Do you think she would risk her life,
her son's life,
if she wasn't certain
her husband was murdered?
If this news is true...
and the Lannisters conspire
against the throne,
who but you can protect the king?
They murdered the last Hand.
Now you want Ned to take the job?
The king rode for a month
to ask for Lord Starks help.
He's the only one he trusts.
You swore the king an oath, my lord.
He's spent half his life
ﬁghting Robert's wars.
He owes him nothing.
Your father and brother
rode south once
on a king's demand.
A different time.
A different king.
- (Noisy chatter)
- (Drumming)
(Hissing)
(Gasps)
When do I meet with the khal?
We need to begin planning the invasion.
If Khal Drogo has promised you a crown,
you shall have it
- When?
- When their omens favour war.
I piss on Dothraki omens.
I've waited 17 years to get my throne back
- (Crowd ululating)
- (Grunting)
(Cheering)
Etayo akloa.
(Blades clang)
(Screams)
A Dothraki wedding without at least
three deaths is considered a dull affair.
(Laughing)
Jadi, zhey Jorah andahlil
Khal vezhven.
A small gift, for the new khaleesi.
Songs and histories from the Seven Kingdoms.
Thank you, ser.
Are you from my country?
Ser Jorah Morrnont of Bear Island.
I served your father for many years.
Gods be good, I hope to
always serve the rightful king.
Dragon's eggs, Daenerys,
from the Shadow Lands beyond Asshai.
The ages have turned them to stone,
but they will always be beautiful.
Thank you, Magister.
She's beautiful.
Ser Jorah, I...
I don't know how to say "thank you"
in Dothraki.
There is no word for "thank you"
Make him happy.
(Waves crashing)
- No.
- (Sober)
Do you know the common tongue?
- (Pin clanks)
- No.
Is "no" the only word that you known
No.
(Continues sobbing)
Rough night, Imp?
If I get through this without squirting
from one end or the other,
it'll be a miracle.
I didn't pick you for a hunter.
The greatest in the land -
my spear never misses.
It's not hunting if you pay for it
Are youasgood withaspear
asyouusedtobe?
No, but I'm still better than you.
(Laughs)
I know what I'm putting you through.
Thank you for saying yes.
I only ask you bwause I need you.
You're a loyal ﬁiend. You hear me?
A loyal ﬁiend.
The last one I've got.
- I hope I'll serve you well.
- You will.
And I'll make sure you don't look
so flicking grim all the time.
Come on, boys,
let's go kill some boarl
Come on, you.
(Whines)
(Grunts)
(Barks softly)
(Woman gasping)
(Woman moaning)
(Grunting, moaning)
(Gasps)
- Stopl Stop.
- (Gasm)
Are you completely mad?
- He saw us.
- It's all ﬁght, it's all right.
- It's all right.
- He saw usl
I heard you the ﬁrst time.
(Whimpers)
Quite the little climber, aren't you?
- How old are you, boy?
- Ten.
Ten.
- The things I do for love.
- (Gasm)