(BELL TOLLING)
(JINGLING)
(SHIVERING)
(DOOR RATTLING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
MAN: Your Grace.
The trial will be getting under way soon.
(CLICKS)
(SOFT GRUNT)
(JINGLING)
You got my money?
Later. Go away.
(EXHALES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Grand Maester.
(WHISPERING INAUDIBLY)
Ser Loras Tyrell.
Are you prepared to stand trial
and profess your guilt or innocence
before the Seven?
There'll be no need for atrial.
(SCATTERED MURMURS)
I confess before the Seven
and freely admit to my crimes.
To which crimes will you be confessing?
A|| ofthem.
May with other men
including the traitor Renly Baratheon.
(CROWD GASPING)
lperjured myself before the gods.
lam guilty of depravity,
dishonesty,
profligacy,
and arrogance.
| see that now.
l humble myself before the Seven
and accept whatever punishment
the gods deem just.
The gods' judgement is fierce,
but also fair.
The Warrior punishes those
who believe themselves
beyond the reach ofjustice.
But the Mother shows her mercy
to those who kneel before her.
I take full responsibility for my many sins
and unburden myself of my desires.
My only remaining wish
is to devote my life to the Seven.
May I be a living example oftheir grace
for others to witness.
You understand fully what this means?
I do.
I will abandon the Tyrell name
and all that goes with it.
I will renounce my lordship
and my claims on Highgarden.
lwill never marry
and I will never father children.
HIGH SPARROW: Brother Loras,
(SHUDDERING)
| ask you to dedicate your life
to the seven gods.
Will you fight to defend your faith
against heretics and apostates?
lwill.
(CONTINUES SHUDDERING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING) No, I can't let them...
Faith is the way, Father.
(LORAS BREATHING HEAVlLY)
(GROANS)
(DOOR OPENS)
TOMMEN: All right.
I'm ready.
l have to go. I'm...
l'm late forthe trial.
MARGAERY: You mutilated him.
You gave me your word.
And l have kept my word.
Once the Queen Mother's trial is concluded,
Brother Loras is free to leave.
And where is the Queen Mother?
Her litter never left the Red Keep.
It appears the Queen Mother
doesn't wish to attend her own trial.
HIGH SPARROW: Go to the Red Keep
and show her the way.
Get the others.
(PANTING)
Where's the king?
Elsewhere, I'm afraid.
What's the meaning ofthis? l was told that...
Ah.
l have more important things
to do with my time
than waste them in the presence...
Please, Grand Maester. I bear you no ill will.
Please forgive me ifyou can.
(PANTING)
QYBURN: This pains me, my lord.
Whatever your faults, you do not deserve
to die alone in such a cold, dark place.
But sometimes before
we can usher in the new,
the old must be put to rest.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(PYCELLE GROANING)
(FLESH SQUELCHING)
(GROANING CONTINUES)
The longer you wait, the worse it'll be for you.
-(GRUNTS)
-(GROANS)
(WHEEZING)
What are you doing?
(BREATHING HEAVlLY)
(GRUNTING)
There's something wrong.
(CHUCKLES) You have
nothing to fear, Your Grace.
The trial will begin shortly.
Cersei is not here.
Tommen is not here.
Why do you think they're not here?
lfthe accused is not here,
she will be tried regardless.
We cannot escape the justice ofthe gods...
Forget about the bloody gods
and listen to what I'm telling you.
Cersei understands
the consequences of her absence
and she is absent anyway,
which means she does not intend
to suffer those consequences.
The trial can wait. We all need to leave.
(SCOFFS)
(GRUNTING)
We all need to leave now!
(SCATTERED CHATTER)
Loras.
Stay with me.
(ALL CLAMOURING)
Let me through. Let me through!
MARGAERY: Get out of my way!
(GROANING)
Let us through!
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVlLY)
(RUMBLING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(ALL SCREAMING IN THE DISTANCE)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(GROANS)
(SPITS)
CERSIE: Confess.
Confess.
-No.
-CERS|E: Confess.
(SPITS)
(GASPING)
CERSIE: Confess. It felt good.
Beating me, starving me,
frightening me, humiliating me.
You didn't do it because
you cared about my atonement.
You did it because it felt good.
I understand.
I do things because they feel good.
| drink because it feels good.
I killed my husband
because it felt good to be rid of him.
I fuck my brother because it feels good
to feel him inside me.
I lie about fucking my brother
because it feels good
to keep our son safe from hateful hypocrites.
I killed your High Sparrow
and all his little Sparrows.
All his septons, all his septas,
all his filthy soldiers,
because it felt good to watch them burn.
It felt good to imagine
their shock and their pain.
No thought has ever given me greaterjoy.
(SCOFFS)
Even confessing feels good
under the right circumstances.
You've always been quiet.
I said my face would be the last thing
you saw before you died.
Do you remember?
Good.
I'm glad to see your face.
I'm ready to meet the gods.
What?
Now?
Today?
You're not going to die today.
You're not going to die for quite a while.
Ser Gregor.
This is Ser Gregor Clegane.
He's quiet, too.
Your gods have forsaken you.
This is your god now.
No.
-Shame.
-(CRY|NG)
-(WA|L|NG)
-Shame.
-(WA|L|NG CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING)
MAN: I'm very sorry, Your Grace.
Very sorry.
(ALL SHOUTING IN THE DISTANCE)
(DOOR CLOSES)
WALDER: For House Lannister!
ALL: Hear me roar!
(ALL CHEERING)
For House Frey!
ALL: We stand together!
(ALL CHEERING)
May we stand together through the centuries,
-good friends to the last.
-(ALL CHEERING)
And when we drive our swords
through our enemies' hearts,
may we speak the words of our alliance,
"The Freys and the Lannisters
"send their regards."
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCATTERED CHATTER)
You don't even have to do anything, do you?
You just sit there, a rich slab of beef,
and all the birds come pecking.
You're welcome to her.
She doesn't want me.
She wants your golden fingers up her twat.
Those two have their eyes on you.
(GIGGLING)
Not my type.
Not blonde enough?
Ladies, have you met
Ser Bronn ofthe Blackwater,
hero ofthe Battle of Blackwater Bay?
-There you go.
-Maybe I'm not in the mood.
Fuck it.
No need to call me "ser"
just because I'm an anointed knight.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
This came together rather well.
Your father would be pleased.
I'm sure he would be.
Huh.
Edmure is back in a cell.
Can't go killing my son by law.
It wouldn't be right.
Give the family a bad name.
So the famous Blackfish
killed by foot soldiers, eh?
Legendary warrior, everyone said.
Have you done much fighting
yourself, Lord Frey?
I'm a bit old for all that.
No, but back in your day.
The purpose of fighting
is defeating your enemies, isn't it?
I've defeated mine.
Riverrun belonged to House Tully
for athousand years.
Now it's mine.
What do you call that?
Victory.
Yes, you're a great conqueror.
Go on, mock me, boy. You think | mind?
The Tullys mocked me for years.
The Starks mocked me.
Where are they now?
You talk about war as ifyou're an expert,
but the one battle I rememberyou fighting,
you were captured by Robb Stark,
the Young Wolf.
But it doesn't matter.
Here we are now, two kingslayers.
We know what it's like
to have them grovel to our faces
and snigger behind our backs.
We don't mind, do we?
Fear is a marvellous thing.
They don't fear the Freys, though.
They fear the Lannisters.
We gave you the Riverlands
to hold the Riverlands.
lfwe have to ride north
and take them back foryou
everytime you lose them,
why do we need you?
Show me.
Your Grace, there's no need...
QYBURN: What are your thoughts
concerning the king's funeral?
As the Sept of Baelor is no longer an option,
perhaps a ceremony in the throne room?
He should be with his grandfather,
his brother, his sister.
Burn him.
And bury his ashes
where the Sept once stood.
(HORSE WHINNYING)
MAN: Whoa. Whoa.
(RAVENS CAWING)
Hello.
From Lord Commander Snow at Castle Black.
I'm...
I'm to be the new maester.
Hmm.
According to our records,
Jeor Mormont is Lord Commander.
He died.
We received no report
from the maester at Castle Black.
Maester Aemon became quite ill
shortly after the election.
He's since passed away.
Which is why I'm here.
This is irregular.
Yes, well, I suppose that life is irregular.
CITADEL MAESTER: The archmaester
will discuss these irregularities with you.
In the meantime,
you are permitted to use the library.
Follow me.
No women or children.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(CAWING)
When we had feasts,
our family would sit up here
and I'd sit down there.
Could have been worse, Jon Snow.
You had a family.
You had feasts.
Aye, you're right. I was luckierthan most.
(PANTING)
What is that?
Tell him.
Tell him who it belonged to.
The Princess Shireen.
Tell him what you did to her.
Tell him!
(VOICE BREAKING)
We burned her at the stake.
VVhy?
The army was trapped.
The horses were dying.
It was the only way.
You burned a little girl alive!
| only do what my Lord commands.
If he commands you to burn children,
your Lord is evil.
We are standing here because of him.
Jon Snow is alive because the Lord willed it.
I loved that girl like she was my own.
She was good. She was kind.
And you killed her!
So did her father.
So did her mother.
Her own blood knew it was the only way.
The only way forwhat?
They all died anyway.
You told everyone Stannis was the one.
You had him believing it, all ofthem fooled.
-And you lied.
-I didn't lie!
lwas wrong.
DAVOS: Aye, you were wrong.
How many died because you were wrong?
| ask your leave
to execute this woman for murder.
She admits to the crime.
Do you have anything to say for yourself?
I've been ready to die for many years.
lfthe Lord was done with me,
so be it, but he's not.
You've seen the Night King, Jon Snow.
You know the Great War is still to come.
You know the army ofthe dead
will be upon us soon.
And you know I can help you win that war.
Ride south today.
lfyou return to the North,
I'll have you hanged as a murderer.
lfyou ever come back this way,
I will execute you myself.
I'm having the lord's chamber
prepared foryou.
Mother and Father's room?
You should take it.
I'm not a Stark.
You are to me.
You're the Lady ofWinterfell.
You deserve it.
We're standing here because of you.
The battle was lost
until the Knights ofthe Vale rode in.
They came because of you.
You told me Lord Baelish
sold you to the Boltons.
-He did.
-And you trust him?
Only a fool would trust Littlefinger.
I should have told you about him,
about the Knights ofthe Vale.
I'm sorry.
We need to trust each other.
We can't fight a war amongst ourselves.
We have so many enemies now.
Jon.
A raven came from the Citadel.
A white raven.
(SIGHS)
Winter is here.
Well, Father always promised, didn't he?
OLENNA: The last time a Tyrell
came to Dorne, he was assassinated.
A hundred red scorpions, was it?
ELLARIA: You have nothing to fear
from us, Lady Olenna.
OLENNA: You murderyour own prince,
but you expect me to trust you?
We invited you to Dorne
because we needed your help.
You came to Dorne
because you needed our help.
What is your name again? Barbaro?
-Obara.
You look like an angry little boy.
Don't presume to tell me what I need.
Forgive my sister.
What she lacks in diplomacy, she makes...
Do shut up, dear. Anything from you?
No? Good.
Let the grown women speak.
The Lannisters have declared war
on House Tyrell.
They have declared war on Dorne.
We must be allies now ifwe wish to survive.
Cersei stole the future from me.
She killed my son.
She killed my grandson.
She killed my granddaughter.
Survival is not what I'm after now.
ELLARIA: You're absolutely right.
I chose the wrong words.
It is not survival I offer.
It is your heart's desire.
(DINGING)
And what is my heart's desire?
Vengeance.
Justice.
Fire and blood.
Your ships are nearly ready.
lsawthem painting the sails.
I'm curious to see how the Dothraki
do on the poison water.
You're not coming with us.
New strategy?
You want the Second Sons
to attack from the west coast?
If we take Casterly Rock,
the Lannisters will have nowhere to run
when you hit King's Landing.
You're not going to Westeros.
You're staying here with the Second Sons.
There's finally peace in Meereen.
You will keep the peace
while the people choose their own leaders.
Fuck Meereen.
Fuckthe people.
I'm here foryou, not them.
DAENERYS: You promised me.
"My sword is yours. My life is yours."
This is what I command.
If I'm going to rule in Westeros,
I'll need to make alliances.
The best way to make alliances
is with marriage.
Who are you marrying this time?
I don't know. Maybe no one.
But you need to lure
all the noble houses to the table?
Are you a queen or fish bait?
I can't bring a lover to Westeros.
A king wouldn't think twice about it.
So that's what you want? To be my mistress?
I'm not proud.
I don't care what perfumed aristocrat
sits beside you in the throne room.
I don't want a crown. I want you.
I love you.
And | make you happy.
You know I do.
Bring me with you. Let me fight foryou.
I can't.
The dwarftold you to do this?
DAENERYS: No one tells me to do anything.
Clever fellow. Can't argue with his logic.
I'm no use to you overthere.
Don't get angry.
I'm not angry. I'm full of self-pity.
Who comes afteryou?
Who can ever follow Daenerys Stormborn,
the Mother of Dragons?
A great number of women, I imagine.
Specific orders will be left for you
regarding the welfare of Meereen
and the Bay of Dragons.
The Bay of Dragons?
We can't call it Slaver's Bay any more,
can we?
You'll get that throne you want so badly,
I'm sure of it.
I hope it brings you happiness.
I pity the lords of Westeros.
They have no idea what's coming for them.
Farewell, Daario Naharis.
How did he take it?
No tears.
I know it was hard foryou.
You turned away a man who truly loves you
because he would have been a liability
in the Seven Kingdoms.
That's the kind of self-sacrifice
that makes for a good ruler,
if it's any consolation.
It's not.
No, I suppose not.
I'm terrible at consoling.
Yes, you really are.
All right, how about the fact
that this is actually happening?
You have your armies, you have your ships,
you have your dragons.
Everything you've ever wanted
since you were old enough to want anything,
it's all yours for the taking.
Are you afraid?
You're in the great game now.
And the great game's terrifying.
The only people who aren't afraid of failure
are madmen like your father.
Do you know what frightens me?
I said farewell to a man who loves me.
A man I thought I cared for.
And I felt nothing.
Just impatient to get on with it.
He wasn't the first to love you
and he won't be the last.
Well, you have completely
failed to console me.
Forwhat it's worth,
I've been a cynic
for as long as I can remember.
Everyone's always asking me
to believe in things.
Family, gods, kings, myself.
It was often tempting
until I saw where belief got people.
So I said, "No, thank you," to belief.
And yet, here I am.
I believe in you.
It's embarrassing, really.
I'd swear you my sword,
but I don't actually own a sword.
It's your counsel I need.
It's yours.
Now and always.
Good.
l, um...
I had something made foryou.
I'm not sure if it's right.
Tyrion Lannister,
| name you Hand ofthe Queen.
You're not one of mine, are you?
No, my lord.
Didn't think so.
Too pretty. (SMACKS)
(GROANS)
Where are my damn moron sons?
Black Walder and Lothar promised
to be here by midday.
They're here, my lord.
Well, what are they doing,
trimming their cunt hairs?
Tell them to come here now.
But they're already here, my lord.
Here, my lord.
They weren't easy to carve.
Especially Black Walder.
What...
My name is Arya Stark.
lwant you to knowthat.
The last thing you're ever going to see
is a Stark smiling down at you as you die.
(UNSHEATHES KNIFE)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(GURGLING)
LITTLEFINGER: Forgive me, my lady.
lfyou're at prayer.
I'm done with all that.
I came here every day when l was a girl.
I prayed to be somewhere else.
Backthen l onlythought about what I wanted,
never about what I had.
l was a stupid girl.
LITTLEFINGER: You were a child.
What do you want?
I thought you knew what I wanted.
lwas wrong.
No, you weren't.
Every time I'm faced with a decision,
I close my eyes and see the same picture.
Whenever I consider an action, | ask myself
will this action help
to make this picture a reality?
Pull it out of my mind
and into the world?
And | only act ifthe answer is yes.
A picture of me on the Iron Throne
and you by my side.
It's a pretty picture.
News ofthis battle will spread quickly
through the Seven Kingdoms.
I've declared for House Stark for all to hear.
You've declared for other houses before,
Lord Baelish.
It's never stopped you from serving yourself.
The past is gone for good.
You can sit here mourning its departure
or you can prepare for the future.
You, my love,
are the future of House Stark.
Who should the North rally behind?
A trueborn daughter of Ned and Catelyn Stark
born here at Winterfell
or a motherless bastard born in the South?
BENJEN: This is where I leave you.
You're not coming with us?
The Wallis not just ice and stone.
Ancient spells were carved
into its foundations.
Strong magic
to protect men from what lies beyond.
And while it stands, the dead cannot pass.
I cannot pass.
(HORSE KNICKERS)
Where will you go?
The Great War is coming
and I still fight forthe living.
I'll do what I can,
as long as I can.
Thank you, Uncle Benjen.
lwish you both good fortune.
(BRANDON GRUNTS)
Are you sure you're ready for this?
I'm the Three-Eyed Raven now.
l have to be ready forthis.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(WOMAN WAILING)
WOMAN: Ned?
YOUNG NED: Lyanna.
Is that you?
Is that really you?
You're not a dream?
No, I'm not a dream.
I'm here.
Right here.
I've missed you, big brother.
I've missed you, too.
(CRYING) I want to be brave.
You are.
I'm not.
I don't want to die.
You're not going to die.
Get her some water.
-No, no water. Just listen.
-Is there a maester?
Listen to me, Ned.
(INAUDIBLE)
If Robert finds out, he'll kill him.
You know he will.
You have to protect him.
Promise me, Ned.
Promise me.
(BABY WHIMPERING)
Promise me, Ned.
Promise me.
You can't expect Knights ofthe Vale
to side with wildling invaders.
TORMUND: We didn't invade.
We were invited.
Not by me.
The free folk, the Northerners,
and the Knights ofthe Vale fought bravely,
fought together, and we won.
My father used to say
we find our true friends on the battlefield.
CLEY CERWYN: The Boltons are defeated.
The war is over.
Winter has come.
lfthe maesters are right,
it'll be the coldest one in a thousand years.
We should ride home
and wait out the coming storms.
JON: The war is not over.
And I promise you, friend,
the true enemy won't wait out the storm.
He brings the storm.
(SCATTERED MURMURS)
Your son was butchered
at the Red Wedding, Lord Manderly,
but you refused the call.
You swore allegiance
to House Stark, Lord Glover,
but in their hour of greatest need,
you refused the call.
And you, Lord Cerwyn,
your father was skinned alive
by Ramsay Bolton.
Still you refused the call.
But House Mormont remembers.
The North remembers.
We know no king but the King in the North
whose name is Stark.
I don't care if he's a bastard.
Ned Stark's blood runs through his veins.
He's my king from this day until his last day.
(SCATTERED CHATTER)
Lady Mormont speaks harshly
and truly.
My son died for Robb Stark, the Young Wolf.
I didn't think we'd find
another king in my lifetime.
I didn't commit my men to your cause
'cause I didn't want
more Manderlys dying for nothing.
But I was wrong!
Jon Snow avenged the Red Wedding!
He is the White Wolf.
The King in the North!
I did not fight beside you on the field
and I will regret that until my dying day.
A man can only admit when he was wrong
and ask forgiveness.
There's nothing to forgive, my lord.
There will be more fights to come!
House Glover will stand behind House Stark
as we have for a thousand years!
And I will stand behind Jon Snow,
the King in the North!
The King in the North!
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: (CHANTING) The King in the North!
The King in the North!
The King in the North! The King in the North!
SOLDIER: Company halt!
Halt!
Come on.
QYBURN: | now proclaim
Cersei ofthe House Lannister,
First of Her Name,
Queen ofthe Andals and the First Men,
Protector ofthe Seven Kingdoms.
Long may she reign.
ALL: Long may she reign.
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SCREECHING)